LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 18
Where am I?
Where is Wu Tong?
Answer me.
Answer me!
You want to eat?
Beggar’s Chicken of Shaoyang.
I remember that a disciple of
Shaoyang once said that
this is your favorite dish.
Eat it.
I won’t harm you.
The way you eat
reminds me of the time
when I was hunted by the five sects.
I had to hide inside the deserted valley.
That place is completely barren.
Only some rotten carcasses.
Take a guess.
What did I survive on?
What is it? You already want to
vomit just by thinking about it?
I spent a year like that.
So, you’ll eat this.
If you spit it out, I’m going to let you
have a taste of what I had.
Eat it!
Yes.
Eat it.
This is the Young Lady Chu that I know.
Now, you look more energetic.
I’m tired.
I want to take a nap.
Are all the famous and
upright sects like this?
I don’t have the intention to kill you yet
and you already want to kill me?
If I was that stupid, do you
think I’ll be able to live until today?
Don’t waste your energy to fight me.
You won’t be able to kill me.
Here are all the most powerful
mythological objects in heavenly realm.
Just take whatever you like.
God of War.
This Dingkun Sword is an ancient
ominous sword. It’s foul and evil.
You... You better...
I’ll take this.
King Bailing!
King Bailing.
Are you okay?
Just now, I saw that the God of War’s
life pillar is flickering.
I didn’t know why.
So, it’s because you are
casting spell on Dingkun Sword.
This is just a false alarm.
At first, I wanted to break her tie
with Dingkun sword and take it away.
But I failed.
Why?
Her life pillar will be affected too
if I try to take away Dingkun Sword?
Of course.
But I’m afraid that Dingkun Sword
is too evil that
it’ll awaken God of War’s memories.
And I’m afraid that her power
will be awakened soon.
King Bailing, you shouldn’t have given
that sword so easily to her back then.
What were you thinking?
For just a moment of her happiness?
You brought this upon yourself.
You...
You are wise and great.
You’ll definitely find a way.
I’m worrying for nothing.
I’ll use a spell to seal
the power of this sword first and
suppress the evil in it.
Are you okay, King Bailing?
It’s quite difficult to use this body
in the human realm
to suppress this mythological object.
I don’t know how long I can suppress it.
Si Ming, go back to Siming Hall now
to seal her life pillar and
chain up her past.
No matter it’s Dingkun Sword
or other things,
I’ll not allow any another
power to stir up her memories.
King Bailing, this...
You can’t interfere with the human realm.
But protecting lives is your duty.
It’s best if she doesn’t remember
those incidents that
she shouldn’t remember.
Only then can she be safe.
Yes, King Bailing.
Finally.
Her life pillar is sealed up.
But her memories are chained too.
And King Bailing is
a stubborn and difficult person.
Looks like it’ll be hard for
them to mend their relationship.
I can only hope that King Bailing
can help her reincarnate sooner
and bring her back to the heavenly realm.
Then, I’ll be able to update this
Tales of the Three Realms.
Let me in! Old Guy.
Old Guy, hurry up!
Lord Flying Snake.
Old Guy.
Wait, who are you calling an old guy?
Do I look like an old guy?
Let me ask you.
Where did the God of War go
to pass through her trial this time?
God of War?
Why are you asking about her?
Of course I want to go there
to compete with her.
- Come over here.
- Tell me.
Come over here.
Something bad has happened.
What happened?
Let me tell you.
But don’t tell King Bailing about it.
I lost the Dingkun
Sword that I’m guarding.
God...
Such a major issue?
So, I must go and find
God of War and get back
the Dingkun Sword before
King Bailing finds out about it.
Hurry up and tell me where she is now.
I’m not going there to fight with her.
She has been reincarnated by God.
How can a powerless deity like me
find out where she is?
You are too useless. Forget it.
I’ll go and find out about this
elsewhere then.
Don’t tell anyone that
Dingkun Sword is gone.
You are just a stinky snake.
I’ll record it down.
You are awake?
Senior Hao Chen.
Where is Si Feng? How is he?
Did you see him?
Did the vice palace lord
take him back to Lize Palace?
He is fine.
You can be rest assured now.
Good.
Xuan Ji.
Do you still remember your vow
to master before you left the mountain?
You vowed that you’ll protect
the secret ground forever.
So, you should always
put the secret ground first.
How could you just promise
to marry someone without thinking?
But I took down Si Feng’s mask.
If I don’t take responsibility for it,
he’ll be punished.
Nonsense.
When did Lize Palace have this rule?
Besides, no matter what,
this is Lize Palace’s matter.
You may be able to interfere this time,
but will you be able to do that forever?
You agreed to marry a man
without serious consideration.
Are you just going to abandon
your father, your sister and...
You’ll spend the rest of
your life with someone just like that?
I... I haven’t thought
that far ahead yet.
Forget it. Later, I’ll bring you to
Lize Palace to explain it to them.
Tell them that you made that decision
on a whim and that doesn’t count.
No. I’ve promised them.
How can I break my promise?
I can’t just wash my hands off Si Feng.
You don’t even listen to me now?
Of course I do.
You do?
Fine. Let me ask you then.
Why were you at Mount Gao?
What were you looking for?
I... I went to Mount Gao to
look for the Mirror of Origin.
Senior, don’t be mad.
I know that I promised you
to not look for
the Mirror of Origin anymore.
But I really want to
restore my six senses.
I want to be like everybody.
I have a friend who said that
he knows this mirror well.
He said that it’s not an evil mirror.
It will just let you see your past.
A friend? It’s Yu Si Feng again.
I put so much effort to teach you
all those years
but you trust him more than you trust me.
Si Feng has the same thought as me.
I want to feel those senses for myself.
Moreover, human has a heart to think.
We have eyes to see.
We have a nose to smell
and a mouth to eat.
If I give up all of those,
what else can I do?
The world has myriads of things
and a man’s heart is incomprehensible.
Before you left, I taught you
to always reflect on yourself
and don’t be bewitched by others.
But in the end,
you still let your desire won out.
I’m really disappointed in you.
Looks like there’s no need to continue
with this trial anymore.
Go back to Shaoyang and continue
your cultivation in Xuyang Peak.
No. I still haven’t heard from
Ling Long and Sixth Senior.
I must go.
Min Xing and Min Jue has already
gone to Mount Gao to look for them.
You don’t need to do anything.
You’ll be grounded in Fuyu Island first.
Practice with Spell of Tranquility
for 20 hours every day.
After everything is settled here,
go back to Shaoyang with me at once
and don’t leave it anymore.
And be a dedicated protector
for your whole life.
- No, senior!
- Go back now!
Do you know what it means
by taking off this mask?
I took it off.
I’ll take the responsibility for it.
What should I do? Tell me.
Marry him. Are you willing to do that?
Do you still remember your vow
to master before you left the mountain?
You vowed that you’ll protect
the secret ground forever.
So, you should always
put the secret ground first.
How could you just promise
to marry someone without thinking?
Are you just going to abandon
your father, your sister and...
You’ll spend the rest of
your life with someone just like that?
Vice Palace Lord.
The disciples are still waiting.
Are we going to bring Si Feng back now?
No.
Since that girl is willing to
risk her life for him,
we’ll let him stay.
Did you bring me the shards
of the Loveless Mask?
They are here.
This is the bark of Kunlun Tree.
It won’t break so easily.
Interesting.
Aren’t you curious
whether or not that girl
truly loves Si Feng?
I don’t know.
Let’s conduct a test then.
Yes, Vice Palace Lord.
The immortal Kunlun Tree.
So, it’s the Loveless Mask.
The mask is removed.
But the curse is still there.
Yu Si Feng.
Looks like you have no choice
but to work hard for Xuan Ji’s love.
Good.
Senior Hao Chen is not
watching me in the yard.
I can check on Si Feng now.
Our fight is not over yet.
How about we give it a go now?
- I don’t want to fight you.
- Then, I’ll bring Si Feng back.
If I win, are you not going
to bring Si Feng back?
Depends on your capability then.
Xuan Ji, are you okay?
Could it be that she’s not
the master of this sword?
I’m fine.
Vice Palace Lord,
what is the meaning of this?
Is it because Xuan Ji talked back to you?
So, you are seeking revenge now?
Isn’t it too shameful
to treat a junior like this?
I saw that her sword is very powerful.
So, I wanted to test it out.
I thought that Shaoyang Sect
has a new talent.
She’s not that powerful though.
I hope that you can stay
away from her from now on.
How dare you!
How dare you talk to
your superior like that for a girl?
I haven’t punished you for the mask yet.
You want to add another offense?
I’ve promised to marry Si Feng.
What else do you want?
It’s still a crying mask
after you took off Si Feng’s mask.
It means that you don’t
truly love Si Feng.
How am I going to explain that
to Lize Palace?
But since Si Feng is
Lize Palace’s first pupil,
I’ll give you a chance.
Vice Palace Lord, are you asking
Xuan Ji to grow the Heart Lantern?
Your life depends on this test.
Don’t you want to give it a try?
That way, I’ll be able to give
palace lord an explanation.
What is Heart Lantern?
Little girl,
bury this shard in the soil
and water it with your qi.
If you have someone you want to love
with all you have,
it’ll grow within two days and
bear the fruit of Heart Lantern.
After that, take that Heart Lantern
and put it in Si Feng’s hands.
If the Heart Lantern is
as bright as before on his hands,
it means that your love
for Si Feng is true.
Do you want to give it a try?
It’s just a Heart Lantern. I’ll plant it.
Fine. I’ll wait for the result then.
Xuan Ji, it was so dangerous just now.
Why didn’t you use the power of
Dingkun Sword to fight him?
I don’t know what’s wrong
with this Dingkun Sword.
It’s like it is throwing
a tantrum just now.
I don’t care about that now.
I must plant this first.
I must grow it.
Then, the vice palace lord and
the others won’t pester you again.
Hero Yu.
This is Shaoyang Sect’s courtyard.
It’s not right for you to just
barge in here, right?
Senior Hao Chen.
Long time no see.
Xuan Ji always mentioned about you.
She said that you are the one
who taught her all her skills.
She has really learned a lot from you.
But I never heard Xuan Ji
mentioned about you.
Looks like both of you are not that close.
Xuan Ji is innocent, naive and
doesn’t know the way of life.
It’s not surprising that she’ll
agree to anything just to help you.
Please don’t take it to heart.
And don’t hope for any
result for your one-sided love.
Xuan Ji.
Will you be able to grow
that Heart Lantern?
Junior.
Junior, eat something.
I don’t want to eat.
I don’t want to eat anything.
If you continue like this,
your body will not be able to take it.
I don’t want to eat. Don’t ask again.
What should I do? Time is almost up.
What if I can’t grow it?
What will happen to Si Feng
if I can’t grow it?
You don’t have a heart.
How can you grow a Heart Lantern?
Yu Si Feng is the one who seduced you.
He deserves this.
She managed to grow the Heart Lantern?
She was just away from me
for a few months.
And she already has the ability to love?
With this ability,
her last chance of passing this trial
will be destroyed.
Now, they won’t be able to tell.
Her two days will be up tomorrow.
Without the Heart Lantern, it’s
time for Yu Si Feng to give up.
WEST WATER PAVILION
Look how unhurried he is.
The daughter of a leader sect
wants to marry him.
How wonderful.
He has really brought pride
to Lize Palace.
Brought pride?
The rules of Lize Palace
have already become a joke.
He dragged the whole Lize Palace down
with his matter.
How thick-faced he is.
We are all from the same sect.
Why do you have to say that?
Although Si Feng doesn’t like to gossip,
it doesn’t mean that these remarks won’t
fall into the ears of our palace lord.
Don’t be bothered by them.
Ruo Yu.
Your scar...
You know about Lize Palace’s rules too.
Losing my mask is a grave crime.
Of course I’ll be punished.
This scar is just a minor punishment
as a warning.
The Sky Hall is going to
make a ruckus today.
And I’ve fought them before.
So, the palace lord allowed me to come
with the vice palace lord to deal with it.
After it’s done, I’ll be sent into
the 13 Punishments Lianyu Pagoda.
I still naively think that
maybe the palace rules
will be more humane now.
But by the looks of
it, I was too hopeful.
So, I’m even more worried about you,
Si Feng.
I didn’t know that
your mask was like that.
Today is the day.
Will Xuan Ji be able to
grow the Heart Lantern?
This is a first.
So, I don’t know.
I believe in Xuan Ji.
Since she could take off
my mask, her love for me
must be real.
When did I fall asleep?
Heart Lantern?
I managed to grow the Heart Lantern.
King Bailing!
King Bailing, so the Kunlun wood that
you planted
can grow into a Heart Lantern too.
That’s not right.
You practice Heartless Tactics in both
the heavenly realm and human realm.
How can you grow a Heart Lantern?
And it’s such a huge Heart Lantern.
When Chu Xuan Ji took your Heart Lantern,
not only it doesn’t wither,
it shines even brighter.
Interesting.
This is just a tactic to make
Yu Si Feng give up.
Si Ming, if you think that you have
too much time in Siming Hall,
I don’t mind throwing you into
Water of Forgetting
and let you go through the
Path of Reincarnation.
King...
Farewell, King Bailing.
Chu Xuan Ji is still not here.
Si Feng, looks like the true love
that you are hoping
is not going to happen.
Si Feng!
I managed to grow the Heart Lantern!
Look. I managed to grow the Heart Lantern.
I know that you’ll
be able to grow it.
Great.
This Heart Lantern is so pure.
It means that you really
have someone who you love.
I already grew the Heart Lantern.
So, you won’t take him away now, right?
Hurry up and give it to Si Feng.
The disciples of Lize Palace
will be your witness today.
If the Heart Lantern still shines
like it is shining now,
it means that the one you love is Si Feng.
And Lize Palace will have nothing to say.
Don’t break your promise then.
Why is it like this?
The one you love is not Si Feng?
Si Feng, I’m the one
who grew the Heart Lantern.
Why will it wither? I...
Of course you are sincere to
save Yu Si Feng from danger.
Xuan Ji, let me ask you.
You agreed to marry him because
you want to help him and save him from
being punished by Lize Palace, right?
Yes.
I want to help Si Feng.
Isn’t that sincerity?
Yes.
Shaoyang Sect has always been
kind and righteous.
My junior was just feeling
compassionate towards him
and wants to help him.
That’s it.
All the misunderstandings
have been resolved today.
Please forget about this
marriage agreement between them.
Let’s not talk about it anymore.
Thank you for your understanding.
Xuan Ji, let’s go.
But, Si Feng...
I...
I’m fine.
Xuan Ji.
You have already done a lot for me.
Next, I’ll settle it myself.
Go back.
Si Feng.
Did I screw this up?
Forget it.
Who can say that wanting
to save your friend is insincere?
This is so touching.
I won’t blame Si Feng on this then.
Chu Xuan Ji, you don’t have to worry now.
Really?
Look. The vice palace lord
has already forgiven me.
I’ll be fine.
Don’t worry. Go back.
Xuan Ji, let’s go.
- Si Feng...
- I’m fine.
Si Feng.
What a pity. Your Loveless Curse
has no chance to be broken now.
Stay here if you want.
Nothing is more painful than having
your hope crushed by the one you love.
And no punishment
is more painful than the suffering
of the Loveless Curse.
Si Feng.
I’m fine.
Xuan Ji
is different from others.
Since the first time I met her,
she is very different from normal people.
I should’ve stayed away from her.
So,
unless it’s Xuan Ji’s personal choice,
I won’t believe in anything else.
Clear you mind.
The cloud is thin, and the wind is light.
This Star Cloud is very calm.
It means that my Spell of Tranquility
is working well.
I won’t be scolded by Senior Hao Chen now.
I’m fine.
You have already done a lot for me.
Senior Hao Chen said that
I made joke out of Si Feng.
Si Feng looked so sad just now.
Will vice palace lord trouble him again?
This is bad. I disrupted my qi
because I was distracted.
- Si Feng!
- Why were you so careless?
I was practicing the Spell of Tranquility
just now. But I kept thinking about you.
So, I accidentally disrupted my qi.
You kept thinking about me?
What about your heart then?
- I...
- Xuan Ji.
When you said that you’ll marry me,
did you say it out of
friendship and pity only?
Don’t you feel anything
different for me?
What kind of different feelings
are you talking about?
When we were at the wine
cellar, I’ve told you how I feel.
If you don’t understand,
I’ll...
make you understand it better then.
What’s wrong with me?
Why is my heart beating so fast?
I feel ill.
Si Feng, do you want to eat this fruit?
It’s especially sweet.
You’re scolded by vice palace lord today.
You must be in a bad mood.
You’ll be happier after eating this fruit.
Si Feng!
Si Feng, I...
Si Feng, why are you acting so weird?
Xuan Ji.
I like you.
More than anyone and anything.
I don’t want to share you with others.
I hope that
you’ll always be mine alone.
This hairpin is a love token
from my father to my mother.
I’ll give it to you now.
Si Feng.
This hairpin is too precious.
You should keep it well.
How can you give it to me?
I give it to you
because it’s important.
I hope that you can understand
my feelings for you and yours for me.
There were many misunderstandings because
I took Sixth Senior’s thing last time.
I can’t simply take
someone else’s thing again.
Si Feng, I never thought that
you’ll become so strange after
taking off your mask.
If I had known that it’ll be troublesome,
I wouldn’t have taken it off.
I can’t take this hairpin. Keep it.
Xuan Ji.
What are you doing?
Why is this cold water?
I...
It’s so hot and uncomfortable.
What happened?
Xuan Ji.
Yu Ning, is something wrong with my mind?
I can’t stop thinking about Si Feng.
I...
I don’t know what’s wrong with me.
It’s so uncomfortable and hot.
Am I sick?
Or did someone cast a weird spell on me?
Yes.
I think Si Feng cast a spell here.
Here? Really?
You really don’t know?
This spell is called heartbeat.
Heartbeat?
It’s like when I see my
handsome Pian Pian,
my heart will beat so fast
like there’s a rabbit inside it.
Xuan Ji.
But I’ve never felt this way before.
And I don’t feel
the same way towards others.
That’s because Si Feng is different.
Different?
Is everyone the same as me?
You look innocent.
But you are actually very bold.
But, if it wasn’t because I’m worried
that it’ll affect my cultivation,
me and Pian Pian would have...
- It’ll affect my cultivation?
- Of course.
Do you know how many couples
have given up the chance to be deity
in order to defend their love?
Looks like this is not something good.
It’s our personal choice.
It’s not up to others to decide
whether it’s good or bad.
You must decide.
You should’ve been
heartless and senseless.
How did you fall in love?
I can’t let you fall into this love trap.
Xuan Ji, what’s wrong?
I don’t know why
I’m feeling hot and bothered.
I’m going to take a cold bath.
This is a symptom when your basics
for the Heartless Tactics are not stable.
If someone goes too near to you
and says something seductive,
you’ll feel that kind of
weird feeling just now.
Did you encounter that lately?
I...
When I talked to Si Feng before this,
the same thing happened.
Is this really because of a mistake
during my training?
It happened to you too when
you were with Yu Si Feng?
This is a symptom showing that
your cultivation is not stable enough.
Be careful not to go too near to him.
I don’t want you to overdo it
and harm yourself and the others.
So serious?
Why would I lie to you?
You should listen to me,
get rid of all distractions,
practice your Spell of Tranquility
and cultivate yourself well.