LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 30
Brother Tong!
If you hurt Min Yan,
I'll kill your beloved flower demon.
She's just a flower demon.
You can take her life.
If I can create one Ling Long,
I can create many copies of her.
Brother Tong, save me!
Sixth Senior!
This is bad!
Our Birth Candles were used up!
You know how to enter
this place by using that item?
You are quite capable as well.
It's a pity that you
don't have much time.
Now, half of your soul is in Mount Buzhou
while half of it is in the human realm.
Let me see how much power you have left.
Take them down!
This demon actually has a malignant aura?
It has tremendous power.
It isn't an ordinary demon.
He's aiming for Xuan Ji,
but he didn't extinguish
Xuan Ji's Birth Candle.
What is he plotting?
Stop!
Let's stop fighting.
I admit my defeat.
Sixth Senior?
We don't have much time.
I want to exchange conditions with you.
Sky Hall wants the spirit keys, right?
As long as you're willing to
give me Ling Long's primordial spirit,
I'm willing to betray the Five Great Sects
and become your subordinate in Sky Hall.
I'll help you obtain all the spirit keys.
No! Sixth Senior, you mustn't do that!
Ling Long wouldn't want you to do this!
What else can we do?
She can't afford to wait any longer.
Wu Tong, you're just angry over
what had happened in the past.
I'll stay here, and you can do
whatever you want.
If you want me to be your dog,
I will.
Ling Long, this
man really loves you.
He loves me that much
even though this is our first meeting.
Why don't you dig out his heart
to see if he's sincere or not?
That's a great idea.
I'll make you pay for
your threats in the past.
Stop!
Brother Wu Tong?
Seems like he's sincere.
Why don't we let him stay
and let him witness our love?
Isn't that more interesting?
I'll do anything for you
as long as you return
Ling Long's primordial spirit to us.
Just you wish.
You want her primordial spirit? Fine.
Exchange it with another life.
Someone!
Second Senior!
Wu Tong, you scum!
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
Kill me if you dare!
Fine. I'll grant you your wish.
Zhong Min Yan, if you want to
retrieve Ling Long's primordial spirit,
you need to show some sincerity.
Kill him in front of me.
Sixth Senior, you mustn't do so.
If you can't kill him,
you won't be able to
retrieve Ling Long's primordial spirit.
Zhong Min Yan, I'm an impatient man.
Min Yan, it's a trap.
Don't believe him.
You mustn't do so.
I will surely save Ling Long
and Second Senior.
Do you think you can return?
Look at how much time you have left.
Zhong Min Yan, this is
the Black and White Ring.
It's made from Xuanyin Steel
and Mingyang Stone.
We need to wear this in order
to stay in Mount Buzhou.
Will you be my dog in exchange
for Chu Ling Long's primordial spirit?
Or will you let both Chu Ling Long
and your Second Senior die together?
You make the choice.
- I'll stay.
- Sixth Senior!
Second Senior,
I'm sorry.
I can't save anyone
if I don't do this.
No.
No!
Second Senior!
You want me to kill my senior?
I can't bear to do so.
But I had cut off one of his arm.
That's enough, right?
I've hurt my senior.
I can't turn back now.
You believe in me now, right?
Fine.
I see your sincerity.
Here's Ling Long's primordial spirit.
Xuan Ji!
Second Senior!
The Birth Candles are dying out.
We should return soon.
What's going on?
Brother Wu Tong!
So, their Birth Candles were
bound by the Binding Formation.
Their Birth Candles had extinguished.
And they can't enter or leave the place.
They will perish in Mount Buzhou.
If Xuan Ji dies there, it means
she will fail her tribulation.
I mustn't let her die in Mount Buzhou.
God of War, you're powerful indeed.
It's a pity that you can't
use your powers here.
You won't be able to escape
no matter how hard you fight.
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
Someone else didn't want
you to escape.
He has cut off your means of escape.
The Birth Candles have been extinguished.
Mortals can't last long in Mount Buzhou.
You can only stay here
until you perish.
Zhong Min Yan is smart.
He made the right decision.
No.
I mustn't die here.
I'm willing to surrender as well.
- Ruo Yu!
- Ruo Yu.
Don't try to persuade me.
I've lost my mask.
If I return to Lize Palace,
I will face death.
Staying here is a better option.
At least I can still survive.
This is pretty interesting.
You want to stay? Fine.
You need to follow his steps.
Show us your sincerity.
Kill them and
retrieve the primordial spirit.
Ruo Yu, don't fall for it!
They wanted us to kill each other!
You are on the verge of death.
You should play your last act
for me before you die.
Every man for himself.
Don't blame me for this.
Ruo Yu.
Si Feng!
- Si Feng!
- Xuan Ji.
Si Feng!
Si Feng! Don't scare me!
Si Feng! You'll be fine!
Si Feng!
We'll definitely escape!
I will kill everyone
who dares to hurt you!
Si Feng!
Si Feng! Wake up! Look at me!
Si Feng! This can't be!
Si Feng! We're home now!
Si Feng! We're out!
- Don't cry.
- Si Feng!
Si Feng! No!
I'm here!
No!
Si Feng!
Si Feng! Please don't scare me!
No!
Look at me! Please don't scare me!
Senior Hao Chen? Please save Si Feng!
Senior, please save him!
Senior!
I beg you!
Xuan Ji, what exactly happened?
Where's Min Yan and the rest?
Father.
Si Feng!
Aunt Ying Hong, how's Si Feng?
How is he?
The person who struck him
wanted him to die.
The sword pierced his heart.
Ordinary people would've been dead.
Si Feng survived due to
his many years of training.
But he's just a human.
His heart was pierced.
It'll be hard for him to survive.
Now, the qi in his body is dissipating.
We can't stop that.
I'm afraid that he can't last for long.
Si Feng, this can't be.
Si Feng, this is not real.
- This can't be!
- Don't touch him!
You were the reason behind this!
Si Feng would never take the risk
in Mount Buzhou if it weren't for you!
He would've never been injured
if he didn't block the attack for you!
If you can't save him, I'll
bring him back to Lize Palace.
- Si Feng!
- No!
He mustn't move in this condition.
Si Feng!
What should we do?
Don't tell me I can only
watch him suffer like this?
What if I reverse my Yang Jue
Skill and use it to protect his heart?
Will he be saved if I do so?
You mustn't!
You can activate the Nine Cycles Spell
by using the Heartless Tactics
in conjunction with Yang Jue Skill.
But it is very risky.
If anything goes wrong, your
blood would flow in reverse.
Not only will you not be able
to save him, you'll die as well.
What do you mean?
Si Feng is in this condition
because of Chu Xuan Ji!
Why aren't you letting her do so
when she has a way to save him?
Xuan Ji, our fate
is predetermined.
- You mustn't force it.
- I will force it!
I will save him! Even when
the possibility is close to nothing!
It's the best if I can save him,
but if I can't save him,
I'll die together with him.
Xuan Ji, stop messing around!
Don't stop me!
I'll do it.
I'll use the Nine Cycles Spell
to save Si Feng.
Hao Chen, you...
I'm better in Heartless Tactics
and Yang Jue Skill compared with her.
It's more stable if I do that.
Senior Hao Chen,
you don't need to do this.
You don't want me to save him?
Are you asking me to witness your death?
Yu Si Feng,
it's fine if you die.
But you've caught Xuan Ji
in your love web.
If anything happens to you
and Xuan Ji harbors anguish
because of this,
even a million deaths are not enough
for you to atone for it.
Today, I may save you,
but next time, I'll show
you my true colors.
Senior Hao Chen, how's Si Feng?
You've sustained internal injury.
Why didn't you tell us
before you did that?
Senior Hao Chen, when did you get hurt?
While I was searching for you,
I saw a suspicious demon at the altar.
And I was struck by his malignant aura.
But it's fine. I know my own condition.
Xuan Ji, Hao Chen was hurt
because of your reckless actions.
- Sorry, Senior. I...
- I said it's fine.
You don't need to worry.
It's just that the attributes of
Lize Palace and Shaoyang Sect
are different.
The Yang Jue qi that I've sent to
him can only stay inside his heart.
It can't travel through his entire body.
I can only continue this
when his body accepts it on its own.
Wait? We still need to wait?
How long can Si Feng last?
Will this method work or not?
Xuan Ji, if my qi can't
travel through his entire body,
you better be prepared.
If a strong spirit energy
is protecting his heart,
we may be able to force the qi
to travel through his body.
There are Pagoda Trees at the base
of this mountain.
If we can find a 10,000-year-old
Pagoda Tree
and create medicine out of its roots,
Si Feng will be fine after he consumes it.
Yes. Xuan Ji, take
care of Hero Yu.
You need to transfer your qi
to protect his heart every five minutes.
I'll follow you.
Hao Chen, you need to recuperate.
You mustn't hurt your own vitality
because of this.
I won't be able to give an explanation
to Senior Heng Yang
if anything happens to you.
Xuan Ji, take good care of your senior.
Let's go.
I'll go as well!
Yu Si Feng isn't that great.
He's not worth sacrificing your life for.
Xuan Ji, I told you before.
You don't know much about relationships.
How could you entrust your future
to a stranger like him?
Senior, I may not know
much, but I know enough.
Si Feng is the person I
want to spend my life with.
If he leaves me behind,
I would rather die.
You're trapped by your relationship.
No class at all.
This is the most despicable
and ignorant act.
Si Feng is the person I
want to spend my life with.
So stupid!
It's no wonder you fail
your tribulations every time.
If I don't help you,
this will continue forever.
Si Feng, please hang
in there. I beg you.
The medicine is here!
Chu Xuan Ji, help him up!
We didn't find any
10,000-year-old Pagoda Tree.
We'll see what a 1,000-year-old
Pagoda Tree can do.
How is it? Is it working?
No.
The spirit energy is weaker
than Senior Hao Chen's qi.
We can't protect his heart this way.
No. I must find it.
Even if there's no
10,000-year-old Pagoda Tree,
I'll find a 10,000-year-old
immortal fruit or something.
Si Feng.
Si Feng, hang in there.
What if they can't find anything useful?
What should I do then?
Should I submit to fate?
No, I don't want that.
Si Feng, you will overcome this.
Si Feng, I believe you can overcome this.
Please get better soon.
I didn't expect my Love Flower
to have so much spirit energy.
Maybe it can save Si Feng.
Its spirit power has protected your heart.
Si Feng, you must hang in there.
You must get better soon.
My king, according to my observation,
there are spirit energy from
the heavens surrounding Chu Xuan Ji.
I wonder what happened?
It's because Xuan Ji used the Love Flower
to save Yu Si Feng.
Yu Si Feng wasn't supposed to live.
I gave the Love Flower to Xuan Ji
in order to get rid of her anguish.
But she actually used it
to save an outsider.
Doesn't she understand
the purpose of Love Flower?
She doesn't understand indeed.
My king, are you angry because
she used an immortal item?
Or are you angry because she used
the Love Flower you gave her?
What a load of nonsense.
Are you still trying to joke around?
The Love Flower I gave her?
I'm just angry because she's stupid,
and she doesn't know what's good for her.
That's why Yu Si Feng is able to
lead her by the nose.
But Chu Xuan Ji has
recovered her six senses.
And she fancies another person.
My king, if you let her
continue her peaceful life,
there's a huge possibility that
she may be able to
return to the heavens.
Are you asking me to let them be together?
No! I mean, that
isn't suitable at all.
But my king, mortals
have a short lifespan.
Even if she is to be together
with Yu Si Feng in this life,
it will only be temporary.
When she returns to the heavens,
she'll understand that
life is but a dream.
By then, she can stay by your side
and continue her relationship with you.
How dare you say that!
You want me to let Xuan Ji
and an outsider to decide her fate?
Impossible!
She belonged to me in the past.
And she'll only belong
to me and the heavens
no matter if it's the present or future!
Since I've come down to guide her,
I will make sure nothing will be changed!
Xuan Ji has disobeyed me many times
because of this Yu Si Feng.
I mustn't let him stay by her side.
I need to sever
this ill-fated relationship for her!
Father.
This is Ling Long's primordial spirit.
We managed to save her.
Where's Min Yan?
Sixth Senior?
He...
Sixth Senior was left behind
in Mount Buzhou.
And he became Wu Tong's subordinate.
Father, did you give Sixth
Senior a secret mission?
He... He severed
Second Senior's arm
and he wants me to tell you that
he'll accomplish his missions.
What? What do you mean by that?
I didn't say anything like that to him!
Why is he...
Why did he do that then?
Xuan Ji, don't
you believe in me?
It's not that.
It's just that, he...
He...
Maybe Min Yan was used
by Wu Tong and the demons.
That's why he betrayed our sect.
Or maybe
that demon who brought you there
was the traitor.
The demon worked together with Sky Hall
to deceive you.
Impossible. Purple Fox
died in Mount Buzhou.
It's impossible for her to deceive us.
What about the disciple of Lize Palace
who entered Mount Buzhou with you?
What about him?
Ruo Yu?
Si Feng!
It's him.
He was the one who hurt Si Feng.
He was the one who hurt Si Feng!
I told you before.
I told you not to act recklessly.
But you won't listen.
Mount Buzhou is a place
unknown to mortals.
But you insisted on going there.
In the end, everything
has become a mess.
It's fine.
It's a lesson for you all.
Now, you know you should
think twice before you act.
As for Si Feng,
you don't need to worry about him.
Hao Chen has never boasted his abilities.
He won't do things
that he's not confident in.
Do you know that
your Senior Hao Chen only risked himself
to help an outsider because of your sake?
Hao Chen is passionate towards you.
And you two were a perfect couple.
But you insist on...
Father, Si Feng and
I love each other.
And we promised to never leave each other.
So, I will never marry
anyone except for Si Feng.
I've told Senior Hao Chen
about my feelings.
Father, I hope you can
understand me as well.
Fine.
Get up now.
I know that
Yu Si Feng is your benefactor.
We'll talk about this in the future.
I need to patrol the area
and set up the Thousand Bells Formation
in order to detect demons.
By doing so, the demons
won't be able to create trouble.
Si Feng, how do you feel?
Si Feng.
Does it hurt?
Si Feng!
The mortal's method doesn't work indeed.
It will only cause him harm
as the spirit energy is too strong.
Si Feng, I'll undo two of your seals
below your ribcage.
If not, you will die.
Silver Snake, no!
Si Feng!
Are you afraid that Xuan Ji
will know that you're a demon
after I unseal them?
But if I don't unseal them,
your blood won't flow.
And they won't be able to save you
no matter what they do.
Don't worry.
The spirit energy inside your heart
is very powerful.
It will suppress your demonic nature.
Listen to me, okay?
Please listen to me!
Si Feng!
Si Feng, how do you feel?
Do you feel better?
Si Feng! Why is this happening?
Why couldn't it suppress your power?
The thing that Xuan Ji gave me
clashes with the spirit energy
within my body.
Why is this happening?
Si Feng, you mustn't force yourself!
Oh right, Palace Lord once told me that
I need to undo your Dragon Crystal Seal
when you're in danger.
And let you consume human.
Si Feng, I'll bring
you some humans.
Wait for me!
Silver Snake!
Come back!
Si Feng, don't overexert yourself!
I know you don't want to
do this, but I have no choice.
Si Feng!
Give me the Dragon Crystals.
I won't give them to you!
Your life will be in danger!
Go and find him.
Find Brother Liu.
Hurry and find Brother Liu!
Si Feng.
Aunt Ying Hong, I'll bring
this medicine to Si Feng.
Be careful. It's hot.
Why is the door sealed with a spell?
Si Feng?
Si Feng!
Si Feng, are you awake?
Si Feng! Talk to me!
Si Feng! Open the door!
Si Feng!
I smell demon!
Why is there a demon here?
Si Feng!
Father!
A demon has captured Si Feng!
I caught its scent!
It's heading toward the forest! //
Let's go!
Where's the demon?
Xuan Ji, do you know where it is?
It has a faint scent.
It's hard for me to locate it.
Let's split up and search.
Okay. Let's split up.
Yu Si Feng, why are you here?
- Si Feng!
- Xuan Ji, did you have a clear look of that demon?
No.
This is strange.
Why didn't the demon kill Yu Si Feng?
Why did the demon escape
after it brought Yu Si Feng here?
Senior Hao Chen, that's enough.
Let's take Si Feng back.
Fine. I need to cast Nine Cycles
Spell to stabilize his pulse for now.
Let's go.
That demon is acting strangely.
Yu Si Feng had received
spirit energy from the heavens.
He should be fine, yet
he's extremely weak.
What exactly is going on?
By casting the Nine Cycles
Spell, I can travel around his body
and understand what's going on.
Strange.
There's nothing wrong with his body.
He's like an ordinary human.
Wait, something
is hidden within.
Demon Poison?
Senior!
Xuan Ji, don't come near me!
Be careful!
It's Demon Poison!
The poison is affecting Hao Chen!
I'm afraid his body will be taken over!
What should we do? He's casting
the Nine Cycles Spell!
If we force him to stop now,
the poison will enter his body!
Let me try!
No! The poison is too strong!
Ting Nu? Brother Liu?
Ting Nu, please save Si Feng!
I can neutralize the poison.
Wait!
Demon! How dare you come here!
Father, although Ting Nu is a
merman, he had helped us many times.
He was once an immortal medic.
His medical skills are superb.
- He's our friend.
- Nonsense!
We're cultivators! How could we
work together with demons?
Old guy, you're stubborn indeed!
What's wrong with demons?
Many kind-hearted demons
are much better than evil humans!
This is an emergency, you know?
It'll be too late if you don't
allow my friend to help.
Father, please let Ting Nu save them!
They can't hold out for long!
Ting Nu, please save them!
Sect Leader, this is an emergency.
Why don't we let him try?
Besides, he won't be able to
do much with us around.
The poison has been neutralized.
Si Feng!
Wait, it's him?
Strange, I tremble with fear
when I look at him.
But I have never seen him before.
Your injury isn't serious.
But there are residues of the poison
inside your body.
You better go on a retreat
and recuperate for a few months.
No!
I haven't captured that demon yet.
Senior, I'm afraid the demon
won't return anymore.
You need to recuperate.
Demon Poison is a big deal.
He Yang, bring Hao Chen back to Shaoyang
for his recuperation.
- We'll take it from here.
- Okay, come.
Si Feng.
Si Feng!
Ting Nu, what's wrong with Si Feng?
Si Feng's condition is complicated.
Yi Huan, I need your assistance.
Xuan Ji, you can wait outside
with the rest.
- I...
- Don't worry.
I'll do my best to treat Si Feng.
I...
Si Feng, I'm going to
reconstruct your heart.
I need you to stay awake.
And bear with the pain.
Thank you.
It's done.
Little Phoenix, you managed
to survive this ordeal.
But there are many ordeals
waiting for you in the future.
You better don't injure yourself anymore.
Okay. I'll seal his Demon Point right now.
Yi Huan.
We should use
the Dragon Crystal Seal on him
when he is fully recovered.
Fine.