LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 52
Because I’m afraid.
I’m afraid that you’ll look for me,
yet I’m afraid that you wouldn’t come.
I wanted to return to the past with you,
yet I’m afraid that everything
would disappear just like a bubble.
If that’s the case,
I would rather not see you.
Why would that happen?
Si Feng, believe me.
From now on, we’ll be together
forever.
We will be together.
We will never be apart.
We will be together forever.
Now, I finally understand.
Eternity
is too far away from us.
I don’t dare to imagine that.
But, at least
we can cherish our days together.
Si Feng, believe me.
Don’t worry.
I’ll undo your Loveless Curse for you.
Si Feng.
Why did the feather mark disappear?
Because...
Because the Loveless Curse is gone.
I don’t know how long I can survive.
I mustn’t ruin Xuan Ji’s future.
Si Feng.
Do you know that
I’ve traveled everywhere
in order to look for you?
Guess where I’ve been to?
I’m sure it’s the places
that we went before.
How did you know?
Because I went to the same places
and reminisced our past there.
Si Feng, do you feel that
I deserved
everything?
Not at all.
I know you cared for me.
And you looked everywhere for me.
Now, I feel smug.
Don’t think too highly of yourself.
Listen, if you dare to run
away again, I’ll ignore you.
You told me that you’ll follow my wish
when you tried to coax me earlier.
Were you lying to me?
Si Feng,
you’ve been to many places.
Why did you decide to stay here?
Don’t tell me it’s because of that Ah Lan?
No.
I’ll tell you the details in the future.
But I want to know what happened
in the past two years.
I want to know what you were up to.
I want to know if
you’ve met any other girls
other than Ah Lan.
No.
Xuan Ji, actually,
I missed you every day.
I wondered what you were up to every day.
I wondered you were happy or not.
I wondered if you’ve met
someone better than me.
I’ve found the best person in the world.
As for this hairpin,
I actually asked Miss Ah Lan
to repair it for me.
Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
I was upset for nothing.
I’ve finally made you jealous.
This hairpin has made a huge contribution.
Anyway, you mustn’t give this hairpin
to anyone else in the future.
Not even for repairs.
If not, I won’t let you off.
I don’t dare to do so
when you’re so fierce.
Here, I’ll put it on for you.
This is great.
Everything is just like the past now.
Oh yeah, Si Feng, I’ve been
meaning to ask you something.
What exactly happened
when you saved me in the secret ground?
Why can’t I remember anything?
You were hurt by
Jade Cup’s malignant aura.
And you fell unconscious.
Of course you don’t remember anything.
How did you get there in time then?
How did you know I wasn’t
able to destroy the Jade Cup?
It’s just a guess.
Think about it.
If the soul within the Jade Cup
could be destroyed easily, the
heavens would’ve acted long ago.
They don’t need to wait
1,000 years for it.
But I feel like something
was beckoning me when I was
trying to destroy the Jade Cup.
And when I tried to
destroy it, I felt terrible.
I feel like
I was related to Star of Mosha somehow.
You defeated Star of Mosha personally.
Of course you feel familiar with it.
There’s nothing strange about that.
That’s not the case.
Actually, I’ve thought about this too.
There are so many brave warriors
in the heavens.
But why did they only send God of War
to face the incoming Asuras?
Every immortal in the
heavens has their own past.
Some were cultivators in their past lives.
Some became immortals after
absorbing the essence of heaven and earth.
But what about the God of War?
What’s her past?
How did she become the God of War?
Xuan Ji,
don’t overthink stuff.
Star of Mosha is trying to control you.
It’s trying to bewitch you.
You should never
go near the Jade Cup again,
understood?
Yes.
I’m just curious.
Promise me this.
Let’s spend the rest
of our lives in peace.
And forget about the past.
Don’t pursue them any longer,
okay?
Si Feng?
Si Feng, what’s wrong?
Why do I feel like
you’re much weaker now?
I sustained some injuries while
I tried to seal the Jade Cup.
It’s fine.
Really?
Yes.
It’s just a minor injury.
Si Feng,
please don’t hide anything from me
no matter what happens.
I don’t want you to suffer in silence.
I don’t want you to suffer alone.
Okay.
Xuan Ji, you should rest now.
It’s late.
You’re here because of the
Glacial Pool and the Snow Lingzhi.
You borrowed the powers
of Juntian Loop and Chehai Hook.
And saved Xuan Ji by sealing the Jade Cup.
But your body can’t withstand
their immense power.
If I’m not mistaken,
it triggers much faster
than the Loveless Curse.
The weapons are still inside your body.
They’re torturing you, am I right?
So, you avoided Xuan Ji because
you thought you will die soon.
Why did you do that?
You do know everything.
Wu Zhi Qi told me that
with my powers, I can only
survive one year at most.
I didn’t expect myself
to survive until this day.
That Glacial Pool saved you.
I remembered something
while I was on my way here.
Rumor has it that
there’s a freezing pool at the end
of the land of Xigu.
And there’s a super rare Snow Lingzhi
that grows around that part.
I guess that Snow Lingzhi
can temporarily suppress
the powers of Juntian Loop and
Chehai Hook in your body.
That’s why you chose to settle down here.
If you’re lucky, when
the Snow Lingzhi
grows into a Nine Rings Lingzhi,
maybe it can fuse the two weapons
into your body when you consume it.
How is it then?
Did you find the Snow Lingzhi?
I’m always
unlucky.
The Snow Lingzhi is
only a small sprout.
For it to grow into a
Nine Rings Lingzhi, maybe
I’ll have to wait 1,000 years.
It did grow.
Gods
are still on my side.
The Demon Citadel
has been in ruins for over 1,000 years.
I wonder if
the ancient records still exist?
We found nothing after a long search.
The Demon Citadel is a huge place.
Don’t give up yet.
Let’s continue our search.
Ruo Yu, look!
Ancient records?
All the ancient records are here!
I’m sure this is the library
of King Asura!
No one was able to come
due to the strong malignant aura.
I’m sure this place
will provide us the solution.
Let’s split up and search.
Okay.
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
This place is collapsing.
You better be careful.
Spirit Beasts of the World?
Is there a way to terminate
my blood contract?
It does exist! In the book,
it states that there’s a type of moth
that lived around the Calamity Pool.
If their cocoons absorb the
blood of the spirit beast’s master,
they’ll follow the blood
of the spirit beast
and terminate the blood contract.
This is great!
Let me see.
But why were the other pages torn down?
Here.
It stated that if you want
the moth to turn into cocoons,
you need to feed them with rare herbs.
Rare herbs? I guess
it means something like Lingzhi.
Isn’t that easy?
The most important thing now
is to find the moths.
It’s stated in the book as well.
Calamity Pool is their habitat.
- Let’s look for them!
- But Silver Snake,
don’t you think this is too much
of a coincidence?
And why were the other pages torn down?
Maybe we’re missing out
on some vital information.
I’m sure it’s not that dangerous.
Anyway, everything is stated in the book.
We should find the moths
before anything else.
- Let’s go.
- Wait.
Okay. Let’s go.
Let’s go.
Yu Si Feng, you spoiled my plan.
I will never let you live in peace!
You want to use the Snow Lingzhi
to save yourself?
In your dreams!
Where exactly are they?
Ruo Yu, let’s look over there.
Silver Snake, you mustn’t go there!
That’s the Calamity Pool.
The water will corrode your body!
Stay here if you’re afraid.
I need to find them no matter what.
Silver Snake!
Ruo Yu, are you okay?
- I’m fine.
- I didn’t ask you to save me!
Seems like we can’t find any of them here.
Let’s take a look over there.
Ruo Yu, look!
Is this the moth’s larva?
Seems like they fit the bill.
This is great!
Ruo Yu, look!
Look what I’ve found!
Lingzhi?
I thought you went to gather food?
Calm down.
It’s stated in the book, right?
We need to feed the larvae
with rare herbs.
Only then, they’ll grow and form cocoons.
I’m so lucky.
I found this Lingzhi before our food.
Relax. We’ll continue
after I feed them with this.
Lingzhi?
But why is there Lingzhi around this area?
I don’t know either.
I saw a crow holding it with its beak.
And I grabbed it from that crow.
I’m amazing, right?
A crow?
Silver Snake, don’t you think there’s
something wrong with the crow?
The crow lead us here in the first place.
Now, it even gave you a Lingzhi.
How is that strange?
It’s only a crow. I’m sure
we can defeat it if it’s a foe.
Look!
They finished the Lingzhi already.
Calm down. I’ll get more
rare herbs for you.
Grow up fast and I’ll take you
to Si Feng, okay?
Xuan Ji, how are you?
I wonder where you are right now?
Do you have any news of Si Feng?
All of us missed you.
Father’s birthday is on the 16th.
We’ve invited all the other sects.
I hope you can celebrate it with us.
From Ling Long.
Si Feng!
Si Feng, Ling Long sent us a letter!
Si Feng?
Si Feng!
Ruo Yu, look!
The larvae are turning into cocoons!
Our effort wasn’t in vain.
Now, we just need to let them
absorb Si Feng’s blood.
And the moths will be able
to terminate my blood contract.
Let’s look for Si Feng right now.
But, how do we find Si Feng?
Although I don’t know
if Si Feng has recovered his power,
I can sense him now.
And, although his power is
weak, I can still locate him.
Ruo Yu.
Ruo Yu, although you did help me out,
you’ve hurt Si Feng many times as well.
Maybe he doesn’t want to see you.
Forget it. I think I should go alone.
You’re right.
I’m too ashamed to see Si Feng.
No one would want to
see a person like me.
But Yan Ran, I’m
worried about you.
Just treat this as my last trip with you.
And one more thing.
This bangle was supposed to be a pair.
I wanted to give one to Ruo Xue
and one to you.
But Ruo Xue is gone now.
I hope you can stay happy on her behalf.
Ruo Yu, I can’t accept that.
You’re really good to me.
Thank you.
But I only have Si Feng in my heart.
You know that.
Of course I know that.
Being good to you is my own business.
It has nothing to do with you.
I treat you like my little sister,
just like Ruo Xue.
Just treat this as a brother’s blessing.
After you terminate your blood contract
with Si Feng,
I will disappear by then.
And I won’t bother you again.
I...
Si Feng!
Why are you here?
Why is this happening?
Si Feng, what’s wrong?
It’s nothing.
It’s nothing? Look at your injuries!
How long do you intend
to hide this from me?
Si Feng!
Xuan Ji, it’s useless.
I’m in this state because
I’ve absorbed Juntian Loop and Chehai Hook
and my body can’t withstand
their power at the moment.
I’ll be fine after some time.
Juntian Loop and Chehai Hook?
No wonder.
That’s why you could seal the Jade Cup
even though I couldn’t suppress it.
Do you know how powerful
the Star of Mosha is?
You actually withstood
this pain because of me?
And you tell me that it’s a minor injury?
No way that’s a minor injury!
It’s because I overestimated myself.
It’s lucky that I’m
the 12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird.
It can’t kill me.
Is that why you made me angry
on purpose and asked me to leave?
Is it because of this?
How could you do that?
Didn’t we agree that
we’ll take on problems together?
Silly girl,
I’m fine since I told you so.
Look.
You see that Snow Lingzhi?
When it matures,
it can merge the powers within me
after I consume it.
Really?
Can that Snow Lingzhi really save you?
Silly girl,
I wouldn’t need to come here
every day if it couldn’t save me.
Stop crying.
If you cry, you’ll affect its growth.
By then, it won’t be able to save me.
How is that possible?
You’re lying.
There’s a golden ring
on the top of the Lingzhi.
Yes.
This is the rare Nine Rings Lingzhi.
I was lucky to discover it.
It takes 1,000 years for it to sprout,
to grow roots,
and to mature.
And the Lingzhi will mature this year.
It will be able to save me
once it matures.
You can rest at ease now.
Si Feng,
if you want me to care for you,
you need to forget about
your worries first.
You can’t just ask me to change
without changing yourself.
I was silly then.
I won’t do this in the future.
Lord God of War, it’s all my fault.
In the past,
you always protected me.
From now on,
I’ll protect you.
Lord Flying Snake?
Lord Flying Snake,
I didn’t know you were here!
Please forgive me!
Keep it down!
I will be done for
if Green Dragon hears about this!
But, Lord Flying Snake!
Lord Flying Snake,
you don’t need to panic.
The Four Sacred Beasts and
Lord Winged Dragon
were sent to the mortal realm
by King Bailing.
You almost scared me to death.
That was close.
Why did King Bailing
send them to the mortal realm?
I heard that he ordered them
to slay demons.
Slay demons?
What demons?
I think it’s those who were
connected to God of War.
God of War?
- You are dismissed.
- Okay.
He actually sent those people down there?
Don’t tell me King Bailing wants
to hunt down the stinky woman?
This is bad. I need to rush there.
Yu’Er, did you finish your homework?
I’ve bought you some food!
Why are you flying?
Where did you thieves come from?
How dare you trespass my territory!
Thieves?
You stole an item from the heavens,
yet you dare to say we’re thieves?
- Heavenly officers?
- What?
You don’t know how to use
the celestial eye you’ve stolen?
Don’t you know Winged Dragon - and White Tiger?
- This is bad!
How dare a Rose Gold Bird
like you steal from the heavens?
Return it to us immediately!
Don’t try to struggle like that
half-demon we met earlier.
You’ll only make it hard for yourself!
You mean Yu’Er?
Where is she?
My lords, my daughter
and I are just lowly demons.
You can take back
the celestial eye if you want to!
- But, my daughter...
- That demon is fierce and stubborn.
She will receive her punishment
somewhere else since she had offended us.
My lords, you two just barged in
without notice!
Of course she’ll try to defend herself!
I know you are magnanimous!
Please don’t hold it against her!
- Please let her!
- Enough!
She’ll handle the consequences
for your misdeeds!
I was the one who stole the celestial eye!
You should punish me instead of her!
What has that got to do with my daughter?
Don’t blame her
for something she didn’t do!
A lowly demon like you
has no right to question us!
Winged Dragon, save your breath.
Retrieve the celestial eye.
You are so unreasonable!
How dare you touch him!
Are you looking for death?
Here’s another lowly demon.
Purple Fox, be careful.
They’re sacred beasts from the heavens,
Winged Dragon and White Tiger.
So what? Listen up!
Wu Zhi Qi will come soon.
If you dare to touch me,
he’ll beat you up!
Wu Zhi Qi?
That damned monkey?
Stop wasting our time!
You lowly demon!
Wu Zhi Qi!
Winged Dragon, let’s go!
We’re no match for Wu Zhi Qi!
So, they’re over there.
How dare she lie to me!
Under King Bailing’s order,
we’re to capture the demons
which are related to God of War.
We shouldn’t mess with that monkey.
So that he’ll not cause trouble for us.
I’ll catch that merman then!
You keep an eye on the God of War!
Little Lingzhi, I’ll feed you
some of my qi.
Please grow quickly.
I heard that Flying Snake
became her spirit beast.
You don’t need to mention
that useless fellow.
Are you trying to tip him off?
But as brothers, I need
to remind you something.
With his bad temper, I
don’t think he’ll listen to you.
You feed the Lingzhi so much qi every day.
Aren’t you afraid that it’ll turn
into a spirit instead of maturing?
That can’t be!
I think the Snow Lingzhi will mature soon.
It will mature within two or three days.
That means we can attend
my father’s birthday.
By then, we’ll return to
Shaoyang Sect together
to celebrate his birthday.
And I’ll ask him for your hand.
Who said I’m willing to marry you?
I don’t think
it’s good for your reputation
if I tell everyone
that you stayed with me.
But, you wanted me to marry you.
That doesn’t count. Bye!
Where did you two go?
I’m starving to death!
Flying Snake, why did you come back?
I’m surprised that you still remember me.
I missed you, you know?
It’s meaningless for me to stay here
and see you two act all lovey-dovey.
That’s why I took a nap in the heavens.
Seems like you two had reconciled.
That’s pretty good.
My personal chef is back.
Go and make me some nice food.
Don’t treat Si Feng as your cook.
It’s fine. It’s easy to feed him.
It’s fine.
Little Snake, tell me
what you want to eat.
Did you find out about their reaction
towards God of War?
I have bad news. The heavens
has issued an order to arrest her.
The Four Sacred Beasts have
descended to the mortal realm.
The heavens
wants to deal with Xuan Ji
because of her identity.
I thought something was weird too.
But I saw that God of War
and Star of Mosha were
the same person
on the paintings in Demon Citadel.
I’m sure there’s something behind that.
Don’t you know what’s going on?
The scroll I saw in the heavens
wasn’t complete.
I didn’t see the most crucial part.
I really wanted to know...
I really wanted to know
what happened as well.
I wanted to know how
Star of Mosha become God of War.
I think King Bailing is the only one
who knows the whole truth.
You’re a heavenly officer,
yet you don’t care whether
Xuan Ji is a demon or not.
She was Chu Xuan Ji when I first knew her.
And that’s the person I know.
Right.
She’s Chu Xuan Ji.
She has nothing to do
with their past feuds.
Why won’t the heavens let her off?
I just hope that
Xuan Ji will never know about these facts.
Don’t worry. The Perfect Fruit
will help to hide your presence.
And I’ve set up a protective barrier.
It won’t be easy for the
Four Sacred Beasts to find this place.
Si Feng, look!
The Snow Lingzhi will mature soon.
Gods are fair indeed.
Now,
we just need to wait
for one more ring to appear.
Si Feng!
- Si Feng! I’ve finally found you!
- Yan Ran?
Ruo Yu?
How dare you still appear
when you’ve committed
so many atrocious deeds?
Xuan Ji, I know I’m sinful.
I’m too ashamed to see you two.
But I’m here to help Yan Ran
with her last wish.
When she’s done with it, I will
commit suicide to atone for my sins.
Ruo Yu was forced to do them!
Si Feng, Vice Palace Lord
captured his sister.
He had no choice too.
Even so, that doesn’t
justify his misdeeds.
Sixth Senior was hurt
because he trusted him.
Si Feng treated him as his best friend,
yet he almost killed Si Feng
with his sword!
Chu Xuan Ji, no one
can compare to you
when it comes to hurting Si Feng.
You...
Ruo Yu, you had no
choice in the past.
It’s fine if you change for the better.
I’ll just treat it as if we’re strangers.
Xuan Ji and I are leading a happy life.
And that’s enough.
How could you lead a happy life with her?
Si Feng, I’m the only one
who truly cares for you.
Silver Snake, do you
still not understand?
Our ties were severed
a long time ago.
I know.
That’s why I wanted
to terminate our blood contract.
I’ve found a way to do so!
It’s true!
Si Feng, look!
If you let them absorb some of your blood,
they will follow my blood
and terminate our blood contract.
By then, you won’t be my master anymore.
No.
Why not?
Si Feng is seriously injured.
His body won’t be able to take it
if you terminate the contract by force.
Chu Xuan Ji, what are you up to?
I won’t stop you
from terminating the contract.
But not today.
Maybe after some days.
After the Snow Lingzhi matures,
you can terminate your contract
whenever Si Feng feels like it.
You’re just afraid that I’ll take over
your place after I terminate the contract.
Yan Ran, don’t force me!
I’ll do it.
You were my spirit beast.
I will give you everything
you want.
Si Feng!
I knew it!
But I’m doing this
just to return you your freedom.
There’s nothing else to this.
You never know what will happen
in the future.
Let’s terminate the contract now.
Silver Snake,
you’ll face a thunderous calamity
if you terminate the contract.
You should be careful.
I’m not afraid.
So what if there’s a thunderous calamity?
This flower?
Isn’t it familiar?
That’s the flower you left behind
when you left the realm.
Green Dragon?
This is impossible!
We ate the Perfect Fruit.
You shouldn’t be able to detect us.
What trick did you use?
You were a heavenly officer
for so many years.
Did you forget the one item
that could help us locate everything?
You...
You took back
Liu Yi Huan’s celestial eye by force?
The celestial eye belonged to the heavens
in the first place.
It was stolen by Liu Yi Huan.
Now, we’re just taking it back.
This shouldn’t be a surprise.
Who killed Liu Yi Huan?
So what if I did kill him?
Not only that,
I will chop off Chu Xuan Ji’s arm
to terminate her blood contract with you.
Try it if you dare!
I’m a dragon! You’re a snake!
Do you think you can win against me?
Although I’m weaker than
you, I’ll make you regret it
if you dare to touch Chu Xuan Ji!
Are you out of your mind?
Liu Yi Huan isn’t dead!
We just took back the celestial eye!
I wanted to terminate her blood contract
with you because...
King Bailing had issued a kill order.
Vermilion Bird, White Tiger,
Black Tortoise and I
are here to deal with her.
I’m here to tip you off.
I don’t want you to die with her.
It’s rare for you to care about me.
But Green Dragon,
seems like you don’t
understand me well enough.
I, Flying Snake, have never been
afraid of death!
Even if there’s a kill order,
even if the Four Sacred Beasts are here,
you need to get through me
before you touch Chu Xuan Ji!
Do you want to die so badly?
Green Dragon, the
heavens is a cold place.
You should come to the mortal realm
when you have the chance.
There are many things more
important than one’s life here.
You’re acting like this because
you involved yourself in mortal affairs!
Seems like you won’t wake up
if I don’t beat you up!
Fine.
I’ve been avoiding you for so many years.
It’s time for us to have a fight!
- Si Feng!
- Silver Snake!
Si Feng!
- Si Feng, how do you feel?
- Si Feng.
Si Feng!
I’m fine.
The blood contract is gone!
- Silver Snake!
- This is bad!
- Why are you stopping? Are you scared?
Leave now!
Fine! You better leave, you coward!
Didn’t you see that?
This is a thunderous calamity.
I don’t know who attracted
the thunderous calamity,
but this area is under
the watch of the heavens now.
It’ll be too late if you don’t leave now.
Xuan Ji is in danger.
Flying Snake, come back!
Green Dragon, here’s an order!
By the orders of King Bailing,
the Four Sacred Beasts are to meet up
and hunt down the God of War!
Yes, my king!
Ruo Yu!
The third strike,
it’s actually the Golden Lightning?
Si Feng, no!
Si Feng!
Si Feng, why is your body so hot?
Si Feng, is it because you can’t
control the divine weapons’ power anymore?
Si Feng, hang in there!
Why is this happening?
It’s hard for me to find you, you know?
Please be safe!
Hang in there! Please be safe!
You must be safe!