LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 36
SHAOYANG
Sect Leader, all the disciples are here.
We can depart now.
Okay. Let’s get ready to depart.
Father.
Master.
- Ling Long?
- Although we are not Shaoyang’s disciples,
you need as much help as you can get
to fight the enemies now.
Please let me and Ling Long
go to Dianjinggu with you.
We don’t mind if we can just tag along.
No matter what, we want to help Shaoyang.
You are not disciples of Shaoyang.
You have no rights to participate
in the Flower Session.
Both of you better stay here.
Father, the demons of Sky Hall isolated
my primordial spirit from my body.
I vow to seek my revenge.
I really want to help you.
Master, Ling Long and I
have fought a long time with Sky Hall.
We know them best.
To know one’s own strength and
enemy’s is the sure way to victory, right?
Father.
Fine. Both of you
can join the Flower Session
with me in Dianjinggu. But,
remember, don’t act
recklessly, understand?
- Thank you, Father.
- Thank you, Master.
DIANJINGGU
Si Feng, look.
Dianjinggu is so beautiful.
What is this?
Any door in the heavens
is prettier than this place.
If the heavens is so good,
why did you come here?
Let me tell you.
Being kicked out and
sneaking out are different.
You’re kicked out.
We are at different level.
We are indeed different.
I’m the master. You are the spirit beast.
We are indeed at different level.
I’ve been discourteous.
What are you talking about?
You are too kind.
Valley Master Rong.
Sect Leader Chu, how are you?
Hello, Brother Dong Fang.
It’s great that Miss Ling Long
has returned to normal.
Thank you, Uncle Dong Fang.
Old man, are you done yet?
When are we going to eat?
Keep quiet.
Please come in then.
I’ve prepared some drinks
- to welcome all of you.
- Valley Master Rong.
I need to talk to you in private.
My fellow elders,
please entertain the others.
- Okay.
This way please.
Let’s go.
What does he mean by drinks?
Aren’t we eating?
Shut up.
You food thief, how dare
you steal from Dianjinggu!
Come down now!
I’m showing respect by eating
your chicken drumstick.
So many people are burning incense for me.
And I don’t even want to eat their food.
Tell us who you are if you dare.
I’ll teach you a lesson!
Listen carefully.
I am Lord Flying Snake
from the heavens.
You can kowtow now.
Kowtow now.
Food thief. Beat him up!
- Yes! Beat him up. Hit him!
- Stop!
My seniors and juniors.
This is just a misunderstanding.
He is here to participate
in the Flower Session too.
But since young, he
is mentally challenged.
Eating is the only thing he knows.
So, sorry. He’s too pitiful.
Fine then. Let’s not fight with a dummy.
- That’s right. Let’s go.
- Let’s go.
You stinky woman,
what is the meaning of this?
Are you humiliating me on purpose?
I’m such a powerful being in this world.
You...
I’ll let you off the hook this time.
Si Feng.
Can I return my spirit beast?
Lize Palace is here!
Greetings, Master.
You left without saying goodbye
in Fuyu Island.
I thought you don’t want to be
the disciple of Lize Palace anymore.
Of course I wouldn’t do that.
I left Fuyu Island because
I had to do something.
Please forgive me.
Hero Yu, you just left and
came back as you please.
How impressive.
Si Feng left to save someone.
Even if he did wrong,
his merits can offset his faults.
Heroine Chu, you are
too much of a busybody.
I heard that you are going to participate
in this Flower Session too.
You better pay more attention
to the competition.
I’ll look forward to your performance.
This way please, Vice Palace Lord.
Seniors and juniors, this way please.
Si Feng, I’ll ask my father to
put in some good words for you.
Lize Palace dislike the intervention
of outsiders the most.
I’ll find a way
to ask for my master’s forgiveness.
Back then, you left
without saying goodbye.
Now, you came back to find me again.
Are you thinking that
you are the same as them
after spending so much time with them?
They are very cunning.
They’ve never treated us kindly.
You are so close with them.
I’m worried that
you’ll end up getting hurt.
Master.
The friends that I’ve made
are different from others.
They’ve never hurt me before.
Please be rest assured.
Does the ’them’
include Chu Xuan Ji who
activated your Loveless Curse?
I was the one with
the obsession back then.
It was not Xuan Ji’s fault.
She is just lying to you!
If it is a mutual affection,
why will you be separated
because of an obsession?
Xuan Ji even gave up
her life in order to save me.
She is sincere towards me.
Sincere?
Then, tell her who you are.
Do you dare do that?
I’ll tell her
when I find the right time.
The right time?
I want to see
when is the right time.
When the time
comes, don’t regret it.
Why are you still here?
Master.
I want to ask you something.
A few decades ago,
did the death of
Sect Leader Shaoyang’s wife
have anything to do with Lize Palace?
Lize Palace has killed many people.
How can I remember?
So, we’ve really killed someone before.
Why?
If we didn’t kill them,
were we just going to let them
find out our identity and kill us?
Si Feng.
You are too young.
You don’t know them well.
Or else, why do you think Lize
Palace will set the no-love rule?
I remember that
around 20 years ago,
a disciple of Lize Palace
was once in love with the daughter of
the old valley master of Dianjinggu.
They could’ve had a happy life together.
They even had a child.
But they found out about
his identity by accident.
The disciples from those sects
took away the old valley master’s
daughter by force and pressured her
to reveal our secret.
In the end,
she committed suicide.
Only by doing so could she
protect the secret of Lize Palace.
Look.
There is nothing that
these people won’t do.
No matter how devoted the lovers
are towards each other,
once they find out about our identity,
there will be no good
ending for the lovers.
Si Feng, listen to me.
Leave Chu Xuan Ji as soon as possible
so that you won’t get hurt.
No!
We owe her this.
I have to set this right for her.
And then, I’ll bring her away.
Lize Palace has kept
this secret for so long.
Nobody has ever found out
about our secret.
I can keep this secret from her forever.
When we want to keep it
a secret, of course we can.
But when we don’t want to do it,
do you think we’ll care
about those who are weak?
During the Flower Session,
the 12 people who were there
when the Demon Whip broke
are all here in Dianjinggu.
Besides the three of us,
that spy must be among
the rest of the 9 people.
Yesterday, I already let out news that
we’ll move our spirit key from our
underground palace to the West Hall today.
And we’ve applied the
blood of merman on the door.
I’m sure that he’ll come forward
with the spirit key as bait.
This colorless merman blood will
turn red once someone touches it.
And that person will be the spy
that we are looking for.
Is West Hall safe?
Don’t worry.
The door of West Hall is
Dianjinggu’s special Vault Door.
No even a fly can enter.
Our Armored Warriors move
when they smell demons.
They are the best opponents
of the demon clan.
It’ll be best if we can
catch that rat today.
But if he manages to escape,
we’ll still know who he is.
I’m just afraid that there are
more than one demons among us.
What do you mean?
Everything is still a speculation for now.
I’ll report back to you when
I have a definite answer.
If it is a mutual affection,
why will you be separated
because of an obsession?
She is just lying to you!
Xuan Ji even gave up her life
in order to save me.
She is sincere towards me.
Si Feng.
How did it go with your master?
Si Feng, someone might see us.
I don’t care.
No matter what happens,
I want to be with you.
Okay.
I promise you that I won’t go anywhere.
I’ll stay here with you.
Okay?
By the way, Si Feng.
I’ve been trying to solve
this Lugong puzzle.
But it’s too difficult.
I still can’t unlock it until now.
But I really want to know
what you wrote for me.
Can you tell me about it?
Maybe it’s best
if you can’t unlock it.
Si Feng, what’s wrong with you?
There are some things that
I need to settle in person.
If anything happens,
no matter what you hear or see,
don’t let your imagination run wild.
Wait for me to come back
and I’ll explain it to you, okay?
Si Feng.
What’s wrong with you today?
Your master still doesn’t agree for us
to be together.
Right?
I’m just
too afraid of losing you.
After we capture all those demons
in Dianjinggu,
I’ll go to Lize Palace with you
to beg for your master’s blessings.
Xuan Ji.
I’m sorry.
I’ll set things right for you.
Did I really guess it wrongly?
Yu Si Feng.
You are indeed a demon.
I won’t let you off the hook
so easily this time.
I’ll show Xuan
Ji your true color.
These Armored Warriors move
when they smell demons.
I’ve already sealed up your demonic aura.
They are useless now.
Thank you for your help.
Let’s go.
According to Wu Tong, we can
open this door with me using my qi
to turn it clockwise and you using
your qi to turn it anticlockwise.
This is why I brought you
into Dianjinggu beforehand.
Let’s start.
Okay.
My lord.
This is not right.
Why is it empty?
This is a Demon Trap Formation.
Leave now, my lord.
Sky Hall can lose its Wolf.
But it can’t lose you.
I have no regrets to serve
you and die for us demon clan!
My lord, leave now!
Leave now!
He’s inside.
Open!
Wolf? So, it’s you.
It’s not him.
There must be another one.
So, it’s you.
Dong Fang Qing Qi?
- I’ll kill you to avenge Qing Rong today.
- Wait.
He can’t die yet.
We still have a lot of things to ask him.
Wolf, you should know that
it’s impossible for you to escape from
this Demon Trap Formation.
You better tell us honestly
who’s your accomplice.
Fine.
I’ll tell you now.
All the demons in this world
are my accomplices.
- You...
- I’ll struck you with Hell’s Nail
and we’ll see how long
you can keep your mouth shut.
You humans are too naive.
I won’t give you that chance
to interrogate me.
A demon came in?
He’s dead?
Vice Palace Lord.
You are late.
Did you say that the spirit key’s vault
is as strong as iron?
But even a demon can come in.
Is it safe here?
Of course the spirit key is hidden
in the safest place in this hall.
Dianjinggu’s traps are foolproof.
But a demon got in.
Demons are wicked.
They must have used some demonic spells
to open the Vault Door.
You have to be careful.
Then, please lend me your qi to
strengthen this Demon Trap Formation.
Okay.
We are willing to help you.
Why didn’t you tell me about this earlier?
How long were you going to
keep this from me?
Please don’t blame us.
We didn’t know the identity of
the demon at first. We had to be careful.
We can’t let anything go wrong.
Now, everybody saw very clearly that
only the palm of
the vice palace lord is red.
I never thought that the
vice palace lord of Lize Palace
is the spy of the demon clan.
Everybody.
Before this, I was worried about
having more than one demon among us.
Now, I already have a definite answer
for this speculation.
Look. What is this?
Rose Gold Bird?
I got this from putting Yu Si Feng’s hair
into a Demon Revealing Formation.
Are you saying that
Yu Si Feng is a demon too?
Yes. When we were at
Qingmu Town before this,
he covered up his own identity
by calling out others of his same kind.
But I was still suspicious of him.
So, I used this way to
test his identity in secret.
And I am right.
These demons are really
despicable and shameless.
Before this, I even considered Yu Si Feng
as a good husband for Xuan Ji.
What a close call.
I almost married off my daughter
to the demon clan who killed her mother.
Yu Si Feng must have approached Xuan Ji
since the start with an ulterior motive.
Since the incident at Fuyu Island,
I’ve been suspecting him.
Finally, I found out about
the truth today.
This time, I won’t let him
escape so easily.
Vice palace lord is a demon.
Yu Si Feng is a demon too.
If that’s the case, we don’t know
how many demons
have infiltrated Lize Palace.
I’m afraid that...
Are you afraid that Lize
Palace is not infiltrated by spies
but is a demons’ nest through and through?
Yes. Not only Yu Si Feng
and the vice palace lord,
even Ruo Yu who disappeared with
the spirit key might be a demon too.
I’m afraid that Lize Palace
is not as simple as it seems.
Luckily, we realized it sooner.
Now, we can plan.
I don’t care if Lize Palace is
demons’ nest or demon clan’s accomplice.
We have to take them down.
To be safe, we have
to trap Lize Palace here
without tipping them off
during this Flower Session.
Or else, if they are all demons
and show their true forms,
they’ll be hard to take down.
Besides having traps and mechanisms
to attack demons,
we have Demon Prison Formation
that is passed down from our ancestors.
But we can only activate
this formation at noon
when we’ve gathered enough Yang energy.
So, we have to find a way
to drag this until noon.
Okay.
If that’s the case,
the rest of us sects will gather
our powerful disciples now.
At noon tomorrow,
we’ll do our very best to capture
all demons in Lize Palace.
Master!
Something is not right.
Let’s go.
Here.
Listen carefully. Hide your weapons
inside your shirt tomorrow.
Don’t tip them off.
Listen to the palace lord’s order.
No mistake is allowed.
Yes.
Master, is palace lord really
going to take down those sects?
I won’t let it happen.
Silver Snake.
Go and find Flying Snake in secret.
Master.
You are here to see me so late at night.
Have you come around?
You want to return to Lize Palace?
Master.
All the disciples outside
are battle-ready.
What is Lize Palace planning?
What are we planning?
Lize Palace has endured for so many years.
We’ve had enough.
It’s time to make an end.
Master.
Are you really going to
attack those sects?
But for the past centuries,
we have been living in harmony.
Isn’t that great?
Living in harmony?
What harmony?
Si Feng.
You are wrong.
They killed Hao Feng.
They wouldn’t let Hao Feng marry me.
My grudge for them runs deep.
I’m going to kill them all
to avenge Hao Feng.
Master.
Who is Hao Feng?
Hao Feng is the daughter of
Dianjinggu’s old valley master.
We fell in love at first sight.
We secretly promised to get married.
But that father of hers and
the elders from those sects
wouldn’t let us
be together.
So,
the one who fell in love with
the daughter of the old valley master
is you.
That’s right.
Back then, the disciples
from those sects
forced Hao Feng to tell them my identity.
They forced her to take her own life.
All these years,
I have been looking for a
chance to revive Hao Feng.
Heaven rewards the faithful.
Finally, I got this chance.
Today, I’m going to
annihilate those sects
and get Dianjinggu’s
thousand-years-old stalactite.
That way,
I can revive my Hao Feng.
My dear disciple,
do you want to help me?
Master.
Your wife has indeed died horribly.
But you already found a way to save her.
If she’s revived, she won’t
be happy when she sees
her own sect being butchered.
I’m willing to beg Dianjinggu for you
to get that thousand-years-old stalactite.
I’ve gone through so many years of pain.
Do you think I’ll change my mind
just because of your words?
Dream on!
I’ve had enough of those sects!
I’ll annihilated them!
I will avenge Hao Feng!
Master.
I can’t let Lize Palace
butcher everyone here.
What is it?
I’m the one who trained you.
Do you think you can stop me?
I was too careless.
I fell into these mortals’ trap.
Wolf, you were so loyal to me.
I’ll definitely avenge you.
After I’ve succeeded in awakening
the Star of Mosha,
I’ll not forget you.
Vice Palace Lord,
palace lord’s disciple has asked for you.
He has something important to tell you.
He summons me so late at night.
Is it about those insane talks again?
Junior!
Yu Si Feng, how dare you!
You took away my Gold Feather
Medallion when my guard was down.
Are you going to revolt?
Master.
Please forgive me.
I have to stop this no matter what.
Please lend me
your Gold Feather Medallion.
Si Feng!
WEST HALL
The palace lord has ordered for us to
sit out from this Flower Session
and return to Lize Palace at once.
He just told us to go according to plan.
Why does the plan suddenly change?
Where’s the palace lord?
We want to speak to him.
- Yes. We want to speak with him.
- Wait, Yu Si Feng.
What is the meaning of this?
This Gold Feather Medallion
represents the palace lord.
Are you going to go against his order?
Palace lord and vice palace lord
are discussing strategies now.
Don’t disturb them. Stand back for now.
I’m going to talk to Valley Master Rong
about our withdrawal now
and then, we’ll leave the valley.
This is your beloved disciple.
He trapped us here.
Release the one in your shadow now.
Shut up!
I need to see Valley Master Rong
for an urgent matter.
Wait here. I’ll inform
Valley Master Rong now.
Tell Valley Master Rong that
Yu Si Feng is here.
Valley Master Rong has invited you
to the west courtyard to talk.
Valley Master Rong, Yu Si Feng is here.
This way please.
Valley Master Rong,
Lize Palace has an emergency.
I’m here under my master’s order
to withdraw from this Flower Session.
Valley Master Rong.
What is the meaning of this?
Senior Hao Chen.
You evil demon.
How dare you ask us this?
Valley Master Rong.
Leave him to me.
- You have more important things to do.
- Okay.
Don’t let this demon go so easily.
Let’s go.
Yu Si Feng.
You evil demon.
You’ve kept us in the dark for so long.
I told you before that if you
use feelings to trick Xuan Ji,
I’ll destroy you.
Yes.
I’m a demon.
But I’ve never wanted to hurt anyone.
Things are urgent right now. Let me go.
Let me settle it, okay?
Or else, it’ll be very dangerous.
Dangerous?
You just want to say that Lize Palace
is aiming for the spirit key
and we are not your match, right?
But luckily, we are ready this time.
No matter what Lize
Palace is, this time,
we’ll annihilate all of you.
Wait here.
I’ll show Xuan Ji your true colors.
Senior Hao Chen!
Xuan Ji,
at first, I didn’t want to awaken your
God of War’s power in human realm.
I just wanted to put you on
the right path so that you can
be a small deity in the heavens.
But since it’s unavoidable that your power
as God of War will be awakened,
let’s make your awakening
even more worth it.
DIANJINGGU
Why is Si Feng not here yet?
The first Flower Session of Dianjinggu.
Chu Xuan Ji from Shaoyang Sect verses
Hao Feng from Lize Palace.
Hao Feng?
Xuan Ji, be careful!
Such a powerful sword.
Even the elders can’t wield
a sword like this.
Who is this person?
He’s so powerful.
Why are you so rude?
You just attacked me right away.
Chu Xuan Ji.
You’ll die under my sword today.
Flower Session is about winning or losing.
Not life or death.
What nonsense are you talking about?
This is more interesting.
Stinky woman, fight well.
Show me your real power.
I’ll laugh at you if you lose.
Little girl, you like to dodge?
What happened?
Something is pulling on my legs.
Die!
Xuan Ji.
Stinky woman, stab the shadow below you.
What is that?
It’s the Fire Lion.
Fire Lion?
Save Xuan Ji!
Sect Leader.
SHAOYANG SECT
Father.
Sect Leader.
Who are you?