LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 10
It’s exactly as Si Feng said.
Does everyone
in Lize Palace know this spell?
It’s embarrassing to say this.
I don’t know these spells.
Si Feng is gifted.
The usual disciples of Lize Palace
can’t even compete with him.
If it wasn’t for
the palace lord forcing him,
I don’t even know what would happen.
His natural gift might be wasted.
What’s wrong with Si Feng?
Why did your palace lord force him?
It’s nothing much.
He just wants him to go back to
the right path. But Si Feng...
Outsiders cannot ask about
what happened at Lize Palace.
Ruo Yu, you talked too much. Let’s go.
What does Lize Palace
got to do with you then?
You don’t see yourself as an outsider?
What do you know?
- I know everything.
- Enough.
- What don’t I know?
- What do you know?
- What do you know then?
- Enough.
- What’s wrong with me?
- Stop arguing.
The exit is near.
Let’s go.
- Move! Me first!
- Don’t be rash!
Get up!
Ling Long!
Si Feng! Don’t go!
Don’t worry. I’ve recovered.
You should be worried
about Zhong Min Yan.
I do, but I...
Shaoyang’s Transmission Charm?
This is bad!
Ling Long and the rest are in trouble!
- Bird demon!
- Let us go!
I’ll kill you if I get out!
Ugly little demon! Let us go!
Stop arguing at this time!
Ling Long!
If Xuan Ji and Si Feng
are baited by the charm,
how much of
Si Feng’s power will be recovered?
Within an hour of using the secret arts,
even if force was used,
only 30% of the power will be recovered.
It’s bad.
Do you think we will be annihilated?
Careful! Don’t come here!
Let them go!
- Ling Long!
- Beware of traps.
You are the one who hurt me?
Yes. You fool!
How dare you embarrass yourself here?
Look out!
- Save them. I will kill him.
- Alright.
Xuan Ji, look out!
- Xuan Ji!
- Si Feng!
Si Feng!
Si Feng.
What are you?
Who are you
to ask me?
The two stars will merge soon.
No one can stop
Sky Hall from doing what they want!
Si Feng!
Xuan Ji.
Xuan Ji!
Si Feng!
- Xuan Ji.
- Si Feng.
- Xuan Ji, how are you?
Xuan Ji.
- Si Feng.
- I’m fine.
What’s wrong with Xuan Ji?
Xuan Ji’s Yang Jue Skill is
between level seven and eight.
Her mental state is unstable.
Something went wrong.
She passed out due to exhaustion.
It’ll be fine when she wakes up.
Really?
Why didn’t I know?
How did you know?
What do you mean something went wrong?
She almost killed Si Feng!
Xuan Ji didn’t do it on purpose.
- What do you mean?
- She wanted to save him
and went mad.
I’m fine.
She didn’t do it on purpose.
No more arguments
now that the demon is killed.
Ruo Yu.
Let’s take a look over there.
Si Feng.
Why did you release all the Quru Birds?
They were controlled by the Aoyin.
Now that the Aoyin is dead,
the Quru Birds are harmless.
That Aoyin cleaned the furnace beforehand.
There’s no residue at all.
I wonder what did these Zhuyu Grass
were used for.
This demon said it was from Sky Hall,
and said some unknown things.
I wonder what Sky Hall is planning?
Unexpectedly, Sky Hall seems like
they disappeared for the past four years
but they have been
doing something secretly.
We don’t understand what does
two stars merging for now as well.
Why don’t we send
letters back to our sects
to warn them?
Look out!
- What is that?
- No worries.
That is Aoyin’s tendon.
It’s a stubborn thing.
It will be stuck onto flesh and blood.
It’s a great material
to make Demon Tying Rope.
Si Feng, let’s go back
since the demon is dead.
Let’s first regroup at Wangxian Town.
If you have no place to stay,
we can stay together.
Alright.
Master, are you still going
to visit Chu Xuan Ji?
You’ll be worried
as long as she isn’t awake, right?
You should know the Loveless Mask
prevents you from falling in love.
You shouldn’t stay here.
I know more about you
regarding my life.
Nothing worries me here.
Find the shopkeeper to pay for the room.
We are leaving.
Master is trying to pay for the room.
Master, wait for me.
- Si Feng!
- Xuan Ji.
You’re awake?
How are you?
Where’s the Aoyin?
We were saved?
How were we saved?
Also, Si Feng.
- Is Si Feng alright?
- Xuan Ji.
Don’t worry.
You killed the Aoyin. Don’t you remember?
Me?
Xuan Ji went mad at that time.
She had no conscience.
Xuan Ji, when you practise next time,
try to be safe, and don’t rush.
I...
Don’t think too much.
Oh, the people of Wangxian Town
want to thank us
with a banquet downstairs.
I’m sure there are
many delicious food for you.
Pack up.
Let’s...
Sixth Senior.
I still have something else to ask you.
Ling Long,
I have something
to talk about with Xuan Ji.
Why don’t you head down,
and greet them first?
I’ll head there with Xuan Ji soon.
Alright.
What is Xuan Ji hiding from me?
Even if there’s a secret,
it should be a secret with me.
When did Little Six and her...
Si Feng, you must be here to see Xuan Ji.
Don’t worry, Xuan Ji is awake.
But, she has something
to talk about with Little Six.
It’s inconvenient for you to go there.
Chu Xuan Ji’s condition
is none of our business.
No one cares. Don’t think too much.
No one cares?
Si Feng cares.
I know you don’t care.
No one cares whether you care or not.
- Si Feng doesn’t care...
- Immortal master!
The immortal masters are here.
We have nothing
to repay for the immortal masters’
help for Wangxian Town.
We can only prepare
a simple banquet to thank all of you.
All of you must not reject our invitation.
- Please head there.
- Please.
Go on ahead.
I’ll invite other immortal masters.
It’s alright. My sister and another senior
have something to talk about.
- They will go later.
- Sure.
Please head over there.
Isn’t that the same as
what happened with Gudiao?
Why did it happen again?
Also, I’m always feeling that
I did something to Si Feng.
Sixth Senior.
Can you tell me
what happened at that time?
You were pointing your fingertips
at Si Feng.
You almost...
But you stopped immediately.
Si Feng is fine.
- You didn’t hurt him.
- I...
I dreamt of it.
Inside my dreams,
I was always killing people.
I was covered in blood.
But why can’t I feel anything?
I...
I almost killed Si Feng.
That’s not it, Xuan Ji.
That was just a dream.
But it almost came true.
I wanted to protect everyone.
But I couldn’t control myself.
I am afraid that I will become a monster
who recognises no one
and kills for no reason.
That won’t happen, Xuan Ji.
Calm down.
Don’t confuse your dream with reality.
But those dreams...
When the dreams overlapped
with the shards,
they...
Everyone. A toast to the immortal masters.
If it weren’t for
their help to kill the demon,
Wangxian Town will
have to suffer from a famine.
- Thank you, immortal masters.
The people of Wangxian Town want
to thank us with a banquet downstairs.
Sixth Senior.
I still have something else to ask you.
Ling Long, I have something
to talk about with Xuan Ji.
Why don’t you head down...
Si Feng.
Si Feng, let’s leave after the meal.
Why are you in a rush again?
We just sat down.
Si Feng knows what he is doing.
He won’t be rushing to his death.
Don’t say that word again. How dare you?
Enough.
Just eat.
Si Feng.
Si Feng, why won’t you drink with me?
Why are you so cold towards me?
You forgot about our relationship?
You forgot that we killed the Gudiao
and save the merman together?
You forgot that we went to Dianjinggu
to punish Wu Tong?
Stop talking.
- Shut up!
- You...
Enough. Let’s eat.
Zhuyu Grass?
It was used as fuel.
I see.
Sixth Senior.
I am too afraid.
The merman told me
I am not my complete self.
What if
I can’t control myself one day
and make all those dreams come true?
Merman?
You mean the shards
of the Mirror of Origin?
Why are you mentioning this again?
Didn’t you say you will forget about it?
Senior Hao Chen
did forbid me
to find the Mirror of Origin.
But
I didn’t give him the shard I have.
- I’m always feeling...
- Xuan Ji.
Do you still have the shard with you?
That must be the problem.
Don’t be deceived by the merman.
Demons like to deceive people,
and create a demon in them.
I’m sure you have a demon in you.
A demon in me?
Why did the demon used me?
How would I know
about a demon’s evil deeds?
It’s just like
the Aoyin controlling the Quru Birds
to destroy all the Zhuyu Grass here.
We don’t know the reason for that too.
Xuan Ji, don’t be afraid.
It’s nothing.
Let’s destroy the shard
and it won’t affect you again.
That darn Chu Xuan Ji.
Why did I meet her?
I can’t allow Si Feng
to get mixed up with her again.
I might as well do the extreme.
Sixth Senior.
Why don’t we forget about it?
Let’s hand it to Master.
- No!
- Even though...
I don’t know
what kind of troubles you will get into.
We can’t tell others.
Let’s try again.
Think of a way to destroy it
and let it become an eternal secret.
Look out!
- Sixth Senior. I can’t move.
- I feel numb too.
I think the spell got reflected.
What about the shard?
The shard has been destroyed.
It’s all over.
But, we are in this situation.
- Why don’t we call for help?
- No.
How can we explain this?
We can’t call them.
How should I explain this?
Use your qi.
Use your qi to break the spell.
Si Feng.
You forgot how well you treated Xuan Ji?
Xuan Ji got hurt because she took
the hairpin from Wu Tong for you.
You cared about her.
I always thought you liked Xuan Ji.
What’s wrong with you?
That’s nonsense.
Lize Palace has its rules.
Disciples should not
be friends with others.
It’s my duty.
Duty?
Fine.
Let go of your duty today.
Did you really forget us?
You don’t care about us and Xuan Ji?
Anything exceeding my duty
will bring its consequences.
You don’t have to think too much.
Fine.
Fine, you forgot everything.
It’s fine if you changed.
But the one who grew up with me...
The one who grew up with me
changed in an instant too.
I didn’t know anything about her
like a total stranger.
Si Feng, I think
I saw a shadow over there.
Do you think it’s a demon?
Where’s the demon?
Where’s the demon you saw?
I think I saw a shadow went in
but I’m not sure if it’s a demon.
Xuan Ji.
Xuan Ji!
Ling Long.
Ling Long, you’re finally here.
It’s not what it seems.
We are just...
- We are...
- Zhong Min Yan.
How dare you!
How dare you bully my sister?
- I won’t forgive you!
- Ling Long.
- He bullied you!
- No. Stop it.
Sixth Senior did not bully me.
Ling Long. Since we disturbed them,
- let’s just leave.
- Don’t touch me!
Let me tell you.
Don’t try to add fuel to the fire.
What did I do?
Can you explain what you are doing?
We were just...
- Zhong Min Yan, I’ll kill you!
- Ling Long!
Xuan Ji, he was bullying you
because he thought you are ignorant.
- Don’t you know that?
- No. Sixth Senior didn’t bully me.
He was just helping me. It’s true.
I was helping Xuan Ji with her troubles.
I tripped accidentally.
You want to kill me? Fine.
I’ll stand here. Kill me.
- You...
- Xuan Ji, move!
I’ll kill him!
You want to kill me?
Fine.
Let’s see how you kill me.
You don’t care anymore
once your temper comes up.
I’ve had enough. Kill me!
Don’t regret it.
You might hug me and cry
when you regain your consciousness.
Why should I regret?
I hate you in all of Shaoyang Sect.
If you die, I’ll laugh in my dreams.
Ling Long.
Stop it.
Use it to defend yourself.
Isn’t this your family heirloom?
Yes. It’s for my future wife.
This dagger
is with you.
This dagger was given to me
by Sixth Senior
before I went up to Xuyang Peak.
Yes.
I gave it to Xuan Ji.
He gave it to you four years ago?
Yes.
Young lady of Shaoyang Sect.
Isn’t that obvious?
Both of them were engaged with each other.
Being intimate for awhile
isn’t something surprising.
Xuan Ji.
He gave you his family heirloom dagger.
You are really going to be
a daughter-in-law of Zhong family.
Keep it well.
Zhong Min Yan.
In that case,
stop behaving casually
and treat Xuan Ji well.
I won’t forgive you
if you don’t.
Ling Long.
Si Feng, let’s leave.
Farewell.
Si Feng!
Silver Snake. Are you satisfied?
I admit that I lured you there
but she isn’t worth your time and efforts.
Isn’t that right?
You don’t have to do anything.
Si Feng!
Si Feng, don’t leave.
I have something to tell you.
I’m sorry. I’m busy.
Si Feng. We didn’t meet for four years.
I don’t want to leave you like this.
We are just strangers.
Stop pestering me.
Don’t get involved with me.
Si Feng!
Don’t touch it!
What is this?
WINE
Are you crying?
Leave me alone.
I have something to tell you.
I could give you an explanation
if you weren’t throwing a tantrum.
Yes. I’m stupid and foolish.
I didn’t see it clearly.
Do you have to act this way?
Can’t we talk at all?
- Can you let me finish...
- Zhong Min Yan!
In your eyes,
aren’t I a stubborn young lady
who always causes troubles?
You look down on me in your heart.
Why are you still compromising for me?
I don’t pay attention
to anyone unrelated anyway.
We will both go on our separate ways
in the future.
- Alright?
- Can’t I say a few words?
You are always like that
since you were young.
You don’t care whenever you got angry.
You don’t show mercy when you were right.
It’s worse if you were wrong.
Do you know what I’m going to say?
It’s fine.
If I have to say,
that Lu Yan Ran is more reasonable.
- At least...
- Great.
You are comparing me with Lu Yan Ran.
I wasted all my time on you.
You are just watching? Help!
It’s useless. Aoyin’s tendon will
grasp firmly on blood and flesh.
It depends on flesh and blood.
We can’t do anything
unless it releases its grasp willingly.
I’ll give you blood if you like them.
Release her and bind me.
Bind me.
It’s not moving.
Yan Ran.
I think the Aoyin tendon
likes Xuan Ji’s blood more.
It’s useless.
I don’t believe it.
Can’t it feel pain? Can’t I cut it?
It’s still not working.
Are you happy?
If I can’t cut it,
I can cut your hand instead.
You’ve caused enough trouble.
She’s the one who caused you trouble!
Chu Xuan Ji.
You caused such a big trouble.
Why are you smiling?
You’ve noticed it?
I made a mess today.
It’s my bad for smiling.
But you won’t have to leave, right?
- Of course I’m happy.
- I have to leave anyway.
There’s no difference.
Don’t talk about these useless things.
That’s different.
She was trying to cut my hand off,
but you protected me.
That means you are worried
and still care about me.
- I’m happy.
- You think too much.
I stopped her because it won’t work.
Do you think I want to drag
your dismembered arm along?
Si Feng, let’s not waste our time.
Isn’t Xuanyuan Sect nearby?
Sect Leader Zhu Shi
is knowledgeable and sophisticated.
I’m sure he can
deal with this Aoyin tendon.
That’s our only way.
Everyone is tired today. Rest early.
We will go to Xuanyuan Sect tomorrow.
What about her?
I’m telling you.
Don’t sleep in a room with Si Feng!
You hear me?
Then...
Where should I sleep tonight?
Si Feng.
I am very sleepy.
I can’t sit on the chair any longer.
Sleep.
Si Feng, where will you sleep?
You don’t have to worry.
I will explain to Zhong Min Yan tomorrow.
You have no choice,
but to stay here for the night.
Si Feng, I wanted to ask you.
Why is Ling Long so angry
about what happened
to me and Sixth Senior?
She even said Sixth Senior is so bad.
I think Sixth Senior is not bad.
You don’t know what is love.
- Don’t think about it.
- Who told you that?
I have someone I like too.
I like Sixth Senior.
Aren’t you sleepy?
Why aren’t you sleeping?
I’m not sleepy now.
I don’t understand.
Although I like Sixth Senior,
Ling Long is just as important
as Sixth Senior.
I don’t wish
that either of them is unhappy.
They had a big argument this time
because I like Sixth Senior.
Do you think Ling Long
hates and looks down on Sixth Senior?
That was why she was angry
when she heard I like Sixth Senior.
Si Feng, since you are so smart,
can you help me?
Is there any way to let Ling Long
like Sixth Senior to?
I have no time to listen to
the issue between you and Zhong Min Yan.
If you are not sleepy,
just get out.
I’m sleepy.
I haven’t wrote to Senior Hao Chen
about my experience yet.
Si Feng ignores me too.
I should write to Senior Hao Chen.
Senior Hao Chen.
I didn’t write to you about my experience
because we met a demon recently.
The problem has been solved.
I will report to you about
what happened for the past two days.
First.
I met Si Feng, but he ignores me.
He is always trying to leave too.
I’m quite happy now that
he can’t leave at the moment.
I hope I can get back this
important friend of mine this time.
Second.
Ling Long and Sixth Senior
had a bad argument.
Ling Long said
her bazi doesn’t match with Sixth Senior’s
so they made up as quickly
as they start a new argument.
They always told me not to worry.
It would be better if they can get along
and care for each other.
- Xuan Ji, what are you doing?
- The fire...
Si Feng, the fire will shorten the tendon.
No!
Si Feng. I told you, right?
This thing will become shorter.
Hand.
Si Feng, how is your injury?
Let me take a look at your injury.
Chu Xuan Ji.
Why are you still so reckless?
This is improper.
Aren’t you engaged with Zhong Min Yan?
How could you do that?
I just want to take a look at your injury.
I don’t need your concern.
This bell...
Didn’t you say you threw it?
What does that have to do with you?
It’s a useless thing anyway.
I don’t know why it’s still with me.
You never realised
such a big thing on you?
- Don’t you feel anything at all?
- Chu Xuan Ji.
Why do you have so many questions?
How would I know?
You are hungry.
I’ll get you something delicious.
Alright.
Delicious.
Si Feng, come closer.
Help me out. I can’t eat it otherwise.
It’s faster this way.
Go to sleep after you eat.
- Si Feng, aren’t you eating?
- Open your mouth.
This is delicious. Try it.
It’s fine.
- Try it.
- Shut up.
Eat.
Si Feng.
I can’t eat if I shut up.
Are you still eating?
I want the soup.
I want that.
That.
Are you full?
Yes.
Si Feng, look at this.
It turned back to normal.
Look.
Stop fooling around. Go to sleep.
Senior Hao Chen.
Nothing special happened.
Grilled fish was delicious.
We ate spicy hotpot.
I’m very happy.
It was fun.
I hope Father will
let us leave the sect more.
Three.
We helped the people of Wangxian
Town deal with the problem of Quru Birds.
The people thanked us.
I’m quite happy.
Zhuyu Grass is so delicious.
It was wasted unfortunately.
Oh.
These Quru Birds
were controlled by an Aoyin demon
from sky hall.
The Aoyin demon said something
about two stars merging together.
We don’t know what it meant.
Si Feng.
Your shadow looks nice.
I forgot. You don’t like people
to praise you.
When I told you your smile looked nice,
you got angry all of a sudden.
I think you really look nice
when you smile.
But I never see your smile
ever since we met again.
I am very worried about you.
I don’t know what happened to you.
I regret it.
I think I missed out a lot of things.
Si Feng, I think it’s weird.
I still miss you
although you are right in front of me.
Si Feng.
Are you asleep?
Your mask
is different from the one in the past.
Don’t touch.
It’s just that
you won’t show me your face ever again?
Can’t we go back to how it used to be?
Finding the Mirror of Origin will fall
into the depths of desire and obsession.
Trapped by the demon within.
It’s bad for cultivating.
Sixth Senior always
uses this way to make people happy.
It works every time.
What’s wrong, Si Feng?
Are you feeling uncomfortable?
No.
I just think it’s funny.
Funny?
The past.
What happened before.
We can never return anymore.
Chu Xuan Ji.
Why do you still come near me?
The person I don’t want to see the most
while roaming the world is you.
We shouldn’t have met.
Why?
Tell me.
Why did you choose Zhong Min Yan?
I chose Sixth Senior?
What do you mean?
Why do you
like him?
Are you asking why I like Sixth Senior?
I think Sixth Senior is very nice.
I want to see him.
I feel happy with him.
I want to be with him forever.
He...
We also have a secret.
Enough.
Stop it.
I understand.
You asked me for yourself.
Why are you getting angry?
Chu Xuan Ji.
Thanks for telling me all of these.
Si Feng.
- Me and you...
- I’m tired.
It’s getting late.
I need to sleep.