LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 58
Are you trying to
revolt against me, General?
Stop lying to me!
Tell me.
What are these?
Every single piece of my body,
who put them together for me?
Do you
feel a tiny bit guilty
about what you did to me?
God of War!
Shouldn’t you call me Rahu Ketu?
You conspired with Southern Lord
and used the Jade Cup of
Southern immortals to seal my soul!
Now, I want you
to explain yourself.
Let me ask you!
Where is my soul?
Isn’t it good to be God of War?
Fine.
All these years,
I’ve lived in confusion.
I didn’t know where
I was born or came from.
I had no name because
you dared not mention it.
I had no family and friends
because you’re afraid that
I’d find out my origin.
And I never had one single soldier
under my command.
You relied on my ability,
and yet you’re scared of me.
You’re afraid that I’d recall everything,
lead the army, and rebel against you!
In fact, the reason I’m so
different is because I’m not myself.
No wonder I felt upset
whenever I killed an Asura.
Because we came from the same clan.
And you, King Bailing,
ordered me to kill them all!
Tell me, why did you do that?
Are you sure you can control me forever?
You deceived me into
becoming the God of War.
I have always trusted you.
How dare you and the heavens
use me like this!
God of War!
You’re being disobedient and rebellious.
This is unpardonable!
What did I do wrong?
It’s your fault.
Ask Jade Emperor to come and see me!
If not, I will burn
the heavens down!
Even though you’re a brave general,
you shouldn’t have
barged into the celestial hall
and bawled at King Bailing!
This heavens,
I could protect it.
And I can kill it.
How outrageous you are!
Take her down!
Bailing!
I want you to explain yourself today!
Bailing.
Just you wait.
I will definitely take it back.
God of War!
- Enough!
- Stop calling me God of War!
I will not let you go!
I will kill you.
I will kill all you rats
and avenge myself!
God of War is attempting a rebellion
and revolting against the realm!
Escort her to
the Altar of Banishment at once!
Yu Si Feng.
Do you see this?
This is the heavens
that you wanted to protect.
They remain despicable.
And they don’t keep their word.
They keep spouting lies.
Heaven and earth are the furnace.
His copper, all things of creation.
In that case, let’s throw everyone
into the furnace for reformation.
Today, I am going to kill everyone
in the heavens.
I shall reorder the three realms.
Do you all think you can guard
this Sea of Life and Death?
Yu Si Feng.
Just stay in this barrier.
- No.
- And watch how I kill them.
No.
The Sea of Life and Death has receded.
Listen my fellow tribes!
Let us storm the heavens!
Look.
That’s Jade Emperor’s mansion.
Bailing.
I’m here.
You can’t go any further!
You can’t destroy Transcendent Furnace!
And I won’t allow you to talk
the stinky woman into doing evil!
You must obey me because
you are Chu Xuan Ji’s spirit beast.
Otherwise, you will be punished.
The stinky woman
is my one and only master.
You are not.
Let her out now!
You used to be
the spirit beast of Chu Xuan Ji.
I’m not going to kill you.
But it doesn’t mean that
you have the right to talk to me.
Scram!
Brother Rahu.
You’re here.
I remember we once promised
that we’d drink and talk every day.
I’m surprised that
thousand years have passed.
Since we’re gathering here
today, why don’t we catch up
so as to fulfill our promise?
Do you think I’ll still believe
what you say, Bailing?
Brother Rahu.
Can’t you even catch up with me?
A cup of wine crippled me
thousand years ago.
If you were me, would
you drink such tea again?
You worry too much.
Brother Ketu.
You’re always on my mind.
That’s why I came to advise you.
For the sake of our friendship from
the heavens to mortal realm,
stop it.
Bailing.
You lie too much.
That’s why you’re deceiving yourself.
Have you ever looked down at your hands?
They’re full of Chu Xuan Ji’s blood.
The blood of God of War. And mine.
It’s not dry yet.
All you want is
a marionette you can control.
Today,
I am going to take revenge
against this blood feud!
I’ve been trying to save you
for thousand years,
but I can’t get rid of
your murderous thoughts.
It seems that Asuras
are incurably murderous.
Forget it.
Look, what is this?
Mirror of 36 Heavenly Spirits?
That’s right.
This Mirror of 36 Heavenly
Spirits restrain all kinds of demons
and get rid of all kinds of evil thoughts.
Today, I am going to capture you with it.
And I hope you will abandon
your murderous thoughts and repent!
Bailing.
In the Sea of Life and Death, I saw
thousands souls of Asuras who were killed.
They’ve been tortured by hatred
for thousands of years.
And they’ve looked forward
to avenge themselves.
You want us to abandon
the murderous thoughts and repent?
Today, I will let them ask you this.
When will you reap what you sow?
Next, it’s your turn.
Rahu Ketu.
So what if you manage
to destroy the mirror?
This is Heavenly Central Hall,
where the strongest heaven’s law lies.
You can’t even figure out where I am.
Don’t you act outrageous here!
I know you’re being protected
by the heaven’s law.
And you think I can’t hurt you.
But what a pity. Heaven’s law
was made when the world was created.
As long as I overturn Transcendent Furnace
and rewrite the rules,
you won’t be able to hide yourself.
What a boaster you are!
Transcendent Furnace
is the root of the three realms.
There is no way you can find it!
Is it?
You seem to have forgotten that I
was once God of War of the heavens.
I happen to know
how to make it show itself.
Stop it!
Stop it now!
Xuan Ji.
Who are you who’ve
trespassed Mount Kunlun?
It’s outrageous of you to come
to Xi Wangmu’s backyard.
If you disturb Jade Emperor’s rest,
heavenly punishment
will be meted out to you.
Heavenly officer,
we came all the way here
to report something to Jade Emperor.
You’re mouthy.
Kick them off to the mortal realm.
- Yes!
- Off to the mortal realm?
We walked a long way!
- It took a lot of effort to come up here!
- What are you waiting for?
Take all of them down!
Old fogey, aren’t you being unreasonable?
Bring it on then!
We’re here to beg Jade Emperor.
We can’t act recklessly.
But do we let them send us
back to the mortal realm?
Since he said that we can’t
disturb Jade Emperor, we will then...
- Jade Emperor!
- Old Jade Emperor, come out!
- Jade Emperor, we’re here to see you!
- Jade Emperor!
- Come out!
- We would like to see Jade Emperor!
- Come out and see us!
- Come out now!
- Save us!
Take all of them down!
- We want to see Jade Emperor!
- Come out, Old Jade Emperor!
Lord Xuan Huo, let them see me.
Jade Emperor, but they...
Jade Emperor.
They are here.
We have here two mortals,
two Rose Gold Birds,
and a demon monkey.
What are you here for?
Jade Emperor, we’re all
family and friends of Chu Xuan Ji.
We came all the way to
Mount Kunlun to ask for your help.
Chu Xuan Ji?
That lass who’s
the reincarnation of God of War.
I remember that her power
of God of War has awaken.
The mortal realm is now invincible.
What else can I do for her?
Jade Cup is opened.
Xuan Ji has become
Star of Mosha, Rahu Ketu.
He’s going to lead the demons
and attack the heavens.
And he wants to reshape the three realms.
You must save the three realms, please.
And save Xuan Ji!
It is true that one reaps what one sows.
The time has finally come.
Jade Emperor.
Why are you still playing chess?
Because I have yet
to figure out this game.
Jade Emperor.
The three realms are going to be ruined.
Aren’t you worried?
I once advised Bailing against
it, but he insisted on doing so.
Thus, what is happening.
Everyone from the three realms
are all in this calamity.
It’s kind of you to
worry about the people.
But the heaven’s law
made me the Jade Emperor.
I must obey the law.
Without a chance, I can’t interfere with
the fate of three realms.
You should leave.
What is a chance?
We came all the way here to see you.
Now that’s a chance.
Both the mortal realms and sects
are fighting against the Heaven Fire
and rescuing the people.
That too is a chance.
Yu Si Feng came to the mortal realm
because of Xuan Ji.
That’s more of a chance.
I think, surely you know his
name in the heavens, Xi Xuan.
He is trying his best
to save the three realms.
We are doing the same thing.
So is everyone else.
And you’re not doing anything about it.
Chance? That’s just an excuse!
Xi Xuan.
He is as persistent as he was.
Lass, you’re right.
But this is their chance, not mine.
Chance is not predictable,
and yet heart is.
I am holding a black stone
and solving this endgame.
It is the chance I have.
If I manage to win this game,
that means my chance is here.
But you see,
now the white stones are
more than black stones.
This shows that
my chance are still far away.
Fine. Since you’re helping us
only if the black stones win,
I’ll help you solve this game then.
Now that the chessboard is
full of black stones, you won.
How could you?
How outrageous you are!
How dare you spoil Xi Wangmu’s endgame!
Hurry and take down this disobedient lass!
Interesting.
It is truly interesting.
It was an unsolvable endgame.
And the ink has dyed
the white stones black.
It is against the rules
to call this a victory.
But it cannot be called a defeat
since the board is full of black stones.
Perhaps I didn’t realize that because
I was so involved in the game.
And you jumped out of the game.
And that’s the solution.
Fine.
I’ll come with you.
Thank you, Jade Emperor!
Jade Emperor!
What about me?
How do I go back?
My lord, what do we do?
What else could we do?
The solution is to jump out of the game.
Let’s walk back.
How dare you!
You didn’t see this coming, did you?
The God of War who used to
protect the heavens...
is now turning it upside down!
What an irony!
You tried to make God of War
serve the heavens, by fair means or foul.
Fine!
Today, I will use this face of God of War
to destroy the heavens
you’ve meant to protect
and avenge my humiliation with my blood!
Rahu Ketu!
You’re ruining the world and the people!
You are unforgivable!
Unforgivable?
I’ve become unforgivable
when I killed the Asuras
thousands of years ago!
The wails you are hearing,
the Asuras I killed
let out the same wails!
They say every living thing suffers.
But why do they have to suffer?
It’s because of the heaven’s law and fate!
Heaven’s law
is made by the Transcendent Furnace.
I just need to overturn the furnace,
and all this suffering
will cease to exist!
Dream on!
I am standing right here,
and you shall not go near the furnace!
You are overestimating yourself!
I will not let you
destroy the three realms!
You want to die?
No rush.
You are next!
No!
Xuan Ji.
Yu Si Feng.
Stop digging your own grave.
Rahu Ketu.
If the Transcendent Furnace
gets destroyed,
everything will cease to exist.
What you love and hate will all be gone.
You can’t do that.
I am Star of Mosha,
not Chu Xuan Ji.
I don’t want love and hate.
Just let it go.
Yu Si Feng.
Don’t think I won’t kill you.
If you really want to kill me,
go ahead then.
I’m going to die anyway
after the furnace gets destroyed.
Instead of dying for no reason,
I’d rather be killed by you.
Didn’t you leave half of
your primordial spirit in Demon Citadel?
I want a complete self.
If the furnace gets ruined,
my memory will be gone.
Even if this body survives,
it’s no different than death.
I’d rather be killed by you.
That’s better than living like
a living dead that has no memory.
I have no interest in killing you myself.
Since you didn’t preserve
any primordial spirit,
you shall fend for yourself.
Jade Emperor.
Bailing.
I told you so.
Xi Xuan.
Jade Emperor.
You’re still in the mortal realm.
I should call you by
the name you use there.
Yu Si Feng.
I know everything you did.
Well done.
Long time no see, Rahu Ketu.
I was wondering who could
stop my divine weapons.
It turns out that Jade Emperor is here.
This has to do with the three realms.
Not only should I be here,
everyone should come here.
Greetings, Jade Emperor.
Xuan Ji, we’ve told Jade Emperor
about your grievance.
He’ll take care of it. You need not
ruin Transcendent Furnace anymore.
Jade Emperor.
Are you all here to stop me?
I’m not trying to stop you.
But the resentment
between you and Bailing
has to do with
all the lives in three realms.
As the lord of heavens,
I have to solve this problem.
Jade Emperor.
This demon is unstoppable.
I tried my best, but I couldn’t stop him.
Please take him down, Jade Emperor!
I told you so.
Everything has karma.
You made the God of War
and killed all the Asuras.
You ordered both the heavens
and mortal realm to kill the demons.
You initiated Heavenly Meteor Formation
and offered up Shaoyang.
You killed the mortals
with Sea of Life and Death.
They’re all extremely tragic incidents.
Those lost lives, they all
belonged to the three realms.
And now you’re accusing
Rahu Ketu of being demonish.
I think you are the one
who’s being demonish!
Jade Emperor.
I did all this to protect
the three realms!
Not at all, it’s to protect your madness!
Is this what you want?
In fact, that day you’ve
made the wrong decision
at Baiyu Pavilion by
the bank of Ruoshui River.
No.
That’s not the case.
Do you refuse to believe it?
Fine. Let me show you
what it would look like
if you did not poison Rahu
Ketu’s wine thousands of years ago.
You need not worry.
In fact, I came with a good news.
Immortals and demons
are having a fierce war.
There’s no good news.
It has to do with this great war.
Two days ago, I submitted
a memorial to His Majesty
requesting for a ceasefire in
the heavens and Demon Citadel.
His Majesty said yes to it.
Really?
Positive.
After this drink with you,
I’ll go communicate the decree.
The entire army of Asura will withdraw
and head back to Demon Citadel.
The three realms
will be peaceful from then on.
Why don’t you finish
this cup of wine?
- Sure.
- Here.
- Please.
Bailing.
You ruined the peace we could have had.
The war broke out again because
the Asuras didn’t receive the decree.
If you could stop back then, things
wouldn’t have turned out this way.
But you insisted on judging others
by your own standards,
and went down to human realm
to control God of War’s trial.
In fact, if you hadn’t
gone down the realm,
this trial would’ve been over by now.
I, Chu Xuan Ji,
have completed all ten trials.
And I have regained my flesh and blood.
I know what love is.
I seek for your permission to come back
to the heavens, Jade Emperor.
Yu Si Feng and I will work together
to protect everyone in the three realms.
Is it my fault?
Is it really my fault?
Bailing.
Everything in this world
has its own conscience.
If you don’t move, he won’t.
But you buried your evil inside
the heart and manipulated others.
Without you knowing,
this evil of yours has long
grown into a very tall tree.
A gigantic and merciless tree.
It’s me.
I’ve hurt the three realms.
It’s all because of me.
You always thought that
it’s God of War who’s being evil.
You thought it’s Rahu Ketu.
In fact, you’re the evil one.
Everything in this world
is originally empty.
Out of nothing, yin and yang spin.
They reinforce and counteract each other.
The heavens is originally empty.
So is Asura.
Since they’re both empty, how can
the heavens be superior?
How can the mortal and
demon realms be inferior?
You cared too much about
the heavens’ safety.
That’s why you became irreversibly evil.
Please give me some hints, Jade Emperor.
How can I make up for it?
Please give me some hint, Jade Emperor!
Too late.
It is already too late.
Jade Emperor.
I caused this calamity.
I know that I’m deeply sinful.
Today, I will strip myself of my
immortal qualities and powers
to compensate the world for what I did.
King Bailing, you are
the head of heavens.
Without the heavenly qualities,
you will devolve into a trivial deity.
Please think twice!
- Please think twice, King Bailing.
- Please don’t do that, King Bailing.
Please think twice, King Bailing.
For thousands of years,
I’ve worried too much.
That’s why I became like this.
Stop talking.
From today onward, you all
should learn from my mistakes
and behave yourselves.
Bailing.
Is this really what you want?
Jade Emperor.
I have made up my mind.
Fine.
Perhaps
this is your chance.
- King Bailing!
King Bailing.
King Bailing!
Rahu Ketu.
Bailing has stripped himself
of his heavenly qualities.
He is now a powerless trivial deity.
Could you have mercy on him?
Jade Emperor.
You shouldn’t have bothered yourself.
Are you trying to make me
change my mind with this show?
Fine.
Then let me ask you.
Will the Asuras come back to life with him
being stripped of heavenly qualities?
With him being stripped of heavenly power,
will I be able to forget
that painful suffering?
You’ve underestimated my pain.
Fine. Even if the three realms
are slaughtered as you wish,
then what?
Everything will be empty after that.
You were a human in the first nine lives
and couldn’t stop being resentful.
But you finally got over it in this life.
And you’ve found
the most important person in your life.
Isn’t this far better than
being a murderous tool?
You once asked me this.
Where else can you go
since you’re not a deity or Asura?
Isn’t the mortal realm
where your heart is?
Or, do you really want to destroy
everything in the mortal realm
and indulge in the anger?
So what if I indulge in the anger?
That’s the path I chose.
I need to figure it out.
Be it Rahu Ketu or Chu Xuan Ji,
in your eyes, they are just
insignificant existence.
Even though my life is insignificant,
I will never let you all mess with it.
As long as the heaven’s law
remains unchanged,
there will be another evil Bailing
even though this one has been banished.
Thus, only by destroying
the Transcendent Furnace
can I get rid of your arrogance.
Jade Emperor.
Fight with me or go away.
It’s the heavens’ fault.
I have no right to stop you.
If you insist on destroying the ruin,
I can’t do nothing about it.
Yet, when the furnace collapses
and the karma vanishes,
all of your friends and family
will return to the chaos void.
Is that really what you want?
Xuan Ji. Don’t, Xuan Ji!
Rahu Ketu.
Turn around and look at
your family and friends.
They could’ve stayed at
Shaoyang for their safety.
But they couldn’t bear to forget
the experiences we share.
That’s why they came here
despite the difficulties.
Although they know they’d be
killed, they want you to know that
they care a lot about you.
Whether you’re Rahu
Ketu or Xuan Ji, in this life,
those around you love you deeply.
They protect you.
You’re no longer
that lonely Star of Mosha.
You’re a family member, friend,
a loved one whom we can’t let go.
Demon Lord, listen to it.
These people are trying to talk you
into turning into Chu Xuan Ji.
In fact, they don’t care about you at all.
They care only about Chu Xuan Ji.
After all, these are all
Chu Xuan Ji’s family, friends,
and loved one.
They’re not yours.
Our great army
has scattered the primordial spirit
around Demon Citadel.
When the furnace is collapsed
and the three realms are ruined,
the world will belong to us demons.
Don’t let their words ruin our grand plan.
Since Bailing didn’t care about life,
why should I care about
love, friends, and family?
They are impermanent.
Jade Emperor, I am definitely
destroying the furnace.
If that’s the case, go ahead then.
Xuan Ji.
All of your friends and family
will return to the chaos void.
Is that really what you want?
Xuan Ji.
No.
No!
What is this?
I have just hit the String of
Yellow Millet and let you foresee
what happens when
the three realms are destroyed.
Illusion.
It is all an illusion!
It is not an illusion.
If you insist on smashing the furnace,
what you saw will become the reality.
I cannot stop you from taking revenge.
But it concerns the life on three realms.
I just hope that you won’t
regret your decision.
Rahu Ketu.
You said you were a heartless man.
But you just shed tears.
How can a heartless man
shed tears?
It’s obvious that you’re
gaining fresh and blood.
Try to accept yourself.
Don’t let your hatred blind you.
Shut up!
I will not believe everything you say!
Demon Lord, if you are wavering
because of their sweet nothings,
listen to what I am about to say
and you will no longer hesitate.
Yu Si Feng has long betrayed you.
He said he came to the heavens
and discussed it with King Bailing.
In fact, they have long decided to
help the heavens change your mind.
If you listen to him and
don’t ruin the three realms,
that shows he can control you.
This Yu Si Feng.
It is obvious that
he wants to be the new Jade Cup
which King Bailing can use
to seal your soul!
Demon Lord.
You’ve broken my defensive spell.
You want to kill me.
Yuan Lang.
I’d have bought into your lie
if you’d framed somebody else.
But I remember every single thing
Yu Si Feng did in his ten lives.
You said he betrayed me.
Do you think I’ll believe you?
Demon Lord.
I am wrong.
I am wrong!
You betrayed the Demon Citadel,
framed Wu Zhi Qi,
and seized the power of God of War.
They are all your schemes.
If Bailing is called vicious,
you can be called a backstabber.
There is no way I’m keeping
a backstabber by my side.
Take your own life.
Demon Lord.
I have been working for you
for thousands of years.
Now that we are going to succeed,
you want me to kill myself?
You were working for yourself, not me.
Don’t think I don’t know
what you’re up to.
If I really destroy the three realms,
my next enemy would be you.
I never thought that
the effort I put into the grand plan
would eventually lead to my death.
That’s really careless of me.
Demon Lord, it seems that
you’ve bought into their nonsense!
And you are not going
to destroy the furnace.
If so, you shall be burnt into
ashes in the Great Gold Flame!
I, Yuan Lang, want to be
the head of three realms!