LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 55
Xuan Ji.
Xuan Ji!
- Si Feng!
Si Feng!
- Si Feng! How are you feeling?
Are you okay, Si Feng?
Si Feng.
From now on, you are no longer
the Star of Mosha, Rahu Ketu.
You’ll be the heaven’s God of War.
From tomorrow onward, you
will be serving the heavens.
You’ll be the one to annihilate the Asuras
and destroy the Demon Citadel.
It has been 1,000 years.
Finally, this day has come.
Greetings, Demon Lord.
Congratulations for coming back
to the three realms.
Yuan Lang?
I remember now.
You were the Left and
Right Lieutenant of King Asura.
Looks like you still remember me.
I’ve been waiting for 1,000
years for you to be revived.
Thank you for giving me
a physical body again.
I’m willing to fight
the heavens with you
to finally seek revenge for
Demon Citadel after 1,000 years.
You can follow me then.
Yuan Lang, you stupid bird.
You are really a bad penny.
He believes you because
he has been sleeping for 1,000 years.
Let me tell you.
I won’t let you escape today.
Wait. I remember that the heavens
has tortured you for 1,000 years too.
Don’t you want to kill them
together with me to avenge yourself?
I indeed detest those people
from the heavens.
I fought with them and
stole their things 1,000 years ago.
So, it’s only normal that
they locked me up.
But now, they even dared
to hurt my Little Fox.
Besides, I found out today that
Bailing was so shameless
to do that to you.
You were once the person
I admired the most.
And Xuan Ji is my good friend.
- So, I have to avenge all of you.
- Good.
Looks like I didn’t misjudge you.
But I have to kill this stupid bird today.
I don’t care what kind of grudge
you have between you.
Before we destroy the heavens, I
don’t want there to be internal conflict.
After we seek our revenge,
you can kill whoever you want.
Just go ahead and do it.
Fine.
After all, that Bailing is more
shameless than this zombie here.
I’ll kill Bailing first,
and then, I’ll kill you.
If that’s the case, come
with me to Fenru City now.
I want to give a present
to the heavens.
King Bailing, Rahu Ketu
has already destroyed Fenru City
and broke the Core Fire.
He even went to Demon Citadel
to revive the Asuras army.
What about Shen Shu and Yu Lu?
Please have mercy on us!
Good-for-nothing.
- King Bailing.
- Tell me.
What bad news is it this time?
Rahu Ketu sent us a war declaration
stating that he’ll attack the heavens
and drench it with blood.
I never thought that
my compassion back then
will lead to him acting so arrogantly now.
He wants to attack the heavens?
Fine.
Pass down my decree.
Put the whole heavens
on high alert now.
We won’t give him an opportunity
to take advantage on us!
Yes, King Bailing.
Xuan Ji.
Xuan Ji!
- Si Feng!
Where is Xuan Ji?
Si Feng, Xuan Ji has already
turned into Rahu Ketu now.
- It’s pointless to look for her!
- I want to look for her.
Calm down!
Even if she’s Rahu Ketu,
she’s still Xuan Ji!
Si Feng, Xuan Ji has become
Rahu Ketu. She’s gone.
Rahu Ketu has summoned all demons
to Demon Citadel to greet him.
He’ll lead an attack towards the heavens
and bring chaos to three realms.
When you were unconscious,
demons are already acting
so rampantly in the human realm.
Now, no one dares to come out.
The world is in a mess now.
No. Xuan Ji must be still alive.
She’s just controlled by
Rahu Ketu for now.
- I’ll look for her tomorrow.
- No.
Majority of demons are gathered at
Demon Citadel now. We can’t be reckless.
I think we better discuss it
with Master first.
I’ll go! You are mortals but I’m a demon.
Since it’s a gathering of demons,
the more reasons for me to go.
Si Feng.
A lot of elders who didn’t obey him
- had been killed.
- Yes.
- I’m worried that you...
- No.
Even if she’s controlled by
Star of Mosha’s soul, I’ll find her.
Star of Mosha’s soul has been harboring
hatred for 1,000 years in the Jade Cup.
As soon as it combined with
Xuan Ji’s primordial spirit,
I’m afraid that her mere 20 years of life
is just nothing compared to Rahu Ketu’s
- tens and thousands of years of memories.
- Yes.
Bailing sealed up her six senses and
took away all of her memories.
He even transformed into Hao Chen and
yet couldn’t stop her from becoming him.
From that, you can see
how deep Rahu Ketu’s hatred is.
Little Phoenix,
you can’t risk your life like this.
Why are you so unconfident in Xuan Ji?
Although Rahu Ketu’s soul
is controlling her now,
it doesn’t mean that
she’s completely gone.
Rahu Ketu has hatred in his heart
but Xuan Ji has love in her heart.
I don’t believe that someone can totally
forget about the person they once loved.
I believe that Xuan Ji is still alive too.
We can save her.
It doesn’t matter
whether she’s God of War or Star of Mosha.
I will stop Rahu Ketu
and bring back Xuan Ji.
Please advise him against this.
Okay.
If that’s the case,
I won’t stop you anymore.
You...
But you have to remember this.
The more people Rahu Ketu kills,
the more demonic he will become.
If you want to get Xuan Ji back,
you have to stop her from
slaughtering people without restraint.
Greetings, Demon Lord!
Welcome back to three realms!
The heavens destroyed
Demon Citadel 1,000 years ago.
Us demons were scattered across the realms
and were suppressed and bullied.
Now that I’m back, I’m going
to stir up the three realms
to restore the power and dignity
of us demons.
On the seventh day
of the month of seventh,
I’ll use the Fallen Bell to burst open
the heaven’s gate and attack them.
Go and swear a blood oath with
the Right Lieutenant later.
Then, we’ll slaughter everyone
in the heavens together.
Attack the heavens!
Slaughter everyone there!
Restore the power of demons again!
This is Demon Lord’s first order
and someone is already defying it.
Well done.
My clan has little power. The spirit
is willing, but the flesh is weak.
I hope that...
Since you are of no help,
why should I keep you?
Demon Lord, you said that we’ve been
suppressed and bullied for 1,000 years.
You want to lead us to
fight against the heavens.
We came here because we respect you.
But not every clan is good at combat.
How can you just kill us like that?
Insolent!
He was just gone for 1,000 years
and now, even a mere Green Sparrow
is teaching him how to lead?
You are humiliating us just like
how the heavens treats us.
Goodbye!
Calm down, Demon Lord.
The heavens annihilated us Asuras
and drove away the rest of your demons.
All of you have been hiding for
more than 1,000 years in fear.
At first, I thought that all of you will
look forward to seeking revenge.
But I never thought that
this insult of 1,000 years
will turn you into mellow
and obedient cowards.
As demons,
are you really going to just hide
in the human realm and be slaughtered?
I won’t accept this
kind of humiliation.
And it’ll be the same
for every demon clan!
I don’t care if you want to
swear the blood oath or not.
From today onward,
we are no longer separated by clans.
All of you will obey me.
We’ll gather here at the seventh day
of the seventh month.
This is an order, not a discussion.
Those who disobey me
will be killed without mercy.
Yes, Demon Lord!
You are dismissed.
Si Feng?
Yu Si Feng.
It’s you?
12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird?
I know that Xuan Ji’s
consciousness is still there.
She won’t let you commit
the sin of murder.
Let her out!
Si Feng.
Si Feng!
Xuan Ji.
You became Rahu Ketu to save me.
Have you forgotten about me
now that you’ve become Rahu Ketu?
Si Feng!
Rahu Ketu, let me out!
Let me out!
Chu Xuan Ji is just the image of
my primordial spirit.
Since I’m already
back, she is gone now.
Stop mentioning about this lowly mortal’s
name again and again in front of me.
Xuan Ji will not be gone.
I’m sure that she’s still here.
She was controlled
by your soul because
she wanted to save me.
Although she was once
part of your primordial spirit,
she had gone through 1,000 years
with 10 reincarnations.
She’s her own person now.
She’s not Rahu Ketu.
Xuan Ji.
I know that you are inside him, right?
Rahu Ketu, let me out!
So what if she’s here?
So what if she’s not?
She’s just a small portion
in this long life of mine.
Among my tens and thousands
of years of memories,
hers is just a drop of water in the ocean.
Do you think she can control me?
Dream on.
Since you once risked your life
to protect my primordial spirit,
I’ll not kill you.
Get lost now.
I promised Xuan Ji
that I’ll bring her back.
I won’t leave until she appears!
Si Feng, wake up, you dummy.
- He’s not Xuan Ji now.
- I believe in Xuan Ji!
She is not the Star of Mosha.
And she doesn’t want to
become Star of Mosha.
Aren’t you afraid that I’ll kill you?
You won’t.
Because Xuan Ji
won’t allow you to kill me.
I already said that she’s just
a part of my primordial spirit.
Do you think that you can stop me?
You tried so hard to lock Xuan Ji up
and used your power to
take the form of Rahu Ketu
because you are afraid.
You are afraid that you can’t control her.
You are afraid that
she won’t turn into a
bloodthirsty demon like you.
Let me out!
Let me out! Si Feng!
Si Feng!
Let me out!
- Xuan Ji.
- Let me out!
Let me out!
Let me out! Si Feng!
Si Feng!
Xuan Ji.
Si Feng.
You are back, Xuan Ji.
I knew it.
I know that you are still here.
You won’t disappear.
Si Feng, why are you so foolish?
He’ll kill you.
I said that I’ll get you out
no matter what.
You promised me that you
won’t forget about our vow.
Si Feng. But, I’m Rahu Ketu.
It really doesn’t bother you?
In my heart, you’ll always be
Xuan Ji no matter what happened.
But I’m not me anymore.
I’m afraid that I can’t control myself.
I’ll kill you.
What we had in the past
will forever be gone.
Si Feng, forget about everything.
Forget about her.
You are not Xuan Ji.
Xuan Ji won’t ask me
to forget about our past.
Yu Si Feng, you are really sentimental.
Your memories with Chu Xuan Ji
are very precious, right?
But to me, they are just
boring and embarrassing.
Boring?
Embarrassing?
You are just jealous of Xuan Ji.
You were betrayed.
But you hate her.
Because you’ve never obtained
this kind of feelings before!
Yu Si Feng.
I’m going to get rid of Chu
Xuan Ji’s memories and you now.
Demon Lord.
You want to fight
the heavens, right?
I’m sure that you still
need a helper, right?
I’m a 12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird.
With my power,
not many can be my match.
Why don’t you consider me?
Let me become your helper.
Demon Lord, he’s really a good fighter.
I can attest to that.
Fine.
If he can withstand one blow from me,
I’ll accept him.
Bring it on.
Stop! I won’t allow you to hurt Si Feng!
I won’t allow you to hurt Si Feng!
Let him go!
Rahu Ketu!
I already said that I’m very powerful.
You should keep me by your side.
Fine.
Yu Si Feng, I’ll hand over
the Fallen Bell to you.
After 10 days,
I want it to be filled with resentment
and use it to tear down the heaven’s gate.
I won’t disappoint you.
Yu Si Feng!
Don’t think that I don’t know
what you are planning.
Chu Xuan Ji is just
a speck of dirt in Demon Lord’s life.
Don’t ever think about
getting back Chu Xuan Ji.
Demon Lord is back in the three realms
to seek revenge from the heavens.
Don’t think that
you can ruin his ambition.
Yuan Lang,
why are you getting so agitated?
Are you afraid that you’ll lose your place
because he’s hotter and more powerful?
I just don’t want to let someone
with an ulterior motive
to stay by Demon Lord’s side.
Si Feng!
I chose him myself.
So, I’m the only one who can
punish or award him.
Don’t ever think about touching him.
Those who disobey me
will not be forgiven so easily.
These are the prisoners we caught
from the human realm recently.
We’ll feed them to the Fallen Bell.
Feel free to use them.
Thank you.
But feeding this Fallen Bell
souls are not an easy task.
It’s a dangerous chore.
You may leave me alone here with them.
I don’t want to accidentally feed
this bell with any of you in here.
If that’s the case,
we won’t disturb you then.
We’ll wait for your good news.
Let’s go.
- Don’t come over here! Don’t kill us!
- Don’t kill me!
Don’t kill us! I beg you!
Left Lieutenant.
Left Lieutenant,
we found a suspicious-looking person.
She’s wearing a mask and looking around.
She might be a spy from the heavens.
- Bring me to her.
- Yes, Left Lieutenant.
- Both of you can wait for me here.
- Don’t kill us.
- Don’t worry.
I won’t hurt you.
Leave through the back of the mountain
now that it’s night-time.
Continue north and you’ll find an exit.
If you go out from there,
you can go back to the human realm.
Come out.
- Let’s go now.
- Let’s go.
- Thank you.
Little Fox, why did you
come to Demon Citadel?
Let me tell you. Wait for me here.
Wu Zhi Qi.
I don’t want to wait anymore.
You were detained in Fenru City for
1,000 years and I waited for you.
And I waited for you when you
helped Xuan Ji opened Jade Cup.
Now that you want to go to war with
the heavens, how can I wait again?
You’ve just gotten your freedom. Why
are you putting yourself in danger again?
What if you are caught by
the heavens again?
I don’t want to live another
1,000 years of suffering.
I can’t believe you, you sour fox.
I’m going to war soon.
Wu Zhi Qi.
You know better than me how
the Demon-Immortal War ended.
No matter who wins,
what has it got to do with us?
We’ll still live our own lives in the end.
If that’s the case,
why do you have to be involved in this?
Isn’t it nice to leave now
and go back to that little hut with me
to live our life in peace?
You don’t like me in human form? Fine.
- I’ll turn back into a fox. As long as...
- Little Fox, look up there.
Tens and thousands of demons are waiting
to seek revenge from the heavens.
We have to seek revenge too!
Have you forgotten who ruined your face
and locked me up for so long?
I’ve endured them for more than
1,000 years! I can’t endure it anymore!
We should’ve gone to war 1,000 years ago.
I’m going to beat them up today!
Little Fox.
Just wait for me here.
Don’t worry.
It won’t take long.
I’ll take down White Tiger Star Lord
and use his fur to make a cape for you.
Then, I’ll extract his core and
spread it on your face.
Wait for me.
Wu Zhi Qi.
This is the last time I’ll beg you.
If you don’t leave with me,
I’ll go into hiding
and you’ll never find me again.
Little Fox.
I know what kind of power you have.
Where can you hide?
Stop fooling around.
Wait for me.
What kind of golden ray is that?
I think it’s the Fallen Bell!
It’s the Fallen Bell that broke
the heaven’s gate 1,000 years ago.
It still exists?
Demon Lord. Once the war
starts, it’ll poison the three realms!
Keep quiet!
Wu Zhi Qi, listen to my command.
Attack the heavens now.
Okay.
Here I go.
King Bailing.
King Bailing, they are coming.
We can’t hold them back without
the heaven’s gate.
- Let’s retreat.
- Retreat?
Why should we retreat?
They are the one who should retreat.
Pass down my order.
Tip over the Mutton Fat Jade Jar
and release the Sea of Life and Death.
Separate the heavens
with the human realm!
King Bailing.
If you release the Sea of Life and Death,
it’ll disrupt the cycle of universe aura.
The corrupted aura will then accumulate
and it’ll turn into another Demon Citadel.
Humans will perish.
Please take back your order!
We have the order of priority.
The heavens is in grave danger now,
we have to protect ourselves first!
Jade Emperor is not here.
I’m in charge here.
Do as I say now.
If you hesitate, you’ll be
beheaded without mercy!
What is that?
Sea of Life and Death.
You rather use the Sea of Life and Death
at the cost of the human realm?
Fine.
Let’s see how long you can hide up there.
Little Fox!
Little Fox. Are you okay?
Stupid Monkey.
You...
You just care about fighting, right?
Why...
Why do you care about me now?
Little Fox.
Are you dumb?
Why did you do that? Why?
Yes.
Why is it
so painful?
You are my everything.
You can throw away your life
but I don’t want you to die.
Little Fox.
Stay strong.
I’ll find you the best medicine.
I’ll cure you for sure.
No.
Stupid Monkey.
You’ll definitely keep
your promise to others
without any care for your life.
You don’t even care about me.
I care about you.
Just that sometimes,
I don’t know what to say.
Little Fox, don’t worry.
I won’t let you suffer anymore after this.
Stupid Monkey.
This promise
is already enough for me.
Wu Zhi Qi.
You made promises with others everywhere.
Can you
promise me something too?
Okay.
After I die,
can you bring me back?
Let’s leave the Demon Citadel.
Stop fighting.
Okay.
I promise you, Little Fox.
I won’t fight anymore.
I won’t fight anymore, Little Fox.
Can you
kiss me?
Wu Zhi Qi.
I...
I love you.
Wu Zhi Qi.
In the next life,
- Little Fox!
- I don’t want to become fox anymore.
- I’ll become even more beautiful
with the appearance that you like.
If I become like that,
will you like me then?
Little Fox.
I’ve been lying to you.
You are beautiful.
You are really attractive.
Brother Wu. What has happened outside?
I won’t fight anymore.
I’ll get you out.
Brother Wu.
What happened?
Little Fox is dead.
I promised her that I won’t fight anymore.
So, I came here to save you.
Let’s go.
Both of you are just going to leave
without goodbyes?
Such disrespect for Demon Lord.
Demon Lord, I’ve already said that
Yu Si Feng is going to rebel.
Now, looks like Wu Zhi Qi
wants to leave too.
Both of them are traitors.
Wu Zhi Qi.
I respected you 1,000 years ago.
And now, you are the only one who
doesn’t need to address me as Demon Lord.
I treated you well.
Why are you leaving me
now that we are defeated?
Is it just like what Yuan Lang said?
Are you going to betray me?
I don’t know what betrayal means.
Just now, Little Fox
died saving me from that battle.
I’ve already promised her
not to fight anymore.
I’m going to bring her home
and bury her demonic core.
Rahu Ketu.
I think I’ve repaid you enough for
speaking up for me
to King Asura back then.
From now on, I’m no
longer in debt with you.
Old Wu.
You want to bargain with Demon Lord?
Aren’t you too arrogant?
What did you say?
I misunderstood you then.
Being sentimental and loyal
are your best qualities.
I wasn’t expecting you to pay me back
when I spoke up for you back then.
Since you want to leave now,
I won’t force you to stay.
You can leave.
But Yu Si Feng has to stay.
Yu Si Feng, you put down
an order to foil our military plan.
That’s a fatal crime.
Do you have anything to say for yourself?
Rahu Ketu,
you have Xuan Ji’s memories inside you.
I did it so that you won’t commit
even more sins of murder
and suffer in the future.
I can kill you.
I can let you go too.
Xuan Ji is making you to do it, right?
Don’t think too much.
For me, Chu Xuan Ji is just a
fragment in my mind. She’s powerless.
But you are quite interesting.
How about this? I know that
you are the leader of Rose Gold Bird.
If you do something for me,
I’ll forgive you for the crimes
that you’ve committed.
What is it?
Find the Rose Gold Bird,
order them to burn their demonic cores
and carry my army over
the Sea of Life and Death.
Burn their demonic cores?
You’ll destroy their cultivations
and turn them into cripples.
It’s their honor to be able to die
for Demon Lord.
Yu Si Feng.
Just agree to it.
Unfortunately, I’m already not
their leader since a few years back.
So, I don’t know where they are.
But Yuan Lang is the Rose Gold Bird
with the most advance cultivation.
With his power,
he can fly through that sea
for seven to eight times without problem.
You can bestow to him this honor of
burning his demonic core instead.
Yu Si Feng.
I’m giving you a chance because
I think that you are very amusing.
Don’t be so imperious.
Since you won’t tell me about
the Rose Gold Bird’s whereabouts,
I’ll have to kill you.
I really don’t know.
If you don’t believe
me, just kill me then.
Okay.
Brother Wu.
Rahu Ketu, Si Feng is my friend
and my savior.
If you want to kill him, I’ll help
him even if it’ll cost me my life.
Brother Wu.
Demon Lord, they are obviously
trying to revolt against you.
Just kill them to prevent
any future troubles.
Interesting.
I haven’t seen such loyalty in
a friendship for a long time.
It’ll be a pity if I kill you both.
But if I just pardon Yu Si Feng like this,
others will think that I’m unfair.
What a dilemma.
How about this.
If the two of you can withstand
three attacks from me,
I’ll consider that Yu Si Feng
has paid for his crime.
But if you die,
you can only blame yourself for
not being powerful enough.
Demon Lord.
Rose Gold Bird is useful to us.
We can’t let Yu Si Feng go.
I’ve already made up my mind.
No need to say anything else.
Brother Wu!
Si Feng!
Si Feng, how are you?
Don’t worry. I’m fine.
You are using the Solar Palm from
the Golden Crow Tactic to attack yourself
in order to expel the demonic power
of the Ocean Wave?
Interesting.
But both of you are
seriously injured right now.
The third one, Soul Breaker, will attack
your heart and soul. It’s very dangerous.
You still want to try it?
Sure.
If we are to die here together
today, I’ll be content with that!
Do it now.
Okay.
Little Fox.
Xuan Ji?
Si Feng.
Si Feng!
- Si Feng!
- Xuan Ji!
Si Feng!
Xuan Ji.
Don’t be afraid. I’ll find
you and bring you back!
Little Fox.
- Brother Wu.
- Little...
Brother Wu.
- Are you okay?
- Si Feng.
I’m fine.
Yu Si Feng, you managed to
withstand the Soul Breaker.
Looks like you are very determined.
I’ve changed my mind about you.
You’ve withstood my three attacks.
I’ll keep my promise.
- You can go now.
- Si Feng.
Let’s go.
Brother Wu.
I can’t leave with you.
Foolish kid.
If you stay, they won’t let you go.
If I leave now, I won’t
be able to forgive myself.
I promised that I’ll stay with Xuan Ji.
No matter what happens to her,
I’ll stay with her until the end.
Just now, I’ve already felt her presence.
She must be waiting for me.
Brother Wu.
I’m sorry for wasting your effort.
If I was the old me,
I would laugh at you for having no guts.
But now, I have only admiration for you.
If I were like you
and realized this sooner,
Little Fox would be...
Forget it.
Si Feng.
I’ll be leaving then. Take care.
See you later.
Yu Si Feng.
You wouldn’t tell me about your clan’s
whereabouts and you wouldn’t leave.
Are you testing my patience?
I stayed because I want to
make a bet with you.
I bet that within three days,
I can call forth Chu Xuan Ji
from the depth of your heart.
What will you do if you win and
what will you do if you lose?
If I can do it within three days,
you can’t seal her at
the bottom of your heart anymore.
Let her out to speak with me.
If I can’t do it
after three days,
I’ll put my life in your hands forever.
Who do you think you are?
How dare you bet with Demon Lord?
Rahu Ketu, do you dare to
take on this bet?
Fine.
I have a condition too.
If you can’t call forth Chu Xuan Ji
within three days,
I’ll force you to tell me about
the whereabouts of Rose Gold Bird.
How about that?
Okay.
For these three days, you can
become my personal slave then.
These are qingtuan from Zhongli City.
It’s Xuan Ji’s favorite snack.
From the aroma of this soup, I can tell
that you’ve put a lot of effort into it.
But this is fruitless.
It’ll be three days already
when tomorrow comes.
You’ll have to admit defeat then.
We’ll have to wait until tomorrow then.