LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 41
Where is Little Phoenix?
He must have gone to look for Xuan Ji.
What answer will Xuan Ji give Si Feng?
Since Xuan Ji chose to
come here to find Si Feng,
I think she believes in him.
Xuan Ji.
Si Feng!
Where are you going?
Xuan Ji is missing.
Something must have happened to her.
- I’ll go and look for her.
- Si Feng!
She is the God of War. She is so powerful.
Nothing will happen to her.
Si Feng, don’t be so foolish.
Look. What is this?
Why is this hairpin with you?
I picked it up from the floor.
Si Feng, don’t you understand?
She left and she threw away
the hairpin you gave her.
She’s making a clean break with you!
This Chu Xuan Ji is really...
Fire!
Si Feng.
Are you okay?
What happened? Why is there a huge fire?
Stop talking. Let’s get out!
- Yes! Let’s go!
- Let’s go!
We can’t go out! There’s barrier here!
This blue flame is the Ninth Heaven Fire.
Ninth Heaven Fire?
Only God of War can conjure it.
It must be Chu Xuan Ji.
She is trying to trap us here.
Nonsense.
Si Feng, stop being so foolish.
Hurry up,
let’s break the barrier together!
Dang Kang.
Xuan Ji.
Since you still love
him, I can only do this.
This is for your own good.
King Bailing, this is bad!
What is it?
After God of War is awakened,
her life pillar has been restored.
I don’t know why but suddenly,
evil spreads out from it.
Looks like it’s unavoidable now.
I’m just worried that
a demon will rise inside her
because of her unhappy relationship.
If this continues and the demon
takes over her heart,
she’ll fall into the path of the devil.
If that happens, she won’t be able
to go back to the heavens.
If she could kill Yu Si Feng
without a doubt,
there would be no demon inside her.
She is obsessed with
love and is crippled by it.
She is indecisive. That’s why
it has turned into an obsession.
Looks like
my decision to do
this for her is right.
Are you going to kill
that Rose Gold Bird
to get rid of the obstacle for her?
It’s just a fire.
It won’t be able to trap
a 12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird.
Moreover, since this is her
demon, Xuan Ji has to kill him herself
in order to defeat that demon.
Then you are doing this to
break the affection between
God of War and Yu Si Feng?
This is the only way.
At first, I didn’t want to
awaken the God of War.
I just wanted Xuan Ji to
follow the path of heaven
and go back to the heavens
with a new identity and memory.
But I was unable to stop it
from happening.
If that’s the case,
I can only let her
get rid of those demons
to help her build up her merits.
You’ve really bestowed great care
upon the God of War.
Luckily, she has finally seen
that demon’s true color now.
So, your effort will
be paid off soon.
Come with me. I have to talk to you.
Father.
Si Feng, you are hurt.
She has injured you so deeply.
- I’m fine.
- Ninth Heaven Fire is powerful.
Take this medicine and use it at once.
Si Feng.
She is trying to kill you.
Xuan Ji will not stab
someone on the back.
You don’t believe me? Tell me then.
Where did the Ninth Heaven Fire come from?
How do you explain the hairpin?
I know.
She’s just trying to keep you here
and burn you to death with
Ninth Heaven Fire, right?
Nonsense.
There are so many of us here.
Was she trying to kill us all as well?
Don’t forget.
She is the God of War.
Demons are her sworn enemies
since 1,000 years ago.
Now that she has awaken,
she’ll do anything to kill us.
She is the God of War.
But she is still Xuan Ji.
- Si Feng.
- There must be a misunderstanding.
But where has Xuan Ji gone?
Could it be that people from
Shaoyang Sect found her
and brought her back?
If that’s the case,
I don’t know if they’ll
make things difficult for her.
It’ll be bad if they lock her up
at Mingxia Cave again.
- No, I have to go to Shaoyang Sect.
- Si Feng, you can’t go!
They know that you are a demon.
If you go there now, they’ll kill you.
I still haven’t gotten the answer
for the promise I made with her yesterday.
I have to go and ask her.
Fine. Even if you want to
go, wait until you’ve recovered.
Yes. If you want to go,
we’ll all go with you.
Shaoyang Sect is heavily guarded now.
It’ll be more convenient if I go alone.
Si Feng, don’t go.
This is my personal matter.
Just wait here for me.
No need to follow me.
Si Feng!
Kneel!
Don’t forget that your mother
died in the hands of
Rose Gold Bird from Lize Palace.
And now, you went to find him again?
Is this how you repay your mother?
Father.
There are good people and bad people.
Same with demons.
The Rose Gold Bird who killed
my mother is not Si Feng.
And he promised me that
he’ll find the killer for me.
I don’t want to put all the hate on him.
I want to believe in him again.
Insolent girl!
Sect Leader.
Since the beginning, humans
and demons are sworn enemies.
Although you had a relationship with him
before, you should forget about it now.
Don’t forget that you are the God of War.
It’s your mission to kill demons.
Do you know how big
your responsibility is?
I should just slaughter all demons
because I’m the God of War?
Even if I am the God of War, I can
distinguish right from wrong. I feel pain.
If you want me to be
a demon killing machine,
I’d rather not be the God of War.
You...
- Sect Leader.
- Father.
You still haven’t recovered,
don’t be so reckless.
Xuan Ji, apologize to your father now.
He is hurt by those
Rose Gold Bird demons.
He still hasn’t recovered yet.
Father.
I...
Great.
Now, you don’t even
listen to your own father.
If you still want to find
a demon, from now on,
don’t call me father anymore.
Father!
If you still respect
me as your father,
swear to God right now that from now on,
you’ll focus in getting rid of demons
to protect the people in this world.
Father, I...
- Do you
- Father.
Want to see your own father
die in front of you?
Father!
Xuan Ji.
Fine, I swear.
From now on,
I’ll focus in getting rid of demons
to protect the people in this world.
Say that from now
on, you’ll break up
with Yu Si Feng and never see him again.
- Father!
- Swear it!
- I...
- Now, every sect in this world looks up to you for direction.
But you are still entangled
with that demon.
By doing so, you’ve betrayed
a lot of people’s trust on you.
Swear it!
Fine.
Since I can’t control my own daughter,
I can only...
I can only appease the wrath
of the world with my death!
- Father!
- Sect Leader!
Don’t do that, Sect Leader.
Xuan Ji, how long are you
going to be so foolish?
If you continue to be like this,
not only sect leader,
even our master will not think of you
as his disciple anymore!
I believe that Si Feng
will not lie to me anymore.
But I don’t want to make Father angry.
Don’t take my swear seriously later, God.
Just act like you didn’t hear anything.
I swear that
from now on, I’ll get rid
of demons with everybody
and break up with Si Feng.
If I break my promise, I’ll...
I’ll...
I’ll be struck by lightning and
lost all my six senses again.
No, you have to swear an oath.
Swear an oath on your father.
If you break your oath, your father
will the ripped to
death on the street.
- Father!
- Swear it!
Do you have to force me like this?
Or else, don’t call me father ever again!
Sect Leader.
Okay.
I swear that
I’ll focus on killing demons
and break up with Yu Si Feng.
If I break my oath,
my...
my father will be ripped to death.
Xuan Ji.
Remember your oath today.
Remember your mission as the God of War.
I know.
What should you do when you see
Yu Si Feng again in the future?
We’ll be sworn enemies.
So...
So, you left the broken silver hairpin
because you are really going to
break up with me.
And yet, I’m so insensible to come here.
Who is it?
I’ll focus on killing demons
and break up with Yu Si Feng.
What should you do when you see
Yu Si Feng again in the future?
We’ll be sworn enemies.
Xuan Ji.
Since you’ve made up your mind,
I won’t make things difficult for you.
It’s indeed guarded by Candle Dragon.
Ruo Yu?
Ruo Yu.
I thought you fell off the cliff.
You are working for the vice palace lord.
It’s too late.
But since you are here,
help me with this.
This is...
Wolf has gone to the secret ground
of Shaoyang before.
The spirit of an ancient
Candle Dragon is guarding it.
Outsiders cannot go near it.
The coins in your hand
is a weapon that has soaked up all energy
for 1,000 years in Water of Forgetting.
It can keep all spirits at bay.
If you can find Jade Cup from
Shaoyang’s secret ground this time,
I’ll let you meet your sister again.
This is bad! Someone is
getting into the secret ground!
Don’t you dare touch the Jade Cup.
Xuan Ji hurt you so deeply.
Why are you still protecting Shaoyang?
Ruo Yu.
If the Star of Mosha is revived,
the world will be in chaos.
The world?
I just want to live in peace.
The world is none of my concern.
Spirit of heaven, gold from Eight Diagram,
break this Greedy Wolf!
- Si Feng.
- It’s you again, Yu Si Feng!
Si Feng, why are you here?
Do you need to ask?
He broke into secret ground of Shaoyang
and hurt the spirit of Candle Dragon.
He’s here to take the Jade Cup.
No. Si Feng won’t do that.
How do you explain
his appearance here then?
He has completely destroyed
the spirit of the Candle Dragon.
He’s really powerful.
Si Feng.
Tell me. Why are you here?
Didn’t you say that
you won’t lie to me again?
I didn’t lie to you.
I didn’t mean to destroy it.
Stop trying to lie to us.
If you didn’t plan this ahead,
why will you have the formation
to trap the spirit of Candle Dragon?
Si Feng.
You are really here for the Jade Cup.
So, this is how you think about me.
Because I’m a demon and since I’m here,
it must be because I’m here
for the Jade Cup, right?
I’m too foolish.
Since you left without
goodbyes, that is your answer.
Why did I come here to find you?
No. I left without goodbyes because I...
I didn’t want to take the Jade Cup.
I found Ruo Yu here.
At first, I wanted to stop him.
I never thought that
he would plot against me.
It was just an accident that
the spirit of Candle Dragon is destroyed.
Ruo Yu?
I saw him fell off the cliff.
Why would he be here?
Ruo Yu is not dead. He has been
working for the vice palace lord.
How did that happen?
How can I believe any of you ever again?
Stop lying.
The 12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird
demons are very powerful.
It’s impossible that a disciple of
Lize Palace will be able to defy them.
Yu Si Feng, don’t use
a dead man as an excuse.
Si Feng. Tell me, why are you here?
Explain it to me now.
You said that you won’t lie to me again.
What’s the point of me explaining myself?
You already have your own answer.
Why are you asking me again?
We’ve let you escape for so many times.
Today, I’ll take you down!
- Xuan Ji!
- Don’t hurt him.
You are still protecting him at this time?
Have you forgotten
what you promised me just now?
I’m not protecting him. I...
I suddenly remember that Si Feng
is 12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird.
He has always been important
to Lize Palace.
He might be useful to us
if we spare him for now.
Don’t think that I don’t know
what you are thinking.
Today, I won’t let him go!
- Master.
- Wait.
Junior.
What Xuan Ji said
just now makes sense.
The Rose Gold Bird
is heavily wounded anyway.
We can keep him in Mingxia Cave first.
With the formation and situation there,
I don’t think he can escape.
Let him have a taste of
that bone-deep pain first.
When the other sect leaders
are here, we can decide together.
Now, the spirit of the Candle Spirit
has been destroyed.
The barrier of the secret ground
is broken.
The demons have already
taken all the spirit keys.
We can’t let anything
happen to the Jade Cup.
But with the barrier gone,
it’ll be hard for us to keep
this Jade Cup safe.
This...
What should we do?
Master, I remember that
the great master of Xuyang Peak
has written down a formation
to summon the spirit of the Candle Dragon.
That’s right.
We do have a secret art
that can summon another
Dragon Candle’s spirit.
But for the past thousands of years,
nothing has ever happened to the
Candle Dragon in the secret ground. So,
nobody has ever used
this formation before.
But don’t worry.
I’ll do my best to summon it.
We’ll be counting on you then,
Senior Heng Yang.
This is not a normal formation.
I need to cast a spell to heaven
for three days straight.
Hao Chen.
Go to Xuyang Peak to summon
all the other protectors here
to help me protect the formation.
Yes, Master.
No wonder Xuan Ji
didn’t want to come back here
no matter what back then.
What’s wrong?
Why can’t I feel Si Feng anymore?
Silver Snake, can you stop pacing around?
I’m getting dizzy from it.
I think Little Phoenix purposely
cut the bond because you are too annoying.
This is none of your business!
Si Feng is very cunning.
And Xuan Ji won’t let anything
happen to her lover.
Now, I’m more worried about
the spirit keys.
Yuan Lang has already
gathered all four spirit keys.
If that’s the case,
he’ll be targeting Wu Zhi Qi next.
No. I can’t let him do that.
- I have to go to Lize Palace now.
- Purple Fox.
How are you going to defeat Yuan Lang
and the others if you go there alone?
Who said I’m going to fight them?
I’m going to find a way
to steal those keys.
Yes.
Good idea.
We’ll steal those spirit keys out
in secret.
Then, that creepy vice palace lord
won’t be able to do anything about it.
And he can’t force those innocent people
in Lize Palace to a corner.
Good. Just steal them.
I have a secret tunnel that can lead you
to Lize Palace. I’ll draw a map for you.
I know that no one can stop you
when it comes to Wu Zhi Qi.
Dang Kang.
Bring Dang Kang with you.
If you are in danger,
Dang Kang can get you out.
Nothing will happen to me.
But since you are so kind to
offer it, I’ll bring it with me then.
Be careful.
Here’s the map.
Thank you.
I’ll get going then.
I never thought that these demons
are so persistent.
They just stole the spirit key
of Dianjinggu.
Then, they came here to steal the
Jade Cup from Shaoyang’s secret ground.
They are too unruly.
I’m afraid that Sky Hall
is bringing those keys
to open the Dimension Chain.
Once they’ve gotten
Juntian Loop and Chehai Hook,
they’ll gather their forces to attack
the secret ground of Shaoyang.
The keyhole of the Dimension Chain
is at the Demon Citadel in Mount Buzhou.
I don’t think they’ll unlock
the Dimension Chain yet.
Demon Citadel?
The world that was led by the Asuras
more than 1,000 years ago?
Yes.
If they want to go there,
they have to wait for Fenru City’s gate
to open at the 15th every month.
So, we still have the time
to get back the spirit keys.
Now, we have Yu Si Feng in our hands.
Actually, we can exchange him
for those spirit keys from Lize Palace.
These demons have been
plotting this for centuries.
Do you think they’ll ruin it
for one person?
But he’s the 12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird.
He’s very useful for those demons.
Even if we can’t exchange him for
four keys, we can get at least one.
- Then, we can stop them for a while.
- That’s right.
If that’s the case,
I’ll ask Min Xing to send a letter
to Lize Palace tomorrow.
I’ll ask them to exchange
the spirit key for Yu Si Feng’s life.
Sect Leader, you can ask
Min Yan to go with Min Xing.
Although he is no longer
Shaoyang’s disciple,
he has fought many times with Sky Hall.
He knows how to deal with them.
I think it’ll be better
if he goes with Min Xing.
Okay.
Where is the hairpin?
Why is it missing?
Since you left without
goodbyes, that is your answer.
Why did I come here to find you?
Si Feng.
Si Feng must have accidentally
gone into the secret ground
because he was here for me.
It must be it.
Xuan Ji, where are you going?
I’m hungry.
- I want to eat something.
- Are you going to visit Yu Si Feng?
- Ling Long.
- You haven’t given up hope on him, right?
I won’t let you go out.
You won’t be going anywhere.
Fine. I won’t go. I won’t go anywhere.
Calm down. I’ll go back to my room now.
Calm down.
Xuan Ji.
This is the Black Hole Cave
that can absorb everything.
Do you think this petty thing
will stop me?
Little Chef?
It’s you.
The stinky woman asked me to
give you this package.
I was just thinking about how to go in.
I don’t need her pity.
Are you upset that she’s not here?
She can’t leave because of her sister.
So, she asked me to check on you.
But this is weird.
You are a 12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird.
How can you be captured by
some mortals? So embarrassing.
I’ve seen 12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird
1,000 years ago.
They are not as weak as you.
Little Chef, why aren’t you talking?
Are you feeling embarrassed?
By the way, the stinky woman
wants me to ask you
about the ins and outs
of the incident as well
so that she can plead for you.
Tell us if you are
in a difficult situation.
Since you can cook so well, I
can consider helping you out too.
I swear that I’ll focus
on killing demons
and break up with Yu Si Feng.
What should you do when you see
Yu Si Feng again in the future?
We’ll be sworn enemies.
Humans and demons are different.
If she doesn’t believe me,
I have nothing else to say.
Why are you venting out your anger at me?
You are so ungrateful.
I won’t care about you.
I summoned all of you
today to tell you something.
From now on, Sky Hall and
Lize Palace are one.
Lize Palace will help Sky Hall to complete
their mission and revive demon clan.
In the future,
you’ll be the demon clan’s
meritorious subjects.
Elder.
We have a letter.
Vice Palace Lord.
There are two Shaoyang’s
disciples outside.
They brought a letter.
[We’ve seen through your plan.
We’ve captured the Rose Gold Bird.]
What does Shaoyang Sect want?
Yu Si Feng has been captured by them.
Those sects want to
exchange him for my spirit keys?
What a joke.
Vice Palace Lord, we have to
find a way to save Si Feng.
Save Si Feng?
He let himself get caught because of
his obsession with God of War.
What can we do about it?
Moreover, he’s a Rose Gold Bird.
If he can’t even from those mortals,
why should we save him?
- But...
- Elder Luo, you are quite talkative today.
What about those two disciples?
They are outside.
Kill them.
Send their heads to Shaoyang Sect.
Tell them that they can do
whatever they want to Yu Si Feng.
Yes, Vice Palace Lord.
What are you doing?
Do you think you can exchange
Yu Si Feng for the spirit keys?
What a joke! Vice Palace Lord
has ordered us to behead you and send
your heads back to Shaoyang! Attack!
Come with me now!
Stop right there.
Who are you?
Senior.
She is my friend.
But she was using
a demonic spell just now.
What a dumb mortal.
At first, I didn’t want to save you.
I was just passing by.
Since you are so
ungrateful, I’ll eat you now.
Purple Fox.
Stop scaring my senior.
I heard from those stupid birds
just now that
you caught Little Si Feng?
So, it’s true.
Don’t you know what kind of
a person Little Si Feng is?
He cared not about his own safety
to find Xuan Ji at Shaoyang Sect.
But you sects just caught him
without any solid reason at all.
You even sent a letter in person
to exchange Si Feng for the spirit keys?
What are you thinking?
But he was at Shaoyang’s secret ground
and destroyed Candle Dragon.
We didn’t accuse him wrongly.
Did you see it with your own eyes?
Back then, you also accused me for
killing those people in Zhongli City
without any solid reason as well, right?
Now, I don’t know what to
believe and what to not believe.
But to be truthful, I don’t want
anything to happen to Si Feng.
If Lize Palace accepted our offer,
I could save Si Feng and
get back the spirit keys.
As for others,
it’s out of my power
to do anything about them.
Are you dumb or
are you too naive?
Do you think that despicable Yuan Lang
will take Si Feng as his friend?
Or do you really think that
he’ll care about Si Feng’s life?
It’s our last solution to exchange
Yu Si Feng for the spirit keys.
But now that they won’t do
that, what should we do then?
Steal them.
Since you sects are so useless
and let Yuan Lang took away
your everything,
I can only do everything myself.
But now, I need your help.
I can’t get into Lize Palace alone.
You want us to help you?
Don’t play tricks on us.
But do you have any other choice right now
except working together with me?
Since you have no other way,
we’ll do it the usual way.
We’ll find a way to get into
Lize Palace first.
Then, we’ll split up
to search for the keys.
And the keys will belong to
whoever that finds the keys first.
How about that?
This is the Kushui Prison.
After Kushui Prison,
we’ll reach Lize Palace.
Okay, let’s go.
Wait.
You have to carry me.
The water in Kushui Prison
has no effect on you
but it’s painful for demons.
Especially us fox clan.
It’s deadly for us.
I can’t even fly through it.
No wonder you need our help.
What is it? Are you shy?
Who is the one who almost
became my consort back then?
If you say it again, aren’t you
afraid that I’ll leave you behind
and get the spirit keys myself?
You won’t I believe that
you won’t do that.
Stop talking. Carry me now.
Actually, I was
biased towards you.
That’s why I always picked on you.
I only realized that
you are a worthy friend after
I thought that you are dead.
I’m not interested to become your friend.
But since you can drop
your prejudice against me,
shouldn’t you trust Si Feng more?
Stop talking. Let’s go.
Okay. Let’s go.
Lize Palace is huge.
Where will they keep the spirit keys?
My lord, according to my
observation, both Rahu and Ketu
are moving again.
Both Rahu and Ketu - are going to be aligned soon.
- Yes.
Rahu and Ketu represent
Star of Mosha’s soul and
primordial spirit respectively.
But Rahu has already
started to flash.
This means that
Star of Mosha’s soul
has sensed his spirit that is
on a trial right now.
He is calling out
to his primordial spirit.
Looks like the Star of Mosha
is going to be revived soon.
Congratulations, my lord.
Even the sky is helping you
to complete grand mission.
Who is it?
Chase after them!
They are really dumb.
Little Pig, go and help them.
You are Ting Nu’s spirit beast, Dang Kang?
Purple Fox asked you to save us?
We’ve already exposed ourselves.
It’ll be hard for us to go in again.
I hope that the Purple Fox can get
the keys. Then, we’ll still have a chance.
Just now, they said that Star of Mosha
is going to be revived soon.
We have to tell Master about it at once.
Let’s go.
SHAOYANG
I never thought that those demons
are so cruel and cold-hearted.
They don’t even care about
their own people.
The vice palace lord of Lize Palace
is always picking on Si Feng.
Maybe Si Feng is really
not a part of their conspiracy.
Min Yan.
Have you not suffered enough
in the hands of the demons?
Even if there’s a wedge between them,
we still have to hunt those
12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird demons down.
Master, my fellow sect leaders,
we found out another bad news
when we went to Lize Palace.
There’s a star map at Lize Palace.
It shows that both Rahu and Ketu
are going to fuse together soon.
As soon as they become one,
it means that Star of Mosha
is going to be revived.
Sect Leader! This is bad!
I just came back from secret ground.
Senior Heng Yang is leading the disciples
to invite the Candle Dragon.
But the demonic flame of Jade Cup
is getting stronger.
Senior Heng Yang tried his best
to suppress it. But he is hurt internally.
How is he now?
I’ve already transferred some energy
to him. He’s fine now.
He’s still performing the ritual to invite
the spirit of Candle Dragon.
There’s an anomaly
in the flame of Jade Cup.
Could it be that Star of Mosha
is really going to be revived?
No wonder these demons are so fearless.
We have to find a way to
intimidate them as a warning.
If that’s the case,
let’s form a formation
and ask God of War to take the lead
and kill that Rose Gold Bird
with her own hands.
Then, take his demonic core
and show it to those demons
to show us our might!
But the God of War was very
close to Yu Si Feng before this.
She couldn’t even attack him
before this. Now,
will she be able to kill him?
Xuan Ji was tricked by the demon that day.
She couldn’t accept it so suddenly.
But she has already made
a promise in front of everyone.
She’ll lead us to defeat those demons.
I believe that she
will be firm this time.
If we want to extract the demonic core,
we need the Demon Prison Formation
in order to trap
that 12 Feathers Rose Gold Bird.
If you are worried, I’ll
enter the formation myself
- to suppress him.
- No.
If you go into the Demon Prison Formation,
you’ll be corroded by it.
Your life will be danger
if you go in for too long.
How about this?
I’ll go in myself tomorrow.
I believe that Xuan Ji
won’t hesitate anymore.
- Sect Leader.
- Say no more.
Tomorrow, please protect
the eye of the formation.
We’ll extract his demonic core
to show it to the people.
- Xuan Ji, this is bad.
- What happened, Sixth Senior?
Just now, those sect leaders have decided
for you to perform a formation tomorrow
to extract Si Feng’s demonic core.
How did that happen?
Didn’t Father agree not to kill him yet?
That’s because they thought that
Si Feng can threaten Sky Hall.
But they never thought that they
don’t care about Si Feng’s life at all.
- I’ll talk to my father now.
- Wait.
So many things had happened.
Everybody thinks that
Si Feng is the devil.
- Do you think we can convince him?
- I...
Besides, the sect leaders of Fuyu Island
and Dianjinggu are here too.
That’s right.
We have to save Si Feng first.
Okay, I’ll go with you.
- Sixth Senior, you...
- I don’t know about other things.
But I know that Si Feng has
gone through thick and thin with us.
No matter what will happen in the future,
I can’t just watch him die.
- Thank you, Sixth Senior.
- Stop talking. Let’s go.