LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 46
Now that Wu Zhi Qi has been saved,
my plan will succeed soon.
And everything will be clear.
I saw Xuan Ji’s background
within Demon Citadel.
She’s the God of War
and Star of Mosha as well.
Although I don’t know why,
I suspect that
the heavens was up to something.
That’s why Xuan Ji had to withstand
nine lives of torture.
Maybe this was connected to everything.
It’s tough for her?
What about you?
Do you think you’re happy
when she’s suffering?
Yu Si Feng, you suffered
the same fate yourself!
Forget it. Just sever your ties with her.
If you continue this,
you’ll be dead next time.
In this life, as long as the two
stars do not align with each other,
she will never become Star of Mosha.
And she won’t suffer again.
If I die,
I will only miss out this life.
But if I do so, Xuan Ji
will never suffer again.
Are you silly or are you
pretending to be silly?
As long as the two stars
do not align with each other?
Do you think you can determine
the movement of the stars?
I can’t do it on my own.
So,
I need someone to help me.
Don’t say that.
I’m not that capable.
I can’t help you with this.
- Wu Zhi Qi.
- Wu Zhi Qi?
Are you kidding me?
He’s one of the strongest demon around.
Maybe it’s his wish to
revive the Star of Mosha too.
Why should he help you?
Are you saying that you can trick him
to help you?
Wu Zhi Qi is a loyal person.
If I want him to help me,
I need to be honest and sincere.
Brother Liu, please
prepare a feast for me.
I’ll meet him.
Xuan Ji.
Our wedding dresses are done.
They just sent them to me.
Are they nice?
Both of our weddings
will be held in two days.
Everyone is busy preparing for that.
Xuan Ji,
what’s wrong?
Are you listening to me?
Xuan Ji!
Senior, why did you lie to me?
Seems like you still
can’t bear to kill him.
You did use the Vermilion Bird Bottle.
Yes.
I’ve asked myself 1,000 times.
But I really don’t want him to die.
That’s why I tried to cleanse his anguish
by using the bottle.
I just wanted to bring him back.
Even if I have to lock him up forever.
But, the Vermilion Bird Bottle
almost killed him instead!
I knew you would go soft on him.
That’s why I helped you out.
I’m doing this
for your sake.
For my sake?
You want me to master
the Sentimental Tactics,
yet you want me to be heartless?
Isn’t this ironic? I can’t do this.
Senior, I’m sorry.
Xuan Ji!
Initially, I wanted us to get married
and let everything return to normal.
But in the end,
it was only my wishful thinking.
Fine.
Since it has come to this,
let’s end this once and for all.
For our wedding,
I won’t force you
if you’re not willing to marry me.
I will give everyone an explanation.
But no matter what happens,
I will always be your senior.
Senior, you’re always the person
I respect the most.
Fine.
I hope you can remember your vow
as a protector of the secret ground.
Protect the Jade Cup.
I will never forget my responsibility.
I won’t let anyone acquire the Jade Cup.
But now, I’m afraid
that isn’t enough.
Now that the Star of Mosha
has reincarnated,
the secret ground is easy to be invaded
as the barrier had disappeared.
The Jade Cup is in a dangerous position.
Promise me this.
If one day, you couldn’t
protect the Jade Cup any longer,
you must destroy it yourself.
If not, the world will be jeopardized
once Star of Mosha obtains
its soul.
The Shaoyang Sect has been protecting
the Jade Cup for many years.
Should I really destroy it?
The heavens wanted to
show mercy initially.
They wanted to purify
the soul of Star of Mosha.
So that he may return to
heavens one day.
But now,
it seems like he has no remorse at all.
And he has let
the heavens down again.
Since that’s the case,
we have no choice but to destroy his soul.
And only the God of War
can do that.
Since
you can’t bear to kill Yu Si Feng,
you should never let him
obtain the Jade Cup.
You need to do this in order
to protect the world
and to prevent that kid
from making further mistakes.
If that day does come,
I will destroy the Jade Cup myself.
I heard that you’re
going to treat me to a feast.
I even skipped my lunch for this.
I was waiting for this.
- Brother Wu.
- Don’t need to be too courteous.
Your injuries haven’t healed yet,
but you’re treating me to a feast already?
Seems like this is not a free meal, right?
Honestly speaking,
I have a favor
to ask of you.
Brother Wu, actually,
I didn’t save you
because I wanted to revive the demon clan.
It’s because of my own selfish desire.
You’re pretty interesting.
Everyone else would hide
their true intentions.
But you’re funny.
You tell me immediately.
It’s either you’re stupid, or
you’re the smartest person around.
But it’s fine.
No matter which type you
belong to, you’re my benefactor.
I’ve laid out some rules before.
Anyone who save me will become my brother.
I will promise you three wishes.
And I’ll do anything to accomplish them.
So, just tell me what you need.
Brother Wu, please promise me that
you’ll not give Yuan Lang the Juntian Loop
and Chehai Hook no matter what.
I think
that’s fine.
But I have three questions for you.
First question.
You don’t want him
to obtain the divine weapons
because you don’t want him
to unseal the Jade Cup, right?
Yes.
Second question.
You’re not the reincarnation
of Star of Mosha, right?
Yes.
Just like what I’ve thought.
The reincarnation of Star of Mosha
will never sustain such injuries
from the malignant aura.
Last question.
You know the identity of Star of Mosha.
But you don’t want to revive him, right?
Actually,
I just don’t want our clan
to be involved in an endless war.
Good!
I like people like you.
Don’t worry.
I’ll never let Yuan Lang obtain
Juntian Loop and Chehai Hook.
Brother Wu, thank you.
Brother Wu, I have another question
for you as well.
Actually,
you don’t want the Star of Mosha
to be revived as well, am I right?
Star of Mosha is the lord of all demons.
If he is revived, he’ll
surely invade the heavens
in order to pay them back
for our humiliations.
That would’ve been fun.
But I hate it when
people order me around.
As the Left Lieutenant, I need to
follow his orders if he’s revived.
And that troubles me.
Why don’t we just forget it?
Just let him stay dead then.
We should just enjoy our lives
and drink to our heart’s content.
Thank you, Brother Wu.
Stop thanking me.
Aren’t you tired of it?
By the way, Brother Wu,
I have something to ask.
The furnace that could absorb humans’
souls, where did Yuan Lang get that?
A furnace that can absorb humans’ souls?
Don’t tell me it’s the Soul Furnace?
What’s the use of this Soul Furnace?
For the Soul Furnace, if
you absorb 99 souls with it,
it’ll form a blood formation.
It enables the user
to absorb the powers of live humans.
And the victim will
turn into a dry corpse.
So, who is Yuan Lang targeting then?
Don’t tell me
this power has something to do
with the revival of Star of Mosha?
How could I forget this?
God of War used her own power
to seal Star of Mosha’s soul.
So, in order to unseal the Jade Cup,
besides using Juntian Loop
and Chehai Hook,
we need the God of War’s power as well.
Don’t tell me
Yuan Lang is targeting Xuan Ji?
It’s no wonder he’s trying to
wake Xuan Ji’s hidden power.
That old bird is devious indeed.
He even dares to target Little Beauty.
This is bad. Xuan Ji will be in danger.
I mustn’t let him succeed.
You’re wrong.
I think you should let him succeed.
Why?
Although the furnace
is immensely powerful,
Yuan Lang can’t control it by himself.
If I’m not mistaken,
he’ll try to lure me with his words.
He needs my power.
Brother Wu, are you saying that
we should turn his trick against him?
And destroy the Soul Furnace
while we catch him off guard?
Yes.
He wants to use the furnace, right?
We’ll make him understand
the consequences.
And give him a taste of his own medicine.
A great plan indeed.
Brother Wu, sorry for the trouble.
You don’t need to stand on ceremony.
You don’t need to
deal with him on your own.
I want to settle my debts
with him as well.
But to make sure we
succeed in our plan,
we still need to make him trust us.
You’ll handle that.
I’ll handle the fight.
Oh right.
I said I would grant you three wishes.
You only told me one wish.
What are the other two wishes?
I don’t dare to be greedy.
Brother Wu, I’m satisfied
with this one wish.
Great!
I love to make friends
with people like you.
But don’t worry.
Since I’ve promised you three
wishes, I will grant all three of them.
It’s fine. You can take your time.
Today, we’ll drink to our heart’s content.
Here.
You are brothers now?
Wu Zhi Qi, I thought you
need to drink with someone
for at least 10 years
before he becomes your brother?
Can you stay away from me?
No.
Your injuries haven’t healed yet.
Go back and sleep.
No. I want to look at you.
My injuries will heal faster
when I look at you.
Fine.
But don’t look at me like that.
You’re really ugly.
Turn into a fox and eat your grapes.
Why are you so heartless?
I’m your benefactor, you know?
You need to grant me three wishes
from today onward.
First, you can only praise me from now on.
Don’t say I’m ugly.
- Annoying.
- Heartless person!
- Unreasonable.
- You!
What are you laughing at?
Are you not used to it?
No.
I’m really envious.
I hope every couple in the world
will have a happy ending like you two.
What happy ending?
Si Feng, listen up. If you spout nonsense
like these, I’ll leave.
Don’t leave!
Little Si Feng, continue. I love it
when you say words like these.
You’re such a drag. He...
- What kind of lousy wine is this?
- Wu Zhi Qi?
When did you come in?
I’m here to drink and chat with you.
What? You don’t welcome me?
How dare you give me such lousy wine?
I was waiting for you.
You made me wait a long time.
This is what you call a wine!
But it’s lousier than the ones
we drank in the past.
When we were in Demon Citadel,
we enjoyed our lives.
We fought the heavens
once we finish drinking.
Those were the days.
I didn’t expect you
to still remember our past.
Of course. I was glorious then.
The troops in the heavens
were trembling when they saw me.
I almost demolished Mount Kunlun as well.
We were so close to success.
We would’ve been the ruler
of the three realms
if it weren’t for that pesky God of War!
That’s right.
That damned God of War
caught me off guard.
I must get my revenge.
If only there’s a way to kill her.
- I’ll do anything for that.
- Is that true?
I’ll gather all our brothers
and make preparations as long as
you’re willing to do so.
We’ll kill the God of War first.
We’ll invade
the heavens after that.
Great!
I’ll use this chance to
tell our brothers that
I, Wu Zhi Qi, have returned.
And we’ll invade the heavens together!
Nice!
My king.
What?
My king, you’re not meant
to be in the human realm.
Now, your human body has reach its limits.
You mustn’t stay here any longer.
Seems like I don’t have much time.
I gave her a chance before.
She wanted love.
I used love to guide her.
But she was obsessed with it.
I tried my best to get rid of her
obsession, yet she disobeys me
time and time again.
She’s walking towards the dark abyss.
And I can’t bring her back.
Seems like
she’s not the old her anymore.
Now, I’m powerless.
I can never guide her back.
My king, are you saying that
you’re going to give up on her?
This tribulation was her last chance,
yet she gave up on it.
Since that’s the case,
instead of witnessing her turning into
a demon and experience endless torture,
I would rather destroy her myself.
My king, could you bear to do so?
You brought her up on your own!
So what if I can’t bear to part with her?
My only concern is the three realms.
This all started because of me.
I should
end it personally.
Yuan Lang, I didn’t expect you
to be so resourceful.
You gathered so many of our brothers
within a short time.
Brothers, thank you all for being here.
It’s all thanks to our Right Lieutenant.
He has been planning this for 1,000 years.
And thank you, my brothers.
Thank you for helping me.
Here.
Let me give you all a toast.
- We’ve been waiting for you.
- Demon Lord, we’ll serve you forever!
Bottoms up!
In the past,
I’ve neglected our Right
Lieutenant and let him down.
But now, I know
who’s truly loyal to me.
Right Lieutenant,
I hope you can forget the past.
My lord, you’re too courteous.
In the past, I neglected you because
I didn’t know your true identity.
Now that the truth has been revealed,
my lord, I will do my best to assist you.
I’m relieved to hear that.
Right Lieutenant had
contributed so much to our clan.
I should reward him.
In the future, Right Lieutenant
will govern Lize Palace.
My lord, I will do my best.
But now, the thing I hate the most
is that God of War.
I truly loved her in the past.
But I didn’t expect her
to be so heartless.
She almost killed me
with the Vermilion Bird Bottle.
Since that’s the case,
I don’t need to
show her mercy any longer.
That’s right.
Now, we just need to retrieve
our lord’s soul.
How about this?
Let’s attack Shaoyang Sect.
We’ll acquire the Jade Cup.
After that, we’ll try to
force the God of War
to unseal the Jade Cup.
What do you think?
That’s too reckless.
I’m afraid it would fail.
Do you have any great ideas then?
Are you able to make her unseal
the Jade Cup willingly?
Oh right, Yuan Lang, you always
come up with the greatest ideas.
Why don’t you tell us your idea?
My lord, if you’re worried that
the God of War is hard to deal with,
I have a formation which you could try.
You have a formation as powerful as that?
Do you need my help?
Sure.
If my lord and Left Lieutenant
can assist me in this,
that’ll be the best.
No problem at all. We’re brothers, right?
We’ll do whatever you say.
My lord, please give me
three days to prepare.
By then, I will make sure
you acquire your soul
and recover your strength.
And the demon clan will dominate
the three realms.
With Right Lieutenant’s intellect,
I’m sure this plan will succeed.
We’ll attack Shaoyang Sect in three days.
We’ll capture the God of War
and retrieve my soul.
This tea is delicious.
Come, have another cup.
- The tea is nice.
- That’s right.
Vice Palace Lord?
Why are you still standing there?
Do you want to stay here forever?
I’m saving you even though
Yu Si Feng might discover us.
You know what to do
when you get out, right?
Vice Palace Lord, thank you for saving me.
I’ll do anything for you.
Great.
You may rise now.
Keep an eye on Yu Si Feng these few days.
I still don’t believe in him.
I only believe in my men.
Yes.
Let’s go.
My lord!
My lord, save me!
My lord, please save me!
I forgot about this.
- Our North Superintendent is still here.
- My lord,
I know it was my fault.
I shouldn’t act on my own accord.
But my lord, please give me another chance
on account of
my contributions to Sky Hall.
This time, I will surely repent!
You’ve said that too many times.
I don’t know when
you’re telling the truth.
I won’t eat my words this time!
If not, I will suffer
a terrible death!
I wanted to kill you a long time ago.
I wanted you to be the last sacrifice
for the Soul Furnace.
But now that I think about it,
it’s more fun for me
if I bring you somewhere.
Is this the abandoned Demon Citadel?
Why is it filled with malignant aura?
1,000 years ago,
the Asura clan of the Demon Citadel
was massacred by the God of War.
The heavens demolished
Demon Citadel in one night.
And it became deserted.
The vengeful spirits of the Asura clan
were stuck here.
That’s why it is filled with
malignant aura.
Most of the malignant aura
had dissipated as Wu Zhi Qi
broke the gate.
If not, we would have no way
to survive in this place.
Why are you here then?
What?
Are you afraid now?
You’re under my control.
You can’t escape from me.
And these vengeful spirits
will soon be mine.
So, you’re trying to
absorb the vengeful spirits?
You want to use me as your stepping stone?
No way!
General Asura,
we’re comrades, aren’t we?
Please borrow me your body.
I’ll use it to appease your
1,000-year-old hatred.
With my soul,
I summon yours!
I didn’t expect
Yuan Lang to still hide information
about the formation
even though he mentioned it to us.
He’s really cunning.
Seems like he doesn’t trust us completely.
Look at his smug face.
It doesn’t matter if he trusts us or not.
I’m sure he still has
some tricks up his sleeves.
But it’s fine. If he wants to
obtain God of War’s power,
he needs our help.
He’ll take our bait for sure.
Si Feng,
I’m relieved that you’re doing well.
Silver Snake?
Why are you here?
You are Sky Hall’s lackey!
I still haven’t settled my debts with you
for hurting Si Feng!
Silver Snake!
Go away!
Don’t come near me!
You can hit me, scold
me or even kill me.
You’re welcome to do so.
But you’ve left Si Feng for too long.
Your spirit power is very weak now.
I need to transfer some qi to you.
You don’t need to care about me!
I will never believe you again.
I’ll kill you.
I’ll kill you!
Silver Snake!
LIZE PALACE
You’re awake?
Do you feel uncomfortable anywhere?
I was too rash that day.
I shouldn’t scold you like that.
Since you’ve returned,
you should never
disobey me again.
If not, I’ll punish you severely.
Master, I’ll obey
your every command,
except for things related to Chu Xuan Ji.
I will never change my mind.
If that Chu Xuan Ji tries to hurt you,
I will never let her off.
I thought you understood
something after you left me.
But if you’re still insisting on doing so,
you shouldn’t return to me.
I don’t have a spirit beast
as willful as you.
Spirit beast?
In your eyes, I’m only a spirit beast.
Master,
I disobeyed your command because
I didn’t want you to be hurt.
My heart hurts when
you suffer time and time again
due to Chu Xuan Ji.
Because I only have you in my heart.
Master,
can’t you just notice the person
who has been around you all the time?
Silver Snake,
not only are you my spirit beast,
you’re one of my most important
friends as well.
There’s nothing
else besides that.
If you think I’m too cruel,
and you don’t know how to face this,
you may leave me.
From today onward, I
allow you to leave me
and lead your own life.
Fine.
Yu Si Feng, you’ll regret this.
Just wait and see. I’ll find a way
to terminate our contract.
After that, I won’t be your spirit beast!
My lord.
Vice Palace Lord, is your formation ready?
I’m here to tell you just that.
Everything is ready.
My lord, we just need you
to lure Chu Xuan Ji into the formation.
Good.
Tomorrow, you and I
will attack Shaoyang Sect.
And retrieve my soul.
But my lord, if we want to
obtain God of War’s power,
we need to harm Chu Xuan Ji.
My lord, are you
really willing to harm her?
I’ve shown her mercy,
yet she tried to take my life
time and time again.
If Left Lieutenant
didn’t save me that day,
the Vermilion Bird Bottle
would’ve killed me.
I will seek my revenge.
I’m willing to kill her for this,
not to mention harm her.
Tomorrow, during our attack,
you should make sure
Chu Xuan Ji falls into our formation.
- Yes.
- And, although Yu Si Feng is acting according to our plan,
I need to make sure that
our plan is foolproof.
You’re pretty tough.
You even became a half-demon.
You’re a human, yet you’re trying
to acquire the demon’s power?
I don’t want you to die on account of
you surviving the Black Pool.
I’ve stabilized the demon power
inside your body.
How about this?
Coincidentally, I lack someone
who could watch over the vengeful spirits.
Follow me and acquire the Jade Cup.
After you accomplish your mission,
I’ll teach you how to master
your power. What do you think?
Is that for real?
I’m the Right Lieutenant.
I’m not an imbecile like you.
You’ll die anyway.
It depends on you whether
to cherish this chance or not.
SHAOYANG SECT
Xuan Ji, help me out.
Which one of them is better?
Xuan Ji?
Xuan Ji.
What’s wrong?
You were supposed to get married
to Senior Hao Chen.
Why did you reject the wedding?
If not, we could’ve been married
on the same day.
Senior Hao Chen is my senior.
He’s the person I respect the most.
But that’s all there is to it.
You still can’t let go of the past?
No.
It’s just that
you’re going to get married.
I can’t bear to part with you.
It’s fine.
Xuan Ji, anyway, I believe that
you can find someone who loves you
and deserves your love.
Just like Little Six and I.
Anyway,
you should stop thinking
about sad things, okay?
Okay.
It’s almost time.
You should doll yourself up.
I’ll check on the decorations.
Si Feng?
Prepare the formation.
The vengeful spirits of Asura has awaken.
Shaoyang Sect,
I will get back
what you had taken from me!
Vice Palace Lord is all set to go.
Let’s start.
Attack Shaoyang Sect!
God of War, your
power is mine now.
Si Feng, it’ll be too late
for you if you don’t quit!
Do you think I would
still fall for your trick?
You want me to show you mercy?
In your dreams.
This time, I won’t
show you any mercy.
Demon Lord, save your breath.
Set up the formation.
Purple Fox?
My illusion spell is pretty good, right?
You plotted this together?
Plot? You’re the master of plots.
We’re just using your own trick
against you.
Yuan Lang, you underestimated me.
Do you think I don’t know
what you’re up to
if you hide everything from me?
What do you think?
I just altered some parts,
and now, you’re the one being absorbed.
Are you surprised?
He who is unjust is doomed to destruction.
Since you’ve created the Soul Furnace,
you’ll have a taste of
your own medicine today.
Yuan Lang, stop struggling.
You created the Soul Furnace yourself.
It has absorbed 99 souls.
It has absorbed malignant aura
as well. It is immensely powerful.
I’m afraid you can’t escape
with your weak powers.
Strange.
Why do I see this tree everywhere I go?
Who’s behind this?
Dingkun Sword!
Don’t slash me!
My god! Please show me mercy!
Brother Liu? Why are you here?
Why did you trap me here?
It’s...
I...
Did Si Feng ask you to come?
Where is he?
You two should settle your own problem.
Si Feng!
Si... You...