LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 59
- Si Feng!
I will not let you ruin
the Transcendent Furnace.
Because I want to protect
my memories with Xuan Ji!
Si Feng.
Then go to hell!
- Si Feng!
Si Feng!
Yu Si Feng. Look, Xuan Ji is back.
Are you worried?
I don’t want you to die.
Hearing these words,
I can die
with no regrets.
Actually...
Actually,
I bet with Bailing.
That
you’re not a murderous demon.
Because
your heart has gained flesh and blood.
This heart wouldn’t bring itself
to destroy the three realms.
Because
I warmed it, little by little.
Si Feng!
- Si Feng!
I’ll save you.
I will save you.
- Si Feng!
Si Feng!
Si Feng.
It won’t do any good.
My heart
has been pierced.
But it’s good.
I won back your heart with mine.
It’s worth it.
Please look after the three realms.
Because there are
where our many memories are.
As long as the three realms exist,
they will never disappear.
Xuan Ji.
Do you hear me?
Remember.
I’ve had
ten happy lives.
Because no matter what,
I could meet you.
And it’s
good enough.
Si Feng.
Si Feng!
- Si Feng!
- Xuan Ji.
Si Feng!
Si Feng, it’s me Xuan Ji!
I’m back, Si Feng!
Si Feng!
Yuan Lang.
You killed my
mother and Si Feng!
I’m going to kill you today!
I want to be the ruler of three realms!
No one can stop me!
Ruo Yu!
You took everything from me!
You locked up my family,
killed my loved one,
and forced me to kill my brother!
- Ruo Yu.
Don’t you ever harm
the three realms again!
I’ve been waiting for
the three realms to ruin.
I’ve waited for one thousand years!
I must succeed.
I must succeed!
- Ruo Yu!
Oh no!
I am the ruler of three realms!
The ruler of three realms!
Jade Emperor, help me!
I want to keep these three realms forever!
Is this your final decision?
This is me and Si Feng’s final decision.
I don’t want the three realms to go!
Fine, let me give you a hand.
Si Feng.
Look.
I didn’t lose the three realms.
Didn’t you ask me to keep our memories?
I did it.
Look what I’ve done.
Please.
Bailing.
Xi Xuan bet with you.
That Rahu Ketu isn’t
some apocalyptic demon.
What do you think?
Jade Emperor.
I lost.
My deeply improper thoughts
have ruined the three realms
and killed many lives.
And I’ve ruined Rahu Ketu
and hurt my own self.
I am unpardonable.
King Bailing.
I am the root of this
thousand-year grudge.
I feel too ashamed to live.
Chu Xuan Ji.
Please grant my death.
Let me free.
I will never simply take one’s life
for my own interest.
Even if he’s
as wicked as you.
Si Feng once said that
revenge is an endless cycle.
In this life,
my heart
has found the more important thing.
There’s no more room for the hatred.
From now on,
we have nothing to do with each other.
This...
Rahu Ketu?
Brother Rahu.
Chu Xuan Ji.
You’ve had a lucky life than me.
You’ve met those whom you care about.
And they’re willing to sacrifice for you.
You must cherish them.
I really wish that
I could live once again.
Bailing.
Do you still remember
the bank of Ruoshui River?
The bank of Ruoshui River.
In the Baiyu Pavilion.
It’s where we drank.
Those days,
I always remember them.
Yes.
I always remember them too.
We had our last drink
one thousand years ago.
You toasted me, and I drank mine.
I toasted you, but
you didn’t drink yours.
Today,
you shall drink it.
Sure.
Brother Rahu.
I shall drink it.
- King Bailing!
King Bailing.
We have finally done drinking.
- King Bailing!
Don’t come over.
I brought this all upon myself.
Rahu Ketu resents someone
and does not forgive me.
In fact, I cannot even forgive myself.
I just want to bring you to justice
for what you did to me and other victims.
You brought this to yourself.
It serves you right.
Vanity is all I’ve cultivated
these ten thousand years.
Now that it’s come to this,
wouldn’t it be a death worth dying?
King Bailing.
Don’t follow in my footsteps.
My obsession with grievance and scheming
eventually led to my big mistake.
Jade Emperor.
I know that I don’t deserve to be a deity.
Today, I’m entering the channel
of karma and recultivating myself.
If there were to be the chance
ten thousand years from now,
I would be sitting by your side
and listening to
your teachings, Jade Emperor.
Bailing,
God willing, may you repent
and be enlightened soonest.
King Bailing!
Listen my fellow deities.
The death of Bailing
is the merit he has earned
by repenting and taking his own life.
The heavens has
done the Demon Citadel wrong.
You shall not kill and
taking revenge on the demons.
From today onward,
the three realms are equal and
shall live in harmony with one another.
Anyone disobeying this
order will be severely punished.
We shall obey the decree, Jade Emperor!
Jade Emperor.
Si Feng died saving the three realms.
It’s not his fault. The fault is all mine!
I beg you.
Please save him.
I’m willing to exchange my life for his!
Xi Xuan is my son.
I certainly hope that he’ll be fine.
But I have no control over life and death.
As much as I want to save him,
there’s nothing I can do.
However...
What?
However, I need not do so anymore.
Someone’s saved him.
What is this?
It’s Rahu Ketu’s heart.
When Rahu Ketu brushed Xi Yuan’s chest,
he’s planted half of
the Jade Heart in him.
The heart has gained flesh and blood.
It can save his life.
Will this heart start beating again
and wake him up?
That depends on you.
Thank you for your guidance, Jade Emperor.
Si Feng will surely wake up.
He will wake up for sure.
He will surely wake up.
Jade Emperor, please tell me
where my daughter is.
I’m the one who stole the celestial eye.
She has nothing to do with it.
Please have mercy on us, Jade Emperor!
You stole the celestial eye
because of your daughter.
It is a father’s love to his child.
And you went to Kunlun to see me
for the sake of three realms.
You have made up for the mistake.
You should head back to Qingyang.
Your father-daughter relationship
is not over yet.
She is waiting for you at home.
Sure!
I’m leaving now!
Thank you, Jade Emperor!
Jade Emperor, what about Purple Fox?
I took them to the Mount Kunlun,
and I’ve made up for the mistake!
Please save Purple Fox too!
Purple Fox died for you, and bears
your sins from thousand years ago.
What goes around comes around.
She will re-enter the channel of karma.
Then where is she?
She has suffered from missing you
for a thousand years.
Why should you go and see her?
Twelve hours from now, she is
going to drink the Water of Forgetting.
- Water of Forgetting?
- She will forget you in the next life.
And she will be free.
Little Fox is at the River of Forgetting?
Deep yet transient love.
Why bother?
Xuan Ji, let’s go home.
Flying Snake.
I know that you had
a deep affection for King Bailing.
You may stay here as long as you want.
You have my word forever.
You may go far away
for as long as you want.
You’re welcome to
come back anytime.
Take good care of yourself.
Si Feng,
let’s go home now.
Wu Zhi Qi.
He’s the most easy-going and
carefree person in the world.
Little Fox.
- Wu Zhi Qi!
- Thank you.
For saving me.
I’m willing to do anything
to save Wu Zhi Qi.
Don’t let me go again.
Little Fox!
Wu Zhi Qi.
Little Fox.
I will never let you go again.
Candied Chinese hawthorn!
Yu’Er.
Old Fogey, where’ve you been?
You’ve been away too long!
I’m starving!
Cook for me!
Sure!
I’m going home to cook for you now.
Gosh, you’re a grown-up.
Don’t cry, it’s so embarrassing.
Oh right, I want to eat scallion pancake.
Buy me some.
Sure.
I’m willing to buy you
scallion pancake for life.
Let’s go.
Old Fogey, I’m telling you.
There are many delicious foods ahead.
Ahead there. Let’s go.
Si Feng,
we’re home.
But
when will you wake up?
It’s okay.
No matter how long,
I’ll always wait for you.
Si Feng. Did you know?
Ling Long and Sixth Senior
are fighting about
who the baby will look like.
Sixth Senior says Ling Long’s too short.
Ling Long says Sixth Senior’s too dull.
I was there when she
chased after and hit him.
Isn’t it funny?
And look at this.
It’s your favorite Qingyang lotus seeds.
Si Feng.
Do you still remember the promise
we made under the Magpie Bridge?
That we’ll be together forever.
Si Feng.
You must’ve had a hard
time practicing sword moves.
You’ve been sleeping for so long.
But the calluses on your hands
haven’t gone away.
I received a letter from
Brother Liu today.
He says Yu’Er isn’t as obedient as you.
She competes with him all the time.
Si Feng.
Si Feng!
Xuan Ji.
Si Feng.
I’ve missed you so much.
I’ve really missed you so much.
Xuan Ji.
Don’t cry.
I’m not crying.
I’m happy.
The tears fell down themselves.
Silly girl.
I knew you’d come back, Si Feng.
I knew you’d surely come back.
Silly girl.
How would I not come back
when you’re here?
Let’s go.
Where to?
Go ask my father for my hand.
Father!
Si Feng? You...
Sect Leader Chu,
I have fully recovered.
That’s great.
Si Feng.
Because of my foolishness,
you’ve had gone through a lot.
- This time I...
- I am alright now.
Father, please allow me to marry Si Feng.
Sure.
Sure!
Xuan Ji?
- Ling Long?
- Get in first.
It’s your wedding day.
You should wait for Si Feng in there.
Why are you lingering out here?
Auntie Ying Hong
has dressed me up long ago.
I felt so bored staying in the room.
Moreover, our sect
doesn’t care about formality.
That’s why I decided to come
and check the guests out.
You are, as always, inappropriate.
Go back and stay in there.
I’ll decorate the venue well.
Xuan Ji.
A kid at the foot of the mountain
helped someone to sent you this gift.
He didn’t mention who the sender is.
[May you have a blessed marriage.
I am pleased for you.]
It’s Merman’s Tear.
It’s from Ting Nu.
But why didn’t he send it himself?
He asked someone else to do so instead.
They’re here!
Xuan Ji, just wait for Si Feng
to come and take your hand.
Go now.
DOUBLE HAPPINESS
Here comes the groom!
SHOUYANG HALL
Congratulations.
Father-in-law.
I, Yu Si Feng, came here today
to take Chu Xuan Ji’s hand.
Please grant me
your permission, Father-in-law.
My good child.
Both of you...
Both of you must get along well.
Rest assured, Father-in-law.
Xuan Ji is the love
I’ve earned from
living ten lives in all the realms.
I will surely adore her.
Forever.
Good.
Hero Yu.
Today, I’m giving you
my daughter’s hand.
Xuan Ji.
I’m here to marry you.
I’ve been waiting for you for so long.
Husband and wife,
bow to Father and bid farewell!
How lovely!
SHOUYANG HALL
Why are you looking at me?
Shouldn’t...
Shouldn’t we blow out the candles first?
I’ve been waiting for this day to come.
There’s no way
I’m blowing out the candles.
Tonight, this bridal
chamber will remained lit.
In that case,
I won’t get changed.
I will
help you with that.
This is such a wonderful moment.
Why are you in a trance?
I remember my mother once told me this.
There’s someone in this world
to whom you’re willing to give
everything, without reservation.
I’m really lucky
to have found such a person.
I am
as lucky.
You said
you’ll give me everything.
Don’t you go back on your word.
I won’t.
Forever.
Ten lives.
THREE YEARS LATER
Uncle Dong Fang is coming.
Prepare more Flower Wine.
- Go ahead.
- Yes, Senior.
People from Lize Palace are coming.
How can we serve them grilled quails?
- Leave.
- Yes, Senior Ling Long.
It’s Father’s birthday.
How can the couplet be hung crookedly?
Let go, I’ll do it.
LONGEVITY
My gosh!
You’re pregnant.
How can you hang the couplet?
What if the baby gets hurt?
Take a rest.
Little Six!
I’m pregnant with a baby,
not some explosive.
Would I explode?
No, why...
Why do you get mad all the time?
They say anger is bad for health.
You see, you holler all the time.
What if you scare...
Scare... Scare Xuan Ji!
What do you do?
Can you clowns let me
have a quiet morning?
I see, Little Six, you’ve mastered
to be double-faced, haven’t you?
With a father like you,
our child will grow up to be bad!
- Xuan Ji!
- Get over here!
They’re finally gone.
Chu Xuan Ji!
Who let you drink?
- They’re all no match for me.
- Father.
- Stop drinking, Father.
- Enough, Father.
- That’s enough.
- It’s okay. I’m happy.
I must drink up today.
Here, cheers!
- Father!
What a joyful day!
- Lord Dong Fang, have fun.
- Oh no, Brother Chu’s drunk.
Hurry up and give me the hangover cure.
Again?
I can’t hold my liquor.
- Give it to me.
- Just don’t drink then.
There’s no way I’m not
drinking today. Hurry up.
- Brother Chu.
- Brother Dong Fang.
I’ve caught you red-handed.
- I can’t hold my liquor.
- You used to tricked me with this cure.
- I can’t drink.
- This time I’m going to punish you.
- You’re drunk.
- I’ll pour it for you.
- Let me pour it for you.
- No!
Here, open your mouth.
Good!
I’ll drink with you.
- Ling Long!
- You’re here!
Congratulations!
Brother Liu, you’re late.
- We’ve been waiting for you.
- It’s all Yu’Er’s fault.
- Here.
- She kept asking for food and drink.
- That’s why we’re late.
- It’s because you’re stingy.
- Have a seat first.
- You always bought so little.
- Of course I needed to buy more.
- She’s blaming me.
You can eat as much as
you want today, have a seat.
Xuan Ji, here.
Carry him for a while.
- Baby.
- Flying Snake?
Don’t cry, baby. There, there.
I heard there’s good food.
Of course I’ve got to be here.
Ask them to serve the food.
Want to eat those delicious food?
Here, help me to carry him first.
Don’t cry.
- Don’t cry.
- He peed.
Carry him!
Careful, the baby!
Yu’Er...
Yu’Er used to pee a lot when she’s small.
You’ll get used to it eventually.
- It’s okay. Here, let me do it.
- Brother Chu, you should stop drinking.
- We’ve just started, fill up the cut.
- Don’t drop the baby!
One thousand years ago,
you’re a created existence.
That’s why every step you took
wasn’t determined by fate.
You’re all on your own.
It’s up to you to be a demon,
an immortal, or a mortal.
I’d like to ask you this.
What does it feel to be a mortal?
It’s good to be a mortal.