LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 35
Zhong Min Yan.
Are you guilty?
I am guilty.
Since you are guilty,
tell me about your crimes.
I, Zhong Min Yan,
disobeyed Master’s orders,
acted recklessly,
worked with demons,
and embarrassed the sect.
I even...
Who killed Min Jue?
It’s me.
Father, Sixth Senior did it
because he was charmed by demons.
He didn’t do it on purpose.
- You can’t blame it on him.
- Shut up!
But...
No one can plead for him today!
Xuan Ji.
I, Zhong Min Yan, killed
my fellow apprentice.
I’ve committed treason.
I have nothing to say.
Zhong Min Yan.
If you know you are guilty,
tell me how you
should be punished yourself.
I should kill myself.
No! Sixth Senior!
Ling Long, your hand...
Who asked you to do that?
You wanted to die so badly?
It’s my fault.
Nonsense.
I remember everything back at Sky Hall.
- Everything at Sky Hall was my...
- It’s me!
I did everything!
Don’t lie to protect me.
Ling Long.
Remember.
You are unrelated to this.
I’m already in deep trouble.
If you get involved as
well, Master will be so sad.
No.
Ling Long.
I came to Shaoyang when I was eight.
When I first saw you,
you welcomed me in a red dress.
You were proud like a rose.
I’ve never seen
such a beautiful person before.
After that, I found out
that you are the sect leader’s daughter.
Meanwhile, I’m just an orphan.
I had sworn at that time to practice
hard because that’s the only way
I can protect you by your side.
I want to see you being proud.
Ling Long.
Please don’t snatch my final dream away.
No.
I, Zhong Min Yan,
committed a huge crime.
I beg you, Master,
give me the death punishment.
Father, Sixth Senior got cheated
because he values the important bonds.
You can’t put all the fault on him.
Master, please spare Min Yan’s life.
SHOUYANG HALL
Master! Please spare Sixth Senior’s life!
Sect Leader, please spare Min Yan’s life.
Stand. All of you.
SHOUYANG HALL
Zhong Min Yan.
You were charmed by demons
and committed a grave crime.
You should be heavily punished.
Seeing that you didn’t do it on purpose,
you may escape the death punishment
but you will still have to be punished.
Someone!
Expel Zhong Min Yan from the sect.
Father, getting expelled
from a sect is an embarrassment for life.
Please reconsider it.
Xuan Ji.
Master is already being lenient.
Don’t trouble him anymore.
Zhong Min Yan.
From now on, you will no
longer be a disciple of Shaoyang.
Hand over your name plaque.
I, Zhong Min Yan, embarrassed my
master and embarrassed Shaoyang.
I’m handing over the Shaoyang plaque today
and not address myself
as a disciple of Shaoyang anymore.
Father, I have something to say.
I, Chu Ling Long, disciple of
Shaoyang, will leave Shaoyang today.
Ling Long.
You...
What are you talking about?
What happened today is because of me.
Min Yan entered Mount Buzhou to save me,
and got charmed by demons.
I am ashamed to be a
disciple of Shaoyang any longer.
Ling Long, you were born
and raised in Shaoyang.
Where else can you go?
Take back what you said.
The world is so big.
I’ll follow you wherever you go.
Since you like to see me being proud,
allow me to be willful for you again.
All of you are leaving.
Starting today, I won’t be
a disciple of Shaoyang as well.
We will all stay together.
Xuan Ji! That’s nonsense!
You think of Shaoyang as a joke?
Xuan Ji, don’t cause any troubles.
I’m not.
We promised to always stay together.
What are you doing now?
If you are leaving, let’s leave together!
Xuan Ji.
I didn’t do it on impulse.
Don’t act rashly.
It will seem like
you are threatening Father.
But I don’t want to separate with you.
Xuan Ji.
We are not kids anymore.
We won’t be together forever.
If we have to separate,
you just have to choose
the most important person to you.
Shaoyang and Min Yan are the
most important parts of my life.
If I have to make a choice
now, I can only choose Min Yan.
If I don’t have
Shaoyang, I might still live.
But if I don’t have Min Yan,
I will die.
Why?
Why do you have to make this choice?
Xuan Ji, you silly child.
Not everything will go
as planned in this world.
We have to make different choices.
I hope that you won’t
have to make any choices in your life.
Alright. Don’t be rash.
I’m still your sister even
if I’m no longer a disciple of Shaoyang.
Min Yan will still be himself.
Father is old.
Can you be filial for me?
I, Chu Ling Long,
beg for the sect leader’s approval.
Ling Long.
You’ve really decided?
I’ve made my decision to leave.
I am unfilial.
I disappointed Shaoyang’s guidance,
and Father’s upbringing.
Disciples of Shaoyang,
Zhong Min Yan and Chu Ling Long,
violated the sect’s laws.
Starting today,
they will be expelled from Shaoyang.
Although both of you are
no longer disciples of Shaoyang,
you must remember, Shouyang Peak
will always be your home.
Thank you, Master.
Stay at the base
of the peak with Sixth Senior for now.
When Father has calmed down, I
will help you persuade him again.
It’s alright.
If you miss me, just
come and visit me.
What’s wrong?
You will miss me?
Xuan Ji.
Ever since I woke up,
my mind is full of
the flower demon’s memories.
It felt like I killed all
the person she killed.
It felt like her wrongdoings
were done by me.
Even the nasty things
that she did with Wu Tong
felt like I’m the one who did it.
I feel disgusted about myself.
Ling Long.
Those are the flower demon’s memories.
They are not yours.
You didn’t do any of those things.
Those were what she did.
You don’t have to shoulder her crimes.
But she looked exactly like me.
She even had half of my primordial spirit.
Can you say it’s totally unrelated to me?
That’s because
she tried to be similar to you.
Your primordial spirit
was seized by her as well.
You are the victim.
They were not your fault.
You and Sixth Senior
have to leave here
and stay away from these troubles.
You will be happy.
Oh. Xuan Ji.
This...
- What is this?
- This is a Memory Pearl.
You lost your six senses
when you were young.
This is an object
that recorded the times when mother
taught you about
identifying items and feelings.
After I leave, if Father feels
sad in front of Mother’s grave,
you have to accompany
him for me and talk to him.
Let’s go.
Sixth Senior.
Take care of my sister.
Let me send you off.
Don’t.
It’s bad if everyone comes.
We are leaving.
There are no lamps or candles here.
Let me get one.
It’s alright.
The moonlight is nice tonight.
It’s enough to light up this place.
How are your injuries?
I’m fine.
My house is right beside.
Call me if you need anything.
I’ll be going back.
Why are you so foolish?
You are saying that?
Aren’t you more foolish than me?
From now on, you will
become a sectless wanderer
just like me.
I don’t mind going anywhere
as long as I’m with you.
Ling Long.
I will never disappoint you.
Xuan Ji, don’t be sad.
Aren’t Ling Long and Min Yan fine?
It’s a good thing
to live together in peace.
If you miss them,
you can visit them often.
Si Feng.
I have something
I’ve been wanting to ask you.
If there’s one day where
we have to make a choice
between two important things,
what should we do?
Didn’t Ling Long say that?
You just have to choose the
most important person to you.
I only know that I won’t give you up.
What about you?
I won’t give you up too.
Do you know?
I actually envy Ling Long and Min Yan.
You envy them?
Xuan Ji.
After I settle everything
in this Flower Session,
will you find a quiet place
and live a relaxed and
secluded life with me?
THE MEMORIAL TABLET OF HE DAN PING
Father.
It’s both of you.
I was feeling troubled because many things
have happened recently.
That is why
I came to speak with your mother.
Your mother was gone
for many years in the blink of an eye.
Both you and Ling Long have grown up too.
I just hope that both of you will be safe
without any accidents in the future.
Father.
Don’t worry.
I already have the ability
to protect myself.
I will also take care of you and Ling Long
and not allow
anyone of you to be in danger.
You naughty girl.
You did worry me a lot in the past.
Unexpectedly,
after you went out to get experience,
you improved a lot.
You got the Dingkun Sword and
even got the Flying Snake
as you spirit beast.
I am very happy.
But I’m always feeling uncomfortable.
Xuan Ji.
Do you feel something
strange about yourself?
Oh no.
Did Father suspect my identity?
If everyone finds out I’m the God of War,
will they see me as a monster
and not be close to me?
Xuan Ji?
Father.
It’s a coincidence that I got
the Dingkun Sword and Flying Snake.
You are really
not hiding anything from me?
No.
Forget it.
If you won’t tell me,
I won’t force you as well.
I’m old.
I can’t stay by your side for life.
In the future, as long as Si
Feng is with you, I will be relieved.
Father.
You don’t oppose me and Si Feng anymore?
How should I put it?
After what happened with Ling
Long and Min Yan, I got over it.
Two people being together,
as long as they respect and love
each other without leaving,
that’s stronger than everything.
Si Feng is a good kid.
I can see that
he is loyal to you.
Si Feng.
I know.
There are many rules at Lize Palace.
I also know that your master
is not too satisfied with you and Xuan Ji.
Don’t worry. I will find a suitable
time to talk with your master.
Thank you, Sect Leader Chu.
I will never let Chu
Xuan Ji down in my life.
Don’t worry and leave Xuan Ji in my hands.
Are you trying to ask for a marriage now?
I know now is not the best time.
It might be a bit sudden.
But my feelings towards Xuan Ji
never changed at all.
Si Feng.
You brat.
It’s hard to keep a lady
when they grow up, right?
As cultivators wandering the lands,
we can’t be bothered
about little things.
Fine.
After coming back from Dianjinggu,
I will find an auspicious day
to help you and Ling Long get married.
From now on, I will never have
to worry about both of you again.
Father, why are you
talking about marriage...
What’s wrong? You think it’s too fast?
- No...
- Fine.
I’ll find another chance
to trouble him again. How’s that?
No, Sect Leader Chu.
I want that badly.
Fine.
Xuan Ji.
Have a good talk
with your mother.
Si Feng.
I told you I’ll be responsible for you.
I kept my promise, right?
I can only get married to you then.
I...
Give me your mother’s portrait.
Si Feng.
You once told me
you don’t know
where is your mother’s memorial tablet.
You can’t even pay respects
to her even if you wanted to.
Today, your mother’s
portrait is here.
Let’s think of this as her memorial tablet
and tell her this good news together.
Both our mothers, I got
engaged with Si Feng today.
I’m sure both of you
feel happy in your afterlife.
Madam Chu.
I, Yu Si Feng,
will definitely take good care of Xuan Ji.
Why are you smiling?
I’m smiling because we’ve
bowed to our parents just like that.
You are now my fiancée.
That’s not counted.
You just bowed in front of my mother
and you said that’s not counted?
My mother saw everything.
Since we went through the ritual,
where are the betrothal gifts?
Isn’t my hairpin enough?
How dare you ask for your betrothal gift?
Both our mothers,
you have to seek justice for me.
No way. That hairpin was given
to me by your mother, not you.
Fine.
Once I come back from Dianjinggu,
I will give you a grand wedding banquet.
No matter what you want to eat,
I will make them for you for a lifetime.
Is that enough?
That’s better.
Flying Snake?
Sorry to interrupt your rituals.
Why are you here
eating my mother’s offerings?
Who asked you two to be
lovey-dovey and forget about my meal?
Look at this stinky woman.
She’s so fierce.
Little Chef, if I had to say,
why don’t you reconsider it?
What are you talking about?
- Aunt Ying Hong.
- Xuan Ji.
You went to visit Ling Long and Min Yan?
We will depart to Dianjinggu tomorrow.
I went to say my goodbyes.
This trip to Dianjinggu is not normal.
You have to be very careful.
I understand.
Hold on.
Xuan Ji.
Where did you get this hairpin?
Hairpin?
What’s wrong with this hairpin?
This is a carving of
the Rose Gold Bird Demon.
Your mother was...
It’s fine if you forgot it.
These Rose Gold Bird Demons
are cruel and evil in nature.
Your father hates them.
Hurry and take off this hairpin.
This is the Rose Gold Bird?
Yes. It’s the Rose Gold Bird indeed.
Back then, Rose Gold Birds
were the allies of the demon clan.
After the Demon-Immortal War,
they escaped to the mortal realm.
Hundreds of years ago,
the righteous sects
worked together to surround
and got rid of them altogether.
Unfortunately, some
of them still escaped.
Aunt Ying Hong.
You and Ling Long said
I’ve forgotten about something.
What did I forget?
It’s better if you don’t remember.
You were still so young at that time.
Xuan Ji, all these years,
we’ve been looking for
the whereabouts of the demon clan.
Tell me.
Where did you get this hairpin?
Maybe we can find some clues here.
This hairpin was a gift
from my father to my mother.
I’m giving it to you now.
Si Feng, this...
This hairpin is too precious.
You should keep it well.
How can you give it to me?
I gave it to you
because it’s important.
I hope that
you can understand my feelings.
This...
I bought this hairpin
when I was at Qingmu Town.
No matter what, you better
not wear this hairpin anymore
in case your father feels sad
when he sees it.
Xuan Ji, where did you
get this hairpin?
This is a carving of
the Rose Gold Bird Demon.
Your mother was...
It’s fine if you forgot it.
These Rose Gold Bird Demons
are cruel and evil in nature.
Your father hates them.
You better not
wear this hairpin anymore
in case your father feels sad
when he sees it.
Xuan Ji.
Si Feng.
You were spacing out.
What were you thinking about?
I met Aunt Ying Hong just now.
I have a feeling that
she is hiding something from me.
Also, Ling Long also wanted to tell
me something about my childhood.
She even gave me a Memory Pearl.
Si Feng.
Can you watch it with me?
Sure. I’m here, don’t be afraid.
Hurry up.
Xuan Ji.
Can you see the faraway mountains?
Remember.
Mountains are green.
I understand.
Look at that flower.
- Flowers are white.
- I understand.
Mother, what color do you like?
I like blue color.
- Can you remember it?
- I remember.
Rose Gold Bird! Xuan Ji!
Mother!
I remember now.
I remember everything.
It’s the Rose Gold Bird Demon.
Si Feng! Rose Gold Bird Demon
killed my mother!
Xuan Ji.
I’m sure
there’s a misunderstanding.
How could it be?
I remember now.
When I was five,
I saw my mother getting killed by
Rose Gold Bird Demon with my eyes.
Although I don’t know
what was pain at that time,
I couldn’t eat, drink
or sleep after that day.
I fainted one day and forgot
everything when I woke up.
When I saw the Memory Pearl, I...
I remember everything.
My mother was really killed
by the Rose Gold Bird Demon.
No wonder Aunt Ying Hong had a
big reaction when she saw the hairpin.
Can you tell me how
your father got this hairpin?
Maybe I can find some clues.
Xuan Ji.
I only know that this hairpin
was given to me by my mother.
But in this world, not all
Rose Gold Bird are bad.
That might be true.
But Rose Gold Bird Demon killing
my mother is the undeniable truth.
This time, I must get
Sky Hall’s demon at Dianjinggu
and ask them about
the Rose Gold Bird Demon.
I have to find the culprit
and avenge my mother.
Fine.
Master.
You should’ve heard
what Chu Xuan Ji said just now, right?
It’s still not confirmed yet.
Silver Snake.
Help me investigate this.
What if I find out
everything is true?
If that is true,
I will help Xuan Ji in her revenge.
But this is unrelated to other tribes.
I believe in Xuan Ji.
She is someone who knows
what’s right and what’s wrong.
Master.
Don’t be foolish.
Although I don’t agree with
you being with her, if you insist
and wouldn’t leave her,
I think it’s better
to get back the Lugong puzzle.
It’s still not too late
before she solves it.
I get it.
I know you don’t want to hide it from her.
But now you have this thing in between,
do you think it’s wise
to tell her your real identity?
That’s enough.
You may leave.
Master.
I’m just afraid that you fell for
her but ended up getting nothing
and fall to the Loveless Curse in the end.
Sect Leader, are you still worried
about finding the spy from Sky Hall?
Yes.
There’ll be a fierce battle
in the Flower Session at Dianjinggu.
If we can’t uncover the spy from Sky Hall,
there’s a big chance
for them to work together
and steal the last spirit key.
Don’t worry, Sect Leader.
I have an idea.
The demon who fought me at Mount Buzhou
extinguished one of
Xuan Ji and the group’s Birth Candles.
He left a flaw there.
Look.
This bottle holds
the merman blood I went
to get from Donghai just now.
Once a merman’s blood leaves its body,
it will become colorless and scentless.
As long as it touches Merman’s Tear,
it will regain
its blood characteristics and turn red.
The demon extinguished
one of the Birth Candles.
His hands will have Merman’s Tear on them.
Luckily, Merman’s Tear won’t disappear
once it’s been touched.
You mean you want to use the
merman blood to find out who is the spy?
That’s right.
When the Demon Whip
was destroyed by Xuan Ji,
there were 12 elders there.
Why don’t we use the merman blood
to test every one of them?
If anyone’s hand can change
the color of the merman’s blood,
that person will be
the spy we are looking for.
However, we have
to do it in Dianjinggu.
We still need
Valley Master Rong’s cooperation.
Valley Master Rong was there as well.
Your plan won’t work if he is the spy.
Don’t worry.
When I came back from Donghai,
I went to Dianjinggu specially
to test Valley Master Rong
with the merman’s blood.
He isn’t the person we are looking for.
He has also promised
to cooperate with our plan.
Great.
We have to find the spy of
the demon clan no matter what.
My lord.
I said you are
just a dog that I picked up.
Do you remember?
It was etched in my mind.
- I dare not forget.
- That’s great.
Come.
Let me see which hand you used
to steal my Dragon Seal.
I have to reward you.
My lord, no.
Don’t, my lord.
It’s this hand
- or this?
- My lord.
No.
No, my lord.
You fool!
This hand is dismembered
with my Reverse Pulse Smoke.
It will not heal.
You have two hours to live
before your blood runs dry.
My lord!
I know my crimes cannot be forgiven,
but Sky Hall needs people at this time.
I can still contribute to you, my lord.
I will be loyal in the future.
How can a dog who bit his master
be of use to me?
My lord.
Aren’t you planning to hit Dianjinggu?
Diangjinggu is famous for its defenses.
It’s even full of traps in the valley.
You will suffer heavy casualties
if you don’t know the area.
Are you saying
you have a way to disarm the traps?
I used to be a
disciple of Dianjinggu.
I saw the defense mechanism map
of Dianjinggu.
Only the Valley Master has the map.
He will never imagine that
someone else has seen it before.
If you can spare my life, I
can guarantee that Sky Hall
will be able to infiltrate
every part of Dianjinggu.
My lord.
I did it once so I
dare not do it again.
Please give me a chance.
What a pity to kill
a dog that is good at biting.
But I’m still angry at you.
Alright.
If you can save yourself, I
will give you another chance.
Although the wound cannot heal
by itself, it’s not totally impossible.
Here’s a fire barrel.
If you can burn your wound
with this barrel of fire,
your bleeding will stop.
Do you want to give it a try?
I appreciate your attitude
of being cruel to others
and crueler to your own.
I will give you another chance.
You have to remember.
If you have other ideas,
I will have tons of ways to torture you.
Vice Palace Lord.
What’s wrong?
I was ordered to find the stalactite
that grows every 3,000 years
in Dianjinggu by the Palace Lord.
I’ve finally found it recently.
I was supposed to report to the
Palace Lord but I couldn’t find him.
The Palace Lord is missing?
- I understand. You may leave.
- Yes.
That lunatic.
Besides there,
where else will he be?
Hao Feng.
After lying here for so many years,
it’s time to wake up.
Spring is here.
I’ve planted many peach
blossoms in Lize Palace.
You will be very happy when you
see something familiar when you wake up.
Senior.
You’ve been speaking to a corpse
for more than 20 years.
What’s the point?
Who let you in?
If the disciples find out that
the Palace Lord of Lize Palace
hides a female corpse in the
inner hall, what will they think?
Shut up! Get lost!
Don’t be angry, Senior.
I’m here to give you a good news.
The stalactites in Dianjinggu have grown.
The stalactites
have really grown?
If you can get the stalactites
at the Flower session,
your Hao Feng will be revived.
She will no longer be an ice-cold corpse.
Hao Feng.
You hear that?
I’ve been waiting
so many years for this moment.
Once I kill all those
righteous sects that killed you
and get the stalactites,
we will be reunited.
Hao Feng.
Be patient and wait a few more days.
I will definitely give you a hand.
Give me a hand?
Those are some glorified words.
Don’t think that
I don’t know the underhanded things
that you did behind my back.
You are just trying
to use me and get the spirit key.
Am I right?
Getting straight to the point.
That’s good.
Let’s work together
at Dianjinggu’s Flower Session.
You’ll get your stalactites
while I get my spirit key.
Killing two birds with one stone.
I don’t know what
you are trying to do,
but I’m just trying to save my Hao Feng.
The rest,
I’ll leave it up to you.
Senior.
We are riding on the same boat.
I can’t wait for the Flower Session.
Stinky woman, didn’t you sleep well?
Flying Snake, keep your eyes peeled
once we reach Dianjinggu.
You can’t miss out any demon, understand?