LOVE AND REDEMPTION
EPISODE 54
This is the medical book that I’ve copied.
Take it.
Your cultivation is not that advanced yet.
When you meet stronger demons,
don’t force yourself.
Be careful.
Mister Yi.
I’m already very grateful to
be able to have this memento.
Ever since I first saw him,
I already know that I’m not for him.
I’m just
a half disciple to him and that’s it.
Chu Xuan Ji.
If both of you are married one day,
send me a wedding invitation.
No matter where I am,
I’ll go there and congratulate you.
Okay.
Mister Yi.
Go now.
I hope that everything will
go smoothly for you from now on.
I’ll pray for you here.
Miss Ah Lan.
Take care of yourself.
Greetings, King Bailing.
Guards.
Detain Flying Snake in the Sky Prison.
King Bailing, what did I do wrong? Why
do I have to be detained in Sky Prison?
Look towards your left and right.
God of War has a deep anguish to her that
even 1,000 years can’t mellow it out.
You must have heard about the great
bloodshed that happened here back then.
Now, when I sent the Four
Sacred Beasts to capture her,
you foiled my plan and
chose to stand by her.
What is it?
Are you going to betray the heavens
and let her bring great disaster to
the heavens again just like before?
I did help her out for a little bit.
But I did it for our friendship.
I wasn’t trying to revolt against
the heavens.
Is that so?
You stole the scroll from my palace
and went to the human realm
to give her the information.
You foiled my plan to make her
destroy the Jade Cup.
Does that count as betrayal?
Make God of War destroy the Jade Cup?
Is that strange?
Flying Snake.
Actually, you had already
suspected my identity before this.
But I used the spell of deceit on you.
So, you couldn’t tell.
So, that person is indeed you.
Yes. King Bailing.
Since you’ve already spent 20 years
with her in the human realm,
you should know that she’s kind.
She won’t attack the heavens.
But why can’t you spare her?
She is kind?
Since you’ve read the scroll, you
should know her identity by now.
Her kindness has
a time limit to it.
Her ego and arrogance have never changed.
I tried to help and save her.
But she’s being difficult.
All of my efforts have been wasted.
It’s hard to get rid of
her demonic character and anguish.
She is destined to bring chaos
to the three realms.
Now, she is even tempted
to open the Jade Cup.
If we spare her again, she’ll
eventually come for the heavens!
I did read the scroll before.
But it’s just a broken scroll.
I don’t understand why
the scroll stated that
the God of War is born from
the destruction of Star of Mosha.
I don’t understand why it stated that
God of War and Star of Mosha are the same.
Is the scroll mistaken?
You are asking too many questions.
You just need to know that
no matter it’s the Star of Mosha
or the God of War,
if they are a threat to the heavens,
they’ll have to be destroyed.
As for you, if you
help God of War again,
you’ll meet the same fate too.
Green Dragon.
Yes, King Bailing.
Take him to the Sky Prison.
Chu Xuan Ji.
I know why you are going
to Mount Shaoyang.
Since you want to open the Jade Cup
to destroy the three realms,
don’t blame me for being so unforgiving.
Shaoyang Sect is just right ahead of us.
I think us demons shouldn’t go there.
We don’t want to ruin
other’s birthday party.
Si Feng.
Perform well when you go to
meet your father-in-law
so that he can marry off his daughter
to you without any worries.
Don’t worry, Brother Wu.
I’ll send you a letter
as soon as there’s good news.
Alright. We’ll wait for
your good news here. Go.
Wu Zhi Qi.
Where are you going?
I have something personal to do.
Don’t think that I can’t tell.
You were whispering with Xuan Ji.
You are planning to
open the Jade Cup, right?
So what if I am.
I won’t allow you to go.
Why do you have to let things
get out of hand?
Even if we don’t do anything,
those deities from heavens
will kill us.
When that happen, it’ll really be
out of our hands. Just wait for me here.
Please help me take care of
this little fox.
Something big will happen today.
Find a place to hide.
Wu Zhi Qi!
Senior Xuan Ji, you are back.
He is...
We are here to celebrate
father’s birthday.
Senior, let us go in and inform him first.
One is your senior and the other one
is Shaoyang Sect’s savior.
Why do you have to inform first?
- Ling Long.
- Xuan Ji.
You are finally back.
The party has started.
- I thought you couldn’t make it. Let’s go.
- Si Feng, how are you?
- Senior Ling Long.
- What senior?
Without them both,
Mount Shaoyang would be burnt to dust.
Let’s go.
It’s good that you came back this time.
Now, we have someone to talk to.
But Si Feng doesn’t look too well.
Maybe he’s tired from the long journey.
With your power, you won’t be
this weak even if you fly to the sky.
Did something happen?
Actually, besides celebrating
Father’s birthday this time,
Si Feng is here to ask Father for my hand.
Really?
After going through so much,
this day has finally come.
Don’t be so happy first.
Father hasn’t agreed yet.
He looks strict usually
but he’s actually very soft-hearted.
Just beg him and he’ll agree.
Let’s go.
Si Feng, the last time four of us
climbed this Mount Shaoyang
was a long time ago.
We’ll have to spend
more time together this time.
I’ve been keeping a few jars
of great wine for you.
Later, I’ll use your kitchen
and cook us some drinking dishes.
We’ll drink until we drop.
That’ll be for the best.
Si Feng, you are faltering in your steps.
Is it because of your old wound?
Yes. But I’ll be fine.
Si Feng.
I’m sorry.
Why are you suddenly apologizing to me?
I doubted you before this.
As your friend,
I didn’t believe in you or support you.
But you did so many things
for us in secret.
I’m really guilty about it.
This is a chaotic world.
It’s normal to be cautious.
I would do the same thing too
if I were you.
No need to feel guilty.
Everything is good now, right?
By the way,
I haven’t congratulated you
for your marriage with Ling Long.
She and I are already married,
when is your turn?
Don’t tell me that
you are here this time...
You’ll know about it soon.
Let’s go.
Si Feng, don’t leave anymore
since you are already back.
Si Feng.
Xuan Ji told me about your great news.
I was very lost before this because
I stayed with the demons of Sky Hall.
So, I told Xuan Ji
a lot of bad things about you.
Now,
I want to apologize to you.
You and Min Yan really think alike.
You each apologized to me.
It’s too much.
Alright now.
Everything is in the past now.
Luckily, after going through
so many hiccups, the four of us
are together again.
Luckily, we are still here together.
It’s a happy day today.
Let’s not talk about the past. Let’s go.
Time to greet our birthday boy.
Let’s go.
We hereby wishing you
- abundance of health and prosperity!
- Abundance of health and prosperity!
Thank you, everyone. Cheers.
Father.
Look who’s here.
I’m back.
I wish you good health and prosperity.
Okay.
It’s good that you are back.
I’m very happy.
Happy birthday, Sect Leader Chu.
Isn’t this the new palace lord
of that Lize Palace demon nest,
Hero Yu Si Feng?
Why is he here?
But he helped Shaoyang Sect before.
- And he guarded the Jade Cup for us.
- He’s still a demon.
Our sects kill demons and monsters.
But now, we have a demon here?
Are we going to dine together
with a demon?
The four of you, come with me.
Father, what is the meaning of this?
Si Feng is Shaoyang’s benefactor.
You brought us to this side hall
because of malicious comment.
This doesn’t conform to
Shaoyang’s etiquette.
Although this place is more secluded,
it’s easier for us to talk here.
It’s okay.
It’s tranquil here.
It’s more comfortable for us to talk.
Xuan Ji, you’ve slimmed down.
Since you are back this time, stay.
Your sister and I miss you so much.
Thank you, Father.
But
besides coming back to
wish you, I have a request.
If you agree, I’ll accompany you forever
at Shaoyang.
What is it?
Father, I beg you
to let me and Si Feng get married.
Sect Leader Chu, after so many years,
Xuan Ji and I
are deeply in love with each other.
Please give us
your blessing.
This thing...
This thing is a serious matter.
I have to consider it carefully.
Father, Si Feng risked his life for
Xuan Ji over and over again.
Nobody else in this world
will treat Xuan Ji as well as he did.
Marriage is no child’s play.
How can I just agree to it?
You have prejudice against him.
When Little Six proposed,
you agreed right away.
How can you compare Min Yan to Yu Si Feng?
Xuan Ji, I need
to think about it.
Father.
You still mind that Si Feng
is a demon, right?
It’s okay.
I won’t force you.
But I want to tell you that
in this life, I’ll only marry
Si Feng and no one else.
Xuan Ji.
I know that both of you are very close.
But just now... Just now, you heard
those malicious comments as well.
I know.
Si Feng is a good man.
And Shaoyang is indebted to him.
But in the end,
he’s still a demon.
You are still young. You don’t know that
gossip is a fearful thing.
I’m just afraid that it’ll be
hard on both of you in the future.
Father.
I know a lot of things now.
In this world, we’ll
meet a lot of people.
But only a few are important to us.
The important people
in my heart are you,
Ling Long and Sixth Senior.
As long as you don’t reject us,
it won’t be hard on me and Si Feng.
Sect Leader, your guests
are still waiting to drink with you.
Easier said than done.
Just like cultivation.
And it’s the same in life too.
Get up first, both of you.
We’ll discuss about this later.
Si Feng.
Looks like it’ll be hard for
your father to agree.
Don’t think too much.
I’m sure that he just can’t
accept it for the moment.
- He’ll be fine after some time.
- Yes, Si Feng.
We’ll help you to convince him.
It’s okay, Si Feng.
I’m very clear about what I want.
If my father agrees, I’ll
marry you at Shaoyang.
If he doesn’t agree,
we can get married anywhere in this world.
Si Feng.
Si Feng, did you pull on your old wound?
I’ll get Auntie Ying Hong
to take a look at him now.
No need to do that.
Well...
I know Si Feng’s body well.
He’s just exhausted from the journey.
Go and celebrate Father’s birthday first.
We’ll be fine.
Let’s go then.
We’ll get going then.
Si Feng.
Hold on, Si Feng.
Let me help you suppress the curse.
King Bailing, you want us to open
the Heavenly Meteor Formation
to attack Mount Shaoyang
in the human realm?
Yes.
Heavenly Meteor Formation is a deadly
formation that uses the power of stars.
Every living thing that is inside it will
be annihilated. The hill will be crushed.
Isn’t it a bit excessive to
use it against the humans?
No.
God of War is already at Mount Shaoyang.
She’ll open the Jade Cup soon.
And then, Star of Mosha will be revived
and the three realms will be in chaos.
I’m opening this formation
to stop the God of War.
But this formation is not targeting
God of War alone.
It’s targeting the whole Mount Shaoyang.
To sacrifice millions of lives
to defeat her?
- This is too much.
- Yes.
Isn’t there any other way?
For the past few days, I’ve
been thinking about the solution.
But the Jade Cup and God of War
are not ordinary in the human realm.
Normal ways won’t be able
to hurt them at all.
So, setting up the Heavenly
Meteor Formation is our only choice.
Desperate situation calls for
desperate measure.
To bury the whole Shaoyang
and wrongly kill millions of lives
are better than letting Star of Mosha be
revived and brings ruin to three realms.
Back then, Jade Emperor asked us
to leave God of War alone.
He said that everything is
a preordained fate.
Don’t you think you should discuss this
with the Jade Emperor first?
We are out of time.
God of War is going to open
the Jade Cup soon.
If Jade Emperor wants to
blame someone in the future for it,
I’ll take full responsibility for it.
Please help me set up the formation
to destroy Mount Shaoyang,
seal the Jade Cup and kill Chu Xuan Ji.
Yes, King Bailing.
Why are you here?
Are you here to laugh at me?
- What are you doing?
- Here’s a dragon scale. Keep it well.
The path of heaven is closed now.
To go to human realm,
you have to go through Heaven Fire.
This dragon scale can help you with that.
Why do I have to go down?
King Bailing didn’t punish me, right?
When you reach there,
look for Chu Xuan Ji at once
and ask her to forget about the Jade Cup.
Ask her to leave Mount Shaoyang
at once without a delay.
What is the meaning of this?
Explain it to me.
King Bailing has ordered
Seven Emperors of North Heaven
to initiate Heavenly Meteor Formation.
He’s going to sacrifice Mount Shaoyang
to kill Chu Xuan Ji
and bury the Jade Cup forever.
What did you say?
I heard it myself. It’s true.
Seven Emperors of North Heaven
have already departed.
If you don’t go now,
Chu Xuan Ji will die.
If she dies, you’ll die too.
I can’t watch you die in vain.
Go now.
Green Dragon.
If I can come back here alive,
I’ll treat you to a drink
as an appreciation.
How is it, Little Beauty?
Are we going to start?
Back then, he used his life
to protect the Jade Cup.
But now, I’m going to open it.
Even if he blames me for it,
I still have to do this.
Wu Zhi Qi, later,
I’ll rip a hole through it
and you’ll keep it stable.
Then, I won’t alarm the
protection rock when I take out Jade Cup.
Don’t worry.
Although the divine weapons together with
the 12 Feathers are very powerful,
I’m still powerful enough
to buy you some time.
We got it. Let’s go.
Si Feng!
Why did you do this?
I...
Si Feng.
I saw it.
I saw your lives starting from
the heavens to nine reincarnations.
I saw what you had gone through.
We’ve missed out on so many things.
It’s not easy for us
to meet each other again in this life.
I don’t want to give up yet.
I won’t let you die.
Give me the Jade Cup.
I want to open it.
Sorry, Xuan Ji.
We can’t open this Jade Cup.
And I won’t give it to you.
- Unless you kill me.
- You...
- Si Feng!
- Take care of him. I’ll chase after it.
- Okay.
- Xuan Ji.
- Si Feng.
Can you manage?
Brother Wu, stop her.
Don’t let her open the Jade Cup.
Sect Leader Chu.
- Go ahead and hit that Longevity Drum.
- Go ahead.
Run, mortals of Shaoyang.
King Bailing is going to sacrifice
Mount Shaoyang to seal Jade Cup.
All of you will die if you stay here. Run!
- Xuan Ji.
- Xuan Ji!
Why did you take out the Jade Cup?
Father, I want to save Si Feng.
Xuan Ji, run now.
- Why are you here?
- Forget about me.
Escape with these mortals first.
King Bailing has given his order...
- Flying Snake.
- Run!
Flying Snake!
Bailing.
Are you Bailing?
Where is Flying Snake?
Are you the one who took the Jade Cup?
He came here without permission and leaked
heaven’s secret to you. He’s unforgivable.
As for Jade Cup, why do you want it?
Have you forgotten about your vow?
What vow did I make with you?
I don’t remember you!
Is that so, Xuan Ji?
You promised me that
you’ll destroy Jade Cup
and kill the soul of Star of Mosha.
Do you still remember that you’ll protect
the world no matter the cost?
This voice.
What you said is...
Promise me.
Destroy the Jade Cup.
We can’t let the demon clan win.
Promise me.
You are set on opening the Jade Cup.
You’ve already forgotten
about my teachings.
Today, I’m here to punish you for
bringing chaos to the world
and poisoning the people.
Hao Chen?
- Senior Hao Chen?
- This...
Senior Hao Chen.
Aren’t you already dead?
Why are you here?
Hao Chen
is just the identity I use
when I’m in the human realm.
I’m King Bailing.
- King Bailing.
Bailing?
Senior Hao Chen.
Until now, you still
don’t repent on your sins.
You hate the heavens
for betraying and tricking you.
You’ll always want to seek revenge, right?
Do you think I’ll forgive you?
For the harmony of the three
realms, I can’t keep you here anymore.
You’ll be punished now!
So, you are King Bailing.
Why?
Why did you lie to me?
I lied to you?
I took the form of mortals and descended
to the human realm to guide you myself.
I just hoped that you can get back onto
the right path and come back to heavens.
I did it for you.
I didn’t want you to die young.
But you were so stubborn
to accept my guidance.
You’ve wasted all of my efforts.
In the end, you can’t even
keep your promise to me.
Now, not only you
don’t want to destroy it,
you want to open it and release
Star of Mosha’s soul.
And as Hao Chen, our
relationship as senior and juniors
for so many years
means nothing to you.
What about you?
Is our relationship for
so many years real or fake?
Or is everything just a way
to help me reincarnate?
You used me so that
I feel depressed and guilty
for Senior Hao Chen’s death.
You purposely forced me to attack Si Feng!
You forced me to make a vow
to destroy the Jade Cup
even though I’ll die!
Have you ever cared about me then?
This is your duty.
If you had valued our relationship
and listened to me
to let thing run its course,
it would not come to this today!
So, before this, you had indeed
accused Si Feng wrongly on purpose.
And I felt so sinful for not being
able to fulfill your dying wish.
But in the end, I’m just a pawn.
You still want to argue
so fallaciously and irrationally?
I’m disappointed in you.
I gave you a lot of opportunities.
But you insisted on going against
the heaven’s will.
Today, I’m going to
sacrifice Mount Shaoyang
by initiating this
Heavenly Meteor Formation
to bury you and Jade Cup forever!
What did you say?
- Please have mercy on us.
- Please spare us, King Bailing.
- Spare us.
- Stop! I’m the one who took out Jade Cup.
I’m the one who go against
the heaven’s will! Kill me if you want!
But why are you killing
these innocent people?
Chu Xuan Ji.
You brought this upon yourself.
How dare you ask me that!
As soon as the Jade Cup is opened,
Star of Mosha will be revived.
He’ll destroyed everything.
If you can’t let go of this obsession,
you’ll bring disaster to the three realms!
So, I’ll have to crush this
wild dream of yours to nothing!
Stop! I just want to save someone.
After I save Si Feng,
I’ll just seal him back in.
I’m God of War. If I can catch him once,
I can catch him again!
- Impossible.
- Why?
The Jade Cup is getting
more and more unstable now.
There is no mythological object
that can seal Star of Mosha anymore.
I can only suppress it
with Mount Shaoyang.
Remember.
You are the cause of this calamity.
And these people will
die because of you.
What is it?
This is bad. It’s the heaven’s wrath.
You can’t go.
Are you trying to die?
This is not something you can stop.
But...
If I’m not wrong,
this is Heavenly Meteor Formation.
What formation is that?
That stupid monkey is still inside.
What about him?
Calm down. A small formation will not
be able to trap that stupid monkey.
Didn’t he ask us to take care of you
before he left?
He’ll be fine.
He did say that.
You once taught me to
take care of the people.
But why are you slaughtering
these innocent people?
To keep the peace of three realms,
some sacrifices are unavoidable.
Instead of letting out Star of Mosha
to bring ruins to the world,
I will rather sacrifice Shaoyang
for hundreds and thousands
of years of peace.
By sacrificing themselves today,
the people of Shaoyang
will be blessed in the future.
What a joke!
The high and mighty King Bailing
treats us like a piece of dirt.
Back then, you took care of me
at Xuyang Peak.
No matter what ulterior motives you had,
those memories are precious to me.
Thank you for your care for so many years.
From now on,
our past relationship is no more.
I won’t let you hurt Shaoyang Sect!
Today, I’ll fight to death with you!
Chu Xuan Ji!
Since you insist to side
the demons and go against me,
I’ll finish you off
once and for all today!
Xuan Ji!
Xuan Ji.
Si Feng!
Si Feng. How are you feeling?
How did this happen?
What happened?
This is bad.
The power of the divine weapons
is bursting because of outside impact.
Si Feng is seriously injured.
He can’t contain the power anymore.
No. I have to save Si Feng.
Give me the Jade Cup.
No.
You can’t open the Jade Cup.
- Promise me.
- Si Feng!
You have to open the Jade Cup.
Yuan Lang? You are still alive?
I’m not here to fight with you.
I’m here to tell God of War the truth.
Xuan Ji.
Don’t listen to him.
He’s just here to trick you
to open the seal of Jade Cup.
Don’t listen to him.
God of War.
Do you know why
King Bailing is so unforgiving when
you want to open the Jade Cup?
Finally, you know the truth.
Chu Xuan Ji.
God of War is Star of Mosha.
Star of Mosha is God of War.
I am the Star of Mosha.
Yes. You are the Star of Mosha.
The soul inside Jade Cup is yours.
Goddess of War.
- No.
- Yuan Lang!
Shut up.
In this world, only Star of Mosha
can open the seal of Jade Cup.
No. You are lying to me.
You are lying to me.
- Xuan Ji.
- You are lying to me.
It’s recorded very clearly on the mural
inside Demon Citadel. Or else,
why do you think that Yu Si Feng
will admit that he’s the Star of Mosha?
Xuan Ji, it’s not true.
Don’t believe in him.
He wants to destroy the three realms.
He must have an ulterior motive.
Don’t believe him.
Since young,
every one of you
asked me to kill demons to uphold justice.
But the biggest devil in this world
is me.
Impossible.
- Xuan Ji.
- Impossible.
If you don’t believe me,
go and ask King Bailing.
He tricked Star of Mosha and
extracted his soul from him.
Then, he used the mythological object
made by its bones
to seal his soul inside this Jade Cup.
And his body was transformed
into God of War.
And God of War’s heart
is just a minor piece that King Bailing
took from the Jade Cup.
Demon.
That’s enough!
What he said...
Is what he said true?
It doesn’t matter that you know now.
He is right.
But everything is going to end now.
Since the beginning,
the devil that you want to kill is me.
What a joke.
What is God of War then?
Bailing.
Why did you do it?
For the three realms.
You stopped me from
getting back my six senses.
You wanted me to feel nothing
so that I could become your puppet!
You can’t be corrupted
if you are heartless to begin with.
Only then can the three realms be safe.
But even after nine reincarnations,
your anguish is still here.
And this time, you even gained
a mortal heart because of Yu Si Feng.
I can’t let you turn into a demon again.
Si Feng.
Si Feng!
Yu Si Feng.
I’ll kill you first.
Let’s see if the Jade Cup
will be broken or not.
Si Feng!
Xuan Ji.
Si Feng! I won’t let
anything happen to you.
Xuan Ji.
No!
I rather die than letting you
become a demon because of me!
Si Feng, I don’t care about that.
I just want to save you!
Star of Mosha or God of War.
I don’t care. I just want you to live!
Si Feng.
If I become Rahu Ketu,
don’t forget about me!
You have to find me!
Xuan Ji.
Xuan Ji!
I’m willing to drink with you every day.
I’m sorry.
Rahu Ketu.
I’ll now bestow this life to you.
And for your whole
life, you’ll fight for me
and for the heavens.
Rahu Ketu.
Why did you kill your own people?
Xuan Ji!
Star of Mosha, Rahu Ketu.
Xuan Ji.
Brother Bailing.
Long time no see.
Ketu.
Xuan Ji.
I am Rahu Ketu.
Xuan Ji!
Where are you going?
Xuan Ji.
The life of human is really hilarious.
This belongs to Chu Xuan Ji.
From now on,
she’s no longer related to me.
Where are you going?
I’m going back to where
I belonged in the past.
I’m going to get back everything
that I lost for the past 1,000 years.
Xuan Ji, don’t go.
- Xuan Ji!
You don’t know me anymore?
Xuan Ji.
If you pests keep on
addressing me wrongly without respect,
I don’t mind to wash
this mountain with blood.
Xuan Ji.
Xuan Ji!