[English subtitles are available]
[ACE TROOPS]
[Episode 23]
[Company of Live and Die Together]
Left, right, left.
One, two, three, four.
[Company of Live and Die Together]
Left, right, left.
What’s up, Company Commander?
Looking at them,
it reminds me of the time when you were recruits.
At that time, you were like them,
[Company of Live and Die Together]
knew nothing but youth
and had to fight for everything.
But now?
You are all veterans
who have won honors in war
and have begun to lead recruits.
Jiang Weixing, Niu Mancang.
Yes. Yes.
We have been informed by the political office that
you have been recommended for military academy.
Really?
Company Commander, don’t tease us.
Why am I teasing you?
It’s true.
This is all rather sudden.
I don’t know what to say.
Then don’t say anything.
Report.
I…
I’m…
I will live up to the expectations of the Party and the people,
and will study hard
to become a revolutionary, young,
professional, knowledgeable,
moral and talented leader of soldiers.
Report to
Company Commander.
There is a cadre in our Niu’s family.
As I said,
I don’t want to talk about the brothers.
It’s hard to mention.
But I can’t help it.
I have to mention it.
Keep in mind that
[Company of Live and Die Together]
how our Company came to be
and what you all went through.
Live and die together.
You go to school for
the comrades of the whole Company.
[Company of Live and Die Together]
Left, right, left.
One, two, three, four.
[Company of Live and Die Together]
Thanks to Gao Liang,
I got a place in the exam.
He signed up for me
and had been busy all the time.
He kept encouraging me
before I entered the examination room.
What’s wrong with you?
It was supposed to be my boyfriend’s job,
and now he’s taken it.
You just say “hmm”.
I’ve been taking part in the Hero Model report Group,
and I don’t have time.
So, you’re not worried that
he’s being so nice to me, huh?
Okay.
Tell you the truth.
There are two main reasons
for this matter.
The first reason
is his warm heart.
The second reason
is that I asked him to help.
I learned the admissions policy from my dad in detail
and asked him to tell you.
No wonder.
No wonder he said to keep it a secret.
He just wants to show off for a few more days.
Why do you boys always do this?
Always says things in a roundabout way.
Nanzheng.
I feel sorry that
I can’t stay with you all the time.
So,
I asked Gao Liang for help.
Although he seems to be
cheeky all day long.
But every time I turn around,
he is standing in place,
being my powerful backing,
which is quite reassuring.
Especially after returning from the war,
I found that he suddenly grew up.
Unlike me,
I’m losing myself.
Don't worry.
It will get better gradually.
The person I like, Gu Yiye,
can do things that others cannot do.
Of course, he will also encounter troubles
that others cannot encounter.
But he’ll figure it out
and get out of the haze.
I grew up
without any good friends,
and never envied anyone.
But some time ago, I was thinking,
if Gu Yiye
is always so tired,
then I shouldn’t be Gu Yiye.
Wouldn't it be nice to
become Gao Liang?
Yiye,
you and Gao Liang are completely different people.
Gao Liang,
just like my family.
He’s a close and dear comrade of mine.
I remember when I was on the front line
and saw him coming back from the dead,
I cried.
At that moment, I was thinking that
I would never let him feel lonely again.
Have you told him about these words?
If he heard these,
he would be moved to tears.
He loves to cry.
That’s it.
A man of his age,
a man of his size,
crying all the time,
is like a baby.
Nanzheng,
your kindness
will hit all men’s hearts.
Then I’ll try to be
a family of him.
But only if
he accepts me.
In fact, he has always regarded you
as the motivation to struggle.
He always wants to catch up with you
and surpass you.
Sometimes,
I kinda appreciate his silly energy.
It shows me the hope of a man.
Your comments
make me feel
a sense of urgency.
Gu Yiye will also have a sense of urgency.
Isn’t that good?
Race, learn, catch up, help, and surpass.
Only in this way can we have the motivation to move forward.
But it’s his rhythm.
Also, a rhythm that
most people accept and are familiar with.
But not mine.
What rhythm?
In battle,
the most important thing is rhythm.
99% of people
just need to follow.
But someone
has to step up
and find his rhythm
in the noise.
It will be hard to be a different person
from others, right?
I’m not doing well.
Really.
No.
You have done well.
Yiye.
I can understand you.
I know you didn’t mean to neglect me.
You were busy settling down
the affairs of Platoon Leader Zhang’s family.
Your heart
is slowly pulling back from the battlefield.
You are trying.
I can feel it.
Nanzheng,
I feel like I owe you a lot.
I like that you owe me.
Owe me for life.
Then I will never forgive myself.
Don’t say unforgivable things.
Yiye,
I think
you should relax.
We are all people who have come back from the battlefield
through hardships.
How nice it is
to be able to
sit next to each other intactly and talk.
Han Chunyu.
Be brave!
Is it Jiang Nanzheng?
No.
This is Han Chunyu.
Hey, Sergeant Han.
By the way,
congratulations on your admission to the military academy.
I’d like to congratulate you
on your bailout to the army academy.
I made a special inquiry.
Our schools are
close to each other.
On weekends,
we can hang out together.
Really?
Sure.
Gao Liang.
I mean,
we are going to be promoted into cadres.
In fact,
there are many things
that would not violate the discipline.
What would be a violation of discipline?
I mean,
we could
hang out,
watch a movie or something.
No problem.
Then let’s invite a few more people
and go to the movies together.
Our company is having the celebration party,
so, I have to get over there.
I… wait a minute.
We’ll talk tomorrow at the train station.
- I want to tell you that we can…
- Hello?
Excuse me, is Comrade Han Chunyu there?
It’s me.
Who is that?
Do you remember
when I asked you a question
at the front camp
and you gave me a hug
instead of an answer?
Sergeant Han,
is there an unbreakable radio?
Platoon Leader Xia.
Later,
I read the interview with you on the military newspaper.
In order to send back the information in time,
your platoon paid a terrible price.
You finally crossed the minefield.
You were the only one who came back,
along with
the blown-up radio.
I didn’t expect
you to read the report.
After I came back from the front,
my heart couldn’t come back for a long time.
Therefore,
I often read the military newspaper or something
and learned from various channels
what we had experienced.
Comrade Han Chunyu,
you know what?
What that hug of yours
meant to me.
I should hug
every comrade who came back from the front.
They are all my brothers,
and so are you.
Thank you.
Comrade Han Chunyu.
I’m here today
to tell you something important,
and to hear your opinion.
Deputy Company Commander Xia,
if there is anything you need, just tell me.
As long as I can help,
I will do my best.
You will go to
the military academy tomorrow
and become a cadre.
So, I won’t keep you from your progress.
I wonder
if our relationship
can go further
on the basis of comrades-in-arms.
Comrade Han Chunyu.
I like you.
Deputy Company Commander Xia.
Call me Xia Lin.
It’s more natural this way.
What you said is
a bit sudden.
I have a poor cultural foundation.
After arriving at the military academy,
I have many classes to make up.
So, I don’t want to
focus on this issue
for the time being.
Comrade Han Chunyu,
I understand your thoughts.
It’s okay.
I won’t bother you too much.
A relationship is a lifetime event.
It’s not easy to meet someone
who makes your heart flutter.
You
are the girl who makes me flipped.
I don’t want to miss it.
Comrade Xia Lin,
I think
the relationship is a matter of two people.
We are not suitable.
Please forgive my frankness.
We haven’t even started yet.
Why isn’t it suitable?
Because…
Because I have a crush.
What?
I’m gonna go back.
Comrade Han Chunyu.
[Zhangmu Station]
The Department of Organization at the Political Science Academy, do you know that?
Report.
I’m going to…
Put things on.
They’re all there.
Diarrhea again?
Oh, come on.
The female soldiers are coming.
I’ve put your book up for you.
What are you doing, Jiang Weixing?
Orange flavored soda.
Sweet?
Yeah.
[Zhangmu Station]
Look at you.
You are really a veteran of love, playing hard-to-get!
Handsome?
[Zhangmu Station]
What are you doing?
Come on, I’ll do it, I’ll do it.
Give it to me. Give it to me
I’ll do it.
I got it.
Well, here you are.
Give it to him.
Hang everything on the mule.
Take care of these things and don’t lose them.
Great.
[Zhangmu Station]
Great. Let’s applaud.
Commander Qin is here.
I know.
Commander Zhao.
It’s been two years.
I’m gonna miss you so much.
Before parting,
give me a hug.
That’s even worse.
So handsome, Company Commander.
Good job, Company Commander.
Company Commander.
You can also be handsome.
Yeah, right.
[Zhangmu Station]
What are you doing?
Is this handsome?
Handsome, right?
Yiye, Gu Yiye, your letter.
It’s from eastern Guangdong.
Commissar asked me to bring it to you
in case of delay.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
Check it out.
Letter!
You can’t even open a letter.
Hello, Comrade Gu.
I’m Zhang Yuanshan, Party Secretary of the village.
Ever since you left,
the village has been praising
the army for its kindness.
We miss you. They miss you.
I shouldn’t have written this letter to you,
but something happened to Zhang Fei’s family.
Shortly after you left,
Zhang’s mom fell ill.
She was devastated by her son’s sacrifice,
and she was too sick to get up.
The village doctor said
she wouldn’t last a few days.
Xiu is reluctant to trouble the troops again.
She’s not willing to write to the army
for help in any case.
The village tried everything,
but there was nothing we could do.
I am writing this letter to you rashly
to ask if you can contact the hospital
to treat Mother Zhang and help Xiu
through your troops.
The 533 train to Gaozhuang
is about to leave.
Passengers who have not yet boarded…
What should we do? The train is leaving.
The train is about to leave.
Qin, take it.
Yiye.
Gu, this is mine and Tong Bing’s.
Yiye,
Xiu is familiar with you.
If you go to help,
she may accept it.
You should go to eastern Guangdong right away.
The problem is how to get there so far away.
It will take a week to get there and back.
If you are late for registration,
you will be punished.
So,
Gu Yiye, you should go there now.
When Gao Liang arrives,
explain the situation to the team leader,
and I will call the academy to explain it.
What are you waiting for? Are you going or not?
If you don’t go, then give me the letter and I’ll go.
Just one.
Yiye goes.
Yiye, don’t hesitate.
This is the time to stand up.
Comrade PLA, the train is about to leave.
[Zhangmu Station]
Nanzheng, you don’t know that
Platoon Leader Zhang and Xiu had a child,
only a few months old.
What’s more, you don’t know that
villagers and I climbed over the mountains to the hospital
[Eastern Guangdong Province, Zhang Fei’s hometown.]
carrying the critically ill Mother Zhang.
She was saved at last.
But the gratitude that came out of Xiu’s eyes
[Emergency Room]
made me feel
deeply guilty.
Comrade nurse, how’s Mother Zhang?
You brought her to the rescue just in time.
Comrade, help him to have a seat.
Are you okay?
He carried my mother for 35 kilometers
and was tired.
I’ll be fine after a little rest.
Don’t worry.
She is in a stable condition. Don’t worry.
Hello,
Comrade Gu, Comrade Gu.
Come here.
Comrade Gu, you can’t do this.
My mom said to me as soon as she woke up,
we can’t let you spend any more money.
Xiu,
I was entrusted by my comrades before I came here,
so, I must take good care of Mother Zhang.
We are a family,
so don’t treat me like a stranger.
I don’t treat you like a stranger,
but you can’t pay the money.
Xiu,
I know you don’t want to show weakness and bother us,
but if you don’t let us
do something,
we will feel guilty.
Comrade Gu.
You can’t do that.
Then you pay for it.
But we agreed that
I borrowed the money from you,
and I will pay it back in the future.
Okay.
Comrade Gu.
Please return to the army after you pay the fee.
I know the army is strictly controlled,
so don’t come again.
Help me thank the leaders of the army
and Fei boy's comrades.
Thank you all.
Thank you.
Nanzheng, do you know that
before Platoon Leader died,
he told the story of Cao Yuhai,
a special hero in the War to resist US aggression and aid Korea.
Before he sacrificed,
his last wish was to let his fiancée forget him,
find a lover
and start all over again.
Platoon Leader even regretted that
[Dean’s Office]
he shouldn’t have married Xiu.
But the sick old woman and the weak mother and child in front of me
are Platoon Leader’s
- only connection with the world.
- Comrade Gu.
Don’t worry.
Relevant government departments have specially instructed us
to bear all the medical expenses of
Mother Zhang.
[Ward]
Fei boy.
The doctor said there’s something wrong with our mom’s heart.
I’m…
I’m just a little scared that
our mom’s
gonna die all of a sudden.
I’m scared that
our child is so young.
I don’t know what to do.
Fei boy.
Tell me.
[Silence]
What should I do?
Nanzheng,
you may never know,
at this moment
my heart is torn to pain.
You have not been to Xiu’s home
and do not know what situation Xiu is facing.
Here,
kindness and generosity
cannot solve the problem.
Good people must make sacrifices.
Good things must have a price.
And I
am the price.
[The Army Academy of PLA]
Left, right, left.
[Go through hardships, be thoroughly tempered. The Fifth Unit of Trainees.]
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Li Shaobing.
Nicknamed Fried Pancakes Lee.
I am a veteran scout
and your tutor.
From today onwards,
your days of suffering will come.
Hide your military medals
from me,
and from yourselves.
That’s history.
If a soldier is weak, only one person is weak.
If the general is weak, the whole army will be weak.
[The Fifth Unit of Trainees.]
The scouts
are the elite part of the army.
You will become
Platoon Leaders and Company Commanders in the future.
If you can’t be an elite,
how can you expect the soldiers you lead
to become elite soldiers?
When you walk out of here in the future,
you must be reborn
and become an ace!
Report.
Trainee Xia Lin reports for duty.
Why late?
Tutor,
This trainee’s situation is special.
He just finished participating in the military district’s
scouting professional tournament last month
and won three championships.
Recommended by Vice Army Commander Wang of Army A.
So, he was exceptionally admitted to the college.
As it was an exceptional admission,
the procedures took some time.
Fall me down.
Chief.
Fall me down!
Yes, Chief.
From the first day you stepped into this academy,
you are no longer soldiers of the Army A,
nor the top soldiers of some military district.
You are the future of the Chinese army.
You
have two options.
First one,
kicked down by me.
Second one,
kick me down
and then walk over me.
Step out of this academy gate.
Understand?
Yes.
[The Army Academy of PLA]
Nanzheng,
on the train back to the academy from eastern Guangdong,
I thought a lot.
The childish eyes of Platoon Leader Zhang’s child,
Mother Zhang lying in the hospital bed,
and the lonely figure of Xiu at the end of the corridor
made me make a decision.
That means living with Xiu,
raising the child for Sergeant,
and taking care of his mother for him.
You are my beloved girl.
I know what this decision
[Bloody Deeds]
means to you.
Forgive me,
at this moment,
I don’t have the courage to face you.
Mule Gu,
where have you been?
I didn’t go anywhere.
I’m taking classes in the trainee team.
Stop talking nonsense.
I had been looking for you several times, but I didn’t see you.
You are a quasi-officer of scouting.
If I don’t want to see you,
[Bloody Hero]
there’s always a way.
Why don’t you want to see me?
Nothing.
I think you are annoying.
Is that okay?
Screw you.
I think you are annoying.
Do you think I want to talk to you?
Well,
how about Xiu?
Sergeant’s mother,
is she in good health?
What else can we do?
Mother Zhang has been hospitalized
with coronary heart disease and other complications.
By the way,
I gave all the money you donated
to Xiu,
expressing wishes for you.
Xiu is alone,
it’s even more difficult,
and she can’t make it any longer.
Aren’t you going to say anything?
If not, then I’m leaving.
Wait, wait. What’s your hurry?
It’s not easy to see you.
Can't you give me some time to be sad for a while?
It's hard for me to hear your words.
I said I didn't want to see you.
You bring it up every time we meet.
What’s the point of being sad?
Let me ask you. What’s the point of being sad?
Who wouldn’t be sad to hear that?
What happened after the sadness?
There will be
no less days to live
and no less housework to do.
She is a woman
with such a weak body.
She remembers Platoon Leader in her heart,
and takes care of the elderly mother.
Serve the elderly, raise pigs, and cook
without saying a word.
She could only cry in secret.
She gave herself up
to take care of the family.
She doesn’t want to
cause any trouble for us
the so-called comrades-in-arms.
What’s the use of our comrades?
What’s the use of the comrades?
Come on, why are you mad at me?
I’m working on the solution.
Come on, come on.
Alright, stop it.
What’s the hurry?
It’s no use worrying.
I mean,
you can see what Xiu needs.
We have lots of comrades there to help, don’t we?
We can think of something.
Stop being hypocritical.
Our concerns mean nothing for her.
I’m begging you here.
Don’t mention it again, okay?
Who’s being hypocritical?
Okay, I won’t mention it.
Then what about Jiang Nanzheng?
How long has the school opened?
She’s gone mad looking for you everyday.
You know that?
You don’t answer her phone,
and you don’t write back. What are you trying to pull off?
Shouldn’t you reply her
by now?
Gao Liang,
go ahead and get her.
Are you nuts?
What are you talking about?
You are totally insane.
Who’s insane here, Gao Liang?
I’m not insane.
It’s you who is insane.
Jiang Nanzheng
is my girlfriend.
You are the one who always fusses around her.
Okay,
go ahead and get her.
You jerk!
What else can you do
except for wasting food?
Dad, why are you here?
Buttons.
And the first one.
Contributing teaching,
and giving you lessons.
[Duty Room]
Hello, brother.
I just came back from training.
[Tutors]
Gao Liang, stop!
It’s none of my business what you did
in Division 234 before.
But now you’re in Army Academy, being a trainee.
And I’m your tutor.
I’m responsible for your behaviors.
Whatever the reason is,
don’t be a jerk!
Remember,
the capabilities of a scout
should not be shown off,
especially in public.
Behave yourself.
Your comrades
have been staying there.
Do you know why you have bigger issues
than others
after the battle?
It’s not because you’re weaker than others.
Instead, you’re more sensitive than others.
99% of the soldiers
in the army
will have their weakness and sensitivity
being worn away and become strong.
But some of them
may need their sensitivity and tenderness.
In other words,
they may be the tentacles and brains
of the army.
Dad,
you may not understand the feeling
when somebody took the bullet
for you
with her own body.
He was lying on your back.
It felt warm.
You would never forget the heat,
and the weight
all your life.
I can never forgive myself.
I understand.
Hurry up!
Are you being funny here?
If you don’t want to die soon
and die miserable
in the future battlefields,
be crueller to yourselves!
From now on,
whoever stand before you
are your enemies.
If you don’t kill them,
they will.
Harder!
Much harder!
Much harder to yourselves!
You, out!
Brother,
the path from a soldier to an officer
is not smooth at all.
There are thousands of difficulties and obstacles,
and narrow escapes.
But they mean nothing
to me.
The most important thing is that
I’ve made up my mind
to stay away from Jiang Nanzheng.
I will not date her anymore.
And...
The situation of Platoon Leader Zhang’s family
is not good.
I can sense
the internal changes of Gu Yiye.
It’s just like a mushroom cloud.
We have no idea
what’s waiting for us.
Jiang Nanzheng,
I’m a petrel,
the unstoppable petrel!
Nanzheng.
Yiye.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
This is for you.
It’s beautiful.
Thanks!
I’ll take it.
Have you made remittance for Xiu?
I had been delayed
by the long queue there.
Sorry.
That’s okay.
Right,
has Mother Zhang been discharged?
Don’t worry. I’ve taken care of it.
How come you don’t wear the red dress?
You promised to wear it for me, didn’t you?
I was not in the mood
thinking of what happened on Platoon Leader Zhang’s family.
I will definitely wear it next time.
Let’s go. The movie is about to start.
It’s a ten-minute walk from here.
Let’s go.
What about not going to the movie?
Why?
It’s your favorite movie.
I finally managed to buy the tickets.
I’d rather listen to you,
listen to you talking about the school,
and talking about Platoon Leader Zhang.
I don’t have to report to duty
two hours after the movie.
We can talk about them on our way back.
There’s still time.
Do you know that
this may probably be the first time,
as well as the last time for us watching movies together?
How come?
Just kidding.
Come on. The first five minutes of the movie are important.
We would get lost if missing them.
Let’s go.
[Pursue virtue practically, serve the country firmly, harden the youth strongly, and sublimate selves continuously.]
One, two, three, four!
[Strive for dreams in our youth and devote ourselves to national defenses.]
[Go through hardships, be thoroughly tempered. The Fifth Unit of Trainees.]
Gao Liang, someone wants you on the phone.
Coming.
Hello.
Sergeant Han.
What’s the matter?
[Be accurate, be online.]
Next month,
there will be a friendly basketball match
between Communication Academy and Army Academy.
I know.
That’s for boys, right?
What are you worrying about?
Our girls are cheerleading.
And I’m the cheerleader.
We will meet
if you take part in the match.
We’re selecting the players.
It’s Xia Lin’s choice. He’s the leader.
Xia Lin?
Is he the Deputy Company Commander Xia
from Division Reconnaissance Company?
Yeah, he’s now our tutor.
Such a coincidence, right?
What a coincidence!
Have you received the letter?
What letter?
The letter I wrote to you.
I post it yesterday.
You should receive it tomorrow.
Why bother to write letters
when we can talk on the phone?
I’m afraid to talk to you in person.
You’re joking about it.
Read the letter first,
and then we’ll talk.
Alright.
I’ll tell you upon receiving it.
[Be accurate, be online.]
I got to go.
Bye.
Thanks.
Liu, have the letters arrived yet?
Yeah.
They are for your First Unit.
Okay, thanks.
[Xia Lin]
[Gao Liang]
Gao Liang, your letter!
Here.
- Thanks.
- You’re welcome.
Emergency muster!
Hurry up!
Muster! Muster! Hurry up!
Time to muster!
Go, Communication Team!
Defense!
[Communication Academy, Army Academy]
Score!
Come on!
Mule!
Come on, Gu Yiye!
Go, Communication Team!
[Basketball Match: Communication Academy vs. Army Academy]
Nice!
Which side are you on?
I’ve never seen
traitors like you!
Which side are you on?
We were winning. One last shot away.
Let’s go.
Are you tired?
Not at all.
Hurry. Eat it. Or it’ll be melted.
I was suddenly struck by the boy
who finally bought an ice cream,
but it accidentally
fell on the ground.
I remember when I was in the Ninth Company,
I was once injured
and had a fever.
You bought me a whole carton of ice cream,
nearly frozen me to death.
You were so handsome when playing basketball just now.
Did you hear us cheering for you?
Why were you ignoring me?
I’ve been writing to you
and calling you recently,
but you didn’t rely me at all.
Gu Yiye,
are you trying to break up with me?