[English subtitles are available]
[Oh My Lord]
[Episode 4]
Have you heard that?
Yes, I have.
-It's true. -Yes, she came, too.
You must be Lord Bai's lovely wife.
You look no different from the painting.
Greetings, ladies.
Lovely wife?
She married a eunuch.
A nominal couple, that's all.
You are so humorous.
For small families,
even a nominal couple can enjoy dinner together.
Different from you
who came from extended and luxurious families,
I guess you have to line up
for dinner with your husband.
Marrying a eunuch,
why do you feel smug?
Precisely.
Right.
For you, a poor hoyden,
you have married up.
Actually, I am already satisfied
with the life that my Lord provides me
since I am fed and clothed.
Madam,
your clothes
must be last year's model.
Look at this.
My Lord customized it lately.
It took half a month to be made and delivered.
My Lord said
pink matched me the most.
As Eunuch Mastering the Seal waiting for castellan,
he didn't perform his duty
but used castellan's power
for private gain.
And you actually took it as glory.
Madam.
Exactly.
You'd better think twice.
My lord has always been diligent
and dutiful.
He dare neither seek private gains
nor neglect any order of castellan.
Please pick your words with care.
Madam.
My Lord.
You're here.
Come on.
By the way, these ladies are struck
on the clothes you customized for me.
How about recommending the dressmaker to them?
Sure, Madam.
Look at yourself.
You miss me so much only after a short while.
So annoying.
See you.
Look how smug she is.
Why are you in a rush?
I haven't finished my acting.
Sit here still.
Don't run around anymore.
Please.
Let me drink a toast to you.
[Guanyu Palace]
This wine tastes good.
It's been a long time since I drank such good wine.
You look quite well.
Your Excellency,
I heard that Lord Bai is a master of swordplay.
Why not ask him to perform
a sword dance of Fuxian City with imperial bodyguards
to cheer us up?
Great. Great.
Bai Li, go perform with them.
Yes.
It's rare to see a eunuch perform sword dances.
One always wants to prove what he lacks.
Lord Bai just lacks manliness, doesn't he?
That's true.
-Look! Look! -Look at Lord Bai.
Are my eyes playing tricks on me?
A eunuch has an Adam's Apple.
It must be the most weird thing in the world.
I heard that a few days ago, an assassin intruded into House of Respectful Affairs,
so Lord Bai didn't finish his examination.
Now he even has an Adam's Apple.
We cannot but
make a connection between these.
Why don't we
seize the day and check him?
Yes.
Bai Li, what's wrong with that?
It's rare.
So weird.
It is really weird.
Yes.
Your Excellency,
that is not an Adam's Apple. Instead, it's a kind of laryngeal disease.
His Lord has been serving you all year long
and suffers from it due to excessive exhaustion.
It's not an Adam's Apple
but a sign of his loyalty.
The reason why his Lord always keeps reticent
is that he doesn't want to bother you with trifles.
Your Excellency, she's talking nonsense.
How can there be such a disease?
I've never heard of that.
That's easy. Imperial physician.
Your Excellency,
there is indeed a disease like that.
That's good.
Stop talking about that.
Continue the banquet.
Luckily, I've journeyed north and south with Chen Pingzhi
and have seen lots of weird diseases.
Oh no, the apple is coming again.
[Moon Pavilion]
Mrs. Zhao,
is that really okay?
You are still a little girl.
You won't understand even if I explain.
It's easy for a girl to pursue a man.
With the help of ambergris and me,
Lord Bai and Madam Bai
will surely become reconciled.
Miss is here.
Lord Bai.
Madam.
It's so late now. You must be hungry.
I specially prepared sweet soup for you.
Miss.
Madam, drink the soup while it's hot.
Or it would not taste that good.
Soup?
Drink it
and you will be reconciled with Lord Bai.
I don't want to be reconciled with him.
He has such a short fuse.
I dare not offend him.
Drink it, Madam.
It's delicious.
What happened?
It's so hot tonight.
General Gu?
Miss Chen.
I'm sorry.
Acting under his Lord's order,
I am going to send you away.
[Wind Booth]
Chen Youyou.
What should I do with you?
Who's there?
[Wind Booth]
My lord.
Mrs. Zhao,
why are you furtively hiding yourself here?
Madam Bai and you had some issues
so I was going to lend a hand.
I used
that drug.
Where is Chen Youyou?
Isn't Madam Bai inside?
Gu Tianhe! It's terrible!
As everything is all right,
why did Wu tell me a ghost story?
Who's there disguising as a ghost?
You...
you don't come over.
Youyou?
Help me!
Where is she?
She was in the carriage just now.
Look for her separately.
My lord,
what's done is done.
Why don't we seize the opportunity
and let her leave Bai's Mansion
to avoid following troubles?
When do I need
you to decide for me?
You said
you didn't want her to stay around, didn't you?
Never return
if you can't find her back.
My lord.
My Lord.
Do I misread him again?
Youyou.
You're awake.
Where am I?
This is the secret base for my snack research.
I didn't expect to invite you here in this way.
By the way, Youyou,
at a late night,
why are you in the wild alone?
Do you know how dangerous it is?
I...
was kicked out.
What?
How can Bai Li be like this?
How can he ignore your safety?
Yes.
I risked myself to get him out of a fix
but he still kicked me out.
I'm pissed off.
Why
do I lose my breath?
Youyou,
why is your face so red?
Could it be that sweet soup?
Are you allergic?
Don't come over.
I...
I still have something to do. I have to go.
Youyou.
Let's go home.
Why do you come to me?
You drove me away, didn't you?
Let go!
Let her go.
She doesn't want to go with you.
Let go.
It's you who should let go.
She is my wife.
Your Royal Highness, please behave yourself.
Let go!
Let go of me!
[Drug]
Go.
Put me down!
You put me down!
[Inn with Luck]
Don’t move.
So where are you going to abandon me?
I'll take you
home.
It's you who drove me away.
You...
Why did you come to me?
Put me down!
[Drug]
I want to go down.
Come on.
This way.
Let me go.
[Drug]
Chen Youyou.
Stop joking.
Am I joking?
You sent me away, didn't you?
You asked Gu Tianhe to hit my head
and it still hurts now.
It's so dangerous for me to fall off the carriage.
I almost died.
It's hot.
Get up.
Come on.
Don't be afraid.
My lord, your heart is beating wildly.
And mine too!
Be careful of fire
as it is dry.
[Drug]
Lord...Lord Qiansui.
I, I didn't see anything.
Go.
[Drug]
Let go of me!
Let go of me! Let go.
Why hasn't the epiphyllum blossomed yet?
Qingshu, stay calm.
Chen Youyou has just riled lord, hasn't she?
Why are they so intimate now?
Put me down!
My Lady,
stay calm.
My lord.
How is Chen Youyou?
The imperial physician said
Miss Chen was okay.
Anything else?
And Miss Chen said...
she wouldn't blame me.
Anything else?
What else should there be?
Didn't she mention
anything about me?
No.
What things concerned you
should she mention?
Go.
Where should I go, my Lord?
What do you think?
Accept punishment at the same place.
Miss Chen.
Why are you here?
Mrs. Zhao is still watching outside.
I don’t want to drink her sweet soup again.
Is that drug's effect off?
Don't worry.
I won't do anything to you.
If I offend you again,
I might be murdered in the wild.
Do you feel better?
It hit me that I caught a cold.
I should not infect you.
I'll sleep outside.
Why doesn't he stop me?
I...I'll take the quilt.
What are you doing?
It's cold in the wood shed.
And you haven't recovered yet.
Stay here.
It's okay for me to stay.
But we should set three rules.
I allowed you to stay but you made a requirement again.
Then forget it.
Say it.
First,
no more threats.
OK.
Second,
no more expelling.
OK.
Third,
no more tantrums.
OK.
My lord.
For tonight,
you sleep here,
and I sleep there.
Forget it if you don't agree.
Anyway, I have been used to sleeping on a small bed...
OK.
Good night.
Don't think I will forgive you so easily.
[Wind Booth]
My lord,
Mrs. Zhao was in a hurry
to pack up and leave Bai's Mansion
in the early morning.
I asked her to leave.
Your Highness.
[Wind Booth]
Youyou,
Mrs. Zhao didn't behave herself.
She put you at risk last night.
So I've asked her to retire.
From now on,
if anyone dares to bully you,
I will surely teach him a lesson.
Does his Highness know
why Mrs. Zhao came to work in Bai's Mansion?
So he knew
it was I who invited Mrs. Zhao here.
I don’t care
your housework at all.
But Youyou is my friend.
I won't allow anyone to hurt her.
It's a misunderstanding. A misunderstanding.
Youyou.
I am devising a new snack
but I met some difficulties.
i hope you can teach me.
OK.
Chen Youyou,
you haven't recovered yet.
You should not run about.
I, I'm fine now.
Well,
have you cleaned the front yard?
In conflict with his Highness,
you're trying to vent your anger on me?
I've already cleaned it up.
Go. Let's go to the Bamboo House.
Chen Youyou.
[Wind Booth]
Yesterday you said you were moving to the wing-room, didn't you?
Now that Mrs. Zhao has left,
why don’t you move?
I knew it.
Tiao.
Take all my stuff
to the wing-room now.
Yes.
Let's go.
You welshed on your promise.
You were as cruel as a wolf.
You quit love with hate.
-You put on sanctified airs. -You...
Youyou,
is he always harsh on you?
Yes!
Yes.
Anyway, stay away from him.
Whoever gets close to him will be unlucky.
If you don't want to see him later,
you can stay here.
OK.
Youyou.
Youyou...Youyou.
Would you like
a bigger hammer?
Sorry.
I somehow forgot myself.
Please don't mind it.
It doesn't matter.
If you feel bad,
just vent your anger.
With me,
you can just be yourself.
Thank you.
Beat you. Beat you.
By the way,
there are a lot of ingredients in the forest.
How about
picking some fresh vegetables and fruits?
Sure.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Are you tired?
Sit down there and have a rest.
OK.
Slow down.
You too.
Youyou.
I've heard a joke.
Once upon a time, there was an earthworm.
It went out for a walk.
While it was walking,
it crashed into a crab.
A crab?
The earthworm was mad and questioned the crab,
"Are you blind?"
But the crab felt innocent,
"I am not blind.
I'm a crab."
It's not funny at all.
Smell it.
Can you smell a faint scent
from this ginger?
This kind of wild ginger
is hard to pick.
But it tastes fresh and crispy.
It is a good ingredient.
Besides, it’s said that it can cure cold and headache.
So it should be that domain lotus in the poem.
Poem?
Domain lotus?
It is read that
Yan Emperor carried this edition forward and thought it precious.
After a harsh time, he got domain lotus and was able to survive.
Even Shen Nung suffered hardships to get it
and continued his life with it.
It's so precious.
Thanks to you,
I have the chance to see it.
Your Highness, you're so erudite.
You know so much things.
You must have read a lot.
Unlike me,
I am almost illiterate.
But your horizon is still broader than mine.
Youyou.
The world is vast.
Every thing you know
and every journey you had
is what you've read.
It's my first time to have received such praise.
That is a fact.
It is a pity that they don't have a good taste.
You're right.
Let's continue the picking.
OK.
By the way,
we can try to
use this wild ginger in the snack.
There might be a special flavor.
[Bai's Mansion]
He really allowed Tiao to pack my stuff up.
Why didn't he stop Tiao?
Youyou.
Miss Jiang.
I've heard what happened
last night.
I didn’t expect Mrs. Zhao
to have played such a trick.
And General Gu
actually left you alone
in the wild.
For an ordinary girl,
she might have lost her chastity.
No need to worry about me, Miss Jiang.
I didn't meet any accident.
But Miss Jiang,
you should not behave like those yentas
and backbite me.
Come on.
Have some green tea
to reduce your internal heat.
I almost forgot it.
This is
the nutritious soup I specially cooked for you.
I used
precious herbs that his Lord gave me before.
After all this,
you should take good care of yourself.
Now that his Lord gave these herbs to you,
you should nourish yourself with them.
I still have a lot.
Don't worry for me.
On the contrary,
you are new in the mansion
and have no idea about his Lord's personality.
It’s common for you
to annoy him.
Miss,
you should be more careful.
But
if anything similar happens again,
you can come to me.
After all, I've known his Lord for years.
Somehow,
I weigh with him.
Indeed.
You weigh some weight.
My father used to be an official of Fuxian City
but was set up by villains.
The Jiang family then came down
and I got lost.
Thanks to his Lord's help,
I was survived.
His Lord is considerate
and takes good care of me.
Of course I know his regard.
It is a pity that
there is
an unbridgeable gap
between him and me.
A gap?
I see.
This gap
must be that He.
He and his Lord...they two...
Youyou, you misunderstood it.
Gu Tianhe is nothing but a guard.
I’ve lived with his Lord in Bai's Mansion for years.
I know him better than you do.
His Lord once
arranged a blind date for Gu Tianhe last year.
But General Gu was so stubborn
that the girl felt wronged and left.
General Gu does look like
a stubborn man.