[English subtitles are available]
Zeng Li!
Look who's here!
Zeng Li.
Do you still remember me?
I remember that in high school,
you were the top scorer for
science subjects in our area.
My mother wouldn't stop praising you.
That was two years ago.
It seems I need to work hard
to update my results.
Zeng Li,
your uncle finally
came home during holiday
and even agreed to tutor you.
Make sure you learn properly.
Just call me Yu Yi.
I'm only older than Zeng Li by four years.
I found something
really exciting.
In the next monthly exam,
you can score full marks.
You must be joking.
Look at all these wrong answers.
I can't even do geometry questions well.
Actually,
between you and a math genius,
the difference is just an auxiliary line.
Look here.
Give it a try.
That's right.
Hey.
How many times have I told you?
Can you wring the mop dry first
before wiping the floor?
Look at how wet the floor has become.
If you don't like the way I do it,
why don't you do it then?
Did I tell you to do it?
Can you lower your voice?
Don't you think it's embarrassing?
Who's embarrassing who?
Who's embarrassed?
Every day,
other than opening your mouth
to eat and complain,
you neither earn money
nor help with chores.
All you do is grumble day and night.
What do you want?
What do you think you're saying?
What am I saying?
You're useless! What are you saying?
It's over between us!
Wreck it!
Sure!
Let's get a divorce!
Don't keep bringing
this up!
Get a divorce!
Do it for real if you want!
Xiao Yu'er.
My name is Xiao Yu.
So your name shall be
Xiao Yu'er from now on.
What do you think?
Okay.
Actually, no matter how difficult life is,
it's still easier than math questions.
What do you think?
I'll help you.
Later, I'll bring you
to have KFC,
okay?
Don't you have to go home for dinner?
I'm an adult.
An adult can have a meal outside
without his or her parents' permission.
That's great.
I also want to be an adult.
You will be soon enough.
Just focus
on studying for college entrance exam,
and before you know it,
you'll turn into an adult.
Do you think I can enrol
in Donghu University?
Of course.
Trust me,
as well as yourself.
I'm here for you.
If I successfully enrol in the university,
you will have graduated by then.
Then I'll continue with
postgraduate studies.
That way, I can look out for you,
okay?
Okay.
Let me tell you.
Around our university,
there're all kinds of delicious food.
KFC is nothing.
Do you agree?
When the time comes,
I'll bring you to try out
each of the restaurants.
Okay. I'll do my best.
Good girl.
When you grow up and leave home,
you'll be independent.
However, by then you'll realise,
actually, it's good to have
your parents around you.
[Sweet Teeth]
[Episode 13]
Zeng Li,
look, all the followers
are really curious about Xiao Yu.
Why don't you just
write another book about him?
I'd better finish the tasks at hand first.
I kind of regret
not visiting the aquarium.
I remember the aquarium in Yancheng
is the largest in Asia.
Why do I feel like I've heard
several largest aquariums
in Asia?
Have you?
Shouldn't you regret
not washing your hair last night?
No.
When you haven't washed
your hair for two days,
you'll begin to wonder even more
how it will be like on the third day.
Do you mean
tonight you're going to challenge
not washing your hair for four days?
Do you want to sniff it?
Dear!
Why did you come to pick me up?
I'm so happy.
Didn't you say you're busy?
It was a lie.
We hadn't seen each other for six months.
How could I not come to pick you up?
Dear, the long-distance flight
must be very tiring, right?
Your hair smells as nice as always.
A couple's public display of affection.
Is no one going to do anything about it?
I know it's torturous,
but I couldn't help
staring at them.
[The meeting was dismissed ahead of time.]
[Ai Jing Chu]
[I'll pick you up at the airport.]
Your boyfriend is going to
surprise you by showing up?
What? No, this won't do.
No, I can't meet him.
Why?
I didn't wash my hair.
-Zeng Li.
-Come over.
Slow down.
Where is he?
Pick up the call.
Answer it.
Hello, Mr. Ai.
Hello, Zeng Li.
Where are you?
You didn't reply to me on WeChat.
I don't see you here.
I just arrived.
I'm not at the airport.
You aren't?
Where are you then?
I'll look for you.
I boarded the vehicle.
No, I mean, I'm in a train.
He's in the airport.
Mr. Ai, we missed out on each other.
What should we do?
So, the train station is here.
It's awkward.
Mr. Ai.
What a coincidence.
You're something.
Lugging such a huge suitcase around,
you managed to avoid me
and even ran so quickly.
It's because I didn't wash my hair.
I mean
how could I meet you in this state?
Was that why you're avoiding me?
[Yes.]
[Not only that, I also
didn't wash my face.]
What a slob.
You must be Zeng Li's colleague.
Hi, I'm Ai Jing Chu.
Hi.
I'm an editor at Huaxi Publishing Company.
I...
We're doing a book exchange.
Why don't I
give you a ride home?
To be honest,
I've had enough
of public display of
affection for the day.
I need to digest it.
I'll get going. Bye.
Take care.
Let's go.
Zeng Li.
How tall are you?
I'm 1.67 metres.
I'm 1.87 metres.
Are you trying to show off your height?
No, what I want to say is
if I stand at this angle
and look at your head,
it's really oily.
Don't follow me.
Slow down.
Stop running
or you're going to fall!
Oh right.
I don't think I've ever
heard you mentioning
your father.
Are you offended?
You don't have to tell
if you don't feel like telling me.
It's nothing.
It's just that my parents
divorced
when I was in high school.
Since I chose to be with my other,
my father minds that a lot.
Later, he remarried
and they had my brother.
However, he's still the same,
doing nothing at home,
expecting others to do the work instead.
His current wife
is not as fierce as my mother.
So it's still okay.
What's wrong?
Why are you suddenly
asking about my family?
Nothing.
I just wanted
to try to know you better.
Tell me.
If Zeng Li saw
this message from Yu Yi,
will she be overjoyed?
It's highly possible.
Zeng Li, wake up.
Look,
whose message is this from?
He said he's back.
Where is he back?
We saw it
half an hour ago.
Out of respect for the parties involved,
[Yu Yi]
-we waited so long for you.
[Xiao Yu'er,]
[I'm back.]
[Zeng Li,]
[I'm Yu Yi.]
[Long time no see.]
[I'm back]
[and I'm probably not going
back to the U.S.]
So, he came back to China
and plans to stay for good.
How long has it been since
you two met each other?
Four and a half years.
You remember it so clearly.
You haven't met each other for so long.
I wonder if Yu Yi
is still as handsome
as he was
when he was in university.
I think you two shouldn't meet.
Many online relationships end when
two people decide to meet up.
In your memory,
he's still the teenager.
When you meet each
other, you might realise
he's gone bald for years.
No way.
We've been keeping in touch.
Besides, a few months ago, his parents
visited him in in the U.S.
They sent me photos.
What's interesting is that
a few months ago, Zeng Li
still mentioned Yu Yi often,
yet she suddenly stopped
mentioning him in recent months.
Why?
I wonder why.
Medical Assistance to African Nations
plans announcement.
Check out the details below.
Our dental centre hospital
will send a doctor
and a nurse.
That means it'll be the both of us.
Why are you asking me along?
Are you thinking about abandoning me?
Why do you
think so highly of yourself?
Why does it have to be you?
Look.
Mr. Ai is
our mainstay.
Professor Wang is old
and had a bypass surgery not long ago.
The only people left are the interns.
We can't send them, right?
If we do the calculation,
we're the only ones left.
You're right.
I know, right?
In that case, go ahead
and contribute to China-African relations.
No, wait.
Aren't you joining me?
Hi.
Who are you looking for?
I'm looking for Dr. Ai Jing Chu.
His office is in that direction, right?
Wait a second,
why are you barging in?
Wait!
-Will you go with me?
-Wait!
Don't go in!
Dr. Ai,
do you have a moment?
Zeng Li,
be honest.
You haven't been dating anyone.
Are you waiting for Yu Yi?
Are you?
I tell others that's not the truth.
I tell myself that, too.
Actually, I'm waiting
for a person whom I really like,
instead of a specific person.
A colleague once
introduced someone to me.
When I saw the photo,
I realised he resembled Yu Yi,
especially
when he smiled.
Usually I won't go
on this kind of date.
In the end, I still went.
What happened next?
At the beginning,
the chat went quite well.
His personality also resembled Yu Yi's.
He's good at chatting
and finding topics of conversation.
Once the conversation got deeper,
he suddenly told me to resign,
saying
young people should engage
in more exciting jobs.
That's when I realised
he wasn't Yu Yi.
Yu Yi is bolder
and able to consider things from
the other person's perspective.
No matter how mundane it is,
in his eyes
it's always interesting.
Therefore,
I came to my senses at that moment
and realise
I couldn't lie to myself.
The person I'm waiting for
is Yu Yi.
Now you've finally gotten your wish.
He came back from the U.S.
and plans to stay for good.
Dr. Ai,
this person is unreasonable.
He barged in after asking where you were.
I already told him you're
getting off from work soon,
yet he still insisted on going in.
What's wrong with you?
This... You're even lying down.
Dr. Ai, he...
Open your mouth.
All done.
Fourth-degree caries.
The four teeth inside
are basically rotten.
There's no other way
except extraction.
Seriously?
Don't scare me.
Once you lie on the hospital bed,
you have to listen to me.
You...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, okay? I'm sorry.
All right, that's enough.
However,
you do have slight caries.
Make an appointment
and I'll sort it out for you.
Sure.
Do you two know each other?
We've been friends
for eight years.
If you two have nothing else to do,
you can get off from work.
Let's go.
Not bad, Dr. Ai.
The entire corridor
is full of your photos.
However,
the photos were badly taken.
You look a decade older in the photos.
That's good.
It's more convincing that way.
Didn't you say
you'd look for me tomorrow?
It's a surprise.
You asked me to bring you
some books on dentistry.
I brought everything I could.
These will keep you reading
for a few days.
This...
There're so many books.
How did you bring these back?
No need to be so touched.
I know you read very quickly.
That's why
I brought you enough this time.
I'm a good friend, right?
In the past, when I
walked by shop windows
and see beautiful clothes,
I'd think,
once Yu Yi came back,
I'd
wear the beautiful dress
to meet him.
I even fantasised
that when he came back,
how I should
greet him
or casually
switch the topic
to whether he had a girlfriend.
However, for an unknown reason,
when Yu Yi texted me on WeChat,
I realised
that recently,
I hadn't been thinking about this a lot.
That means
you
are in love with Dr. Ai.
Of course you have no time
to think about Yu Yi anymore.
Not necessarily.
In this world,
do you know what is the thing
that people think about the most?
What a person can't get
or what that gets away.
For example, a rabbit
doesn't have a carrot.
All it has is a cabbage.
It'll think cabbage is tasty.
However, if a carrot is hanging
right in front of you
and you can reach it
by taking two steps forward,
of course you'll jump
to reach the carrot.
Can you resist it?
What if you finally
eat the carrot,
and realise the cabbage
is more to your taste?
You have to eat it
before you know how it tastes.
When you two put it this way,
I realise I'm becoming
more pretentious.
Yu Yi and Mr. Ai
are
outstanding people.
What gives me the right
to choose between them
as if they're vegetables,
right?
You two
are my best friends.
That's why you're making it so dramatic.
Look.
[The Story of Xiao Yu and Xiao Yu'er]
If Dr. Ai
sees this novel,
what will he think?
Dr. Ai doesn't know
this novel
is based on a true story.
I'm actually looking forward
to Yu Yi's thoughts
when he sees this novel.
The two of them
will never read this
kind of romance novel.
Don't be so sure.
Isn't it going to be
the book's signing event soon?
What if it becomes a bestseller?
No,
I don't want to be popular.
From now on, this novel
will
disappear
in our cafe.
That's right.
The Story of Xiao Yu and Xiao Yu'er.
Third chapter.
Where's the third chapter?
Let's see
if there's any content
that isn't suitable for kids.
Let me see.
No, there isn't!
[I didn't expect Yu Yi to come back]
[so suddenly.]
[How should I face him?]
[Also, what does he think of me?]
[My head hurts.]
Eat slowly.
Nobody is going to snatch it from you.
It's so delicious.
Judging by what you just said,
you mean
your return to China
is equal to demotion and
salary reduction in a way?
It's more or less the same.
The remuneration is indeed
not as good as back in the U.S.
However, over here,
I can look after my family,
right?
The boy is all grown up.
Come on.
After all, we're going
to turn 30 years old soon.
Don't include me in this case.
I'm two years younger than you.
Not if you round up the numbers.
Don't mind this.
How is it, Mr. Ai?
Do you have a girlfriend?
You know what?
I'm into a girl now.
Really?
Before this, I didn't tell you,
because I was considering
whether I should come
back to China or not.
Therefore, I also didn't dare
to think about that.
I didn't want to waste her time either.
Now that you've come back,
you can focus
on this matter.
I'm not sure whether
she has a boyfriend.
Here's what I'm thinking.
I plan to treat her to a meal,
but I haven't met her for so long.
I'll need someone to
liven up the atmosphere
and that's you.
Me?
It's strange lately.
People keep asking me to be their wingman.
Dr. Ai,
who taught you
this Internet slang?
Here, have a chicken wing,
your favourite.
Sure.
Back in the U.S.,
when I ate roast chicken
with Zhang and the rest,
they'd fight with me over chicken wings.
It's good to eat with you.
You like to eat drumsticks
and my favourite is chicken wings.
Oh right.
I have yet to tell you
about something.
Nowadays,
I like to eat chicken wings, too.
Really?
You can have it.
I'm joking.
Eat it.
You scared me.
I almost cut ties with you.
Come on.
Come on, it's a bonus for heartbreak.
Happy breakup to us.
Come on, let me see your face.
She even scratched
your face with her nails?
That's not it.
She just slapped me.
Your face bled from a slap?
Yes.
That's the part
I must learn the lesson.
Next time,
I have to see whether the girl
does manicure
and whether her nails
are gem-studded.
Besides,
she's the one who wanted a breakup.
Why was I
slapped instead?
I don't believe in you.
If you did nothing wrong,
would she have slapped you?
So, she wanted to break up with you.
What did you tell her?
I said okay.
Come on, let me see your face.
Look.
Poor fellow.
Let me blow it.
I'll slap you, too.
You deserve it.
[Outpatient Building]
200 joules, twice.
Again, 360 joules this time.
Dr. Wu.
Haven't you gotten off from work?
Didn't I tell you not to come anymore?
You seem be unwell recently.
I made you
chrysanthemum and
Japanese honeysuckle tea.
I don't need it.
Go back.
What's wrong?
Are you in a bad mood?
Let's play games together.
Level up by two stars will do.
What about three stars?
Just now, when a patient
arrived at the hospital,
he was still breathing,
but he passed away
while I was treating him.
Sorry.
I don't know what I should
do to make you feel better.
You shouldn't apologise to me.
It's just that
we might be in different worlds.
When it comes to true love,
it exists,
but at the same time, it doesn't.
When two people date,
it's fine as long as they're happy.
When two people are dating,
it's fine as long as they're happy!
Deng Hao Ran's latest quote!
Ma Yi Yi, record it!
Can you keep your voice down?
Look,
Zeng Li and Wu Ying
met the right kind of men.
Why didn't I?
Tell me.
I promise I won't hit you today.
Do you want to hear the truth?
How many relationships have you
been in for the past the three years?
Sheng Ming.
Zhang Teng.
What does it have to do with you?
There're good and bad people.
They're incompatible with you.
Besides,
each time you're dating,
it's not because you like the person.
You do it because you're lonely.
In other words,
you get into relationships
just to have a relationship.
It'll either end up like
you and Zhang Teng,
he realised it sooner than you did
that you're not suitable for each other.
So he broke up with you.
It may even end up like
you and Sheng Ming.
You didn't even know him,
yet you thought so highly of him
and leapt right into the relationship.
Don't cry.
Who's crying?
I'm not criticising you.
I just think
you should stay if you're happy together.
If not, you should end it amicably.
There's no point keeping it going.
Are you
including yourself?
It's different for us.
In recent years,
we've been dating others.
In fact, you're just looking for one
who can keep you company
and tolerate your ways,
right?
I'm actually really anxious right now.
In my prime,
if I don't get to meet the one
with whom I can spend the rest of my life,
when I become older,
will I end up a spinster?
That's why
before you delve into a relationship,
you have to think
if you like the person
and whether you're
suitable for each other.
Do you just want
a person to keep you company?
I know you're unhappy,
but if you need my company,
I'll be here by your side.
I'll be quiet
and not say a single word.
Liu Yu Cheng,
you don't need
to revolve your life around me.
Both of us
have our own things to do.
I'm very happy to be keeping you company.
You're only 21 years old.
You should enjoy
your university life
and the best age
in your life.
Whether it's taking part
in club activities,
gaming with your friends,
having a meal with someone,
going on a date, watching a movie
or being in a relationship,
it's still better than spending time
in the emergency department all day.
It'll bring more value than this, right?
You don't have to worry about me.
I do time management every day.
Keeping you company is
what I have to do daily.
It's also what I wish to do.
It's time for me to return
to the lifestyle of my age.
Write papers, get qualifications,
do consultations,
accompany my parents,
as well as
marrying a person.
Do you think
I can't marry you?
Is that why you're ignoring me?
I may be young,
but I'm really
a responsible person.
If you're willing,
I can marry you anytime.
What you're saying is very childish.
You haven't even reached
the legal age to marry.
Who knows whether
you'll stay in China
or return to Malaysia?
Since the beginning, the both of us
have nothing in common.
Blending into each other's life forcibly
will only make everything worse.
I've gone back
to my usual pace.
You should go back, too.
Wu Ying.
Please don't say that.
I have no idea
why you're suddenly saying this.
However, I think what you're wrong.
Right now,
I don't know how to counter your argument.
Give me some time
and I'll let you know
all these aren't issues.
No,
I'll prove to you with my actions
that we can be together.
[Break Room]
Wu Ying,
your mother is here to visit your father.
She's worried it'll interrupt your work.
So she didn't come to you.
If you aren't busy,
do you want to drop by?
I'll go over now.
Your mother is also here.
Go back.
You really don't have to come anymore.
Do you want to go upstairs together?
Maybe later.
Your bottle.
I gave it to Wu Ying.
The nurses from their department say
you bring her lunch every day.
She doesn't want to eat it, I think.
Why are you wasting your time
on her?
What's your relationship with Wu Ying?
We're friends now.
It's been three months since I was
transferred to Donghu University Hospital.
To be frank,
we'll be more than friends.
I can tell
that she has no feelings for you at all.
Only a young man
of your age
will think of feelings
as the only requirement
for a relationship.
What else?
Only when two people have
feelings for each other
that they can be together, right?
In a relationship,
feelings are only a small part of it.
First of all,
you're six years younger than her.
Do you think this is just
a number?
That means you lack
six years' worth of social
experiences, compared to her.
Don't you understand?
Let me put it this way.
A woman her age
is mostly in a stable relationship,
being financially stable
and having
a few branded bags.
Can you give her any of these?
You can't.
You bring her food everyday
and sweet-talk her every day.
That will work for a little girl,
but you aren't able to provide
a sense of security to
a woman who is mature.
Wu Ying and you
aren't suitable for each other.
[Chapter Five. A Girl's First Love]
[Tutored by Xiao Yu,]
[in the exam by end of the term,]
[Xiao Yu'er made it to
the top ten in class.]
[She became one of the top students,]
[but her parents' marriage]
[didn't go so well.]
[After fighting for over a decade,]
[the couple finally separated.]
[When they're dividing
the family's properties,]
[relatives from both sides were present.]
[They seemed to be the judges,]
[but they were in fact like audiences,]
[as well as actors and actresses]
[in a cheesy soap opera.]
Let me ask you.
You want a divorce, right?
Why do you get
to own the shares and savings?
I even gave you the house.
Shouldn't these be mine?
The house?
The house was
given to me by my company.
I paid for the renovation
and our family savings
was from my earnings in stock market.
Do you think asking people for favours,
as well as tips,
and trading in shares
don't require money?
Asking for tips?
How did you ask for tips?
Don't think that I don't know that!
Zeng Jian Guo,
what are you trying to say?
You dress up and go out every day.
What have you done outside?
You've done shameless things.
Are you going to pretend?
Nonsense!
You're always so distrustful.
Tell me!
How much money have
you earned over the years?
I'm the breadwinner.
I'm the breadwinner,
Our daughter will live with me.
What's wrong?
Zeng Li is a child of the Zeng family.
In the future, when you remarry
and get her a stepfather,
what is she going to do?
Ask Zeng Jian Guo.
Other than giving his daughter
a surname,
what else has he given her?
What do you mean I didn't raise her?
Why did you push her?
Xiao Yu.
Come on.
I don't want to go home.
It's late.
Your parents will be worried.
Are you afraid?
If you're afraid, hold my hand
or my sleeve.
[Yu Yi]
[What about this Saturday?]
[I'll make a reservation.]
[Okay.]
[Zeng Li]
[Xu Heng Heng]
[Mr. Ai,]
[I booked a private chef.]
[7 p.m. this Saturday.]
[Do you have plans this Saturday night?]
[Ai Jing Chu: Do you have
plans this Saturday?]
[I'm going to meet
a friend this Saturday.]
[Zeng Li]
[I'm going to meet
a relative this Saturday.]
[Ai Jing Chu]
[Okay, it's fine.]
Can you change the time?
She's busy this Saturday.
No way.
I begged the female restaurant manager
for so long
to get this
slot on Saturday.
If you cancel it right now,
who knows when
there will be a slot available again.
Please cancel it for me.
Thank you.
[The Story of Xiao Yu and Xiao Yu'er]
[Chapter Five. A Girl's First Love]
[Who would own the belongings?]
[It was stated clearly one by one.]
[When they're talking about Xiao Yu'er,]
[her mother immediately said...]
Our daughter will live with me.
You're divorced. If you
get her a stepfather,
what is she going to do?
Other than giving his daughter
a surname,
what else has he given her?
What do you mean I didn't raise her?
You people.
Have you ever considered
her feelings,
even if it's just a little?
Let's go.
[Holding Xiao Yu'er's hand in his,]
[Xiao Yu brought her away quickly]
[from everything that's causing
her embarrassment.]
[Xiao Yu'er didn't know]
[where they're going,]
[but she felt at ease.]
[She thought]
[she's very fortunate.]
[Xiao Yu stood out]
[among other boys of the same
age in terms of studies.]
[He is mature]
[and he knows her well.]
Why did you stop walking?
Are you afraid?
If you're afraid,
you can hold my hand
or my sleeve.
[He knows her fear,]
[her embarrassment]
[and her anxiety.]
You are the star of night,
I see you in the dark
Have you ever dreamed about me before
[Just like a ray of sunshine,]
[he lit up her entire world.]
Two hearts beating close while
hiding under the starry sky
[Funeral]
Slowly growing familiar with
the courage in your whisper
It's fine, I'll keep you company.
[From then on,]
Whenever I can't go on
Let's go.
[She'll no longer call Xiao Yu]
["uncle".]
I wish I could hear the words
for you and you wanna talk
You once stopped by when I'm lost
[Yu Yi]
Xiao Chu,]
[I asked her to dinner
this Saturday evening.]
[Why don't you join us?]
The right encounter makes
waiting not that long
Okay.
[Ai Jing Chu]
I know that you're
the feeling I know I miss you
I know your everything
All the stories about
her childhood are real.
What about this person?
Your eyes
Is he also real?
And your light
shining turns me into...