=Please Don't Spoil Me=
=Episode 20=
Is this the eunuch from the Cold Palace?
Where's Little Six?
Little Six is not feeling well today.
I'll be replacing him for a day.
Replacing him for a day?
Why am I not notified of this?
You're making our work very difficult.
This is a little gift for you.
I hope you can accept it.
Go ahead.
Let them go!
Thank you.
Go on.
I look pretty good!
Sugar figurine!
Sir, how much is your sugar figurine?
It's 10 pennies for a stick.
If you can complete poems with me,
then you can take these for free.
People in the Capital are weird.
This is a sure way to lose money.
Brother Qian.
The stall owner wants to
meet new friends through poetry.
He's a man of culture.
He's not like you
who thinks everything in terms of money.
Brother Wen Chang, you should try it.
Yes.
You should try it!
Come on. Show us what you got!
Please.
Then, do allow me to try it.
A bridge of moonlight spans
across a thousand miles.
I'll say "as the plants show a thousand
miles of green during the autumn."
What a great poem!
I have another one.
I'm wondering if you can
complete this poem too.
The clouds appear beneath
the morning sun every day.
Sir, listen carefully.
It's the clouds appear beneath
the morning sun every day,
but they will just come and go
as the day goes by.
He's not wrong!
He wrote, just like the tide that rises
and disappears.
He's not wrong at all.
Have a look.
(The clouds come and go, just like
the tide that rises and disappears.)
This is great! Just like I said,
you'll surely rank top
in the upcoming Imperial Examination.
Right!
Brother Qian, I'm flattered.
Brother,
you're able to decipher
the meaning of my poem.
This proves your poetry skills
are at least on par with mine.
Ah, no way this is true.
I'm Xu Wen Chang. Nice to meet you.
And I'm Yue Chuan.
Brother Yue, greetings.
Wait a minute.
Xu Wen Chang?
You're that Xu Wen Chang?
(Xu Wen Cheng,)
(a great scholar.)
(He's the kind of child
every parent wants to have.)
Brother Yue, do you know me?
Of course I do!
You will rank first
in the upcoming Imperial Examination!
It's my honor to meet you.
Brother Yue, I'm flattered.
Although I want to be ranked first,
the Imperial Examination
has yet to start.
You've surely congratulated me
too early.
Believe me.
You'll rank top in
the upcoming Imperial Examination.
Brother Yue is really confident
about my abilities.
Of course!
(You're the best scholar)
(in my novel. The smartest one.)
(I'm really happy to meet him here.)
(I can't miss this opportunity.)
Oh right, have you guys had your meal?
How about
we find a place to chat and eat?
(Zui Xiao Restaurant)
Brother Yue, let me introduce you
to Zhou Ren, or Brother Zhou.
Nice to meet you.
And this is Qian Si Xian,
or Brother Qian.
These two are my classmates.
We're here
for the Imperial Examination.
To be honest,
I've studied for 15 years
for the sole purpose
of passing the Imperial Examination
to serve His Majesty
and this country.
Although there are many great scholars
who are attending
the upcoming Imperial Examination,
I'm confident about my abilities.
I am determined to get the top rank.
How inspiring! Let's have another drink!
Cheers!
It's released!
The first poem of today is
the Song of Wei Town by Wang Wei.
Share it with me.
The Song of Wei Town?
♪Listen to the sound of tides♪
♪They are saying I do♪
♪The setting sun is listening
to your whispers♪
♪I have told you too many of my secrets♪
♪I am being too sweet♪
♪The whole galaxy is shining for you♪