Our Secret
EP12
Anyway, I feel happy
to stay with Ziqi, Shadi,
and you.
It's really great.
You're nice, too.
Well.
Now that your direction is clear,
let's start
with a small goal.
Let's work together!
OK.
Hello.
Xianxian, come back quickly!
There's something wrong.
I don't know
if your grandmother can make it through this time.
I have to go back to take care of her.
Congcong is still young.
I can't leave him alone.
Are you gonna be okay on your own?
Yes, I'm OK.
Mom, don't worry.
Grandma will be OK.
Your father
teaches senior three and has to live in school.
You need to take care of yourself.
Don't be distracted by these things.
School will begin soon.
Remember to study hard.
Understand?
I got it.
By the way,
your living expenses...
At the table.
I will remember to take it.
I should eat fruit every day.
I need to text and call you.
If I have anything, I can call Auntie Li.
I remember it all.
Jinyun
I have to thank you.
You're welcome.
Her grandma's health is very important.
Don't worry.
We will take good care of Xianxian.
Auntie, don't worry.
Then I'll go.
Here you are, Xianxian.
Here.
Time is limited,
so I didn't prepare anything.
Eat some wonton first.
Xianxian, how about
I tell your mother that
you live here
during this period.
Siyue,
what's your opinion?
This
depends on her own idea.
It's okay, aunt.
I can take care of myself.
All right.
If you have something,
you can come to me.
Don't be shy.
Remember to come here to eat.
It will be more lively with more people.
Thank you, aunt.
You two take your time.
I'll go out to buy some fruit.
Eat it.
Don't forget your wallet again.
Got it.
I can't eat so much.
You can eat more.
What if
my grandma...
Don't talk nonsense.
The best thing you should do now
is to take good care of yourself.
Don't let your mother worry about you.
When your grandmother is recovered,
you will go to see her
happily and healthily.
That's good.
Don't worry.
Your grandma will be all right.
Eat quickly.
Aunt,
I'll go back first.
Xianxian
Why don't you stay for a while?
I'm leaving, aunt.
I've been at your house all day.
It's too much trouble for you.
Then you should be more careful when you live alone.
Tell me if you have anything.
Siyue, you go to walk Xianxian home.
-Okay.  -No, no, no.
It's close.
I can go back by myself.
All right.
Then be careful on the road.
Don't worry, aunt.
OK.
I'm leaving. Goodbye, aunt.
See you later.
Be careful.
If my parents allow you to come to my home,
it will be great.
It is OK.
It's the same with you calling me at night.
Aren't you afraid at home alone?
And in case...
Don't say it.
I thought it's okay,
but when you say it...
Shadi
Don't talk.
Get out of here!
Someone at home!
It's me!
You hit me pretty hard.
You...
Why are you...
Before your mother left,
she left a spare key in my house.
I knocked on the door for so long. Why don't you answer?
I'm afraid.
I thought it was...
It's okay.
The security guard just
caught a thief downstairs.
A thief?
Look at the door.
It's marked by someone.
Hello.
She's all right.
She's next to me.
You can go home first.
Who?
Song Ziqi
Kong Shadi told him
that something happened to you.
They're both on their way here.
It's too scary.
Isn't that too much trouble for you?
It doesn't matter.
Don't say that.
Then thank you for taking care of Xianxian.
As soon as I finish my businesses,
I'll be right back.
Let's keep in touch.
Goodbye.
Here you are.
Aunt,
I'll trouble you for a while.
You are
always so sensible.
It's great that you're okay.
I'm still a little scared.
I told you to move in.
By the way, Siyue,
you help Xianxian pack up
and move in as soon as possible.
It doesn't matter.
I can pack the luggage myself.
Fortunately, Xianxian is okay.
It's a false alarm.
I told you.
They live so close.
If anything happens to her,
Siyue is sure to rush over at the first time.
But I'm worried about her.
You think everyone is as heartless as you.
Fortunately, Siyue is very considerate.
If something happened to me,
will you come?
You speak with your conscience.
I've been with you every time you have an accident
since you were young.
It seems to be that.
Remember something good about me, okay?
You do more bad things than good things.
How can I remember?
Well, let's go.
Where to go?
Anyway, we're hanging out.
You don't want to go home so early, do you?
There is a restaurant ahead.
I'll treat you to dinner.
Come on. I'll treat you.
I can't believe that you invite me to dinner.
Did I hear you right?
What's wrong?
For the sake of
helping me a lot,
I'll give you a reward today. Let's go!
Thank you, Little Princess.
Today my mother told me that
grandma looks much better.
The doctor said
she can leave the ICU soon.
And...
I'm moving to
Zhou Siyue's home tomorrow.
Is this
God's arrangement?
Suddenly
this summer
comes to an end.
Good morning.
Have you packed up?
You just take one suitcase with you?
We live so close.
If I forget something, I can come back and get it.
Where to go?
Go shopping.
This is good.
This is OK, too.
Get some juice.
Get some instant noodles.
We need to buy some shampoo.
Wait a minute.
Do I look like I need shampoo
to prevent hair loss?
I don't need it.
I have a lot of hair.
I'm not afraid.
I don't know which one you like.
We can buy a few and have a try.
Let's take the most common one.
We need to buy bath lotion, too.
I have.
I can take it.
OK.
You're quite diligent and thrifty.
You are too extravagant and wasteful.
I'll lead the way.
Give it to me.
I'll take it.
Lead the way.
Let's head for the stationery area.
Here is stationery area.
What do you want to buy?
Take a look.
This is so cute.
Childish.
It's fancy.
It's expensive but difficult to use.
When did you see me use it?
This is amazing.
Are you a child?
My little brother doesn't even use this.
What does your brother know?
Come on, come on.
One for each person.
OK.
Make up for your missing childhood.
Come on, come on.
What else?
Ding Xian
Zhou Siyue
Keke
Why are you two
together?
This is my new friend.
OK. You're the boss.
Why are you two together?
I...
Why can't we be together?
Don't talk about this.
I heard you play billiards very well.
Find a chance to play.
Can you ask something useful?
What are you two doing?
Don't interrupt when girls talk.
What's going on with you two?
Nothing.
Tell me the truth.
We...
You and Zhou Siyue live together, right?
No.
You didn't tell me such a big thing.
I knew it from Keke.
It's not what you think.
I just stay at his house for a few days.
Can I come in?
Auntie, come in please.
Xianxian, I bring you a new towel.
How's the room?
Time is limited.
I just arrange it briefly.
Tell me if you need anything else.
No, I don't need.
I'm happy to see you.
You're clever and sensible.
I wanted a daughter
like you a long time ago.
I forget to collect these photos.
This is a picture of Siyue when he was a child.
Auntie, is this in Keshan?
Yes, it is in your hometown.
This is Siyue's first visit to Keshan.
Unfortunately, there was a flood.
His grandfather sent him to your house.
After coming back, he cried all day
and said he would never go to Keshan again.
The flood probably frightened him.
This one is interesting.
This is a picture of Siyue wearing a dress as a child.
This photo...
Mom
Why do you take out this photo again?
Why are you here?
I'm chatting with Xianxian.
If he bothers you in the future,
you can tell me.
I'll help you teach him a lesson.
OK.
But he's nice.
Take a shower later and then go to bed.
Siyue, help Xianxian tidy up.
Thank you, aunt.
In this photo,
your look is very unique.
My mom always liked to
dress me up during that time.
Who remembers things as a child?
Take a bath and sleep.
Ding Xian
Hey, hey, hey.
Hello.
You still say like this.
He even asks you to take a bath.
It's not what you think.
Come on.
You are not allowed to be absent
at the girls' group meeting tomorrow. Bye.
Why don't you lock the door?
Go on.
Where is the hair dryer?
Mom
The hair dryer is
in the cupboard under the sink.
Look for it carefully.
Ding Xian
We're going to be late.
Still asleep.
The second set of national broadcast gymnastics for middle school students,
the Time Is Calling.
Get ready.
Zhou Siyue, are you crazy?
Hurry up.
Why do you ride your bike today?
You're too slow.
I don't want to be late.
I didn't beg you to wait for me.
If you are in a hurry, you can go first.
I spoil you too much.
If you don't want to be late,
you can beg me to give you a ride.
I don't need.
Lazy bug.
Childish.
Good morning, Shadi.
Good morning.
I've seen this.
How about living next door to Prince Charming?
Put those two words away.
He...
He's simply not in his right mind.
You don't appreciate the happy life you enjoy .
You have to tell me everything today.
Living under the same roof
is really not what you think.
Imagine that
you and Song Ziqi
meet every day.
Are you happy?
By the way,
I lived with him for a while
when I was a small kid.
Tell me the story.
I tell you.
Song Ziqi always loved to run away from home
when he was young.
At that time,
the relationship between our two families was good.
He always loved coming to live with me.
He slept on the floor in my room.
He snores,
grinds his teeth and farts
when he sleeps.
This is not the most tiresome thing.
Do you know what it is?
What?
Every time
I got up from a nap,
he was lying on the bed
and I was lying on the ground.
How could he do that?
It seems
I'm still quite comfortable.
Thank you.
And then?
You didn't
say anything else at night?
About what?
I'm so tired.
It's boring.
Boring?
Think about it.
Isn't this Full House?
There is a long way to go.
Stop watching so many idol dramas.
Instead, I think
the closer the distance is,
the easier it is to be disillusioned.
You get it.
It seems that you lived with others.
You...
Then you say.
I don't know how to say it.
Anyway,
I'm quite happy.
A fickle woman!
Childe,
how's it going?
You and Ding Xian live in the same room.
You're talking nonsense.
In the same room?
Am I wrong?
Anyway, Little Monster
is also a beautiful woman
with beautiful eyebrows and clear eyes.
She is a girl.
What about me? Why should I take him in?
A boy.
I have to pay for his family dispute.
What's the matter?
You both look at me like this.
When do you plan to go back
this time?
In my opinion,
your dad is too cruel this time.
It's not the first time he has done this.
But it's longer than before, isn't it?
Even if
your father is angry,
I think your mother
will be worried about you.
Let's play games.
My mother goes to play cards.
Make do with it.
Do you usually
eat alone?
But now
I have one more person to eat together.
It's quite lively.
Not bad.
Really? Then you should cherish me.
I'm not afraid.
I'll go to your home
and eat there every day.
Keep dreaming.
It's a little salty.
My mom doesn't cook usually.
Otherwise,
I'll take you out to eat.
No, I think it's delicious.
And it's comfortable to eat home-cooked food.
OK, you wash the dishes
after eating.
I often help you make up lessons for free.
You need to make up to me.
All right.
Childe, I will wash.
You also prepared some fruit.
Can I watch TV?
Sure.
Where is the remote control?
Did you hide it?
How can I hide the remote control?
No.
You get up and let me have a look.
I didn't hide it. Don't touch me.
I saw it. You just hid it.
Here.
You're still quibbling.
Have you finished your homework?
You just want to watch TV.
I have finished.
Let me have a look.
OK.
If you can grab it, I will let you watch TV.
Zhou Siyue
Don't push me.
What's up?
My brother and I
robbed the remote control at home
for so many years.
You're a little rude.
Because you usually watch TV in a comfortable environment.
Look at you.
You're like my brother who couldn't grab the remote control.
As like as two peas.
Did you use the website
I gave you last time?
Yes.
I quite like it.
Thank you.
I'm glad you enjoy it.
It's worth
my effort.
If you want to use a computer,
you can use mine.
The password is six zeros.
Really?
Here's the remote control.
Then I'll borrow your computer.
Don't play too late.
We have to get up early tomorrow.
Got it.
I asked you to go to bed early.
Look, you're going to sleep again
in class today.
I had gone to bed early.
I was playing cards with Zheng's wife this afternoon.
She said Zheng stays at home
and helped his son with his lessons.
Zhou Zongtang, you lied to me.
Would you please stop crying?
The children will be back soon.
I told you many time
but you don't believe me.
Zheng was there at that time.
He answered a phone and left.
Jiang stayed with me all the way.
You can ask him.
You think I don't know.
Jiang is your friend.
He lied for you.
I wouldn't believe him.
Zhou Zongtang, tell me the truth.
Are you cheating me?
What are you talking about?
I can't talk with you.
Xianxian, you are here.
Why don't you say hello when you go home?
Didn't you tell me when you came back?
Haven't you eaten? Yun
The children are back.
I'm going to cook.
You are back.
I'll help your dad.
Come in.
Do you have questions?
I'll teach you when I finish this.
No. You can go on.
Aren't you preparing for the National Olympiads?
I come to see you.
The room is a bit messy.
Sit down.
Have you read all these books?
I want to tell you
I won't tell others what I heard
this afternoon.
I promise.
I swear.
How can a couple not quarrel?
Don't be too sad.
What's the matter?
You find my home
is not as harmonious as you think.
Are you psychologically balanced?
No.
No?
Maybe
a little.
But I didn't gloat.
It's okay.
My mother
doesn't have a job,
so her focus is on my dad.
You know my dad. He's busy at work.
He doesn't have much time for my mother.
So my mother is always paranoid.
She listens to rumors.
I'm used to it.
And look at my mom.
She grew up in a honeypot since she was a child,
so she thought
everyone around her would be good for her.
She's not the sort of person to bear a grudge.
She may forget
many things in two or three days.
But I remember
all the grievances
my mother suffered.
What's up?
Do you find that
I'm not as good as I usually look?
No.
Of course not.
Don't lie to me.
I think you are very good.
We're both seventeen.
There will definitely be a lot of troubles and confusion.
But no one is perfect.
Don't put so much pressure on yourself.
I'm not like my dad.
I won't let the people around me be wronged.
Drink it.
Have a good sleep after drinking.
When
Shadi and Keke asked me,
I didn't know the answer.
But I think
there may be
neither fantasy
nor disillusionment for me.
Sometimes, he is very considerate.
Sometimes, he's annoying.
Sometimes, he's fragile.
But all this
only makes me happy.
Because at the moment,
he really
exists in my heart
and will not disappear
in front of me.
What are you laughing at?
I feel like
we've been getting along well lately.
And I know a lot of his secrets.
What are the secrets?
Tell me.
No way.
I promised him to keep the secrets.
It's boring.
But I can't imagine that
you can get something on Zhou Siyue.
He has been excellent since childhood.
Have you heard about He Xingwen's family?
His father seems to have had an accident on the construction site.
Stand up.
Hello, teacher.
Sit down please.
Some people may have heard about
what happened to He Xingwen's family.
Although it is a voluntary contribution,
I still hope everyone can lend a helping hand
to help He Xingwen
and his family
get through the difficulties.
He looks really pathetic.
But I was angry
when I thought of what he had done before.
He's so mean.
I feel like
I'm helping the bad guys.
You're stupid.
Your expression is not suitable.
I don't like him.
But this is a different thing.
You should help if you have the ability.
But I'm still angry.
He reported Ding Xian before.
And the last time we were punished because of chatting.
He is to blame for these.
Maybe
he also did the thing about Siyue last time.
You're right. He did it.
We all know that Auntie talked to him later.
You know it all.
It doesn't matter.
Anyway, the money is not for him.
It's for his grandparents.
Two old people have just lost their son.
It would be sad for them
to find that their grandson is not living well.
You donated all your pocket money.
Do my best.
If the same thing happened to me one day,
I should also hope that everyone can help me.
So much.
It's the same.
It is a token of my affection.
Let's go.
Thank you.
And
I'm sorry.
Look at this.
If you can't solve it,
just ask me directly.
Don't split hairs all day.
There will be more mistakes.
I can't rely on you all the time.
I have to work hard on my own.
Good.
Your idea is good.
I'm satisfied with you.
By the way,
can you go to Huaqing University directly
after the National Olympiads?
This time
if I win the first prize
and plus some other awards,
it should be OK.
What's the matter?
No.
I envy you very much.
If you go to Huaqing University,
you can go to Jiangling with your father.
Jiangling is big and prosperous.
I'd like to see it, too.
Ding Xian
How about
you come to Jiangling with me?