Unforgettable Love
Yiyue, will you go with me?
Where are you taking me to?
Why are you here?
I'm not finished yet.
Others express their love
to those
people they like.
But you express love to motivate your rival.
So well intentioned.
Thanks for setting up the venue.
Have you ever thought about
what if He Qiaoyan
did not come here?
Then he's not qualified
to make Yiyue happy.
And I will take her to German.
Good afternoon, Sir.
Good afternoon.
Xiaobao
What happened to him?
I don't know why Xiaobao
insisted on playing basketball by himself
on the playground
and refused to go back to classroom.
My apology, Sir.
Can we have a minute
with Xiaobao alone?
Yes.
Sure.
Thanks.
No problem.
Xiaobao
Why do you want to play basketball?
Is there anything
you want to talk to me?
To play basketball.
You want to play basketball
with your daddy, right?
Playing basketball is fun.
If your daddy is here
he will teach you how to play basketball.
And he will try his best
to win you by tricks.
Daddy
Xiaobao, say that again.
Good boy.
Go, my boy.
Coming for you.
Do you think
there is love in the world?
Forget about it.
You are unrequited.
Even if you say so,
I don't buy it.
Then what do you think love is?
No clue.
But I know that
I have nothing to do with that thing.
Your anxiety disorder
has been lasting for years?
Since the second year after studying abroad.
Something wrong?
You know...
I was like a bird escaping from a cage
in the first year
when I went abroad.
My design work in that year
earned me the Broom Top Award.
But I knew it later that
at that time
the award I won at home
was not by my design.
It was all
my mother's plan.
Your parents
don't support you work in design industry, do they?
No, they don't.
But my mother
doesn't allow me to fail.
She knew it was extremely hard to
win that award.
And
people around
knew I was in the competition.
So...
From then on
Every time
when I face a design script
I would become anxious.
And the anxiety becomes
more and more severe.
Honestly
I haven't been able to
draw a single design
since last year.
Think I'm pitiful?
Just feel sorry for me.
You've seen all my embarrassment
anyway.
This is nothing.
It doesn't matter whether others
think you are pitiful or not.
It matters that
how do you think of yourself.
Are you willing to live with it?
People like us
never take our heart
seriously.
Ignore it
for different reasons.
Till it's sick.
Cheers.
Is Xiaobao asleep?
Yes.
I've made my decision.
I'll do what you said.
You are willing to
get you memories back?
With you and Xiaobao.
I have the guts to do that.
Thank you
for everything you've done
during these days.
Thank you for your company
and love.
We will get through this together
if we love each other devotedly.
I want to give you and Xiaobao a happy life.
Mr. He, I guess you come here
not for your illness.
I'm here to express my gratitude.
All this time
Yiyue treats you as her
most trusted friend.
All that you need to do is
continue to play that role
and never cross the line.
I can't promise you that.
That depends on you.
But I can promise you that
no matter what happens
I'll make her happy.
Remember what you said today.
Excuse me.
What will you do next
about that thing.
I'll find a way to
get my memories back first.
I knew a senior fellow apprentice in school.
He once helped someone
like you
regain his memory
through hypnosis.
I can introduce him to you
if you don't mind.
I appreciate.
I can't make sure that I
can help your friend
get his memories back.
But we can have a try.
So
tell him to come to me
tomorrow afternoon.
Thanks a lot.
Wait a second.
I remembered that
you had a roommate
who became a designer.
Right?
Yes, right.
His name is Zhou Xingyuan.
Why?
I think five years ago
he was the judge for the Broom Top Award.
Yes, he was.
Do you have his contact?
I wanna consult him some questions.
Yes, I have.
No problem.
I'll send his contact to your phone later.
Thanks.
Nobody is here except us.
So tell me
how much money you were paid.
I don't know what you mean.
You were driving that day
and why you stopped?
Just felt uncomfortable.
You knew something would happen.
So you found an excuse to quit driving.
What's your evidence?
To be honest.
I've got part of
my memories back.
I just want to save my time.
It's fine if you don't tell me the truth.
But I will recall everything sooner or later.
I am not afraid of that.
I had nothing to do with that car accident.
You go for them.
Them?
So
there were people who
planned the accident.
Right.
And Yiyue's intuition
was correct.
You told Mr. Zhang
that you've got your memories back.
Will the people behind this
do something to you
for hiding themselves?
I told him on purpose.
Since I can't get my memory back
so let the people in my memories
come to me.
Qiaoyan, how's it going?
It seems that hypnosis doesn't
work for me.
I still can't recall anything
after these days.
It's fine.
There's no damage to your neurons
neither to your brain.
So you must still have your memories.
But for now
we don't know
how to rouse them.
Give me a hug.
Everything is fine.
You will get your memories back.
Weiwei
I remembered that you love chicken wings
when you were a kid.
I don't eat these anymore.
Too many calories.
Right.
Didn't I tell you to go back?
Why are you still here?
Listen to mom and go home, will you?
That home has been
a broken picture to me.
But every step I take here
is practical
and real.
Anyway.
I have to apologize to you
for having your family here
without letting you know.
It's too impulsive.
Sorry.
I was busy in business
and didn't answer your call
when you were in danger.
It was my fault, too.
I'm sorry.
I...
Better not touch me
with your hand.
Disgusting.
And I don't need your apology.
Can you even count the girls
who you have coaxed?
But I don't care.
Let's go.
I said
you and me
are just supervisor and subordinate.
Leave me alone.
Let go of me!
You...
Welcome to my secret garden.
What a good place
on the top of your bar.
I feel vibration under my feet.
We are
dancing above their heads.
We are the super VVVIp.
Here, enjoy your drinks.
When I graduated from university
I've made up my mind that
I would earn my own place
in this city
to eat and sleep.
Even a tiny bed
can protect my dream.
Because I will never
go back to that home.
Every day when I go out
I will dress myself well.
It's like arming myself
from head to toes.
I'm afraid to show a trace of timidity
and make others know that
I have nothing.
You ready?
Ready for what?
Walking alone at night
needs many things
to arm myself.
With no home
I build myself a shell.
With no knight
I forge myself a sword.
Stand still.
Where you stand is the living room
and it's a big balcony outside.
Here is the bedroom
and inside is a large dressing room.
Here are the kitchen, bathroom and the second bedroom.
And maybe there will be a children's room.
I want to give you a home
where you can save all your dreams
and tiredness.
I love you.
I'll give you a home if you want.
I'll give you my love if you want.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for falling in love with you
from the very beginning.
Will you?
Sure.
Bye.
Damn.
I left in a hurry this morning.
I took
Wen Gu's phone by mistake.
What am I supposed to do right now?
Where is Wen Gu?
Even I am here.
Why is he so late?
I guess he's coming soon.
Call him, Ruowei.
Tell him to be quick.
I get another meeting
later.
Sorry for that.
He's coming soon.
He may be in a traffic jam.
I'd like to praise him due to
his achievement last month.
He seems never change his bad habits.
Can't reach him?
Fine, I'll call him.
Don't...
I apologize for being late.
Didn't find my phone this morning.
Loot at your
forgetfulness.
Then have you found it now?
Yes, it's here.
It's too early.
Let me buy Xiaobao a cotton candy.
Excuse me, can I get one of these?
How much?
Five yuan.
Xiaobao
Mom is here.
Slow down, no hurry.
Slow...
Mom
Bad guy took away my mom.
Don't worry, Xiaobao.
Back to classroom and find your teacher.
I'll send driver to pick up you.
Bad guys took away my mom, save her.
What else did you see
besides that car?
A three-zero-two-seven-three(license plate number)
A three-zero-two-seven-three
You did a good job, Xiaobao.
Don't worry.
I'll go find you mom right now.
She will be fine.
Brake! Brake!
♪ Wind is blowing, moon is shining ♪
♪ Where is the shaky boat floating to ♪
♪ In the river of time ♪
♪ you have my company ♪
Don't go.
Yiyue
Don't go, Yiyue.
Qiaoyan
Do not leave me.
Yiyue
I won't leave you.
Everything is fine.
Yiyue
Where is Xiaobao?
Aunt went to pick him up.
They'll be back soon.
Why do you wear this?
What happened?
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
When I was kidnapped
you had a car accident
on the way you went to save me.
But thanks to the air bag
we were both fine.
You've just been hit in the head.
Doctor said it was not a big deal.
We can go home
after two days of observation.
Glad to see you're safe.
The people who kidnapped me
is the enemy of Heshi group.
They are from AM Group.
They admitted everything.
You can rest assured.
The police
has arrested everyone
of them.
I remember now.
It was the brake failure.
There's a big truck coming to me.
I was dazzled by its light.
Then I hit the tree
on one side of the road.
It's all right now.
Back to then
it was because
your brother
found the huge financial loopholes
of AM Group.
The desperate Liao Zilang
was pushed too much.
So he bribed Mr. Zhang
and asked him to be an informer in your family.
Mr. Zhang knew the brake was broken.
But he sold this information to Liao Zilang
because his brother
owed Liao Zilang money.
And then he was asked to
find a reason
to refuse to drive.
And what about that track?
Your guess was correct.
That truck
was planned to
kill you directly.
But the rain was too heavy.
Your car lost control
and just rolled out from the road.
Qiaoyan
It was not your fault.
The culprit has been under arrest.
Yiyue
Thank you.
It was you that saved Xiaobao and me.
The lullaby you sang that day
was the most beautiful song
I've ever heard in my life.
What a joke
has destiny
made with us.
I saved your life.
But you saved mine, too.
We can never
live without each other now.
Are you being serious?
Of course.
I'm impressed by your work.
So I remembered very clearly that
you are the winner of golden prize
who got votes from all the three of us.
But my mother told me...
About that
I told Zhou to
find the person in charge of that year
and asked.
It was a
minor misunderstanding.
Your mother mistaken
another people's work
as yours.
And the name of that person
is only one word different to
the name of your work.
Are you alright?
I should have thought of that
since my mother has never
cared about my design.
So how did she even know
the name of my work.
Difference in profession makes one feel worlds apart.
Your mother didn't know design industry.
So of course she's not interested in knowing your work.
Why did you
help me on this?
I've heard about Zhou
and his personality.
I don't think he is
the person to do that kind of thing.
More importantly I believe that you are
good enough to win the golden prize.
Thanks a lot.
Now the misunderstanding is gone.
What do you plan to do next?
What the heck.
Why did I lose again?
Stick out your tongue.
Don't you know
tenderness toward women
stop before going too far
and the outstanding usually bear the brunt of attack?
All I know is you have to admit defeat.
I'm out.
Childish.
Open your mouth.
It's Ning Fang.
He said he's coming to visit us tonight.
What?
Tell him not to come.
No visit in this hospital
after 9 o'clock
You are such a weird man.
You don't like him, do you?
Why should I?
You are the only one I know
who dislikes
Ning Fang.
Then I won't be
the only one soon.
Who else would be?
You
Why would I dislike him?
Because the husband to sing and the wife to follow.
So childish.
Who are you sending messages to this time?
Ruowei
You said that no visit in this hospital
after 9 o'clock.
So I will tell her not to come.
No need to send messages.
She won't come anyway.
How do you know?
Wen Gu told me
he has a basketball game today.
You're right.
Look.
Honey
My Gugu...
Gugu?
My Gugu
has a basketball game tonight.
I'm going to be his cheer leading.
Can't pay you the visit.
Look at this Yang Ruowei.
Since she fell in love
she has thoroughly interpreted the meaning of
needing no friends when in love.
It's just right that they won't come.
Let's continue.
Come on.
No, I'm hungry.
Hungry?
Aunt brought us
a lot of food today.
Go eat some.
What she brought are all
luxurious tonic soups.
Right.
My stomach has nothing but soup and water.
I...
I would like to eat at roadside food stalls.
Let's go.
Thank you, sir.
Wait, wait.
My shoes.
Drop them again.
I haven't been so crazy in a long time.
Last time was
in my childhood.
You were crazy like this when you were a kid?
No.
I mean
I haven't been so purely happy
for a long time.
It seemed that
I was in the same age
with Xiaobao.
♪ Little kids with seldom worries ♪
♪ Looking around in the sunshine ♪
Didn't you say my father was at home?
He just left for business in company.
You hide when something happens.
Did I teach you that?
Sorry, mother.
I can't handle He Qiaoyan.
All right, all right.
Let the failure
become history.
Do you have a plan
about what to do next?
Yes.
I want to focus on my career first.
Good.
That's what your father and I want.
Go to the company
and work as your father's assistant for a year.
You still have
a lot of things to learn.
I don't want to work in our company.
I want to continue to design.
No way.
Mom, I've made my decision.
Alright, since you made your decision,
do it.
But then
never tell others you are my daughter.