[English subtitles are available]
[Crush]
[Episode 1]
[On air]
Welcome to a new day
in Golden Hits Studio.
Today is Thursday.
[Today is a little cloudy.]
[You’re like the most delicate flower,]
[floating outside the blue window.]
[It’s like you might fall
into my heart anytime.]
You switched the channel?
No. Why?
Nothing.
The first song for today
is a classic song that
matches the sky today.
It's best to wind down your car window,
feel the wind in your face
as you listen to this song.
Fall by Xu Guan Chun,
composed and written by Yi Jin,
a very mysterious songwriter and lyricist.
This doesn't sound like Miss Xi.
♫ If wishes and future hadn't
come into contact ♫
♫ Perhaps ♫
Although Xu Guan Chun
has released a new song,
everyone still prefers
the song you wrote.
Switch it off. It's too noisy.
When Lin Yang's Dream Under
The Night Sky is available online,
I wonder if Xu Guan Chun's new song
will still be in the charts.
Lin Yang was surprised that
you're willing to write a song
for a rookie like him.
Netizens are curious of who Yi Jin is.
It's a super topic now.
Miss Xi has always wanted to
invite you for an interview.
Do you want to consider it?
No.
I understand.
You don't want Yi Jin's identity exposed.
But Miss Xi knows us well.
We'll maintain confidentiality
and make sure nobody knows.
Many listeners are now asking why
we change the channel host.
What should we do?
Can we just straightaway tell listeners
I'm the substitute host?
Fang Fang.
Keep calling her.
Alright.
Wu Yan.
Can you keep to the script?
Just start the second segment later.
Listen to my instruction.
Alright.
Sorry, I'm late.
Miss Xi.
Why can't your phone be reached?
I dropped my phone because I was in hurry.
Wu Yan.
The song will end soon.
Think of something to wind it up smoothly.
Alright.
Welcome back to Golden Hits Studio,
brought to you live on 27.1 FM.
Many listeners asked why
the host sounded different today.
Actually, this is a little game
our programme team has planned
for our listeners during the opening
to test the auditory skills
of our listeners.
Alright then. Next up is...
Hello, everyone.
I'm Nie Xi.
The ability to differentiate a voice
will allow one to enjoy music better.
It seems that our listeners
have very sharp ears.
There's always someone in your heart.
There's always something in your mind
that you can't shake it off.
Hello? It's been a while
since I hear from you.
I have time today.
See you later.
I knew it.
The manager of Xu Guan Chun called.
They heard your Dream Under The Night Sky.
Now they want to meet up.
I think they'll ask us
why we didn't give them the song.
What should we say?
The truth.
His voice doesn't suit the song.
I'm afraid they won't accept it so easily.
I'll send you home first.
Drop me at the nearby park.
I want to sit there for a while.
Pick me up after you're done.
[27.1 FM]
Miss Xi.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Everyone in the team just needs to
write a reflective report.
How did it feel to be at the anchor desk
for the first time?
It's hard to tell
because I was too anxious just now.
Let me ask you then.
If I couldn't make it today,
what will you do?
Do you plan to keep reading the script
and make today a non-interactive show
without taking calls from listeners?
I...
You're very brave today
but don't be carried away.
This is not campus broadcast.
You're still not prepared for
the position of a radio host.
You should know it yourself.
I understand.
I'll continue to work hard, Miss Xi.
Alright then. You can clock off now.
Quickly go back for class.
I'll get going then, Miss Xi.
Someone is here for you.
No, I have no idea. I don't know him.
I'll leave now, Miss Xi.
Goodbye.
Why didn't you pick up my call?
I don't want to.
How did you know where to find me?
Cheng Yin told me about it.
Wu Yan. Xu Qian and I are not...
Whatever it is with the two of you
is none of my business.
Wu Yan...
[Playlist: Everything will be alright,
so don't be sad okay?]
♫ Spending all the years ♫
♫ For an exchange of apology ♫
[Xu Guan Chun, Fall]
♫ Stubbornness and determination ♫
♫ Refuse to listen to other's advice ♫
[Fall]
♫ Watching the memories ♫
♫ Burn in flames ♫
♫ I'm willing to take the fall ♫
♫ But I can't escape from rising ♫
♫ The hurt along the way
can only be written, not erased ♫
♫ The blue past ♫
♫ Is now covered in snow ♫
♫ How can love melt? ♫
[Oh, no. Was I out of tune again?]
Now, let's conclude humanism,
the most important theory of therapy.
Firstly, humans have a tendancy
of self-actualization.
Rogers thinks that
humans are born with
a basic motive.
I saw a guy in the park today.
Absolutely divine.
Totally a prince charming at first sight.
I don't believe you.
Show me the photo.
I didn't dare to take a photo.
When the broadcast station was recruiting,
you even had the guts to get
the first-year campus prince to sign up.
There's nothing you dare not do.
This one is not in the same league.
Finish the assignment.
I'll see you all next week.
[Good afternoon, everyone.]
[I'm your host, Xu Qian.]
[Today, the first song I'm going to play]
[is a newly-released song.]
[It's a song by newcomer singer Lin Yang.]
♫ The earth is quiet  ♫
♫ Like the eyes of the stars ♫
What are you doing?
♫ Every expression on your face ♫
Losing myself in Xu Qian's voice.
I think you're
losing yourself in your own jealousy.
♫ The heart ♫
Don't deny it.
♫ From one star ♫
♫ To another ♫
What is it?
Listen to this song.
♫ Tears are like crystals  ♫
♫ Submerged in the sea of stars ♫
♫ Continuing its trajectory ♫
What a good song.
I have to check it out.
You really have an occupational disease.
Why don't you just text Xu Qian directly?
I won't.
I've drawn the line with them.
[Dream Under The Night Sky, Yi Jin]
It's Yi Jin.
I knew it.
He didn't post it
in his page again
to give fans a preview.
[Billboard Chart]
It's in second place in the charts now.
It's going to make this Lin Yang famous.
Your Yi Jin again.
What kind of person is Yi Jin?
With a song, he made Xu Guan Chun
famous overnight.
But no one knows
who he is.
This time, he worked with a newcomer.
That's just too mysterious.
Do you think he's a writer?
Or a language teacher?
Or, he's a pervert.
You're the pervert.
Don't insult my idol.
I'm praising him.
He's a low-profile to a perverted degree.
Have you come across anyone
who says that to praise others?
Do you want a beating? Do you?
Alright. Stop hitting me.
Stop running.
Come here.
Milk is on the first level.
Fruits on the second level.
Drinking water is by the side.
Thank you.
If you really want to thank me,
then write another song for Xu Guan Chun
as a compensation.
You gave your Dream Under The Night Sky
to newcomer Lin Yang.
Xu Guan Chun's side is not happy about it.
Whether he's happy or not,
it has nothing to do with me.
Dream Under The Night Sky
is now catching up on
Xu Guan Chun's new song.
They're having a tough time on publicity.
They think we're attacking them.
I tried to explain to them
that his voice doesn't suit the song.
But they just can't understand.
They think we're giving an excuse.
This is a problem that
the company needs to resolve.
Nian Qin.
Aren't you being unreasonable?
You're lucky I know your temper.
Anyone else is going to be mad at you.
I still have work. I'm leaving now.
Wu Yan.
Let's have dinner together tonight.
I'll invite Wei Hao.
I have something to attend to.
You two go ahead.
Wu Yan. I want to talk to you.
You don't have to.
I treated you as my closest friend.
Way better than I treated Wei Hao.
But since you never wanted to talk to me
before you two want to be together,
there's nothing to talk about
now or in the future.
Wu Yan. We're not...
So, did Wei Hao ever like you?
Why do you ask me that too?
I'll change the question.
Did he ever say he likes you?
We grew up together.
We've been together for ages.
We're like an old couple.
Have you ever seen an old couple
say they love each other everyday?
So, Wei Hao has never actually
uttered explicitly that he likes you.
It's not compulsory to utter it.
Look.
In the past, he'd always buy me breakfast
or go shopping with me.
When the hostel gate is shut,
he'd come pick me up on his bike.
Aren't these expressions of
liking someone?
Then, have you ever said you like him?
You may think that confession
is a meaningless ritual.
But a clear relationship is based on that.
If both of you don't say it,
you'll be guessing it
until it dies out.
I...
If you need words to convince
even after being with each other
for so long,
isn't it a waste of
all those times together?
Now it's really all a waste.
In that case, I can let go everything
and marry Yi Jin.
I'm so happy.
Just cry if you want to.
Why should I cry
if my new life has just begun?
Group message from the radio station.
I'm now walking towards
the path of realising my dream.
I have to focus. No time for romance now.
A pretty girl claims she's the
composer and lyricist Yi Jin.
She revealed her relationship
with music star Xu Guan Chun.
Oh heavens.
This...
Yi Jin is a girl?
Why did the fake news suddenly surface?
I'm sorry you had to
work overtime on this.
Thank you.
The record company will release
an official notice later tonight
to clarify that she faked the identity.
But Xu Guan Chun is
too popular these days.
I'm afraid we can't stop this fake news
from snowballing.
Everyone will only be interested
in the gossips.
The fake Yi Jin will make a mark.
I'm really curious.
A girl is claiming that she is Yi Jin.
Aren't you anxious at all?
Close your eyes.
This is my world.
It doesn't have a hint of chaos.
I only write songs I want to write.
It's not important
who Yi Jin is.
Is it really not important?
At that time,
did you also close your eyes like this
and tell yourself that it's not important?
It's too late.
[Why did I call myself Yi Jin?]
[Yixiyijin, a night and a day.
It represents my ambiguous]
[but heartwarming love stories.]
[Yiguyijin, the old and the new]
[It represents the impact and
interaction of thinkings]
[between my upbringing
in Chinese tradtional studies]
[and my higher education abroad.]
[This two ideas are merged
by the word Yi Jin.]
That's gross.
It's definitely fake.
Why are you so worked up?
How did you reflective report go?
You told me before
that you want to invite Yi Jin
for an interview
but it never happen.
Why did she suddenly want to come?
She is fake.
Fake? How can it be?
She's really a fake. I can warrant that.
The real Yi Jin...
I'll get the real Yi Jin
to come to our show.
Alright. I'll wait for it.
If you can't do it,
I'll have to take it that
you're just giving excuses.
[The reason I didn't go public
with my real identity]
[is not about staying low-key.]
[It's because I love my life.]
[Life as a public figure]
[is too much a burden.]
[But,]
[I did write my first song, Fall]
[as a token of our love]
[It's from the male perspective.]
[Nie Xi]
[He told me his feeling]
[when he first saw me.]
[That first time we met on the beach.]
[I was touched]
[so I wrote this song for him.]
[But he's now denying everything.]
[He even denied that I'm Yi Jin.]
Miss Xi said her director has ordered
to invite the fake Yi Jin
for an interview.
She's in an awkward situation now.
I know you don't care.
But Nian Qin,
can you at least visit the station once?
At least let them know Yi Jin is a fake
and cannot be interviewed.
Nie Xi is my best friend.
Can you do this for me?
[Tomorrow's music guest
is a mysterious big shot]
What are you so focused on?
I'm checking if there's any celebrity
coming to our station.
Usually when a celebrity is coming,
they're announce it in Weibo.
But it's so weird this time.
I asked Miss Fang Fang and others
about the guest in this coming show
but they have no idea too.
We don't have a class tomorrow.
You can go have a look.
How's your Yi Jin doing?
I don't know who to trust.
If the record company says she's a fake,
then where is the real Yi Jin?
That's why
I believe the girl.
Who would want to
create rumours like that?
Notice.
Tomorrow morning at eight o'clock,
please gather at the lecture hall
of the main building.
Counselors will announce arrangements
on internship matters.
It's about internship again.
Please sign the attendance for me then.
You've really put your whole heart
into that radio station career.
I love you.
[Crippled at such a young age.]
[Yu Xiao Lu is calling.]
I'll go up on my own.
You don't need to come down.
Inner first column on the left.
Second row from top.
I got it.
[It's him.]
[He's blind?]
[His eyes are pretty.]
Do you need help?
No, thanks.
[Inner first column on the left.]
[Second row from top.]
[I feel like a thief.]
[Cheng Yin]
Come back quick,
Mr Zhao said if you don’t
come back before the session ends,
you’ll flunk the subject, hurry up.
[Seventh floor.]
[I really don't want to go.]
Hello? Miss Fang Fang.
I need to go back to campus.
[Tenth floor.]
Mr Su.
Nian Qin.
I'll follow Xiao Lu.
Alright. This way please.
Work interview, postgraduate interview
and civil servant interview
are the three major categories.
Some students
have contacted the organisation
for internship.
As for the rest,
the university has arranged
two organisations for internship.
One group will be going to the
high security prison.
The other
will go to a special education school.
I heard you're going to
the high security prison.
...to proactively apply to go
to a high security prison.
-What is high security?
-Cheng Yin.
The inmates are all felons who
are convicted for over 50 years.
You mean murderers?
Not just that.
Drug dealers, smugglers or kidnappers too.
Do you want to join me?
No, thanks.
You pampered girl. I'll let you in
on the horror stories later.
Sang Wu Yan.
Where do you plan to go?
Special education school.
For the rest of you, give your names
to the class monitor.
Sang Wu Yan. Come with me.
I...
Alright.
[Good morning, everyone.]
[This is Golden Hits Studio]
[on 27.1 FM.]
[Yesterday,]
we have given a preview that
a mysterious guest will
come on the show today.
In our studio now is
famous songwriter and lyricist Yi Jin.
Hello, everyone. I'm Yi Jin.
Yi Jin. I have a question for you.
Two days ago, someone claimed
to be you on the internet.
There was a huge uproar about this.
Why didn't you come forward to clarify it?
Everyone is entitled to their own opinion.
I don't care
how they think.
Why did you decide to
embark on songwriting?
Did you dream to be a songwriter
when you're young?
I just like music.
I never thought about it at that time.
Facing such a large number of music fans,
why did you intentionally choose to
avoid the public?
To keep my life private.
Is this the only reason?
This is the only reason.
In that case,
I'm really curious about
why you choose to
accept this interview invitation?
I feel I have wronged my song.
For the song to be heard in the way,
it's a failure on my part.
What were you thinking?
Are you planning to go for
postgraduate studies?
No, I don't want to.
I also don't plan to
become a psychotherapist.
I prefer working in a radio station.
I'm very sure of this.
But if you go for postgraduate studies,
you don't have to make it your career.
You can choose the academic path
like your father.
[Can you make this quick?]
[Hopefully I still get to hear
a little part of it.]
Even if you go for postgraduate studies,
you can still
work part-time at the radio station.
Mr and Mrs Sang
really hope you can go back
to pursue your postgraduate studies.
I know you have your ideals.
I totally understand
and support you.
But you should at least
think of your parent's hopes.
Mr Zhao. I have decided
to become a professional radio host
and I plan to achieve success in this.
I've made up my mind.
Wu Yan. Are you really going to
bet on your future?
I want to bet on a path that is mine.
If you don't have any other matters,
I'll go back now.
I'm not done.
The internship is very important.
It'll directly affect your graduation.
I'll work hard on the internship.
Goodbye, Mr Zhao.
Oh right, Mr Zhao.
About my plan,
I'd like to personally tell my father.
Can you...
Don't worry.
Thank you, Mr Zhao.
Goodbye, Mr Zhao.
[For the last question,]
[it's my personal question as a host.]
Do you have any preference
when you listen to the radio?
I don't like it
when someone request a song I don't like.
[We'd like to thank Mr Yi Jin]
[for coming on the show today.]
[Thank you.]
[You're welcome.]
It's...
It's Yi Jin?
What did Mr Zhao say?
It was Yi Jin.
What are you talking about?
Did you know who is the guest
of our radio show today?
It was Yi Jin.
If I was in the station,
I could meet Yi Jin.
I missed my chance to meet Yi Jin.
This is a curse of your destiny.
My condolence to you.
My condolence...
You don't have to apologize.
We all have our own difficulty
in this line.
Scandals are like swamps.
It's not easy to get your name cleared.
I will let him know.
Don't worry.
He gave us a call on this.
He sounded genuine.
Next time...
We'll talk about it when it comes.
Alright. I'll send you to the school.
[Xiamen Special Education School]
Children, we know that
Chinese Braille is made up of
vowel and consonant sounds.
The two combines to
become a Chinese character.
Two to three Chinese characters
make a phrase.
Phrases are arranged into
a complete sentence.
Moreover, in between some phrases,
we need to do word segment continuation.
Today, we're going to practise
word segment continuation for numerals.
Mr Su.
Xiao Wei.
Twelve is a numeral.
Remember to do a continuation.
I got it.
Good girl.
Alright. Class dismissed.
On your feet.
Goodbye, Mr Su.
Goodbye.
Mr Su.
Do I know you?
I think you don't.
Do you need help?
Do... do you need help?
We've met
at the radio station.
Yes, in the elevator.
I'm the new teacher intern.
I'm Sang Wu Yan.
How about you, Mr Su?
Su Nian Qin.
Nian Qing?
Nian Qin.
Q, I, N.
Su Nian Qin.
Mr Su,
do you know where is
the school director's office?
I'll take you there.
Okay.
-Slow down.
-Wait for me.
Slow down, slow down.
Slow down.