[English subtitles are available.]
[Luoyang]
[Episode 23]
Li Ji is important.
Now that he's dead, we don't have any clues.
Did he try to
escape out of fear
and die?
What a coincidence!
The manager of Tianxiang House
and his family all died.
Now Li Ji died as well.
It seems that
he had long been targeted.
The killer waited until now
because Li Ji
was in our dungeon.
Wait.
Sir Wu decided to have
Li Ji transferred at the last minute.
How come the killer
got to know it so soon?
Hongyi is so talented.
He draws portraits so well.
It's nothing.
[Liu Feng, younger brother of Liu Ran]
Anyone can do this.
Does it look like him?
You didn't draw it so well,
but they do look remotely similar.
I need to go out.
Hongyi,
the beef soup is still warm.
You can have some before you go.
Hongyi.
I'll have it when I'm back.
Well,
I can draw a portrait for you
if you like it.
What did he say?
Are you okay, sister?
I can learn how to draw.
I can draw for you.
I'm impressed by myself.
[Interior Guard Services]
I was lucky
that I could draw this portrait
based on Liu Feng's description.
He saw Kang Jin not long ago.
His memory of Kang
should be accurate.
Also,
the identity documents
of the caravan are authentic.
What did you get?
Li Ji is dead.
He told me before he died that
there was an entertainer
with Kang Zhanbi when they were arguing.
The entertainer was suspicious,
so I went to Tianxiang House.
However...
Everyone was killed.
The Divine takes action quickly.
People who saw the entertainer
won't survive.
The caravan from the Ke Tribe
must be hiding a bigger secret
than we thought.
We have to ask
the Intelligence Services
for help
to look into Kang Jin.
[Home of Gourmets]
Yunzhi,
what are you up to so late?
I'm making noodles.
What noodles? They smell so good.
They're from the Home of Gourmets.
How did you get it?
Lord Hongyi rated it
as "Premium".
I went there myself
to get the noodles.
Who are you cooking for?
Lady Liu Ran.
She said she was hungry
and wanted some noodles.
Did she?
I walked past her room just now
and saw the lights were off.
She must be asleep.
My bad.
Lord Hongyi wants some noodles.
He isn't home.
I see.
You are cooking
for Liu Feng.
I've noticed that
you've been
hooked on him
ever since he came
to our mansion.
You two grew up together,
didn't you?
Are you not already
sick of him?
He has changed
a lot.
In what way?
He doesn't look
as pale as
he used to be.
He also looks
mature now.
He even has a beard.
It makes him look composed.
He is nothing like
the spoiled little boy
when he was at home.
He has turned
into a real man.
I'm going to sleep.
My noodles!
Shen Fei!
There aren't many
cases regarding the Divine.
The Divine hasn't shown up for five years.
People believe
they have been wiped out.
In the first year of the Taicheng reign,
a Deputy Minister of Justice
was killed by the Divine.
The case is from the Grand Court.
In the second year of the Taicheng reign,
over 30 households in Jingyang Village
at the foot of Mount Song
were massacred by the Divine.
The case is from the Henan Prefecture.
[Yanqing,
officer in the Intelligence Services]
These only show how cases were closed
without any investigation details.
How can I know
the Divine really did all these?
It means that the authorities
closed tricky cases
by blaming them
all on the Divine
because there was no way
to investigate further.
Am I right?
Sir, a secret letter.
[Please look for Kang Jin, Wu Siyue]
Young lady.
[Coffins Store]
Tomorrow is Valentine's Day.
Her Majesty kindly
opened the south of Luoyang
for three nights.
People are all welcome to go.
Young lady,
it's Valentine's Day tomorrow.
Would you like a lantern?
[Coffins Store]
I'm good.
Sir,
a lantern, please.
which one would you like?
This one.
Sure.
There you go.
Thanks.
No problem.
Tomorrow is Valentine's Day.
Here you are.
Let's go over there.
Let's go, kid.
Mother, I want this.
Why are you here?
Didn't you send a secret letter
to the Intelligence Services?
I didn't think you'd come yourself.
Are you alright?
I'm good.
I got revenge.
Everything is good.
I'm just living from day to day.
Gao...
Let's have a walk.
What's going on with the portrait of the outlander?
The man on it is Kang Jin.
He is part of a caravan from the West.
I suppose he has something
to do with the Divine.
The Divine?
Do you mean the Divine
is chasing after the caravan?
Kang Zhanbi died of rattle poison.
Strangely,
Li Ji, who fought with Kang,
died unexpectedly when he was
under escort from the dungeon
to the Henan Prefecture.
Using rattle poison to cover
the real cause of death
seems to be the Divine's style.
I'll look into Kang Jin soon.
Thanks.
Come to think of it,
Baili Hongyi and I
fight against the Divine
to avenge our family's death.
You also risk your life
to bring it down.
What for?
To protect Her Majesty
and Luoyang?
Don't flatter me.
It's just my job.
Miss, your lantern is so pretty.
You can have it.
Thanks.
Amazing.
One more time.
Brilliant.
One more.
I can't believe someone wants to destroy all this.
Put the lantern
right here.
Sure.
Careful.
Okay.
Ding,
you good?
Yeah.
Go help with something else after this.
Yes.
Further down.
Sure.
Over there.
Put it over there.
Careful.
Remember to hang them all up.
My lord,
you're finally back.
Why are you home so late?
Tomorrow is Valentine's Day.
Uncle Baili asked them to decorate the place.
It makes sense.
What? My lord,
tomorrow is Valentine's Day.
And then?
Valentine's Day!
You should prepare
some gifts
for Lady Liu Ran.
Like what?
Like...
Cosmetic products that she uses
or accessories that she likes.
Any of them will do.
Brother,
tomorrow is Valentine's Day.
I got you some festive pastries.
Who are they?
What did they do?
This one looks creepy.
He can't be a good guy.
This one looks familiar.
Perhaps, he is an official.
Look.
Have a closer look.
You only care about cases.
The portraits were sent here
under Madam Yang's order.
They are all
outstanding men in Luoyang.
They're decent and good-looking.
Madam Yang wants to see
if you fancy anyone.
Madam Yang said that
she'll keep on looking
if you don't like any of them.
Brother.
It's none of my business.
I'm just a messenger
but I think it's a good thing.
Li Ji's death
can't be an accident.
He must've been murdered.
The killer was informed
as soon as Li was out of our Services.
I guess there are moles in our Services.
This case is tricky
and important,
but we do
need evidence.
I'll keep looking into it.
I'll keep you updated
of any evidence.
I only have one request.
You can try
your very best
but you can't risk your life.
Yes.
I can't imagine
my sister's life here.
Liu Feng.
Yunzhi.
It's so late.
What's up?
I remember you always had food
late at night when you were little.
I made some noodles for you.
I know you like
mandarin fish soup the most
but I still can't make it.
It's fine.
I haven't had it
since Chunhe left.
You can have some noodles.
I spent a while on it.
There is...
Yunzhi, you can go.
I'm going to sleep.
The noodles...
You can take it back.
Yes.
Chunhe,
where are you?
It's been so many years.
Are you doing okay?
♫Rain is telling me where flowers are♫
Hongyi,
I know you will come.
♫Boats sailed across desert♫
Hongyi.
♫Candles lit up the way to stars♫
What hair oil do you use?
Sweet olive oil.
I'd buy some when the season of sweet olive comes.
♫You are talking about me♫
Do you like the scent?
I made you some spicy soup.
♫I grabbed the corner of your top♫
Is it good?
Not bad.
♫But I was speechless♫
♫We are supposed to be against each other♫
Hot.
♫But fate brought us together♫
♫I already fell for it♫
Go.
Hey guys,
it's silverware.
Careful.
Sure.
Same for you guys.
It's the best wine
from Gaochang.
Be careful.
Sure.
Liu Feng.
Sister.
Liu Feng,
why are there
so many people?
what are you up to?
Look,
these are the best specialties
from the West.
I brought them back
particularly for you.
They look gorgeous, right?
Also, I hired
these servants
to look after you.
You don't have to do
anything by yourself.
Liu Feng,
how can you afford these?
Did you go back home?
No.
I've earned money.
I've been away from home
for so many years.
I have savings to cover them.
In the future,
you can let me know
whatever you need.
My money is all yours.
I'm not like Baili Hongyi.
He is so stingy.
Liu Feng,
you misunderstood
Hongyi.
He is good to me.
There is something
you didn't see.
I hope so.
Anyway, I'm back.
I will take better care of you.
By the way,
do you know
where Chunhe is?
You were kids.
I didn't think you two
were being serious.
How come you still think about her?
She was just
a maid.
She doesn't have family
and not even a surname.
She left right after you left home.
I guess,
she must be married now.
I'm telling you the truth.
Have some soup.
Hongyi,
you're up.
Did we
wake you up?
Thank you
for the portrait.
It's fine.
You'd better treat my sister
better in the future.
Liu Feng.
Did you make the soup?
Yes.
Alright. I'll leave you to it.
Hongyi,
it was cooked for a while.
Have a seat.
I'll get you some.
Sit down.
Try some
and see how it tastes.
There you go.
Is it good?
How's it?
My sister is always a good cook.
Do you like it?
I can get you more.
I want more, too!
Liu Feng.
Liu Feng,
save some for Hongyi.
Liu Feng.
So good.
What's wrong with him?
Hongyi, why are you smiling?
Never mind.
He ate all the soup.
How about I make you another bowl?
It's fine.
My lord,
Gao Bingzhu is looking into this man for Madam Wu.
An outlander?
Gao's been reading
documents in the Hall of Skills
for 4 hours since he came back.
He said he would
interrogate Hua Qingzhi in an hour.
Hua didn't confess
even after he was
interrogated for three days.
Can Gao make him talk?
Baitan,
have you ever seen the shape of wind?
I haven't.
The wind is invisible.
It is invisible,
but you can see it
when a branch is bent in the wind.
All creatures leave their trails
as long as they exist in the world.
Give him a chance.
Chen Qingzhi.
You were born in Yongzhou
on July 19th, the second year
of the Qiande reign.
You were smart.
You could compose poems at five
and write articles at nine.
You went to school in your region
at eleven.
You got married at nineteen
and had a son the next year.
Your son is named Chen Chao.
13 years ago,
your wife and son died in a flood
so you became alone.
11 years ago, you started to serve
the Intelligence Services
and changed your name to Hua Qingzhi.
Madam,
I just got a message
from the Intelligence Services.
It's for you.
Kang Zhanbi and Kang Jin
led the caravan.
It is made up of 14 people.
Kang Jin has a house
at 3 Xingjiao Place, 2nd Ave.
People here
all know my background.
It's not a secret.
Anything wrong with it?
Nothing.
I'm going to read you a poem.
The sun rises in Yongzhou.
Hands feel cold when holding jade.
Fog starts to surround the mountain.
I can't smell any scent of rice.
Does it ring a bell?
It's from a regional exam paper.
You know that
exam papers in different regions
are stored in our Services.
Interestingly,
the examinee who wrote it
has the same name as your son.
He is also called Chen Chao.
It's not uncommon to have
the same name.
Why did you secretly
check this paper
14 times throughout these years?
Why?
[Iron]
Siyue.
Why are you following me?
I'm working on a case nearby.
I saw your horse
outside the alley,
so I came to find you.
Did you?
I'm worried about you.
Li Ji died
strangely.
The case
is dangerous.
I am worried.
I saw you go out.
I...
Madam,
I'm sorry.
Where are you going?
Stay close.
Here is a story.
A talent called Chen Qingzhi
was picked by Four Season Divine.
The Divine invested a lot in him.
Of course, the Divine trained
many talents
like him,
because these people
were more likely to work as officials.
Once they did,
they naturally became the Divine's
mole in the Court.
Chen Qingzhi
was quite impressive.
He was picked by the Intelligence Services
but he had to cut off
all connections to join the Services.
It means that
he could never see
his son and wife.
I believe
Chen Qingzhi
had struggled a lot.
Nonsense.
[Kang Jin's house, Xingjiao Place]
No one is in there.
Whose house is it?
So many weeds.
It must've been deserted for a while.
An outlander called Kang Jin.
I guess someone wants him dead.
What's wrong?
A person was hung
on the beam.
It was Kang Jin.
Wait.
How are you sure
it was not Kang Jin who did it?
People from the Ke Tribe
always keep their houses tidy.
They won't fight at home,
so Kang must be the victim.
Do you think
Kang Jin is dead already?
There are signs
of struggling.
He could be alive.
Let's go ask around.
I've looked
into Chen Chao.
He studied at North Sea Academy.
Now he is doing a basic job
in the Court of Imperial Sacrifices.
Chen Chao
isn't related to me.
North Sea Academy
has something to do with the Divine though.
The Academy was established
by Lord Freedom
before he was arrested.
Chen Chao managed to cover up his identity
as a disciple of the Divine
by taking the Imperial Examination.
You know what?
His file is still at the Services.
You are?
May I ask you a question?
Are you close to your neighbor Kang Jin?
No.
Do you know Kang Jin?
Excuse me,
do you know Kang Jin,
an outlander living
in that alley?
He is your neighbor.
You should at least know him.
Neighbor?
I don't know.
I don't know him.
I have no idea.
Do you live nearby?
Yes.
Do you know Kang Jin
who lives in that alley?
No.
I've never seen him.
Sir,
you can go
ask other people.
Thanks.
Chen Qingzhi,
we're the same.
We've lived a hard life.
Your wife was killed by the Divine.
They controlled Chen Chao
and used him to force you
into working undercover
in the Intelligence Services.
I know you have lived
in the fear of exposing
your identity
for years.
The only comfort for you
is to learn about what your son is doing.
Have you ever thought
about what the Divine would do
to Chen Chao
if they knew that
your cover was blown.
He doesn't know anything.
He has nothing to do with this.
Leave him alone!
Leave him alone.
I won't get him involved.
I am Chen Qingzhi.
Chen Chao is my son.
What else do you want to know?
I will tell you all.
I will tell you everything.
Any news?
I asked around at a few shops.
No one knows him.
You mentioned that
Kang Jin was staying
in Guanglin Inn.
Why did he stay there
if he has his own place?
Two explanations.
He was doing business
under the table
or he was protecting himself from trouble.
So strange.
How come no one here
has seen Kang Jin before?
He has a business
in the West.
He stays in Luoyang
only a few days every year.
Understandably,
his neighbors don't know him.
We must have
missed something.
How about we go back
and send more people here?
I will dig him out
for you
at all costs.
You just mentioned that
he stayed in Luoyang
only a few days every year.
I didn't tell you that.
He is mysterious.
How did you know?
A neighbor said so.
Mother, look.
Fish.
Mother, look down there.
Sir,
you just came over.
What else do you want to know?
Your neighbor is a merchant from the outlands.
Do you know him?
He asked me
the same question.
I don't know
the merchant you are looking for.
Kang Jin said
he gave his neighbors wine
every time he was back from the West.
Don't you know him?
Right.
I don't know about others
but I paid him
every time he offered me wine.
I didn't take advantage of him.
Kang Jin isn't doing
any wine business.
Madam,
please tell us the truth.
Money is everything.
You seduced my wife
because you have money, huh?
You can do whatever you want
because you are rich, huh?
You will pay for it.
[Kang Jin, merchant from Ke Tribe]
It's outlanders' clothes.
Here are some gold and jewelry.
I think they belong to Kang Jin.
Do you mean Kang Jin has an affair?
Kang Jin had no shame and seduced
my daughter-in-law.
He also packed his belongings
and wanted to leave with her.
My son found out about them.
My son lost his mind and...
He tied Kang up?
Miss,
my son was impulsive
but he isn't a bad person.
Please forgive him.
Don't arrest him.
Calm down, please.
Do you know where they are?
Don't move.
You!
Listen,
I'll end your life here!
Hua Qingzhi said that
Four Season Divine
had been managed
by Lord of Spring and Lady of Autumn
after Lord Freedom was arrested.
Moles and assassins from the Divine
and working in different places
were all assigned by Lady of Autumn.
She seems to have
a lot of power.
What did she
ask them to do?
The assassination in the south of Luoyang,
the killing in the Grand Court,
the murder of Chen Que and Agent Han,
and the attack on Sir Wu.
Did the 16th Night work for her?
She was only a killer
and operated under her command.
Hua Qingzhi
hid information and misled us
when the killers were operating.
Kang Jin,
I'll kill you now
and that promiscuous woman next!
You will meet in hell.