Bye, guys. See ya.
See ya, man.
ECLIPSO
LET THERE BE LIGHT!
Is anyone there?
Anyone there?
Help!
Is anyone there?
NETFLIX PRESENTS
Hey, Tonic Girl here.
For superhero tonicity,
the secret is a balanced diet.
You can trust Eat Salad.
You pick, you mix, you enjoy.
Energy for the whole day!
This morning's weather forecast
is brought to you by Tonic Girl.
Like every year, I'm proud to announce
the start of voting
to rank your favorite superheroes.
Tell us your pick in the comments below.
Who will be this year's winner?
Acteon maybe?
Will Furor beat out Optima?
I know who my money's on.
See you on the 25th for the results…
Nibbles, that's mine.
Don't forget to vote! Your--
Yes?
Sure, I'm on my way.
I'm in my car.
See you soon.
Lieutenant Moreau. What's the story?
Good morning.
Morning.
So?
Right.
Well, the story is arson, as you can see.
One floor is burned out.
Five wounded, three seriously.
The suspects, aged 18-19,
were refused entry to the club.
Unlikely they were packing flamethrowers,
so it's a case for you.
But I got started without you--
Good job. I had a shitshow to handle,
but I've got this now.
-Okay, but--
-Guys, usual procedure. Secure the scene.
Lock it down, the whole caboodle.
What can I say? Thank you and…
and goodbye.
Right.
Where the hell is Forensics?
In no hurry, obviously.
Been and gone already.
-Been and gone?
-Yeah.
Let's stay on top of everything.
Ten a.m., Moreau's here.
Ten a.m., Lorenzi's busting balls.
Did a super-granny hold up a minimart?
Come in.
What the hell took you so long?
I was with Lorenzi. He's in a bad way.
-Been hitting the bottle, I think.
-Right.
Moreau.
Since you stopped working with Pack Royal,
your results have slipped.
I let you handle super-criminality, but…
let's be honest, you do jack shit.
Yes. I mean no. I…
I went through a bad patch--
Lasting ten years?
I'm on it.
I work out, I jog--
Start jogging with Lt. Schaltzmann.
-Come in.
-Morning, Chief.
Sit, Lieutenant.
This is Moreau. You met earlier.
Moreau, this is Lt. Cécile Schaltzmann.
Spent four years in Financial Crimes.
Police academy valedictorian.
So?
So I'm sure you'll get along.
Schaltzmann's keen
to learn your street smarts--
Stop that now.
Stop it!
I tried being nice and understanding
and all that HR management bullshit,
but now it's over.
Got it?
This is not a suggestion. I'm telling you.
This is your new partner.
Thank you, Moreau.
Thank you!
-Excuse me.
-Yes.
"Keen to learn your street smarts"?
-Sure.
-No.
Don't speak for me. Thank you.
-Luxurious.
-Women are on the other side.
-There's a door with a dress on it.
-Hilarious.
We got a call to a high school.
A hostage situation.
Here and here.
Let's roll.
Ready in five.
Moreau?
Lieutenant, take a look.
All units, launch intervention.
What's he doing?
Back up!
-What are you doing?
-Nothing.
I'm unarmed.
Whoa, no kidding.
Don't move!
Candy?
Back up!
Stop! Look at me.
Everyone, hold position.
Wait for orders.
Helps me think.
Keeps me calm.
It's too late.
It's too late for them.
Spent all year busting your balls,
they're gonna flunk.
You're a smart kid.
You have abilities.
Besides that.
You want to ruin everything?
No! Let me go! Stop!
You're hurting me!
The kid says the nightclub wasn't him,
but Forensics says the burns match, and…
he bought these two days ago,
to, and I quote,
"Light up those assholes
once and for all."
He just freaked out.
You have powers or you don't.
-I defer to the specialist.
-Yup.
Come on, let's go.
Hold on.
-Lily, sweetheart!
-Mom!
Are you okay?
Come on.
Go, drive.
Since you ask so nicely.
Out of candy?
So if he didn't torch the nightclub,
who did?
Two guys with the exact same power,
is that possible?
Yeah, if they're related.
But it's not automatic.
Really?
-Shit! There, that's perfect.
-Sorry?
Drop me at the roundabout.
The roundabout?
I can't park here. It's--
No sweat. I can get your ticket canceled.
Wait, I haven't stopped!
-What do I do?
-I don't know.
Improvise. Be creative.
Sure.
Go boil your ass!
Gigantic douchebag.
Hey.
Here. You never saw me.
Dispatch, do you copy?
Henri?
Careful, possible superhuman involvement.
Officer on site requesting backup.
Henri, where are you?
We're sending a patrol…
I'll bust you up.
Monte Carlo! Remember the name.
Monte Carlo…
Henri!
I didn't hear you come in.
What the hell?
I'm just testing a new model.
Needs a few tweaks.
-You good?
-Great.
Aren't you done listening to that?
I'm keeping up to speed.
You don't share anymore.
We don't work together anymore.
That reminds me, I hear there's new blood.
-Schaltzmann, right?
-Yup.
I took a peek at her file.
A real smart cookie.
A girl I'd love to work with
when I'm back in shape.
-She's cool?
-Yeah.
You see? My kind of liaison officer.
A liaison officer worth liaising with.
Watch and learn.
Did you get meatballs?
I got your meatballs.
That fish soup you bought had no relish.
Or croutons.
So I went without dinner.
RESIDENTS RESCUED BY PACK ROYAL
THREE TERRORISTS ARRESTED
FIVE YEARS OF EXPLOITS HAILED BY SJA
LE PACK ROYAL REUNITED
Freeze!
SUPERCOOK
So, Pierre, what have you concocted
for this challenge?
Today, Aurélie,
we're preparing surf 'n' turf.
Now, the really hard part
is getting the cooking times right.
You have a head start.
That is so phony.
Can you identify someone by their powers?
The great detective
needs his old friend Monte Carlo.
Can you or not?
Depends.
Who needs computers when you have this?
And my famous database.
What are the powers?
Flames. Throwing flames.
Hands firing flames six to seven meters.
Okay, fire powers, fireworks, arson…
Here we are.
Brasero.
Forty-two.
In an out of prison
for assault, corruption,
and last but not least, wife-beating.
Basically, a classy guy.
-Children?
-Negative.
Okay, there's enough food
for two or three days in the kitchen.
Four cheese was sold out. I got ham.
And ravioli.
Kind sir, you spoil me.
I'll see you out.
All good?
All good.
Just a little…
You taking your meds?
It's not about medication.
I'm just a bit tired.
Nothing to do with meds.
Take them. Keep the doctor happy.
I want to see Naja.
What's with you? Getting cocky?
It's important.
You demand to see me?
Are you…
Are you the boss?
I'm playing here.
Wanna try?
I have to talk to you.
Good or bad news?
Both.
Monday's headlines:
Another incident linked to a fire power
at a high school in northern Paris.
This comes only a few hours
after a nightclub was torched
a few streets away.
Gang turf battles,
organized crime, or isolated incidents?
That's the big question.
For now, the police have no explanation.
That's all we could salvage.
The substance is the same
found at the high school.
Forensics can't trace it.
The kid won't say who sold it to him.
No leads, and five casualties.
-Fire power reminds me of--
-Brasero.
Forty-two, jail time, petty crimes.
Domestic abuse.
When were you planning on sharing or…?
I'm sharing now.
-He have any children?
-No.
The teen has no links to him.
So Brasero is our number one suspect.
Find him, question him.
Where he lives, how he gets by,
who he sees on the weekends.
Get to work.
Pleased with yourself?
In general or on a specific issue?
Let me make something clear.
I'm not your driver or assistant.
I'm your partner, which means…
sharing intel.
-Can you grasp that concept?
-Sorry.
-Okay, sweetie?
-Yeah.
Look, I have info on Brasero.
After getting out of prison,
he worked at a restaurant in Paris.
He also saw Callista.
He joined her lame rehab program.
How do you know that?
Hero Tracker.
Best on the market. Expensive.
But the sources are reliable.
-I'll call you back.
-What?
Fuck! Stop that!
-Cut that out!
-Back off!
-None of that here!
-He started it!
That's your last warning!
Put the gear away. We're done.
-Idiot!
-Let it go!
See you tomorrow. Smiling.
Great work, girls.
Let's go!
Alex?
Who's the guy you owe money to?
-Don't worry, it's cool.
-I am worried.
Leave that, I'm talking.
What's going on?
It's cool, I said.
How do you attract this shit?
-What happened?
-It's not even my problem.
Forget it.
Here. Spare you a beating.
Keep it.
Take it, don't waste my time.
Thanks.
Stop all that, honestly.
-It's not my fault.
-It never is. Go on.
Getting back in shape?
Sounds like hard work.
-You good?
-Yeah, I'm good.
Monte Carlo?
Look in on him.
What's up?
Guys torching stuff all over.
So you came looking here?
Good job, Detective.
Brasero ring a bell?
I helped him when he got out of prison.
We can't find him.
Look harder. What can I say?
You won't help me?
Great to see you, Moreau.
Happy now? Shoes off.
Can I go in?
Yeah, but maybe your feet are sweaty.
Those socks, they leave marks.
-Who's she?
-Rules are rules.
I forgot to display them.
What really leaves marks is your bullshit.
It's mind-blowing. Moreau!
You know her?
Would you mind answering when I call?
Don't bother waiting.
What's so urgent?
Medical examiner wants to see us.
Are you still working with Callista?
-Seems fishy.
-"Seems fishy"?
Are we back in the '80s?
Are you a thousand years old?
She keeps me in the loop.
This is an investigation.
Seeing people, asking questions.
The basics.
Yeah, well…
Answer your phone, that's all I ask.
Brought in after a fire in a squat
a few days ago.
A camping stove, they said.
All right.
What does it have to do with us?
His toxicological panel matches
the substance you sent to the lab.
-It was in his blood?
-No.
His blood is the substance.
Establishing cause of death was tricky,
but we finally figured it out.
Exsanguination.
His blood was drained
to make the substance.
Puncture marks here and here.
He was fed by a tube.
I think the idea
was to keep him alive.
So he had a long, painful death.
Any identification?
Arthur Laguens. Brasero.
The neck tattoo confirms it.
Never seen anything like it.
I'd pay to talk with the guy who did it.
He's a genius!
He's not a genius.
A torturer and killer is not a genius.
Excuse me, I…
Brasero's dead?
But how?
What was his job?
Waiter.
Were you happy with him?
He hated being the freak show
for everyone.
People would happily pay
to see him do his…
tricks.
You ended it?
Yes, I did.
He refused to use his powers when we…
You know.
Normal guys, boring. Guys with powers…
He had a reason for starting therapy?
He'd been depressed since leaving prison.
He was withdrawn
and struggled to accept his abilities.
Last time I saw him,
he looked in a bad way, he'd lost weight.
I thought, "Another one on a diet."
Not many ladies voting.
All you heroines, hit those comments.
I'd like to thank my sponsor, Rubie's.
If you want to rock the mask
and superhero style,
the best costumes are at Rubie's.
Excuse me, may I?
Yeah.
Lily, right?
Enjoying the video?
Yeah.
You're in tenth grade, right?
How's it going?
I know high school can be tough.
It's okay.
It's just I weird people out.
Who?
Those chicks over there?
Forget 'em, they're morons.
Look…
If you need to talk, look me up anytime.
I'd like that.
Or call this number.
It really helped me.
Who is this?
Someone you won't weird out.
See ya.
You know what I'm like.
I glide and I slide.
Well, glide out and quit stealing booze.
Promise, buddy. I promise.
Long day?
-Sorry?
-I said, "Long day?"
Yep.
-Go if you want.
-I'm good.
I feel great.
So, triple espresso,
but we're out of Red Bull.
Sorry.
Thanks.
No problem.
Get some sleep. Nothing's happening.
Leaving things as they are.
-Thanks.
-See you tomorrow.
Quick question.
How many wounded were treated
at the nightclub?
-Five.
-Five? Are you sure?
Shit, there are six on the video.
If you're innocent,
you wait for treatment, right?
On my way.
-How long's he been here?
-Admitted two days ago.
When we saw your alert, he was a match.
This way.
I've got this.
Amine, isn't it?
Lieutenants Moreau and Schaltzmann.
Hi.
-How'd you do that?
-I told the doc.
Burned myself while ironing.
-While ironing?
-Yeah.
On your shoulder?
Yeah.
Isn't that you?
Can't see zip. Quality's shit.
-"Quality's shit"?
-Terrible.
Maybe we should ask the bouncer?
-What bouncer?
-That one.
In flames and out of a job.
-Don't blame me.
-Shall we bring him in?
Sure, let's get to know him.
I never met him.
Wasting your time.
Who's your supplier?
Of what?
I'm so sorry! Apologies.
Did I hurt you?
Hold on, let's unstick this.
It hurts here?
Hurts like hell. But that's nothing
compared to what's next.
What's next?
Well, if we don't find the antidote…
What antidote?
You didn't check for side effects?
You don't know?
Ask your buddy,
the guy you were with at the club.
No, of course, you can't because…
by the time we got to him, you know,
he'd exploded.
Bits everywhere.
What I suggest is,
you tell us who sold you the stuff.
We'll find him and get you the antidote.
Or in 24 hours,
we'll see if you explode like your buddy.
I want that stuff.
The antidote.
Talk.
There was a dude…
selling it outside school.
What was his name?
His name?
Ismael. His name's Ismael.
-Ismael what?
-I dunno.
He had his head shaved on one side.
And an earring.
Maybe lives in Bluebell Towers.
Shall we go?
-Moreau.
-Yes.
And the antidote?
So, anybody notice some stock is missing?
Any thoughts?
For example, did anyone think,
I don't know…
"Hey, we're a box short"?
Anything like that?
No?
Perhaps someone noticed
Ismael's dropped off the radar?
-You don't find that odd?
-The guy doesn't show. Shit happens.
You, shut it!
Chewing gum!
So, none of you geniuses here
made the connection?
Nobody thinks,
"Stock's missing, a guy's missing,
maybe the shithead's fucking us over"?
Nobody?
No, nobody.
Except Rudy.
So we're all gonna thank Rudy
for raising the bar.
Thanks, Rudy, for raising the bar.
What we're doing here isn't just business.
We're not just here
to make some fucking money!
This is about justice.
There you go. So find Ismael for me.
Wherever he is, find him.
Or I'll shoot one of you.
You. I'll shoot you.
Find him.
Beat it.
How's it going with the girl?
-Don't worry, I--
-I'll worry if I want.
-You okay?
-Yeah, you have visitors.
Police! Stop!
Lost him. He went back down.
He's in there. Come on.
Hi.
Do you have…
the cola candy in the little bottles?
Not the tangy ones, the others?
Do you have them?
I'll take a look.
Police! On the floor!
He had the stuff on him.
What the heck!
She told me to help myself.
You wanna drive?
Of course.
Schaltzmann.
-Thanks.
-After you, sir.
Come on!
Shoot! Yeah, shoot!
-You in?
-That shit's dangerous.
If it was, why would they sell it?
Plus, it's free anyway.
-Pure profit!
-Not interested, okay?
One hit, and you're a new man.
-Nothing to lose.
-What's going on?
We're waiting for you.
Nothing.
-You planning a heist?
-No.
A heist, why go there? We're just talking.
Sure you are.
You coming?
Yeah, just doing my laces.
Right.
Where's this from?
I don't know.
-You don't know?
-No.
What I know is that Brasero is dead.
You like the sound of "homicide"
as an extra line on your résumé?
-I don't know.
-Still don't know?
Where's the laboratory?
Well?
Forget it. He won't talk.
-Twenty euros says she makes him.
-I'm in.
How many sellers?
I don't know.
That's all you know how to say?
How many buyers did you have?
-I don't know.
-Shit!
Nothing doing, he's playing me.
I'll try.
Wait! Let's lose the cameras
and leave me alone with him.
From now on, decaf for the lady.
You good? You need anything?
Let's have a chat.
Well? Ismael sing for you?
We have a lot in common.
Could become my new bestie.
He won't say a word.
Anything on him?
Conviction for dealing hash, no big deal.
So what do we do now?
We eat.
Seriously, you have a food issue.
Yes, when I'm hungry,
I can't think straight.
I'll get us takeout.
There's a restaurant I know.
You're gonna love it.
Chicken.
-Hot sauce?
-No sauce.
-Drink?
-No.
Pay over there.
Excuse me, are you Mister Cold?
That's me.
-Can I get a selfie?
-Be my guest.
Thanks.
Henri, no time.
At last! How do I get you
to pick up the phone?
-Do I need to grow tits?
-Great idea.
Is it true there's a drug
that gives you superpowers? For real?
-Looks that way.
-Folks will believe anything!
Having superpowers
means having a mission!
With great power comes…
comes great…
-It's not…
-I'm going into a meeting…
-Wait, I have something for you.
-Go ahead.
I've piqued Mr. Detective's curiosity.
When I heard Brasero was dead,
no thanks to you, I might add,
I thought I'd see
if there were other missing superheroes.
And?
Guess what, there's a guy named
"Eclipso the Enchanter."
MISSING
Not well-known, small-time conjurer.
Some advertising work, nothing major.
Super uncool, basically.
What's his superpower?
Blindness.
He blinds people remotely.
A flop, career-wise.
Anyway, more interestingly,
this guy Eclipso
has been a no-show the whole week.
Stay here, don't go out!
-You okay?
-I can't see.
-Don't move.
-I can't see!
All units, North Precinct under attack!
Copy, North Precinct.
All units, request immediate backup…
You okay?
-How many are there?
-I don't know.
Don't move.
Get out!
Guys!
I'm up here!
Here!
I'm here!
Okay? It's me, Moreau.
Get in there!
Bring him out!
Keep going!
-Careful!
-Don't move!
Get her!
I got this!
-Freeze!
-Grab her, now!
Hands up!
Police!
On the floor!
Just taking samples of the explosives,
then we're done.
Keep me posted.
Better?
Any news on Guillot?
Yeah, he'll make it.
Any left?
She sees everything before it happens?
No, not everything. She…
No, she gets these flashes
with certain people. Like…
Flash!
Without warning.
The flash comes without warning.
And so, did you two…
No.
No, are you kidding me?
So, no girlfriend?
No boyfriend either?
So, no kids, I guess.
How about a fish? A rat?
I have a little cat who's… dumb.
What happened earlier?
What do you mean?
Is there something I should know?
Schaltzmann!
They're ready for your statement. Coming?
Listen to me!
I don't wanna die! Why would I lie?
I swear to God, I was working alone!
I didn't wanna share the cash,
it was just me!
Chin up a little.
Chin up.
There, stop.
Good.
-What are you doing?
-Hold still.
Really suits you.
You won't do it again?
-Got it now?
-Yeah.
Kill him.
No, stop!
Stop! Fuck! Are you serious?
Naja, please!
Let me go! Naja!
I saw a guy with powers!
Stop. What?
I saw a guy.
His name's Moreau. He's a cop.
Made a chick float in mid-air.
-In mid-air?
-Swear to God!
That's good.
What the fuck? Stop!
Guys!
In mid-air.
Find Moreau for me, please.
-Has Alex left?
-No, he's in there.
Where are Karim and Vincent?
Better things to do?
Don't ask me.
Where are they?
Forget it, you're not their mom.
Why do I bust my ass for you dopes?
I'm no snitch, that's all.
Beat it.
-You three are banned.
-What?
-Beat it!
-Hold on, let me explain.
-It's them, not me.
-Who?
I told them I wasn't interested.
Not interested in what?
Go easy, guys. This is serious shit.
And it's free, right?
Yeah, free tryout.
-You stoked?
-I'm stoked.
You're not stoked?
Sure, it's just…
We're doing this.
-All good?
-You bet we're good.
It's me.
We gotta review the dosage.
Tragedy tonight in northern Paris.
Two teens were found dead
after inhaling the mystery substance
that's been circulating recently.
After the fire and blinding powers,
a reworking of the formula
has now taken two lives.
Law enforcement recommends caution
to anyone coming into contact
with the blue substance.
We have wiretaps on Ismael's friends
and a squad is staking out his place.
But we've turned up nothing so far.
Hold on.
I need your help. It's Lily.
Come with me.
All good?
Her daughter's missing.
Take her statement.
I'll check out her place.
Nothing.
I found nothing.
They must know she has powers.
We've gotta find her.
Now you want to help?
They tested their shit on two of my kids.
They didn't survive.
-I realized that Lily--
-Beat it. Go.
Moreau, call me back.
Let's go.
Not until we know where Moreau is.
-Let's go!
-Wait.
Wait for what? Let's go now.
What the hell? Come on!
Now we go!
Drive!
What are you doing?
It won't move!
Police! Get out!
Fuck! It's him.
Give me the gun.
Give me the gun!
Moreau, stay with us.
Stay with us, please.
Come on, help me.
Help me!
One, two, three.
Come on.
All right.
I'm coming!
Moreau's one of you guys?
We met Moreau on an intervention.
Gigaman spotted his potential
and wanted to recruit him.
Did you know?
That's how Moreau
became our liaison officer.
Chairmont never knew about his powers.
He was so flattered we wanted his help,
he didn't think twice.
How long did you keep it up?
Not long.
Stop!
You okay?
Get his pal?
Have you practiced?
A bit.
But I'm not sure if I can…
Take cover then.
What?
If you can't handle it, I'll go alone.
That's close enough.
Back up!
-Put your gun down.
-Stop or I'll shoot!
Put your gun down.
Let me go or I'll kill you!
Don't be a fool.
I said stop.
Don't move.
Moreau never forgave himself.
He gave up on his powers and…
I found another use for mine.
-We should've kept at it.
-At what?
Look at you, Monte.
And Lily?
Where does she fit in?
She's Gigaman's daughter.
She was five years old then.
Moreau had this on him.
A telephone number.
Most likely found it at Lily's.
Elisabeth Caghieri.
Psychologist
specializing in superhuman abilities.
Hold on…
She was Brasero's shrink.
We interviewed her.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-I'll call Chairmont.
-And tell him what?
That Moreau has powers
and we played him for ten years?
He'll love that.
You have a better idea?
Thank you. I'm making progress.
Gosh, sorry.
-No problem, see you next week.
-Okay.
Thank you, Doctor.
Next.
Come in.
Why did you need to see me so urgently?
How can I put it?
It's a kind of…
knot.
A knot of anxiety.
Something that constricts me, literally.
A dull pain.
You mean the pressure
is too much to handle?
-Sit down and we'll talk.
-Can I lie down?
Let's get to know each other first.
-Of course.
-Take a seat.
So, tell me about your powers.
Could I get a glass of water? I'm…
-Yes, of course.
-Thanks.
Be right back.
-You're…
-Here.
You're so kind.
-Much better already.
-So, your powers.
I first became aware of them
in April 1976.
Dad had gone to buy cigarettes.
I never saw him again.
Is it not by the depth of his wounds
that one takes the measure of a man?
Yesterday, I woke up
floating above the bed.
For the first time in ages.
I think you have gained
an enormous amount of control.
Often the nightmare wakes me.
And then…
Their father is living this experience
with them,
sharing this power,
and so I feel excluded,
as if I cannot understand…
PSYCHOLOGIST SPECIALIZING IN DISORDERS
LINKED TO SUPERHUMAN ABILITIES
When you're stressed, the thing to do
is to picture people butt naked.
That's my life.
Seeing through clothes
means no mystery. My libido…
On a day-to day basis, it's too much.
I see her naked all the time,
so to rekindle desire…
What scares you?
If I tell her, what'll happen?
What will she think?
That I'll put her in danger?
Your anxiety is over her reaction.
Exactly. She loves me as I am.
Without any powers.
If I tell her,
it might break something between us.
She may think I'm gonna hurt her.
Let's continue this next week.
I'll see you out.
THE COLLABORATION BETWEEN PROF. DATO
AND DR. CAGHIERI ENDS ABRUPTLY
DUE TO AN ETHICAL DISAGREEMENT
Hello, Lily, this is Elisabeth Caghieri.
You missed today's appointment.
I'm worried.
Please call me.
There he is.
She was my most brilliant
Head of Research ever,
but we had to sever ties with her.
What do you do here exactly?
Fundamental research on superpowers.
Identification, analysis,
transmission, reproduction…
Anything that helps explain
how it all works.
What's to explain?
You have powers or not, period.
Right?
What was Caghieri working on?
Molecular and physiopathological causes
of mental illness in superhumans.
I don't understand.
The link between
psychiatric disorders in superhumans
and their powers.
-Mathias, it's me.
-What do you want?
Where's Lily? What have you done?
Don't worry about her.
You promised you'd leave her alone.
I promised no such thing.
Your job's done. It's not your problem.
A young boy's parents asked for our help.
He had a severe sociopathological disorder
due to his induction powers.
What powers?
Hypnosis,
depriving others of their free will.
I see.
Basically, no one could say no to him?
The parents had no special abilities.
They were overwhelmed.
They wanted us
to rid their son of his powers,
thinking that would solve his problems.
I refused.
It's not our decision to make.
I supplied you enough people.
This has to stop.
People?
Morons with two-bit powers.
People are dying. It's gone too far.
It's not helping, it's killing you.
All this is your fault.
Look, she's a young girl.
So? You'd give your life for her?
Let me at least check that she's okay.
If you want.
And Caghieri?
She conducted the experiment in secret.
She meant well.
And it worked.
She successfully eradicated his powers.
But to no avail. The child went mad
and murdered his parents.
He was declared of unsound mind
and institutionalized.
We kept it out of the press.
I made sure Elisabeth
never got another research post.
Mathias Najarovski, 35 years old.
Goes by Naja.
He used Caghieri's skills
to reproduce powers.
And I'm betting his hideout
is also his lab.
How many guys?
A dozen, maybe more.
Let's do it.
How? The hideout's an absolute maze.
If they have Lily's powers, it's suicide.
-Whatever, we can take them--
-Cut the crap!
You have Parkinson's, don't you get it?
The police must be looking for her.
You're in pain?
What do you think?
Mathias, she's 15. Let her go, please.
I was ten.
Wasn't a problem for you then.
I regret it every day.
Keep it up.
No, Mathias, don't do that.
-You're gonna--
-Don't tell me what to do!
Ever again.
All right.
If you want to keep her alive,
she needs Midodrine.
Glucose isn't enough
to keep her blood pressure up.
Do it.
You need to wake up now.
Without you, it's hopeless.
Can you hear me, Moreau?
What's the point of having superpowers?
Schaltzmann!
-Police.
-I want to speak to an inspector.
-What's up?
-It's about the missing superhumans.
She's ratting him out.
Act fast. He's holding a young girl.
Please hold, putting you through.
If Chairmont wades in,
it'll be a bloodbath.
More on tonight's latest incident.
In Rosny, near Paris, two police officers
were attacked by two individuals
who had robbed an ATM.
According to surveillance camera footage,
the suspects fired
destructive blue lasers.
The two individuals then
caused mayhem in a nearby park.
The injured officers
were rushed to a hospital
where they remain in a critical condition.
We have visitors. Check it out!
Rudy, with me. Move it, guys!
Wake up!
Go stash that!
What about those two?
The kid stays with me.
Right? You're staying with me.
Wake up!
Truck keys!
-What about me?
-Improvise.
Mess up and I'll mess you up.
Let's go!
Let me go.
Put it down, son!
Holy shit.
Out of shape, sweetie.
I've heard a lot about you.
A pleasure to meet you.
Go on.
Lily?
What's that fool doing?
-I'm on it!
-Wait!
No problem. Overshot!
Let me go!
Stay with me!
Stay!
Don't leave me alone.
We're gonna make it out of here, okay?
Together.
Head down.
Move.
You owe me an explanation.
Everybody in position.
Leave us alone now.
We're tired.
You okay?
Hold it!
Take him.
A few days on, let's revisit
Pack Royal's incredible intervention
to rescue two kidnapped superhumans.
As we've learned more
about the past of "Naja,"
one question remains one week later:
Who is the mystery superhero
who overpowered this dangerous criminal?
Who is he? What are his powers?
Nobody has an answer to those questions.
But for sure,
we haven't heard the last of the man
the public has named Titan.
You okay?
I brought you these.
My guiltiest pleasure.
You've got a supername now
and all that.
I don't know if I could do it.
We can talk if you want.
Rest up.
-Hey.
-Yes?
Thank you.
I cannot keep him.
Not with his… stuff.
It's against the rules.
-But, sir--
-Quiet!
You drop out of sight
to lead an illegal investigation.
You put civilians in danger.
I should fire you too.
I'm reassigning you.
Pack Royal Liaison Officer.
Scram, I have work to do.
We're agreed, right?
You haven't got…
anything special?
No, nothing special.
-Well?
-Your Air-widget thing doesn't work.
I keep sending
and absolutely nothing happens.
Hurry, it's started!
Know what? I'll use my old cable.
Nothing like the old techniques.
There we are.
Nine superheroes are still in the race.
In ninth place, look who it is…
Mister Cold!
Mister Cold, with one breath…
What a has-been!
Retirement's not bad. Nice and quiet.
Moreau shops for you, I cook for you.
Where do you see a retiree?
Who saved you from that big dope?
God knows what you were doing
with your tiny fists.
Nothing.
I was watching you. Watching you with…
great admiration.
"Great admiration." Right.
Enjoy it, kiddo, because mark my words,
it's comeback time for Monte Carlo!
-It is?
-Yes.
Maybe get a style makeover then.
-You're talking style?
-Yes.
You, half-punk, half-Smurf?
"Half-Smurf"!
-All good?
-Yep.
Is Moreau here?
On the balcony.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm talking about the beautiful Callista.
She stands in 4th place…
Who's the punk now?
Who's the Smurf?
Where am I? In…
Fourth.
-Where am I?
-Fourth.
I wasn't sure.
My ass.
Online competitions are rigged.
It's a total scam.
Monte Carlo, you're in!
-Where am I?
-Third!
You've been voting, and MC,
Monte Carlo, is your third superhero!
Amazing.
Yeah.
-Aren't you pleased?
-Me, you know…
As if I take any notice of that.
I see who's headed for first.
Here.
What's this?
Where'd you get it?
I had it made for you.
I thought it might come in handy.
And I heard that North Precinct
has a new liaison officer.
And that she's totally tip-top.
HOW I BECAME A SUPERHERO
Subtitle translation by: Simon John