[English subtitles are available]
Jack.
What is this place?
Last time I said something wrong.
I shouldn't have said that about you.
None of this matters anymore.
Congratulations, Si Yan.
You have completed the mission.
You will wake up soon.
Really?
That's not right.
I am not yet the Head Matron.
So how could I complete my mission?
Where is Qi Yi?
Qi Yi! Qi Yi!
Who the hell did this?
How did he become like this?
What's going on?
A person who looks like you
killed him with a hairpin.
What?
Who pretended to be me?
Si Yan.
Don't stay here anymore.
You're about to wake up.
To wake up?
No.
I can't wake up.
Jack.
I beg you.
Please help me.
Please help me save him, okay?
It's okay if you need to read a file,
ask the system for help,
or even send me back to the initial interface.
I just want him to come back to life.
I beg you!
For Qi Yi?
I can't leave like this.
I can't let him die because of me.
Even if you restart the game,
you still can't change the result
that Qi Yi, the NPC, will die.
Are you sure you want to refuse
to wake up for him?
I know.
You will never understand how I feel now.
But without Qi Yi,
my waking up will be meaningless.
For him,
I can give up everything.
So no matter what the result is,
I want to try again.
I can save him.
Really?
But if I saved him,
then one of the people in the game
would be gone.
Even so,
are you still going to save him?
No one is more important than him.
No one.
I just want him to be alive.
Right.
No one is more important than him.
Fine.
Until then,
cooperate with me
to handle the situation right now.
But you can tell no one about this matter.
It must be confidential.
You can't even tell Yi.
Can you see me?
Si Yan, what's wrong with you?
It's before the autumn hunt.
What's going on?
Am I reborn?
So Qi Yi is not dead now.
I still have a chance.
Prince Xiu,
before it's too late,
you have to cancel the fall hunt right away.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not kidding with you.
Then why did you cancel
the autumn hunt out of blue?
Do you know that
the autumn hunt is the most important event
in the East Mansion every year?
I know that.
You may not believe me when I say this,
but something bad will happen
during the fall hunt this time.
At that time, someone will die.
How can you just stand by and ignore that
someone's life is at risk?
Si Yan, are you drunk, or do you have a fever?
What nonsense!
Someone will die? Who?
The clansmen are now coming to the East Mansion.
If the fall hunt is canceled now,
I will be the first one to die.
Prince Xiu.
Moreover!
Now the fall hunt is the only chance
to annul our engagement.
Are you really going to marry me?
That's not a good deal for me.
Fire! Fire!
Come on, someone!
What's going on?
Your Highness,
I just found a black shadow
jumping into the courtyard,
and then the wall was on fire.
Assassin?
Could that be the assassin
who assassinated Qi Yi?
Yi is too narrow-minded.
There are assassins.
Be careful.
Thank you.
Where is the assassin?
Brother Xiu,
an assassin broke into the mansion
and set fire to it.
Brother Da has led people
to investigate the west side.
You go with me to investigate the west side.
Go put out the fire!
Yes!
Brother Xiu, what's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just so happy to see you.
So it was you who set the fire.
Yi, go catch the assassin first.
Otherwise, more people will come,
and it will be hard to explain.
I'm not afraid of the cold.
I'm not afraid to die either.
I'm just afraid that
I don't understand you.
Qi Yi.
This time I will protect you.
Prince Xiu is so romantic.
Yes. Yes. Yeah.
Tell Prince Xiu
to change all the chiffon.
Have you seen Prince Yi?
Go, go, go!
Stop.
I know you're in a hurry.
These linen curtain hats are
thin, sun-protective,
waterproof, sweatproof and easy to carry.
It is suitable for masters.
This is way much better
than a chiffon curtain hat.
Don't dawdle.
You guys can go and give it to your maters.
Go, go, go!
I have been waiting for more than 2 hours.
It's my business.
Don't worry about it.
You'd better handle
all the hats you have right now.
If you can't deal with that properly,
how much money will be lost?
It's such a waste.
How did she know?
Is Prince Yi in there?
No.
Why do these tents look exactly the same?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Where exactly is Qi Yi?
Right.
I can fly a kite to find him.
I must hurry to find Lan Miao.
Si Yan, why are you here?
Don't cover.
I know who you are making it for.
Lan Miao, lend me the kite.
Qi Yi.
It's an emergency.
I don't have time to explain.
I made it for Prince Bao.
Qi Yi.
Si Yan.
Why are you here?
Why can't I be here?
About curtain hats,
I can help you solve that problem.
How are you going to thank me properly?
Have you seen Prince Yi?
Your husband is right here.
Why are you looking for Prince Yi?
Mrs. Huang is watching from behind.
Play well.
I don't have time for this right now.
Where are you going in such a hurry?
To fly a kite.
Kite, please.
Take me to find Qi Yi.
Didn't you write that wrong?
Shouldn't that be "Cheer up, Prince Xiu"?
Don't rush to be jealous first.
I want to tell you something.
Just now, Brother Xiu hugged you.
And now you come to me.
Brother Yi. Si Yan.
Lan Miao gave you this.
So it is her.
Out of no reason,
why did Si Yan ask to change the purple chiffon?
What was she thinking?
Yi.
Come.
What do you think?
This is your first time hosting a fall hunt.
Naturally, you have to
do something different from the previous years.
You have a point.
I think it's not dramatic at all.
The color is great.
Why the purple chiffon is still here?
Change it now.
Otherwise, His Majesty will ask you
to change the setting.
Prince Xiu,
change
and rearrange everything.
How do you know what my father thinks?
I...
I guessed.
How pity, Prince Xiu.
You need to rearrange everything now.
So mean.
In my opinion,
it's not that hard to set up a hunting ground.
It's all about simplifying.
Just leave some flowers and plants to decorate.
And get someone to chop firewood
to boil water for tea.
That will be idyllic
and bring some freshness during the hot days.
That sounds like a great idea.
Then, please...
I'm not going.
There is no need.
I'll just get some footboys
to take care of that.
Prince Xiu, do you care about her?
You have already started
to protect your fiancée.
Lady Si Yan.
You've got a lot of charm.
Prince Xiu didn't mean that.
I just happen to do
something else.
Prince Xiu's clothing is torn.
I'll go get him a new dress.
Si Yan is really concerned about Prince Xiu.
Why don't Your Highness come with me?
I do not know where Prince Xiu's clothes are.
Let's go.
My clothing?
Is my dress torn?
Why do you drag me here?
Let's stay here, okay?
Chat, or do whatever you like.
Just don't go out.
You were the one who set the fire last night.
If you dare to go out,
I'll tell everyone about that.
Are you threatening me?
As long as you don't go out,
I can do anything for you.
I really do not understand you more and more.
What the hell do you want?
You really can't go out.
It's dangerous to go out.
Stop making these weak excuses.
Is it in your heart that
I,
Brother Xiu
and Brother Bao
are so ridiculous?
It's not like that. You misunderstood me.
No one will act like a fool,
willing to be fooled by you again and again.
It's you I like.
You have no idea about what I think.
I did these all for you.
The reason why I took the task
is that I was set up by someone.
My engagement with Prince Xiu
is only a temporary one.
We planed to get the first prize
in the autumn hunt
and go beg His Majesty to cancel the engagement.
Do I make myself clear now?
Then why didn't you make yourself clear earlier?
I almost thought you were really going to
marry Brother Xiu.
Aren't I telling you now?
About the annulment of your engagement,
I'll try to fix that.
No need.
No need?
So you mean
you regret it again?
No, I don't regret it.
Is there anything more important
than annul your engagement?
Yes.
Today,
there's nothing
more important than you.
I'm sorry.
I have to protect you.
Wait for me.
Qi Yi.
Hold on for a while.
I'll be back soon.
Someone hid an arrow here.
So it's a plan.
I won't let you get your way.
Prince Xiu is in the carriage.
He wants to talk to you.
Prince Xiu?
My lady, I have deceived Si Yan
into the carriage as you ordered.
She should be in the misty forest by now.
Thank you.
Where's my arrow?
Father, we should go this way.
Go.
What kind of brother is Yi?
He left without telling us,
and took away my carefully selected horse.
Luckily, I have let you arrange it in advance today,
or else how can we win the first prize today?
How are things over there?
All done.
Father, since you are determined
to let me get married,
don't blame me for being unkind.
Yun Li, act accordingly in a while.
I'll make you a knife case when I'm back.
Go.
Xiu.
Are there any beasts you're talking about?
Father, I saw it with my own eyes
when I prospect this place.
We should go further inside the woods?
Maybe we'll find one.
Wait.
Why do I feel like
we just passed by this place?
No, father.
You have to be patient.
Go.
Congrats, Da, you've caught your first prey.
Thanks for your assist, Tong.
You're welcome, Prince Da.
It's because you are good at archery.
Da, why are you looking at me like this?
No-nothing.
Prince Da, what reward do you want
for the best hunter prize?
I just want my father to be proud of me.
It doesn't matter what the reward is.
Prince Xiu and Prince Yi
have been engaged.
Have you never thought about marriage?
I aspire to a great career.
Marriage is not in my plan.
But...
But what?
But it would be nice if Tong had a sister.
That's a good one.
Only by killing you
can I become the real Miss Min.
Watch out!
You
are a woman?
Is the target of mine
related to the lotus flower?
How can you do this?
I don't want to see you anymore.
Prince Da.
I couldn't control myself.
I almost thought I liked men.
Prince Da, I've been in love with you
since the first time I met you.
But I'm just a maid.
I couldn't get close to you,
that's why I decided to do this
Dressing up as a man
is the only way I can think of to get close to you.
But, Prince Da,
You are not nervous talking to me.
I don't stutter anymore.
I really don't stutter in front of you.
Prince Da, I'm so happy for you
that your trouble is gone.
I shouldn't do this in the first place.
Prince Da, please punish me.
-You?
Where is Qi Yi?
Tell me! Where is Qi Yi?
What are you doing?
Oh, my god. Why are you here?
I hid you so well.
What are you doing here?
Your knockout drops are not strong.
I fainted because I was unguarded.
Get out of here!
Besides, it should be me asking you.
Why did you do that to me?
What are you up to?
Why do I feel like
I've been here?
Not only been here, but you died here.
Leave now.
I don't care how.
You don't know how sad I was!
Is there something you didn't tell me?
Qi Yi.
I've been having a hunch lately.
I had dreams.
Yeah, what I have dreamed of
always happen in reality.
I dreamed that
you had a detoxicating elixir on you, right?
How did you know?
I also dreamed that someone would hurt you.
You will die!
Someone would hurt me?
Here?
Oh no, he's coming soon.
Trust me.
I can't explain things to you now.
I'll dress like you
to lure the killer out.
No way. I'll do it myself.
I can't let you do that.
I'll be a shadow
and lure the killer out.
That way we can live.
I am smart.
You have to trust me.
I trust you, too.
You can definitely protect me.
I warned you.
Don't forget who you are.
Yet you've thwarted our plan
again and again.
Did you forget who fed you?
Who got you into East City?
Why do you have to kill Qi Yi?
What's the reason for Master to hate Qi Yi?
Who is Master?
How dare you ask that?
As for the assassination of Qi Yi,
shouldn't it be a task of yours?
What?
Did you really fall for him?
I knew it.
How can Master let you
go on an assassination plan alone?
Say it.
Where is Qi Yi?
Qi Yi, watch out!
What a pair of love birds.
But tonight,
both of you are going to be killed by me.
Qi Yi, you lived for now
doesn't mean you'll always be lucky.
Staying with that woman
will eventually kill you!
You'll regret it!
Father,
why don't we take a break?
We seem lost.
I told you to specialize in
horse back riding and hunting,
but you never listened.
You are a prince.
How can you be like this?
I'm ashamed!
Father, wait for me.
I have never been good at this.
It's useless to learn it.
I think it's not that you're not good at it,
it's that you pretend to be.
Is it something that I have done to you
that makes you so reluctant
to show people who you really are?
All you do is
pretend to be an idiot and hang out with girls.
I think that's fine too.
There is wine to drink, music to sing,
and flowers to admire.
Isn't it happy?
You seem happy enough.
You are the prince of East City.
How can you stay with a person
from nowhere every day?
My reputation
is all ruined by you.
Don't hurt him.
Are you saying I can't do that?
Father, we all want to do different things.
Everyone's path is different.
Even if you get lost,
you will see special scenery.
Am I right?
You can't ask me
to be like Da and Yi.
As for Yun Li,
he has lived a miserable life,
orphaned and displaced since childhood.
Since I brought him to East City,
I won't ask him to leave.
Do you know his true identity?
He is a descendant
of the notorious Yun family in South Jiuzhai.
The Yun family specializes in crooked ways.
They make poison and harm people!
If you keep such a person by your side,
it'll be like taking a tiger as a pet.
He is different from the ruthless Yun family.
How?
What do you know? You know nothing!
I know that
he cares about me wholeheartedly
and he will never hurt me.
I also know that
he is the person I must protect with my life.
Yun Li's father died in East City.
Do you know that?
Father,
let's gt out of here.
Did you hear wolves howling?
Father,
please cancel my engagement with that maid,
or I don't think I can find a way out.
Keep up.
Hurry.
Is anything wrong with the Second Lady's tent?
The Second Lady felt unwell.
She's resting in the tent.
Don't you see that we are all outside the tent?
Let's search elsewhere.
I'm fine. Let me walk.
The road is bumpy, don't jiggle.
Do you have a lot to ask me?
Yes.
But,
I'd rather wait until you want to tell me.
Qi Yi.
What?
That's a sneak attack.
Too many things
feel familiar today.
But there's one thing
I'm sure it didn't happen.
What is true and what is false?
It's like the moon in the sky.
At this moment,
it's meaningless to struggle about that.
Some people may think that
what happens in this game world is fake.
But these two unique memories
will eventually become some kind of reality.
No one is more important than him.
Si Yan
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't be selfish.
But for you,
I can give up everything.
I love you, Si Yan.
Who are you?
I am your exclusive butler, Jack.
You are so handsome.
Too bad I'm the only one who can see you.
What a waste!
Miss Si Yan.
I am only wearing it for you.
In the whole world,
you are the best.
It's my job to make you happy.
Such a handsome butler.
I can see you but not touch you.
Looks like you're useful after all.
Try some.
Cheers.
Thank you.
Jack, time-out.
Miss Si Yan.
There are only two time-outs.
You have used both of them.
Today, you can have a day off.
You are not the butler, but my friend, Li.
Do you like it?
I love you, Si Yan.
Saying it out loud,
makes me feel better
in the endless darkness.