Hello. I'm R.L. Stine.
I write the Goosebumps books.
You know, werewolf legends
haunted people's dreams
for hundreds of years.
Imagine... a full moon,
someone beneath it...
- [ Wolf Howling ]   - slowly turning
into a ferocious wolf creature.
Our parents and our grandparents
loved to be scared...
by the classic werewolf tales,
and I hope you will enjoy
"The Werewolf of Fever Swamp."
I'll see you after the show.
Right now
I'm going for a quick bite.
[ Woman ]
What a great space.
It's twice as big
as your old bedroom, Grady.
It's kind of... used.
Well, it's rustic.
Rustic's in these days.
Is this a bloodstain?
No.
That's just, um, dry rot.
[ Girl Screams ]
- Ew!
- Emily, what's wrong?
That's it. That is it.
I don't care what you and Dad say,
I am not living here.
- What is it now?
- The medicine chest.
- Cool!
- Oh!
It's a little corn snake.
- It was a corn snake.
- Oh, gross.
Hi there.
Give the snake an earring,
it'll look like your old boyfriend.
- Snakes don't have ears.
- Mom!
Emily, we live near a swamp now.
You're gonna have to get used
to things that crawl and slither.
- Besides yourself.
- Oh!
Grady, set this free in the swamp.
Me?
Have fun.
- Mom!
- Go on.
A little wildlife never hurt anybody.
Just don't go too far in, okay?
[ Animal Screeching ]
[ Rustling, Whistling ]
- [ Frog Croaking ]
- [ Grady ] Wait a minute.
It wasn't this far.
[ Croaking Continues ]
I'm not lost.
I am not lost.
[ Emily ] When summer vacation
is over, I'm out of here.
A boarding school would be
better than this hole.
You know, Emily, you're not the
only one that doesn't wanna be here.
But at least I'm trying
to make the best of it.
After running into that weirdo
in the swamp yesterday,
I thought you'd be on my side.
Mom and Dad have been talking
about this experiment for years,
and I'm not gonna be
the one to ruin it.
Gee. And the one time
I was counting on you.
Ohh!
- [ Snickering ]
- Ohh!
[ Birds Chirping ]
[ Braying ]
Everything's off the truck.
Great. [ Sighs ]
This place is beginning
to feel like home already.
So, uh, when
do you set the deer loose?
Oh, not for a while yet.
Your mom and I have to tag 'em...
and make sure the trip here
hasn't sent any of 'em into shock.
[ Sighs ]
Did you ever think...
that you would be spending
your teenage years
in a place like fever swamp?
Not in my wildest dreams.
Hey, this is a great opportunity
for you, you know?
Most kids don't get to
expand their horizons like this.
Ah, I'll bet you'll make
lots of new friends.
Oh, yeah, right. Like that
psycho I ran into last night.
He is not a psycho.
He's a-- He's a hermit.
I asked about him
in town this morning.
He lost his family a while ago,
and ever since then,
he's been a little strange.
But he just lives off the land,
doesn't harm anybody.
I don't feel right about this place.
It feels so--
It just feels so weird.
Look, Grady.
You see these deer here?
Up until a couple of days ago,
they had never seen a swamp before.
Now your mom and I get to study
how they're gonna adapt.
Believe me, they will,
because it's just natural to adapt.
And pretty soon,
they're gonna love it here.
And so are you.
Very interesting.
Glad I could be
a part of your study.
[ Various Animal Sounds ]
[ Deer Braying ]
[ TV Static ]
Grady, that's really annoying.
Grady!
- There's nothing to do here.
- [ Sighs ]
[ Deer Braying ]
I saw you move in yesterday.
You live here?
I didn't know any kids lived here.
People usually don't move
in to Fever Swamp.
They move out. Hi.
I'm Will Blake, and I live over there.
Grady Tucker.
So, what are those deer
you got in that pen for?
Well, my parents are scientists.
They're studying how the deer
will adapt to the swamp.
Scientists, huh? We don't get
many scientists around here.
It sounds like you don't
get much of anything.
Yeah. It's old-timers mostly.
We're the only kids.
I bet you had lots of friends
where you came from.
Yeah. I had like twenty
right on my street.
- Oh, that must've been great.
- It was.
So, uh, do you wanna play catch?
You got a mitt?
Uh, I'm not much for baseball.
I've got some targets out back.
You've got a B.B. gun, don't you?
Our family kinda
doesn't believe in guns.
- Oh.
- [ Animal Snarling ]
You been in yet?
- Yesterday.
- Did you get lost?
Yeah.
People say the swamp starts
to grow inside your head.
You get confused,
turned around.
Sometimes people go in and
are never heard from again.
You know why your parents
got that house so cheap?
Yeah. Because
it's a piece of garbage.
No. 'Cause the old lady
who lived there...
went into the swamp one day
and... never came out.
So let's check it out.
Wait a second.
It's okay.
I know my way around.
[ Sighs ]
[ Grady ]
This is incredible!
Dinosaurs used to live
in places like this.
[ Will ]
They still do. Alligators.
You know, some of the most
successful predators live
in swamps and jungles.
So, how come they call it
Fever Swamp?
'Cause people around here believe
there's a fever that
comes from this swamp.
It makes your body
get hot like an oven,
and it gets inside your head
and starts boiling your brain.
Makes you do crazy things.
Even makes you run into the swamp...
and stay there.
- Maybe we shouldn't be here.
- [ Animal Snarls, Screeches ]
[ Will ] Oh, no!
We gotta get outta here!
- What is it?
- Shut up and run!
[ Panting ]
Over here.
[ Both Panting ]
[ Will ] The Swamp Hermit.
I thought he only came out at night.
[ Grady ]
I saw that guy yesterday.
[ Will ]
It's lucky he didn't see you.
- He did see me.
- That's bad, Grady.
They can't prove it, but he's the
real reason people keep disappearing.
- My dad says he's harmless.
- Don't believe it.
He's been roamin' around
this swamp for fifty, sixty years.
Come on.
He can't be that old.
He's even older than that. People
like him don't age like the rest of us.
- It's impossible.
- It's true.
He'll never get a day older
as long as he keeps finding victims.
The moon is full tonight.
You'll hear him howling,
and you'll know exactly what he is.
Nothing else on earth
howls like that.
- Like what?
- Like a werewolf.
[ Wolf Howling ]
[ Emily ]
Dad, why can't I drive into town?
I have a license, you know.
You just got your license,
and you don't know the roads.
[ Sighs ]
So I'll drive slow.
Is there any mail for me today,
like from my friends?
Mail doesn't come until Wednesday.
Amazing it comes at all.
I hear you met the neighbor boy
today. What's he like?
- He's okay.
- Yeah?
Without a car, I'll never
meet anyone my own age.
Oh, Emily, come on!
It's not like we're on the moon.
His name's Will.
You know what he said?
He said there's a fever
you get from the swamp.
The fever boils your brain
and makes you go nuts.
- That's ridiculous.
- Are you sure?
Did you know that a lot of people
have disappeared around here?
Did you know that the lady that
owned this house disappeared?
But Will knows what got her.
A werewolf.
- [ Scoffs ] Well, that's just great.
- Werewolves.
I don't know about this Will.
Will knows the swamp, Mom.
And you know who he thinks
that werewolf is?
The Swamp Hermit.
All right.
I've heard just about enough.
Now, listen. There is
no such thing as a werewolf.
Those stories are just old folk legends.
There's never been a shred
of scientific evidence.
And also, there's no such fever
as the one you described.
And as I told you before,
that old hermit...
is a harmless old eccentric
who has never hurt anyone.
Or no one's lived to tell about it.
[ Sighs ]
[ Gasps, Panting ]
No!
[ Thermometer Beeps ]
[ Panting ]
Normal.
[ Wolf Howling ]
[ Howling Continues ]
[ Deer Braying ]
[ Door Creaking ]
[ Panting ]
- [ Animal Snarls ]
- [ Grady Screams ]
[ Barking, Snarling ]
[ Grady Yells ]
I didn't do anything!
Grady?
- [ Barking Continues ]
- He's gonna kill me! Help!
Grady! Go away.
Honey, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
That was trying to kill you?
Did I hear someone screaming?
Oh.
It was Grady.
He was being licked to death.
Where were you?
You missed all the excitement.
Something upset the deer.
I went outside to check 'em.
You left the door open.
Well, I think
we've found the culprit.
- Hey, boy.
- He is huge!
So that's who's been howling.
What are you doing scaring
people like that? Huh, boy?
Wonder who he belongs to.
No collar, no tags.
He's probably a stray.
- Well, he seems friendly enough.
- Can we keep him for a while?
I bet he'll make a great watchdog.
- I don't know, Grady.
- Oh, come on, Dad!
Life in the country
is not complete without a dog.
You want to live here, you
gotta take the whole package.
- We'll see.
- Come on, Dad!
Okay. I'll tell you what.
I'll check in town.
If nobody claims him,
then we'll talk about it.
But... he sleeps outside.
Deal.
Excuse me. Doesn't anyone
care about what I think?
- [ Barks ]
- See? Someone cares.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Dog Barking ]
Come on, boy. There you go.
Here we go. Come on.
That's okay.
Sit.
How long's it been since you had
someone to play with? Huh, boy?
Neither of us has to worry
about it anymore.
Don't get too attached to that
dog, Grady. He might have a home.
I'm thinkin' about calling him
Vandal on account
of the way he broke in last night.
[ Mom Chuckles ]
What'd you bring that out for?
There's going to be
a full moon tonight.
Full moon?
It'll be really spectacular.
The sun, the moon and the earth
will be lined up...
So the earth's shadow
will pass over the moon.
A lunar eclipse.
Ooh.
Can I still get tickets?
[ Sighs ] Someday something's
gonna impress you kids.
I just hope
I'm around to see it.
[ Various Animal Sounds ]
[ Will ] Did you hear
the howling last night?
- [ Grady ] Yeah. It was Vandal.
- Is that what you think?
[ Barking ]
Come here, boy.
Good boy. Don't worry.
If that Swamp Hermit comes around,
Vandal will smell him a mile away.
- Won't you, boy?
- [ Barks ]
What's this stuff tied to the trees?
Wolfsbane. It's supposed
to ward off werewolves.
Of course, educated people
know it doesn't work.
Oh, right.
The educated people use silver bullets.
Shows how much you know.
The fact is...
werefolk invented that silver
bullet story themselves
so poor people couldn't
afford to hunt them down.
- "Werefolk"?
- I suppose you'd call them were-persons.
Maybe we should go back.
I don't know this part of the swamp.
[ Screams ]
[ Barking ]
[ Barking Continues ]
Wow!
Where are we?
The bog is supposed to be
the heart of the swamp.
Right in its very center.
A couple of years ago,
a kid fell in.
Sucked him down like quicksand.
There's no tellin'
what's down there.
- I wonder how deep it is.
- Let's find out.
What's it feel like?
Like green,
slimy mashed potatoes.
Ah, this is too gross.
Hey! Hey, wait a second!
- What is it?
- Something's got me! Help! Help me!
There's something down there!
It's got my hand!
[ Both Grunting ]
Oh! It was only a shoe.
[ Laughing ]
Sucker.
You're not funny.
Oh, man, that was awesome. You
should've seen the look on your face.
Come on, Grady.
I couldn't help myself.
- [ Laughs ]
- [ Vandal Barking ]
- [ Gasps ]
- [ Barking Continues ]
- What's the matter, boy?
- [ Snarls, Barks ]
Somebody's watching us.
I thought you said that didn't work.
Do you believe
everything you hear?
[ Barking Continues ]
Come on. Let's get out of here.
Come on, boy.
[ Headphones: Rock ]
Oh, how cute!
A bunny!
[ Screams ]
It was horrible, Mom.
It was just sitting there...
looking up at me
with those big, innocent eyes.
So I reached out to pet it.
Well, honey, didn't you realize
something was wrong
when it didn't run away?
I thought it liked me.
- What's wrong?
- It's that stupid dog. I know it is.
We should've taken it right
to the pound when we found it.
Hey, you leave Vandal alone!
He's not bothering anyone.
I'm not so sure about that, Grady.
- [ Vandal Groans ]
- What are you talking about?
- Come take a look.
- Stay.
- Oh, that's sick, Dad.
- It was mauled by some predator.
Just like half a dozen other
animals in the area last night.
- It just killed them for no reason.
- Oh, come on, Dad.
Vandal didn't do this.
I mean, look at him.
Bite marks are canine.
So what? It could've been anything.
It could've been a wolf.
Grady, there are
no wolves in the swamp.
How do you know?
Look, the swamp's a pretty
brutal place, you know?
If that dog's been living there,
he could've become just as brutal.
And he was outside all last night.
The bite marks. I bet they're big,
right? Too big for Vandal.
No, Grady, they're not.
We think it was Vandal.
It's not Vandal!
There might be something
going on out there,
but it has nothing
to do with my dog.
- We'll get you another dog.
- No!
[ Vandal Whimpers ]
It's okay, boy.
No one's gonna hurt you.
I'll make sure of it.
I don't want another dog.
He's completely irrational.
Maybe he has that swamp fever
he's been babbling about.
[ Will ] It's the Swamp Hermit
killing all those animals.
I've got to find his shack.
I can't let them blame Vandal.
They'll take him away.
Oh, man! No one actually goes
looking for the Swamp Hermit!
Getting yourself wasted
isn't gonna help your dog.
Well, if you're that scared,
then go home. I'll do it myself.
Oh, I wish I'd never even told you.
All right. I'll go. But I'm outta
there before the moon rises.
[ Various Animal Sounds ]
One bite. One bite, man.
That's all it takes,
and you'll be just like him--
A werewolf.
If he kills you, you're lucky.
You see anything werewolf?
I don't know.
It's dark in there.
[ Both Boys Screaming ]
Will!
Get me out of here!
Get me out of this thing!
Will! Help!
Help me!
Will!
I'm sorry. I swear I won't
come around here again.
[ Growls ]
- What are you gonna do?
- [ Growling Continues ]
Help! No! No!
Let me out of here!
Let me go! Ow!
Let me go! Get me out of here!
I didn't do anything!
[ Growls ]
What are you gonna do with me?
You can't keep me here.
Everyone will be looking for me.
[ Panting ]
Just let me go.
Please.
I won't tell anyone.
I promise. I won't tell.
If you let me go,
I'll never come back here, ever.
You'll never see me again.
My parents are probably
on their way now.
And they've got guns.
Really big guns.
Have you ever seen
an elephant rifle?
[ Animal Howling ]
[ Howling ]
[ Howling Continues ]
- Mom! Mom!
- Grady? What's wrong?
Mom, we've gotta get out of here.
What's happened to you?
Where have you been?
We've gotta go to a motel.
Anywhere, just as long as
we're away from the swamp.
- Dad!
- All right. I've had just about enough.
You're really beginning
to scare me, Grady.
You should be scared.
Dad!
Your father went to get supplies.
Emily took the other car.
Now, unless you're planning on
hitchhiking, nobody's going anywhere.
- [ Panting ]
- Grady.
Honey, you gotta tell me
what's wrong.
It's that Swamp Hermit, Mom.
What happened?
Did he hurt you?
- No. Not exactly.
- Did he threaten you?
- No.
- What, then?
H-he's a werewolf.
Oh, I don't have time for this.
Oh, come on, Mom.
You gotta listen to me.
You and Dad base everything
on science, right?
Things you can prove and explain.
But what if the world
isn't always like that?
What if you knew something was
true, but you couldn't prove it?
Something horrible. You knew
it could never be explained.
What would you do then?
- [ Growling ]
- What was that?
[ Vandal Barking ]
[ Gasps, Whimpers ]
- [ Barking Continues ]
- Oh, no! Vandal!
Oh, no! The deer.
- [ Barking Continues ]
- [ Grady ] Vandal, what is it?
Oh, no!
Grady, go call the sheriff
to get rid of that dog.
Mom, you can't think
Vandal did this!
Do you think a dog
can do that to a fence?
It's gonna take all night
to catch these deer.
Are you gonna help me,
or do I have to do this myself?
You saw it, didn't you, boy?
Don't worry.
I won't let it near you again.
Mom, no! You don't
know what you're doing!
I'm sorry, Grady.
It has to be done.
Mom, that dog is
the only protection we have!
It'll warn us when
the werewolf is coming.
You wanna talk about werewolves?
Fine. We'll talk about werewolves.
Tomorrow we'll talk about everything
from werewolves to flying monkeys!
But right now we have to catch
the rest of these deer...
and put this dog
where it can't get to them.
Grady, it's time to get
your priorities straight.
Come here, boy.
They are straight, Mom!
Grady! Open the door!
You'll be safe in there, Mom!
It won't be able to get you.
Grady! Grady!
Vandal?
Where'd you go, boy?
Vandal!
[ Indistinct Groaning ]
Will?
Vandal?
Mr. Blake?
Mrs. Blake?
Grady? Somebody?
I'm in here! Help!
Hello?
Mom? Dad?
Will?
Will!
Hello?
Where is everyone?
It got Will.
Grady, is this
your idea of a joke?
[ Animal Growling ]
[ Growling Continues ]
[ Wolf Howling ]
Will?
Grady?
[ Animal Growling ]
[ Growling Continues ]
[ Screams ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Gasps, Whimpers ]
[ Whimpering ]
Let me out!
[ Screams ]
[ Snarling ]
What is it?
S-some kind of wolf.
- [ Snarling Continues ]
- [ Both Gasp ]
[ Both Scream, Shudder ]
[ Snarling Continues ]
Shh.
[ Snarling Stops ]
[ Both Panting ]
- [ Both Gasp ]
- [ Snarling Resumes ]
Vandal! Will!
[ Snarls ]
[ Wolf Howling ]
[ Wings Fluttering, Bird Squawks ]
Will, if you can hear me,
answer!
[ Animal Groaning ]
Vandal!
[ Snarling ]
- [ Animal Shrieks ]
- The net!
- [ Rustling ]
- [ Gasps ]
Got him!
[ Animal Growling ]
You got the werewolf.
You!
I've waited a long time for this!
[ Swamp Hermit Groans ]
You took my wife and children.
Everything I ever loved!
I swore one day I would take
your heart the way you took mine!
[ Growling ]
A deer.
Run, boy!
Look out!
[ Screaming ]
- [ Werewolf Snarls ]
- [ Grady Gasps, Pants ]
[ Growling ]
[ Groaning ]
- Get away!
- Will!
- Get away, Grady!
- You! You're the werewolf!
I don't want to hurt you,
but I can't help myself, Grady.
[ Pained Groaning ]
There's gotta be
something we can do.
No. Leave, now. Go!
[ Groaning Continues ]
[ Screams ]
[ Growling ]
- [ Snarls ]
- [ Screaming ]
- [ Vandal Barking ]
- [ Grady Gasps ]
- [ Werewolf Snarling ]
- [ Vandal Whimpers ]
- [ Vandal Barks ]
- [ Werewolf Shrieks ]
[ Barking ]
Thanks, Vandal.
Thanks, boy.
Poor Will.
[ Birds Whistling ]
[ Mom ] Come on, you guys.
You can finish that later.
Okay.
So, you two start school tomorrow.
- Yep.
- You'll make some friends.
I hope they have some normal
boys-- Non-werewolf types.
I thought you'd like
the werewolf type.
Now, listen, you two.
We've talked about this.
We know that it was some kind of
a wolf that attacked you that night,
but there is no evidence to
suggest that it was a werewolf.
Except what I saw.
And you haven't seen will around,
have you?
There has to be
some rational explanation.
Anyway, it's over.
And I know one thing.
I was wrong about Vandal.
With my apologies.
Honey, not at the table.
[ Dad ]
How's he doing?
[ Mom ]
He seems okay.
[ Dad ] Oh, good. Maybe
he's finally over those nightmares.
- [ Chuckles ]
- [ Sighs ]
- [ Door Closes ]
- [ Snarls ]
[ Gasps, Panting ]
It's only a dream.
Only a dream.
[ Wolf Howling ]
[ Howling Continues ]
[ Howling ]
I hope you enjoyed that story,
and I hope
you weren't too scared.
Remember, there's no
such thing as a werewolf.
Time for me to say good-bye.
Have a scary night, everyone.
[ Howling ]
Captioned by Grant Brown