Oh, hello. I'm R.L. Stine.
I write the Goosebumps books.
Today's story is
"A Night in Terror Tower."
It all begins right here
in the torture chamber.
Eddie and Sue are about
to make their first visit.
It might also be their last.
Do you know the scariest part of
the tour? It's trying to get out.
I hope you enjoy your visit.
Uh, excuse me, miss?
Could I get this gift wrapped?
[ Screaming ]
- Get up, you!
- No, no, no!
No! No, I'm innocent!
Go on! Get up!
It's off to the tower with you.
- [ Screaming ]
- Go on!
Move along.
Go on. Get in there!
[ Groaning ]
Stop! Just leave me alone!
Don't torture me!
- Go on!
- [ Screams Echo ]
[ Man On TV ]
When in London, see Terror Tower.
A nice place to visit, but you
wouldn't want to stay too long.
Whoa.
I'd like to see the tower.
It's where they lock people up
and torture them.
Yeah, that sounds like fun.
But I bet you anything we're gonna
go to another boring museum.
[ Snores ]
All right, tourists.
Back on the bus.
Hey, where's my film?
I know I had another roll.
- Mad pickpocket strikes again.
- Obnoxious little brother strikes again.
Never even felt me take it.
Have to admit,
you are getting pretty good.
Got the fastest hands in the West.
[ Blows ]
Let's go. Let's go!
No lagging.
All right, tourists. Now, I'm afraid
we're running out of museums.
- But we can go to Terror Tower.
- [ Eddie ] Terror Tower! Yes!
Too bad Mom and Dad
had that business conference.
[ Sue ]
Yep, we're on our own.
Step lively!
Come along. Come along.
- [ Bell Tolls ]
- Ladies and gentlemen, behold!
Terror Tower--
where hope dies,
light is extinguished...
and the soul yearns for its release.
Now, follow me, everybody,
and please, stay together.
They used to
torture people up there.
They used to lock them up in the
tower and let them starve to death.
That was hundreds of years ago,
Eddie. Now they just sell postcards.
- Still looks pretty creepy.
- [ Scoffs ]
[ Man ]
Go back! Go back! Go back!
Run for your life.
For your own good!
[ Echoing ]
What's wrong, Eddie?
- Up there!
- Up there?
- What?
- Well, I-I thought--
- Oh, never mind.
- Come on. We better catch up.
Historians say the castle
was built in the year 400...
and used as a walled fort.
Now, if you'll all follow me--
Stay together, everyone.
Please, stay together.
Later, it became a prison.
That started many years of cruelty
and torture within these walls.
Lovely postcards depicting
the instruments of torture
are available in the gift shop.
Now, if you'll kindly follow me,
we'll climb to the tower.
[ Tourists Murmuring ]
[ Creaks ]
- [ Woman Gasps ]
- [ Quiet Chattering ]
[ Shutter Clicks ]
Everybody in?
Guards.
I'm so sorry. I'm afraid I have
to give you some rather bad news.
- [ Murmuring ]
- [ Eddie ] Bad news?
You will be imprisoned
in the North Tower.
There, you will be tortured...
until you tell us the real
reason you chose to come here.
Tortured?
Did he say tortured?
Take them away.
[ Breathing Heavily ]
[ Chuckling ]
Just a little Terror Tower joke!
[ All Mutter, Sigh Relievedly ]
We Brits have to
have some fun, you know.
- He really had me goin'.
- Yeah, me too.
Now, if you'll just follow me,
we'll enter the torture chamber.
Now, please, stick together. I'll carry
this high so that you can find me.
There are hundreds of passages
and secret chambers.
It's rather easy to get lost.
[ Chattering ]
Y-You sure you wanna go up
in the torture chamber?
- I thought you couldn't wait to see it.
- I know.
There's-There's something
about this place.
Don't worry.
I'll hold your hand.
[ Scoffs ]
Real funny.
[ Tour Guide ]
This way, tourists. That's it.
Stay together.
Boy, if I was the king of England,
I know what I'd do first thing.
- What's that, Your Majesty?
- Put in elevators.
Don't dawdle, tourists.
Keep moving!
That's it. Come right in.
Welcome to the torture chamber.
This is the rack.
As you can see, the prisoner
was forced to lie back here.
Then his arms and legs
were tied off so,
and then when
the big wheel was turned,
the ropes pulled his arms and legs...
and stretched them out straight.
Sometimes,
when the wheel was turned,
the prisoner was stretched
and stretched...
until his bones were pulled--
[ Imitates Popping Noise ]
- right out of their sockets.
- [ Tourists Chuckle, Groan ]
That's what I call doing
a long stretch in prison.
- [ Scattered Chuckles ]
- Good one.
Now, if you'll all follow me
over to the thumbscrews.
[ Tourists Chattering ]
Hey, Eddie.
Let me take your picture.
[ Giggles ]
Great, hold it just like that.
Hurry up. I can't hold this
stupid look much longer.
Just a sec.
[ Gasps ]
- Forget it.
- What?
I'm going to see the thumbscrews.
[ Breathing Heavily ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Screaming ]
Sue!
It moved!
It tried to get me!
It did?
- How can that be?
- [ Tour Guide Clears Throat ]
You mustn't touch the displays.
It's very bad form.
Why do parents let children
go off on their own?
- [ Sue ] But-- But I--
- [ Groans ]
[ Tour Guide ]
The North Tower is next.
- I hope you're wearing your climbing shoes.
- [ Sue ] I know it moved!
I could have sworn--
This place--
It does things to your mind.
Thought I saw weird things
a couple of times.
- [ Tour Guide ] This way!
- We better catch up.
Come on. Let's get out of here.
This place gives me the creeps.
Come on, Eddie.
- [ Scoffs ] They're only wax.
- Right.
- Only wax.
- Eddie.
Can you imagine being a prisoner
and being marched up these stairs?
Yeah.
This place is creepy.
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Chuckles ]
Sorry. [ Laughs ]
- [ Woman ] Are you all right?
- Come along, tourists.
Kids.
[ Sighing ]
We are now at the top of the tower.
This... is the chamber...
where the most important
political prisoners were kept.
Perhaps... you can feel...
sadness in this room.
It was here...
in the early 15th century...
that the young prince and
princess of York were brought.
Imagine.
Two children...
dragged away from their home,
locked away in the drab chill of
this cell at the top of a tower.
What happened to them?
The prince and princess
weren't here for long.
That night as they slept,
the lord high executioner's
men crept up the stairs,
their orders...
to kill the two children...
to keep the prince and the princess
from ever taking the throne.
- [ Man ] That's terrible.
- [ Tourists Murmuring ]
- [ Footsteps Departing ]
- Sue. Look at this.
[ Sue ]
"Long live freedom."
[ Gasps ]
[ Thunderclaps ]
- [ Eddie Screams ]
- Danger! Danger!
- [ Screams ]
Did you see that?
What's going on?
That face.
"Danger."
Did he mean, to us?
- What was that?
- I don't know.
This is too weird.
[ Panting ]
Where is everyone?
Hello?
Hello! Is anyone here?
Let's get out of here, Sue!
What if the place is closing?
- I don't wanna get locked in!
- Take it easy, Eddie.
Let's just go. We'll catch
up to the group downstairs.
[ Eddie ] They couldn't
have gone very far, right?
Of course not. In a couple of
minutes we'll be laughing about this.
- Yeah.
- [ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Gasps ]
You scared us.
We lost our tour group.
Can you show us the way out?
- [ Sue ] You work here, right?
- [ Chuckles ]
Wait a minute.
I thought you were a wax figure.
What are you supposed to be anyway?
A guard or something?
You will come with me.
Hey, that's pretty good
how he stays in character.
Hey, man, that's pretty good.
So is this the way out?
- Hey, cut it out!
- You know why I'm here!
Let go of him!
Cut it out!
- Leave us alone!
- Do not move.
Do not try to escape.
You will come with me... now.
[ Chanting In Foreign Language ]
- [ Chanting Conintues ]
- [ Sue ] What's he doing?
[ Eddie ]
The door. Get ready.
- Now!
- [ Mutters ]
Eddie, wait!
I don't remember going down this far.
- What does he want from us?
- Let's not wait to find out.
This may be the way out.
- Oh, it's locked!
- Try pushing!
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
[ Screams ]
[ Man ]
You've entered the king's dungeon.
Abandon all hope.
[ Screams, Shrieks ]
You've entered the king's dungeon.
Abandon all hope.
Wait a minute.
It's not real.
None of it!
It's a recording.
It's only a display.
What do you want?
- You know.
- Why are you chasing us?
You know why.
Now... you will come with me.
I won't hurt you.
But if you don't,
why, I'll have no choice.
- [ Laughs ]
- No! Let me go!
[ Screaming ]
This way!
It's some kind of tunnel.
Maybe it'll lead outside.
We don't have much choice.
Hurry! Go!
Go, go, go!
- [ Water Running ]
- Yuck! Come on.
[ Eddie ]
This thing goes on forever!
I see light!
It's him!
Come on, Sue. Hurry!
You can't escape me!
[ Eddie ]
Up the ladder!
Go!
Come on! Come on!
Hurry!
[ Panting ]
[ Screams ]
- Oh, come on!
- I can't!
- You can't escape from me!
- [ Struggling ]
[ Squeaking ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Muttering ]
[ Screaming ]
I'm sure that's not part of the tour.
- [ Horn Honks ]
- Hey, help me lift this.
Hope the bus waited for us.
[ Shrieks ]
Don't count on it.
What are you doin' in the sewer?
- We lost our tour group.
- And a man chased us!
A man? In the tower?
Yeah, he was dressed in black.
He grabbed us,
and he tried to get us to go with him.
- But we ran away.
- There's no man in the tower.
I'm the only one here after closing.
- But he chased us!
- That's impossible.
I should call the police.
- But we didn't do anything!
- He chased us!
How are we supposed
to get back to the hotel?
Our parents'll be waiting!
You remain right there.
What is he doing?
Is he calling the police?
Let him!
We didn't do anything.
What if he's calling
the guy who's chasing us?
- [ Tires Screeching ]
- [ Sue ] Hey, there's a cab!
Hey!
- [ Chuckles ] Are we glad to see you!
- Where to?
- The Balmoral.
- All right. Jump in.
[ Classical ]
That'll be 12 pounds, 60 pence.
I don't really know your money.
Could you get the
right amount from these?
What are those?
Coins. Isn't it enough?
Now don't play games with me.
Those aren't real coins.
We take British pounds here.
Now, are you gonna pay me
in British pounds?
Or are we gonna
have major trouble?
But... why would our parents
give us play money?
Where are your parents?
In the hotel?
Yes.
Th-They're at a conference.
We'll get them to come down
and pay you.
But in real money this time,
if you please.
And if you're not back in five
minutes, I'm comin' in after you.
[ Panting ]
They'll be down, I promise.
And you don't have to be so rude!
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
- What was wrong with that money?
- I guess Dad made a mistake.
Eddie, do you have
the key to the room?
No. I thought you had it.
I guess I didn't take it.
I can't remember.
- Excuse me, sir?
- What can I do for you?
Can you tell us where
the conference is being held?
I beg your pardon, but there is no
conference right now at the hotel.
But our parents said!
Well, perhaps
you misunderstood them.
Perhaps the conference
is at another hotel.
May we have the key
to our room then?
- What room are you in?
- 1415.
1415.
[ Computer Beeps ]
That room is vacant.
What?
There is no one in that room
at the present time.
But we are.
That's our room.
- What's your last name?
- [ Gasps ]
Your last name?
Eddie, what's our last name?
I don't know.
Eddie, there's something
wrong with us.
You don't know your last name.
Do you think it might be possible
to check into this hotel
sometime this evening?
- Yes, madam. Right away.
- Thank you.
Now, why don't you run along.
And when you figure out
who you are, come back.
I'll be glad to help you then.
- Madam.
- Thank you.
- What is going on?
- Just calm down. We can't panic.
- The driver! Now you can panic.
- Come on.
We'll hide in the restaurant.
Come on.
As I'm sure you are aware,
a jacket is required for
gentlemen in the Balmoral Lounge.
Jacket?
I'm sorry.
My brother doesn't have a jacket.
Most odd.
- [ Fingers Snap ]
- A jacket...
for the young... gentleman.
Could you seat us
somewhere in the back?
I wouldn't dream of
seating you anywhere else.
Right this way, please.
[ Quiet Chattering ]
[ Grunts ]
- What are we gonna do now?
- I don't know.
- Welcome to the Balmoral.
- May we have a menu, please?
Our high tea includes scones,
croissants, sandwiches--
We'll have that.
Thank you.
[ Sighs ]
Why can't we remember
our last name, Sue?
I don't know.
If only we could find Mom and Dad.
Eddie, I can't even
remember what they look like.
Neither can I.
Sue, where do we live?
Do we live in a house?
I can't picture it at all!
- I can't remember!
- This is crazy!
Shh. People are staring.
There must be something wrong
with our memories.
I can remember what I did today.
So can I.
I can remember our room number,
and that Mom and Dad
were at a meeting.
But those memories are wrong.
Eddie, I can't even remember
yesterday or the day before that.
Can you?
No.
I can't.
What's wrong with us?
Sue, what's the matter?
I don't know.
I feel strange.
I feel like... something
awful is gonna happen to us.
I think you're right.
Well, maybe if we explained.
What? That we lost our memories,
and we can't pay him?
Hey, maybe we sneak out
through there.
Mmm.
Hmm! Mmm!
Grab those kids!
[ Gasping ]
[ Continues Gasping ]
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
- It's really not that bad.
- Oh, no! No!
Run, run, run!
That's all we do anymore!
I know, I know!
Keep running!
Wait a minute.
No one's following us.
What is this place?
I guess it's the hotel kitchen.
[ Whispers ]
Get down!
He gave up.
I think we're okay.
[ Sighs ]
This has got to be
the worst day I've ever had.
How do you know?
Can't remember any others.
[ Giggles ]
- What's so funny?
- That jacket.
[ Sighs ]
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
[ Laughs ] Did you really think that
you could escape from me?
- Give it back.
- Give what back?
Don't play games with me.
Give it to me. Now.
If I give it back to you,
will you let us go?
Give what back, Eddie?
What's he talking about?
- Will you?
- Hand it to me.
The "mad pickpocket."
When did you take that?
In the dungeon
when he grabbed me.
- Now will you let us go?
- Yes.
We will go now.
That's not what I said!
- [ Chanting In Foreign ]
- Stop that!
No! No!
[ Screams, Groans ]
[ Eddie Screams ]
[ Gasps ]
Eddie?
Oh, come on, Eddie.
Please be here.
Eddie?
Eddie, where are you?
[ Grunting, Chattering ]
[ Chuckling ]
[ Grunting, Belching ]
[ Children Chattering ]
[ Animal Lowing ]
- Where are you from?
- Is this a theme park?
- Can you tell me where the hotel is?
- Are thee a traveler?
What do you want?
Why are you staring at me?
[ Woman ]
Get thee inside!
Now! Get! Get!
Excuse me,
I'm looking for my brother.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, ma'am.
I'm looking for my brother. He's
wearing regular clothes like me.
- Have you seen him?
- It's too late for the boy.
What does that mean?
I smell evil--
evil all around you.
Your time is comin', dearie.
[ Man ]
She be the one.
- [ Crowd Murmuring ]
- [ Man #2 ] It be she!
What do you want?
Who are you?
- Stranger.
- [ Sue ] Go away!
What do you want?
I'm just looking for my brother!
- [ Horse Whinnies ]
- [ Woman Shrieks ]
Time to go now.
[ Gasps ]
I said it was time for us to go now.
Where is Eddie?
- Do you know where Eddie is?
- Eddie?
[ Laughs ]
Do not worry about Eddie.
Come now.
You cannot delay your fate.
You've made a mistake.
You've got the wrong girl.
I don't know you.
I don't know anything.
You will come with me now.
It is time.
No!
I'm not coming with you.
[ Laughing ]
- You've got to hide me.
- No. You get away from here.
- Please!
- [ Groans ]
- [ Chicken Clucking ]
- I'll pay you! I'll pay you! Here.
Take them.
Take them all.
Gold sovereigns!
I saw one once when
I was a small lass.
Will you take them?
Will you hide me, please?
All right. Quickly!
- Into the basket.
- Please.
I'm looking for the girl.
Yes.
She's right here, sire.
I put her right here in this basket.
She's all wrapped up and ready
for you to take her away.
[ Laughs ]
Guards!
[ Chicken Clucking ]
Liar!
I'm sorry, lass.
I hope you can forgive me.
But I dare not go against
the lord high executioner.
Executioner?
[ Chattering ]
[ Woman ]
Take her away.
- [ Man ] Go on!
- Take her away!
[ Chattering Continues ]
[ Man ]
Straight to the tower!
- Sue!
- Eddie!
- I was hoping you got away.
- Silence.
- But we didn't do anything.
- We're innocent!
Lock them away.
Where are we?
What's happening to us?
[ Sue ]
I don't know.
Everything's different.
- [ Door Slams ]
- You okay?
Yeah. I wish I knew what they
think we did to deserve this.
You have done nothing
to deserve it, Susanna.
Your Grace.
I wish I could say
I rejoice at your return.
- May I rise?
- Yeah, sure.
Your Grace.
No. It's okay.
- You're that face we saw.
- Who are you?
You... do not remember me?
Why does everyone think
we'll remember them?
My name's not Susanna.
It's Sue!
My name is Morgred.
I am the king's sorcerer.
Sorcerer?
- Did you bring us back in time?
- It's not an easy story to tell.
You are not...
Eddie and Sue.
- What?
- You are Edward and Susanna,
the prince and princess of York.
[ Grinding ]
I do not expect you to believe me.
But my words are true.
I cast a spell upon you.
- I tried... to help you escape.
- [ Eddie ] No!
It's not true!
My name's Eddie, not Edward!
- Shh.
- Just Eddie?
What is your last name?
- I, uh...
- When I sent you far into the future,
I gave you new memories
so that you could survive...
in a new and distant time.
But the memories were not complete.
So that's why we couldn't
remember our parents.
- But our parents--
- Your real parents--
your only parents,
the rightful king and queen--
are dead.
No. Sue.
Your wicked uncle
has named himself king.
And he has ordered you
to the tower...
to get you out of the way.
But what's he gonna do to us?
[ Creaking ]
Edward of York
and Susanna of York,
by order of the king...
you have been condemned
to execution...
- by beheading.
- No.
So it is decreed,
and so it shall be done.
[ British Accent ]
Now I remember.
So do I.
The spell has worn off.
Good Morgred, I commend thee
for thy valiant service...
to Susanna and me.
I promised your parents
to keep you from harm.
[ Crying ]
And now--
Oh, do not despair.
You did your best.
We may be gone,
but the idea of freedom lives on.
My brother,
let us face the executioner's ax
with dignity.
[ Groaning, Screaming ]
[ Groaning, Screaming Continue ]
[ Morgred ] If only there
were something I could do.
I don't understand. If you
sent us to the future once,
why not again?
Because the executioner
grabbed the three white stones,
and without them
my magic is weak.
[ Groaning, Screaming Continue ]
I wanted to come to the future
with you to make sure you were safe.
Alas, it was not meant to be.
Instead, the executioner sent himself
into the future to catch you
and bring you back.
I failed.
I failed,
and now we all shall pay...
with our lives.
[ Groaning ]
- [ Metal Clanking ]
- [ Men Groaning ]
Bring forth the condemned.
[ Drum Beating ]
Stay!
My Lord High Executioner.
Spare the girl and boy.
Do with me as you must.
But first allow me to
send them into the future.
[ Distant Screaming ]
What harm can they possibly
do you there?
And allow them to grow up
and become strong,
to find a way to return
and take their revenge?
I think not.
Bring forth the condemned.
Be brave, Edward.
Be brave.
Yes, Susanna.
[ Distant Screaming Continues ]
[ Groaning, Screaming ]
[ Screaming ]
Chin up, Edward.
You are a prince.
- Please! Please, spare me!
- [ Mutters ]
Edward, be brave!
No, I can't! I'm afraid!
Please! Please!
Let go of me!
Guards!
Morgred! The spell!
[ Both Grunt ]
Fastest hands in all Britannia.
- [ Giggles ]
- [ Chanting In Foreign ]
Guard, seize him!
- [ Both Groan ]
- [ Continues In Foreign ]
Long live freedom!
- [ Screaming ]
[ British Accent ] Hey! You're
not supposed to leave the group!
I could get in trouble.
[ Door Opens ]
There you are!
We've been looking
all over for you.
- We made it!
- Yes!
Made what?
What are you going on about?
Don't you know you
gave me quite a fright?
If I lost two tourists,
they'd have my head!
I'm afraid it's my fault.
Morgred!
[ Chuckles ]
Mr. Morgred.
Uh, I'm Sue and Eddie's guardian.
They're my responsibility.
I, uh-- I'll make sure
they don't get lost again.
Yes, well-- hmm--
Well, come on then.
The tower closes in five minutes.
You wouldn't want to get locked in.
No, no.
We wouldn't want that at all.
All right now.
To the bus! To the bus!
Step lively, tourists.
Step lively!
Those children should be disciplined.
Excuse me. But we never
heard the rest of the story.
Yeah.
What happened to the prince
and princess in the tower?
Nobody knows exactly.
When the king came
to the dungeon,
the prince and
the princess were gone.
What happened to them
is a mystery to this day.
Come along.
Edward!
Have you been up
to your tricks again?
[ Eddie ]
Hey, don't look at me.
That's our story.
Time to go.
The tower is closing.
How do you get out of here? Can
somebody show me the way out?
How do we get out really?
Somebody help me. Let me out.
Let me out of here.
[ Echoing ]
Captioned by Grant Brown