[ Wind Whistling ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Man ]
Goosebumps.
Viewer beware.
You're in for a scare.
[ Chuckles ]
- I wish you weren't going.
- So do I.
But your Aunt Eleanor's sick, honey.
She needs me.
- I know, but--
- I'll be back as soon as I can.
I know. It's just that
I'm worried about Dad.
He's been acting so weird lately.
He's under a lot of pressure,
Margaret.
He never has time for me anymore.
He's even stopped
calling me Princess.
I thought you hated that.
I do.
But it just seems like he's changed.
I bought a card for Aunt Eleanor.
That's very thoughtful of you,
sweetheart.
Come here.
And Dad's always down
in the basement--
ever since he lost his job.
- What does he do down there anyway?
- [ Boy ] He's a botanist.
- He studies plants.
- I know that. But all the time?
He wants to prove
to the university that
they made a mistake
when they let him go.
You know, it's never
really fun to be fired.
I know all that.
I just think something's wrong.
Something else.
- Like what?
- I don't know.
Give him a chance, Margaret.
It's a tough time for him.
Everything's going to be fine.
I'm counting on you two
to take good care of your father.
Go get your dad.
I don't wanna be late for my plane.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- Say hi to Aunt Eleanor for me.
- I will.
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye-bye, sweetheart.
And, Mom? Don't worry.
I'll take good care of Dad.
[ Laughs ]
Oh, Margaret?
I left Aunt Eleanor's number
next to the phone in the kitchen.
- Okay. Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
Dad?
He never hears stuff
when he's working.
Dad?
Stay out of the basement!
We're sorry,
but Mom said to get you
because she didn't want to be late.
Look, kids,
I'm sorry I raised my voice.
I just don't want you
down in the basement.
Okay? Now, come on.
Walk me outside. Okay?
Okay now, kids. Don't forget
what I said about the basement.
And why is he so freaked
about the basement?
Because he doesn't want us
messing with his work.
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Horn Honks ]
[ Boy ]
Yes!
[ Video Game Beeping ]
[ Whining ]
What was that?
- [ TV Turns Off ]
- Hey!
Just listen.
- Do you hear it?
- [ Whining ]
Maybe it's the wind.
- That's not the wind.
- [ Whining ]
It sounds like it's coming
from the basement.
- Sounds like-- like an animal.
- Like it's hurt or something.
- [ Margaret ] We have to go down there.
- But Dad said that--
I know what Dad said, but
what happens if there is an animal,
and it's, like, a stray cat
or something, and it's suffering?
- We have to go down here.
- [ Whining ]
We?
We'll just take a little peek,
make sure nothing's wrong.
[ Creaking ]
[ Whining ]
- It's so hot in here. How can Dad stand it?
- Shh!
- Do you hear it?
- I'm not sure.
[ Boy ]
Whoa.
[ Margaret ]
It's like a jungle.
I can hardly breathe.
Listen. It sounds
like the plants are breathing.
I wonder if Dad's
doing the rain forest.
I'm studying it in school.
Casey, let's get out of--
[ Whining ]
- What are you doing?
- That plant just grabbed me.
Come on.
Plants don't grab people.
What happened to your finger?
I pricked it on one of the thorns.
- [ Horn Honks ]
- [ Together ] Dad!
Phew. My sweater!
It's in the basement.
- Casey!
- I gotta get it.
Dad'll know
we've been down there.
Oh!
[ Growling ]
Casey, come on.
Hurry up.
Hurry!
Casey, come on.
Move it!
Casey! Hurry.
Come on, Casey.
What are you doing?
Hurry!
Oh, shoot.
Casey, hurry up!
Casey!
I got it.
- [ Casey ] Hi, Dad.
- Did Mom make her plane?
Yes.
- Were you in the basement?
- We heard some noises.
Like someone was crying.
Did you go into the basement?
We were scared.
The noises were-- were strange and--
No.
Did you go into the basement?
- Yes.
- We didn't touch anything.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry.
You kids okay?
Yeah. We're fine.
Okay. Come on.
Okay, have a seat.
[ Clears Throat ]
Now, if I explain to you
what I'm doing in the basement,
- would you feel better?
- I would.
Okay. Now--
[ Exhales ]
I'm gonna try to explain this
to you as simply as possible.
Botanists often try to take
good qualities from some plants,
and put them into another.
And that's what you're doing?
No, no, no, no.
I'm doing something...
a little bit more unusual.
I can't tell you
what it is right now.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Maybe you could tell us later.
- Yeah.
Well, maybe.
Hey! Uh,
Mom rented us movies.
I could make some popcorn and
we could stay up late and watch 'em all.
Uh, no, no, no.
I have a lot of work to do.
Maybe some other time.
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
- Something's not right.
- We shouldn't have gone down there.
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Yawning ]
- Yum.
- Don't you dare.
That's for Dad.
There's some more in the pan.
Dad, breakfast is ready.
[ Whining ]
Dad? Breakfast.
[ Whining Continues ]
[ Video Game Sounds ]
Yes!
You wanna go outside
and play catch?
- You know how Dad is when he's working.
- Yeah. Weird.
He's not weird.
It's just that his work is more
important than breakfast, that's all.
- He'll eat it when he's ready.
- [ Footsteps On Stairs ]
See? I told you.
[ Sighs ]
Well, I'm going outside to play.
Dad.
I made you some breakfast.
I'm not hungry.
[ Door Closes ]
Plant food?
Mom, I saw him.
He was eating it.
[ Mom ] I'm sure it has something
to do with his work.
But the way he looked--
He always gets wrapped up
in his experiments.
Don't worry. How's Casey?
He's okay.
He's out in the yard playing.
Mom, when are you coming home?
Aunt Eleanor's just recovering
from her surgery.
- She still needs me.
- Mom, I can't explain it,
but I've just got this really
bad feeling about Dad--
Hi, honey.
Everything okay?
Aw.
That's a shame.
Margaret? Yes.
You're right.
I should spend more time with her.
Absolutely. You're right.
We miss you. I will.
Bye.
I hope Aunt Eleanor
starts feeling better.
[ Muttering ]
[ Dad Groans ]
[ Water Running ]
- [ Water Continues ]
- [ Dad Muttering ]
[ Groaning ]
Margaret?
- [ Clock Ticking ]
- [ Footsteps ]
- [ Door Creaking ]
- What are you doing?
Shh!
I'm scared, Casey.
I saw something last night.
Dad cut his arm, and this
green stuff was oozing out of it.
- You're nuts.
- And he was talking to himself,
and he had leaves growing
out of his head.
- [ Yawns ] Cut it out.
- I'm not kidding, Casey.
- Do you want to know what I think?
- No. What.
- I think Dad's a mad scientist.
- [ Groans ]
[ Dad ] Margaret, Casey.
Come here, kids.
Hey.
Have a seat.
It's almost ready.
Coming right up,
two of Dad's specials.
Hey, Dad, what's with the cap?
I thought you hated baseball.
So I guess you kids think that your
old dad's acting pretty darn weird.
Huh?
There something wrong,
Margaret?
Something bothering you?
- Come on. Talk to me.
- I saw you last night...
- in the bathroom.
- Spying on me?
No. I mean that--
No. You're just...
concerned about me.
- Right?
- Dad,
why are leaves growing
out of your head?
Well, that's... just a side-effect.
It's only temporary.
It'll go away soon,
and my hair will grow back.
That's why I'm wearing this cap.
Why was there green stuff
coming out of your cut?
Well, uh, that wasn't
coming out of my cut.
That was fluid that comes from...
the leaves.
Now--
I'm working on something,
and it's very, very unusual.
I'm trying to build a plant...
that is part animal.
You mean, you're taking animal cells
and putting them into plants?
I can't say any more.
How about some breakfast?
[ Spoon Scraping ]
- Eat.
- Um, what is it?
It's my special recipe.
Go ahead. Dig in.
- Doesn't smell so good.
- It'll taste just fine.
What's the matter with you two?
Pick up your spoons and eat it.
- [ Doorbell Rings ]
- [ Gasps ]
[ Doorbell Rings ]
When I get back,
I expect those bowls to be empty.
[ Doorbell Rings ]
[ Dad ]
Dr. Marek.
- What are you doing here?
- Watch for Dad.
As I said a few weeks ago,
I'll come by and check
on how your work's coming,
- and I was in the neighborhood.
- Come on. Hurry.
You know, I've always thought
that you were.
It wasn't my idea to let you go.
The board forced me.
But I'm not giving up yet.
So now let's see what kind
of progress you've made.
Oh! Hi, guys.
How are you?
- Have you finished your breakfast?
- Yeah. It was pretty good.
Look, I'll-- I'll just
be down there, okay?
Hey, um--
I want you kids
to go outside and play.
[ Birds Twittering ]
I don't believe anything
Dad says anymore.
At least Dad told us
about his experiments.
Yeah, but what about that gross junk
he tried to make us eat?
Good one.
[ Dad ] Dr. Marek, if you
would have backed me...
- when I brought in my numbers...
- [ Dr. Marek ] I tried to.
They were good numbers.
They were very, very good numbers.
But the university
never got the numbers.
- [ Margaret ] Casey?
- Wait.
- I was always trying to make a case.
- Dr. Brewer, please.
- All by myself--
- Listen to me--
[ Arguing, Indistinct ]
[ Dr. Marek ]
No!
Captioned by Grant Brown