[ Wind Whistling ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Man ]
Goosebumps.
Viewer beware.
You're in for a scare.
[ Chuckles ]
I call it home sweet home. I'm
entering it in the city art show.
Sara, that's just beautiful.
- It belongs in a museum. Nice work.
- Mm-hmm.
She showed us the exact
same picture last family night.
Amy, wait your turn.
[ Sighs ]
This week,
I thought it would be nice
to show a movie
I made all about us.
[ Videocassette Loading ]
- [ Pop ]
- There's Mom sticking to her diet again.
And Dad's getting his hair just right.
[ Clears Throat ]
Here's how come Sara
hogs the bathroom so much.
- [ Laughs ]
[ Sara ] Jed, you're such a pain.
Guess whose new sweater
Amy's trying.
- You little geek!
- [ Videocassette Ejects ]
Amy,
where's your sense of humor?
Yeah. I could win a fortune on
that Fractured Family Video show.
How many times do I have to tell
you not to try on my clothes?
That's not very nice.
Next time, ask to use the camera.
- Sorry.
- Now can I have my turn?
So, Dennis,
how was your family picnic?
Were you bothered by any ants?
[ High-pitched Voice ]
No, worse. Termites.
You've heard of the Terminator. Well,
we had to call in the exterminator.
- [ Laughing ]
- [ Sighs ]
- That's the best part.
- This is so embarrassing.
You said I could get a new one.
So I did. Why don't you
look behind the couch?
Really?
You really got me a new dummy?
[ Dad ]
Well, almost new.
I was-- I was passing the
secondhand store near my office.
There he was,
just sittin' in the window.
[ Amy ] Oh, wow. He's great.
"Slappy"?
Daddy, thank you.
"Karru marri odonna loma...
molonu karrano"?
Sounds like a foreign language
or something.
It probably means
"It takes a dummy to want a dummy."
[ Sara Laughs ]
You and I are gonna make
a great team. I just know it.
It's nice to meet you, Slappy.
[ High-pitched Voice ]
It's nice to meet you too, Amy.
[ Normal Voice ] It must
be great to have a new home.
- [ Male Voice ] You got that right, kiddo.
- Amy!
Amy, if I catch you in
my room again, you're toast.
- Got it?
- I was just trying it on.
I didn't hurt your dumb sweater.
Well, just stay out.
Now go to bed.
- Don't have to.
- Yeah, we don't have to.
- [ Gasps ]
- Come on.
- Mom says so.
- [ Amy ] That's weird.
Look, Dennis.
Here's your new friend, Slappy.
Good night, Slappy.
Good night, Dennis.
[ Clatter ]
Dennis.
Ah, Dennis.
[ Footsteps ]
[ Door Creaks ]
[ Sara ]
Mom! Dad!
- [ Breathing Heavily ]
- Sara, what is it?
It's ruined! Just look!
It's totally destroyed!
Oh, wow.
- What'd you do that for?
- I didn't do it. I found this in the hall.
How could you?
You're always jealous of my art.
- I didn't. Why would I?
- So who did, the tooth fairy?
Pretty dumb, Amy. Even I wouldn't
try and get away with that.
- Jed, stay out of it.
- We'll talk about this later.
Now go get dressed.
I'm always blamed
for everything around here!
[ Footsteps Departing ]
[ Mom ]
Amy! You'll miss your bus!
Coming.
Sorry you had to end up with
such a bizarre family, Slappy.
Ew! Red paint?
What's going on?
How did this get here?
# If you're happy and you know it #
# Clap your hands #
# If you're happy and
you know it clap your hands #
# If you're happy and you know it #
# And you really wanna show it #
# If you're happy and you know it
Clap your hands #
[ Laughing ] Hey! Thank you,
thank you, thank you, ladies and germs.
And now I'd like to turn
the family night stage over...
to Amy Kramer
and her little pal, Slappy.
Take it away, Amy!
Hee, hee!
[ Sighs ]
[ As Slappy ]
Hey there, family. Nice to see ya.
[ Normal Voice ]
So, Slappy,
how do you like being part
of the Kramer family so far?
[ Slappy ] It's fantastic, but then
my last family was a pine tree.
[ Groans, Laughing ]
- So, what did you think of Dad's song?
- [ Slappy ] That was your dad?
Well, what a relief. I thought the
cat got stuck in the dishwasher.
- [ Laughs ]
- Amy, that's not very nice.
- Slappy!
- And how about that mother of yours?
She went to a store and asked
the clerk if he had anything her size.
And he told her to try
the freight elevator. [ Laughs ]
Amy!
- But it's not me. It's him.
- [ Jed ] Oh, right.
"The dummy made me do it."
I wouldn't laugh.
You're such a booger-brain,
you tried to grow an eggplant
by burying a chicken.
Hey, cut it out.
- Yeah, cut it out.
- You call yourself an artist?
Why don't you give up brushes
and try using a roller?
- Is this supposed to be funny?
- No! I can't stop him!
- Help me get him off!
- Hey, hey! Easy on the threads.
- Well, I can.
- Amy, what's gotten into you?
- Kids, come on! Get-- Come on!
- [ Grunting ]
- I'm not saying those things.
- Okay.
- Slappy is.
- [ Dad ] Okay, young lady.
That's enough. Up to bed.
And take the dummy with you.
[ Slappy Laughing ]
[ Amy ]
Who are you? What are you?
Talk to me!
[ Sighs ]
Maybe I am crazy.
But not crazy enough to let you
do the talking for me.
[ Children Shouting In Distance ]
[ Amy ]
Wow, this poster's turning out great.
So, you think Shane's
gonna ask you to the dance?
I wish.
But I could always go with Tyler.
- Alicia, what have you got there?
- Dolls. I found them.
Sorry.
She's such a snoop.
That's okay.
It's not like I play with them anymore.
How come I always get stuck
babysitting? Tina never has to.
It's because you're in the middle.
The oldest one gets to do...
whatever they want, and the
youngest gets away with everything.
It's like a rule or something.
Sometimes I wish I didn't have
any brothers or sisters.
[ Girl ]
Yeah. Tell me about it.
Amy, you're in big trouble.
Who said you could go into
my room and steal my markers?
I didn't steal them.
We were just borrowing them.
Well, you're using them up.
You never even asked.
I told you to stay out of my room!
Just stay out of my life!
Hi, Slappy.
My name's Alicia.
- Alicia, don't touch that.
- She won't hurt it.
[ Alicia ]
He said he couldn't breathe in there.
Hey, Margo.
You can forget about Shane.
He thinks you got a face
like a can of worms.
- Amy!
- Stop it! I didn't say it. He did.
He's funny. Ow! Hey!
He won't let me go!
- Amy, cut it out!
- Stop it! Let her go!
Let me go!
- Help me!
- [ Laughing ]
Let me go right now!
Help!
[ Screams ]
[ Laughing Continues ]
Let me go right now!
Make him stop!
- Make him stop!
- Amy, what are you doing?
I'm not doing anything!
Stop it! Let her go!
What in the world--
Uh-oh.
- Are you all right?
- Stay away from her!
What is going on up here?
Slappy grabbed Alicia
and he wouldn't let go!
- What?
- You're such a liar-- A big, fat liar!
I don't ever want to see you again--
Not ever.
Margo, it wasn't me!
Amy, this has gone far enough.
But--
You are staying in your room
until your father gets home.
I don't want to hear
another word about that dummy.
[ Slappy Laughing ]
[ Sighs, Laughing ]
[ Amy ]
This can't be happening.
[ Laughing Continues ]
[ Children Shouting In Distance ]
[ Dad ]
Amy, this isn't funny.
You can't keep blaming
a doll for things
you don't want to
take responsibility for.
Slappy's not a doll.
He's a dummy.
I can't help it
if he's haunted or something.
Why won't anybody believe me?
- Amy, this is just getting too weird.
- "Weird" with a capital "W."
[ Mom ]
Come on now, you two.
We're here to help Amy as a family,
not to criticize.
Look. I know it's hard to believe,
but there's something going on,
- something I can't explain.
- [ Jed ] Yeah, right.
Pumpkin, when I was your age,
I had two older brothers
and a baby sister to deal with.
I-I know what it feels like
to be caught in the middle.
Nobody's listening to me!
It's all Slappy's fault!
Amy, if you really and truly believe
that Slappy is responsible for all this,
then maybe we need
to get some help.
- You mean like a doctor or something?
- Like a total headshrinker.
- Sara!
- I'm not making this up!
- Can I watch TV now?
- [ Sighs ]
- [ Door Slams ]
- What?
[ Thumping ]
[ Door Creaking ]
[ Static Crackling ]
[ Door Opens ]
[ Footsteps Departing ]
[ Gasps ]
[ String Plucks ]
[ Groaning ]
What the... Amy!
- [ Mom Sighs ]
- [ Groans ]
Oh, Amy, how could you?
He was gonna hit Dad.
I had to stop him!
Who was?
What are you talking about?
[ Strings Snapping ]
- [ Mom ] Amy!
- I didn't do it! He did!
- [ Sighs ]
- Okay.
This stops here and now.
- But-- but--
- No "buts," young lady.
I want you back upstairs
and in bed now.
We'll discuss this in the morning.
[ Vehicle Passing ]
[ Jed ]
Way to go, Amy.
Oh, be quiet.
I never did anything.
Jed, Sara, get ready for school.
- I am ready.
- They want to talk to Amy alone.
Amy, your mother and
I have talked about this,
and we want you to tell us
what you think we should do.
You mean like a punishment?
I think we both know
that's not the answer.
This is about a lot more than
wrecking your father's guitar.
Amy, we want to help,
but we can't begin to understand
what's happening here...
if you keep blaming
Slappy for everything.
I'm telling the truth.
[ Sighs ]
I'm late for an open house.
When you're ready to tell us
what's really bothering you,
then we'll talk.
- Is that clear?
- [ Door Closes ]
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Margo ]
This is gonna be a really cool dance.
[ Girl ]
Yeah.
Let's put up a few more signs here,
and then let's go down
to the next block.
- It's gonna be the best dance--
- Hi, Margo.
[ Sighs ]
You're never gonna
hurt me again-- ever.
Hey, kid, wait, wait--
Hey-- Hey, come on!
[ Splashing ]
So why'd you do it?
Really?
- Do what?
- Wreck Dad's guitar.
You knew you couldn't
get away with it.
There's no point in me
telling you the truth,
'cause you think I'm crazy anyways.
Well, tell Jed
to wipe his stupid feet!
[ Slappy ]
Hey, Amy?
- Hmm? [ Gasps ]
- Guess who!
- [ Laughs ]
- Keep away from me.
But we're partners, Amy,
remember?
Wasn't very nice of you to
dump me in the sewer like that.
What do-- What do you want?
Don't you get it yet?
You can't get rid of me.
What are you talking about?
Don't you remember, Amy?
You spoke the words.
- "Karru marri odonna loma"--
- "...Molonu karrano"?
You and I are one now.
Inseparable.
You are my slave.
No, I'm not gonna be your slave.
You can't make me!
Ha! I can make you
do anything I want.
You have no choice.
Your whole family thinks you're crazy.
I've seen to that.
[ Laughs ]
They'll lock you up. They can
only see you on visiting days.
- No!
- [ Laughs ] Whoa!
Amy, I can hurt you and your
family in a hundred ways.
No! I won't let you!
- Amy?
- Sara!
- Amy, what is--
- Sara, he's-- He's-- He's--
[ Laughing ]
Hey, Sara, wanna play?
[ Both Scream ]
Hey, what's going on?
You can run,
but you cannot hide!
- [ Laughs ]
- [ Both Screaming ]
- What are we gonna do?
- I can't believe it.
- [ Slappy Laughing ]
- [ Both Scream ]
Ready or not--
[ Laughs ]
See? I told you.
No one would believe me.
I know. I'm sorry.
I believe you now.
- [ Slappy Laughs ]
- [ Footsteps Departing ]
I think he's gone.
[ Together ]
Jed!
Jed?
Jed, are you okay?
[ Lamp Shatters ]
Yoo-hoo!
Lookin' for somebody?
I've seen better swings
on playgrounds. [ Laughs ]
- [ Footsteps ]
- Where is he? Where'd he go?
- Gotcha!
- [ Gasps ]
- Amy!
- [ Grunts ]
Yee-haw!
From now on,
this family belongs to me.
You're mine, Amy.
You're mine.
[ Laughing ]
[ Screams ]
[ Breathing Heavily ]
- What was that?
- [ Dad ] What's going on here?
Amy was telling the truth!
Slappy was after us,
and then he turned out the lights!
- But Jed saved us.
- What? Slow down.
Yeah. What's going on?
What'd I do?
If you didn't do it, then who--
[ Laughs, Goofy Voice ]
It's good to be back in the family again.
[ Laughing ]
[ Laughing Continues, Echoes ]
Captioned by Grant Brown