[ Wind Whistling ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Man ]
Goosebumps.
Viewer beware.
You're in for a scare.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Indistinct Voices ]
Who's there?
[ Screams ]
Got ya.
What a krej.
I told you he was a krej.
That's jerk spelled backwards,
you krej!
What's your problem, Terra?
What have a ever done to you?
[ Laughs ]
That's it. I've had it.
- [ Terra ] Mom.
- [ Boy ] Come back here!
[ Mom ]
Michael!
- [ Mom ] Michael!
- [ Terra ] He won't leave me alone.
She's the one,
she's always doing this to me.
He's lying.
Michael, what are you doing
with that?
I want that cleaned up
and you too.
I got you good,
almost as good as at your party?
[ Kids Talking ]
Gosh, Henry,
I wonder if it's a CD.
No, Josh, a football.
[ Laughing ]
Awesome, thanks, Mona.
I don't have this one.
Of course not. You said it
was lame and you threw it out.
But now you'll probably like it,
now that he's in love.
[ Laughing ]
[ Mom ] Michael, can you give me
a hand with the cake?
Mom, I don't want Terra at my party,
she's ruining it.
Well, your friends seem
to find her very entertaining.
Yeah, but it's my party.
Michael, take this inside.
I'll go get some candles
and you can make a wish.
I did make a wish,
but Terra the terrible is still here.
- [ Screams ]
- [ Kids Laughing ]
Hey, Michael, aren't you supposed
to serve your guests first?
[ Kids Laughing ]
[ Man ]
Watch out, kid.
I've been wanting this
for a long long time.
A clock?
- An ugly clock.
- A magical clock.
Magical?
That's what the man
at the antique shop said.
Hey, Dad,
what are these numbers for?
- They tell the years.
- Hey, cool!
Don't touch it.
How can a clock be magical?
Well, the legend is that
a stranger old man
built the lock over
a hundred years ago
and put a magical spell on it.
But they say whoever discovers
the magic must beware.
- [ Cuckoo ]
- [ Together ] Oh.
- [ Cuckoo, Cuckoo ]
- Seems to work fine
The man said there was something wrong with
the clock but he wouldn't tell me what is was
- [ Clock Noise ]
- Terra, stop that.
Now I don't want either of you
to put a finger on this clock, alright.
Yes, Daddy.
Come here.
- [ Dad ] Terra.
- Yes, Daddy.
[ Dad ]
I thought I told you not to touch this.
If I find that there is anything
broken on this clock
you are in serious trouble.
Yes!
[ Eerie Noise ]
[ Noise ]
[ Loud ]
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Cuckoo Cuckoo ]
Try explaining this one, Terra.
[ Clock Ticking ]
Dad, how's the clock?
What's going on,
my birthday was three days ago?
I get to go to your party.
Alright, real funny joke.
Michael, will you tell me
what you want for breakfast
because your friends
will be here soon
and I still have to pick up the cake.
Alright, guys, the joke over.
What joke?
Gosh, Henry,
I wonder if it's a CD?
No, Josh, it's a football.
[ Laughing ]
Awesome. Thanks, Mona,
I don't have this one.
Of course not.
You said it was lame
and you threw it out.
But now you'll probably like it,
now that he's in love.
[ Laughing ]
[ Think ] This is all to weird.
Everything's happening all over again.
[ Think ]
The cake, Terra. Not this time.
Michael, will you take this inside.
I'll go get the candles
and you can make a wish.
[ Think ] What's happening to me?
Maybe I'm losing my mind.
- Whoa!
- [ Kids Laughing ]
Michael, aren't you supposed
to serve your guests first?
[ Kids Laughing ]
[ Dad ] Enough. Michael, you have
been going on about this all day.
I'm telling you.
I'm caught in a time warp.
- He doesn't feel warm.
- I'm not sick.
I'm sorry
you didn't like your birthday.
I didn't like it twice.
Look, you guys have
got to believe me.
I woke up and
it was three days ago.
Michael, try to get some sleep.
Okay.
You're going to feel
a lot better in the morning.
Like I always say,
tomorrow's another day.
Better be.
[ Screams ]
[ Running Music ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Screams ]
[ Screaming ]
Michael.
What is it, sweetie?
Are you having bad dreams?
Oh, I know what it is.
You're just excited because
it's your birthday tomorrow.
Well, it actually is tomorrow.
Happy birthday, Mikey!
My big boy is six years old.
Six?
[ Screams ]
What's wrong, little buddy?
Hair?
I can't be six. I'm twelve.
- Of course you're six.
- No, I'm twelve!
Honey, it's his birthday,
let him be twelve. If he wants.
If I'm six. Where's Terra?
Terra? Who's Terra?
Oh, Terra.
[ Whispering ] His invisible friend.
[ Dad Whispering ]
He has can invisible friend?
Tell me, Mikey,
what does Terra look like?
[ Think ] Terra's gone.
Disappeared, that means I'm next.
Michael, close my office door
and get back into bed.
[ Michael ]
Time's going backwards.
Honey,
we've got a write on our hands.
That would make a great science
fiction story some day.
Time going backwards.
Backwoods, the cuckoo said,
that must be it.
I've got to turn it back around.
[ Dad ] Michael, Michael.
It's gone.
The cuckoo clock is gone.
What cuckoo clock?
We don't have a cuckoo clock.
Oh, stupid.
Don't call your father stupid.
Not him, me.
Dad's not going to buy
the clock for another six years.
He's delirious.
The antique store, that's were it is.
I've got to get there.
The only place you have
to go is to bed, young man.
It's late and the last thing
we need is a grumpy boy.
Hey, birthday boy!
How about a giraffe?
[ Think ] I'm a twelve year old
mind trapped in a six year old body.
How about an octopus?
[ Clown ]
My time's up.
What's wrong, Michael?
I've got to get out of here.
I've got to get downtown
to the antique store.
What's an antique?
I'm getting younger by the day.
But it's your birthday.
You're getting older.
[ Michael ]
You don't understand.
Today I'm six, tomorrow
I may be nothing.
If you're nothing can
I have your presents?
You can have them all right now
just don't tell my mom where I've gone.
[ Kids ]
Michael, where are you going?
Kids, my presents.
[ Traffic Noise ]
Hey, kid, you got the time.
[ Think ] Oh, thank you,
thank you.
- Oh, no!
- [ Banging On Door ]
Oh, Dad.
Your friends said you would be here.
What's the matter with you, Michael?
Running away from your party like that?
Dad.
You know, you're not
allowed down here by yourself.
I'm very angry with you.
I've got to get the the clock.
It's very very important.
I don't even want to discuss it.
I'm very disappointed in you.
Come on.
We're going home before your
mother worries herself to death.
[ Clock Ticks ]
[ Dad ] I don't care.
You can keep all of your reading.
"...small dogs, and all your spotted
dogs, I'll keep clifford. The end."
Read me another, please, Dad.
Just one more.
Come on. Please.
It's time for lights out.
Oh, is he still awake?
[ Dad ]
He's afraid to go to sleep.
Michael, I want you to stop it
with this time travel nonsense.
You're not going to disappear.
Terra did.
Stop with this Terra.
Who's Terra?
Honey, maybe if you read him
just one more story
it will calm him down.
I've been reading for two solid hours.
Mom, Dad, don't argue over me.
It's not worth it,
I'm not going to be here
much longer anyhow.
He doesn't seem to be warm.
Listen, buddy.
I'll leave your night light on.
Try please to go sleep.
Everything's going to be just fine.
- Good night, Son.
- Not goodnight, goodbye.
[ Think ]
I'm alive, wait a minute.
Spinning dinosaurs.
What's that smell. Oh, no.
Oh! Oh, does Mikey
want his diaper changed.
[ Think ] I'll just explain to her
I have to get to the antique store.
Mama!
[ Think ]
Oh, great.
I hope you're not running a fever.
[ Think ]
Where's she going?
Maybe I should check
your temperature.
[ Think ]
Oh, no. Anything but that.
Hey, what's with my little man?
His temperature's normal.
How would my little buddy
like to go for nice walk downtown.
[ Think ] Wait a minute,
we could be on to something.
Yeah, maybe do
some window shopping.
[ Think ]
Getting warmer.
Take a look in that antique store.
[ Think ] Bingo!
[ Mom ]
You can't go to Antique Store.
[ Think ]
What's wrong with the antique store.
The antique store charges
an arm and a leg.
[ Think ]
So give them an arm and a leg.
Maybe we shouldn't go anywhere.
He's getting fussy.
[ Think ] How's thing?
[ Laughing ]
Oh, he's fine.
[ Think ]
Hurry up, times running out.
Let's go to the Antique Store.
We're just going to look.
[ Think ]
Let's go. Let's go.
[ Laughing ]
Oh, look at that stuff, Mikey.
[ Think ] Where's the clock.
I've got to find the clock.
Cuckoo!
Right up here.
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Think ]
One minute left, here we go.
Clumsy fool.
[ Low Noise ]
[ Clock Noise ]
Grab that baby!
[ Dad ]
Michael!
[ Noise ]
Oh.
Michael, how many times have
I told you to stay away from this clock.
You're twelve years old,
act like it.
I am twelve! I am twelve, Dad!
I love you.
Well, I love you too,
but keep your hands off my cuckoo.
Okay, guys. Lunch is ready.
Mom. Mom, I love you.
I'll get Terra.
Who's Terra?
[ Dad ]
Michael, come here.
I think I found the flaw,
the year 1988 is missing.
That's the year Terra
would have been born.
Who's Terra?
Ah, nobody, Dad. Nobody.
Come and eat, you nut.
I'll be there in a second.
[ Think ]
So Terra has never been born.
I supposed there is someway to
go back in time and get her, right?
I guess I probably ought
to do that, and I will,
one of these days.
Captioned by Grant Brown