[ Wind Whistling ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Man ]
Goosebumps.
Viewer beware.
You're in for a scare.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Car Idling ]
[ Engine Stops ]
- [ Man ] Okay, everybody grab something.
- [ Dog Whines ]
I know what you mean, killer.
I didn't want to move here either.
Come on, sweetie.
You know we needed more room.
Yeah, come on, Kitty.
Give it a chance.
[ Horn Honks ]
- Hey, Carlo.
- Hey. Come to help us unpack?
No. But I will.
Guess what.
It only took me eight minutes
and 46 seconds to get here.
Ah. You see? We're practically
in the same neighborhood.
[ Kisses ]
Come on, Killer. Let's go.
When we moved into our new
house, everyone was happy--
Everyone but me, that is.
[ Groans ]
Here, sweetheart.
- Oh, Killer.
- I'll get him, Mom. Come here, Killer.
I had a feeling
something bad was gonna happen.
Guess what. I was right.
- [ Kitty ] Killer?
- [ Whines ]
[ Barks ]
Killer, what's gotten into you?
[ Whining ]
Come on. Outside.
Out you go. Good boy.
- [ Barks ]
- Take my advice.
When your dog whines
and paws at something
and you go see what it is,
be careful.
- [ Barking Continues ]
- Be very careful.
- Oh, it's a kitty.
- [ Whining ]
- Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
- [ Whining Continues ]
- Come here.
- [ Whining ]
[ Barking, Whining Continues ]
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Come here.
There we go.
Come on, Kitty.
Come here.
[ Whining ]
- [ Snarling ]
- [ Kitty Screaming ]
[ Panting ]
[ Barking Continues ]
[ Gasps ]
- Gross.
- [ Growls ]
- [ Screams ]
- Kitty, what happened?
- That thing! It's alive!
- You were scared by a sponge?
[ Kitty ]
Butt out, okay?
- [ Whining ]
- Killer was after it. He could tell.
It has eyes and everything.
- It's just your basic sponge.
- [ Killer Barks ]
Must have been the light
reflecting on it or something.
- My china.
- Oh, no.
My mother gave me these dishes.
- Get that dog out of here.
- Come on, Killer.
[ Barks ]
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
[ Wind Whistling ]
[ Creaking ]
[ Squeaking ]
[ Glass Shatters ]
- [ Kitty ] Watch out!
- Ow! My foot.
- Daniel, what-- What happened?
- It was an accident.
I was washing my face
and I went to reach for my towel,
and it was there.
- What was there?
- That ugly sponge.
I don't know how it got in here,
but it was staring at me.
It was staring right at me.
Katrina, please.
This isn't funny anymore.
But I-- I swear,
it was right there.
Please. Now go find a broom
and clean up this glass.
- And be careful not to cut yourself.
- I need stitches, right?
[ Mom ]
Hardly.
[ Killer Panting ]
[ Scraping ]
[ Yips, Whines ]
[ Whining ]
[ Clears Throat ]
Eat a proper breakfast.
But cold pizza's got all
the basic food groups on it.
Uh-huh, and so does your face.
Uh, go and get yourself
some cereal.
Look out.
Paper towel with eyes.
Very funny.
Hey, have you guys
seen Killer this morning?
I thought he was in your room.
He was with me last night,
but he wasn't this morning.
- Danny, you seen him?
- No.
I'm gonna go take a ride
around later. See if I can find him.
It's not like him
just to run off like that.
Bad things were happening,
and they were getting worse.
First it was my mom's
smashed dishes.
Then my brother's cut foot.
Now my dog had disappeared,
and I thought, "What's next?"
My brakes!
[ Screams ]
[ Grunts, Groans ]
[ Exhales ]
This proved it.
Something was definitely going on.
- [ Roaring ]
- [ Gasps ]
- You scared?
- Nah.
[ Sighs ]
[ Daniel ]
What happened?
- I trashed my bike.
- Wow.
Everything's going wrong.
- Did killer come home?
- No. Dad's checkin' the pound.
There's something weird
going on here.
I have this creepy feeling
it's all tied in with that sponge.
Here she goes again.
Killer sponge from Mars.
All I know is that ever
since we found that sponge,
we've had nothing but bad luck.
[ Growling ]
[ Gasps ]
Get away from me!
- See? What did I tell you, huh?
- This is better than The X Files.
- What are you gonna do with it?
- I'm gonna get rid of it once and for all.
[ Snarling ]
What if it's a new
species or something?
Then it's about to get extinct.
Kat, this sponge is amazing.
It needs to be studied.
[ Kitty ]
No. It needs to be dead.
I'm asking you in the name
of science not to do this.
- [ Gasps ]
- You're right. Forget science.
Bury the stupid sponge.
[ Snarling ]
Say good night, spongy.
Think our bad luck's
about to change.
[ Kitty ]
I was right about one thing.
Our luck was going to change--
from bad to worse.
[ Squeaks ]
You're gonna catch a chill, Kitty.
Come on inside.
It's bedtime.
- Still no sign of Killer, huh?
- No.
But he'll turn up.
I know he will.
Everything's gonna
be all right from now on.
- [ Squeaks ]
- Come on inside.
[ Squeaks ]
[ Rumbling ]
What happened?
[ Kitty ]
Everything's dying.
Kat, what happened?
What do you think?
[ Snarling ]
What are we gonna do with it now?
We need an expert.
I'm gonna take it to school.
Maybe Miss Vanderhoff
will know what to do with it.
Aha.
Just as I suspected.
It's a sponge.
I know that.
But what kind of a sponge?
Garden-variety natural
kitchen sponge, by the look of it.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, this thing is weird.
It has eyes and everything.
Eyes?
Sponges don't have eyes.
Well, maybe it's not a sponge then.
I don't know.
I-it moves around a lot.
All this bad stuff's been happening.
Look, can't you just check it out?
Dissect it or something?
Please?
Check back with me
tomorrow after school.
Thanks, Miss Vanderhoff.
Oh, and Miss Vanderhoff?
- Mm-hmm.
- Just make sure that whatever you do,
you put it back in its cage
when you're done.
Bye.
Oh!
[ Kitty ]
Things kept getting weirder--
And I mean weird.
"Encyclopaedia of the Weird"?
- Does it have her picture in it?
- [ Laughs ]
So what does the book say?
It says that your weirdo sponge
is actually a grool.
A grool?
What's a grool?
Theoretically, a grool
is mythological creature...
believed to be
a living bad-luck charm.
- You mean it causes bad luck?
- Exactly.
And then it feeds
on the bad luck it causes.
Each time something bad happens
it gets stronger.
Well, that explains all the accidents.
Does it say how to kill it?
Mmm, no.
- Do you really buy all this?
- Straight from the book.
Just be glad you didn't find a lanx.
- [ Daniel ] A what?
- A lanx.
It's this little vampire potato
that sucks the life force
right out of you.
- It's got these mean little teeth--
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Let's just deal with one monster
at a time, all right?
Why don't we just mail it
to the north pole,
- or drop it in the ocean or something?
- Not a good idea.
If the owner gives a grool away,
the owner dies.
I must be the owner.
I'm the one that found it.
That's right.
Lucky thing you dug it up
from the garden.
Oh, but I left it with
Miss Vanderhoff at school.
- You what?
- Does that count?
- I wouldn't wait around to find out.
- We have to get it back now!
[ Man Humming ]
# You are my sunshine #
# My only sunshine #
# You make me happy
when skies are gray #
# You'll never know, dear
how much I love you #
# Please don't take #
# My sunshine away #
- It's not here.
- It's gotta be.
Okay. Just-just stay calm.
Everybody spread out and search.
# You'll never know, dear #
[ Tape Running Down ]
- [ Resumes ]
- # Dear, how much I love you #
# Please don't take
my sunshine away #
[ Sniffing ]
- [ Gasps ]
- What?
- [ Groans ]
[ Whispering ]
It's bubble gum.
- [ Door Rattling ]
- Hide.
[ Tape Player Continues ]
- [ Electrical Buzzing ]
- Hmm.
[ Whispering ]
What happened?
[ Clicking ]
- What's he doing?
- Fixing the lights.
- [ Groans ]
- [ Gasps ]
Come on.
- Is he dead?
- [ Kitty ] No. He's breathing.
- [ Scraping ]
- I know that sound.
[ Daniel ]
We've gotta get help.
You just stay with him, all right?
I think it came from the shelves.
I'll go check it out.
[ Daniel ]
Okay.
Oh, man. He took a really
bad bump on the head.
[ Carlo ]
He's out cold.
"Danger. Acid."
- [ Snarling ]
- [ Kitty Screaming ]
- Oh!
- Kat! Watch out.
[ Daniel ]
Kat, are you all right?
It's okay. I'm fine, really.
[ Scraping ]
Oh, no.
Look at this mess.
It's going everywhere.
The door's blocked!
We're trapped!
And that thing, the grool--
It's growing. What are we gonna do?
We'll have to go out the window!
Come on.
[ Kitty ] I'll grab his legs. Come on.
We'll have to carry him up.
- [ Daniel Groans ]
- [ Clatters ]
- What's that?
- It's his tape player.
- [ Tape Player: Indistinct ]
- [ Snarling ]
[ Kitty ]
Look at the grool. It's shrinking.
- Why? What's happening?
- I don't think it likes the music.
Neither do I,
but why would it hate the music?
[ Daniel ]
'Cause it makes you wanna puke.
Yeah, but why does
it make you wanna puke?
'Cause it's so happy.
That's it. The grool loves bad,
so it must hate good.
Happy is good.
Go turn up the music.
I'm gonna see if
I can get it in its cage.
[ Tape Runs Down ]
Daniel?
Daniel, what happened?
Nothing.
[ Carlo ] It's growing again.
We've gotta do something.
- What?
- Sing the song, Kat. Sing!
- I don't know the words.
- Well, make something up.
- Um-- um--
- And make it corny.
Did I ever tell you
what a wonderful sponge you are?
- [ Carlo ] Great. It's working. Keep going.
- So-- So handsome.
- So terrific.
- Of course.
Brilliant.
Kill it with kindness.
I love your big, beautiful eyes--
All of them.
I love what you've done
with your hair.
And-and that skin-- So damp
and yellow and absorbent.
When I grow up, I wanna
be a killer sponge just like you.
- [ Carlo ] Uh-oh. Look at the chemicals.
- [ Janitor Groaning ]
- [ Daniel ] What's that smell?
- It's growing again.
- [ Coughing ]
- [ Janitor ] What-- What's happening?
Kids! Kids!
Stay where you are.
I'll take care of it.
- [ Coughs ]
- I've got this under control.
- [ Kids Coughing ]
- [ Janitor ] Ah.
Aha!
- Hey, it worked.
- All right.
[ Daniel ]
Cool. It shrunk.
[ Kitty ] As it said in the
Encyclopaedia of the Weird,
I couldn't get rid of the grool.
- It's mine forever.
- [ Knocking ]
So I did the next best thing.
Good morning, "Grooly."
Another beautiful day.
- There you go. Enjoy your music.
- [ Dance Pop ]
[ Killer Barking ]
- [ Barking ]
- Killer!
Oh, Killer, you're back!
- Come here, boy.
- Killer! How's it goin', big guy?
- Yeah!
- Oh, boy, where have you been?
- See? I told you he'd come back.
- Good boy.
- Okay, everyone... French toast.
- Oh, all right.
- Yes!
- Yeah.
Killer.
What did you bring me, huh?
What did you bring back?
What is it?
- A potato?
- [ Snarls ]
[ Screaming ]
Captioned by Grant Brown