[ Wind Whistling ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Man ]
Goosebumps.
Viewer beware.
You're in for a scare.
[ Chuckles ]
Earlier on Goosebumps--
I'll be back as soon as I can.
I know. It's just that
I'm worried about Dad.
He's been acting so weird lately.
He's under a lot of pressure,
Margaret.
But he never has time
for me anymore.
He's even stopped
calling me Princess.
Look, kids, I'm sorry
I raised my voice.
I just don't want you
down in the basement.
- Do you hear it?
- I'm not sure.
- [ Casey ] Wow.
- It's like a jungle.
- What are you doing?
- That plant just grabbed me.
[ Muttering ]
I'm trying to build a plant...
that is part animal.
So now let's see what kind
of progress you've made.
Go ahead. Eat.
Dr. Marek, if you would have backed me
when I brought in my numbers--
- [ Dr. Marek ] I tried to.
- Casey?
[ Dad ] You had your chance.
You had your chance.
Doctor, please.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
No!
[ Screams ]
- What are you doing?
- [ Casey Groans ]
- Casey?
- Get it off! Margaret!
Real funny.
- Help me! I'm caught.
- Casey.
Margaret, come here quick!
Please, Margaret!
- Get it off! Get it off! Get it off!
- Casey!
Get it off! Margaret!
Aah! Get it off!
Pull, pull, pull!
- Hold still.
- Get it off!
[ Whimpers ]
- [ Squealing ]
- [ Margaret ] You okay?
- They were fighting.
- Who?
I don't know.
Dad, I guess, and Dr. Marek.
- In the basement.
- A-Are you sure?
I couldn't see,
but I heard them.
- Then that thing got me.
- [ Gasps ]
- What are you doing?
- That plant tried to choke me.
You shouldn't have been
near the window.
Well, Casey heard a fight
in the basement.
- There was no fight.
- But I heard it.
I'm telling you,
there was no fight.
- Where's Dr. Marek?
- He just left.
I didn't see him leave.
- Are you interrogating me, Margaret?
- No.
Now, you tell me, what were you doing
next to the basement window?
I was playing,
like you told me to.
Did you put him up to this,
Margaret?
Is this some more of your spying?
We were playing.
What about that plant?
It's part of my work--
work that you've now disrupted.
You're not a mad scientist,
are you, Dad?
No, I'm an angry scientist.
Now, both of you,
up to your rooms.
- But we could have sworn we heard--
- Did you hear what I said?
- Yeah, but--
- Go!
[ Clock Ticking ]
[ Voice, Muffled ]
[ Grunts, Groans ]
[ Thunderclaps ]
[ Mechanical Whirring ]
[ Whirring Continues ]
What's that noise?
[ Thunderclap ]
I put locks
on the basement windows--
from the inside.
So don't try getting in
through there either.
Stop gawking at me.
Now, I'm going out for a little while.
I'll be back in a couple of hours.
[ Thunderclaps ]
I'm calling Mom.
I can't believe it.
It was a white piece of paper with
Aunt Eleanor's phone number on it.
It was sitting right here
on the counter.
- What do you think happened to it?
- I think Dad took it.
- He didn't want us to call Mom.
- That's crazy.
So is leaves growing out
of your head
and green gunk coming out of your arm.
And also eating plant food and
trying to make us eat it.
And lying about Dr. Marek.
Why do you think
he's lying about Dr. Marek?
He said Dr. Marek left.
Did you see him leave?
Wh-What are you saying?
Do you think Dad's done something
to Dr. Marek?
I don't know, Casey.
Wh-What are you saying?
- I'm saying it's possible.
- No, it isn't. He's our dad.
Where are you going?
If Dad took the number,
it might be in his room.
- You're going in his room?
- You want to talk to Mom, don't you?
- [ Thunderclap ]
- [ Gasps ]
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Did you find it?
No.
- Margaret.
- What?
Come on. Let's go.
- [ Ringing ]
- Don't answer it!
- Why not?
- I don't know.
- Well, it might be Mom.
- [ Answering Machine Beeps ]
[ Dad's Voice ] Hi.
You've reached the Brewer family.
At the tone,
please leave a message,
and we'll be sure to get back to you.
- [ Beeps ]
- Hi. This is Gloria Marek,
Dr. Marek's wife.
I was wondering
if my husband was there.
I'm a little worried.
He was supposed to be home hours ago.
If you hear from him
or you know where he is,
could you please call me
a 555-0101?
- Thank you.
- [ Beeps ]
I don't like this, Casey.
I don't like it one bit.
- [ Clattering ]
- Dad!
- [ Beeps ]
- Hi. You've reached the Brewer family.
At the tone,
please leave a message,
- and we'll be sure to get back to you.
- No way. Come on.
- He's coming. He's coming!
- [ Tape Running Fast ]
- [ Machine Beeps ]
- Hi. You've reached the Brewer family.
At the tone--
[ Stops ]
Hi, Dad.
- What are you doing out of your room?
- I, um,
needed to go to the bathroom.
Where's Margaret?
She's in her room.
- Did you go in my room?
- No.
Okay. I forgot something.
I have to go back out.
I want you back in your room.
Is that clear?
[ Gasps ]
- Casey?
- Yes, Dad?
- I'll be back in an hour.
- Okay, Dad.
Stay in your room while--
- Yes, Dad.
- You too, Margaret.
[ Footsteps Departing ]
[ Door Closes ]
- You were great.
- He seemed so angry, Margaret.
He had Dr. Marek's wallet.
He dropped it and I... saw it.
What are you looking at?
There's something
under these covers.
Wh-What?
[ Thunderclap ]
- [ Gasps ]
- [ Screams ]
- [ Casey ] Gross.
I have to get to the bottom of this.
I have to know the truth.
And I have a feeling
the truth is in the basement.
Look for anything we can use
to protect ourselves.
Who knows what those plants can do?
Look. Weed killer.
Come on.
[ Grunting ]
Help me.
[ Creaking ]
Let's go.
[ Rumbling ]
[ Growling ]
Look out!
[ Squealing ]
- [ Squealing ]
- What are these things?
Whatever they are,
they aren't exactly friendly.
[ Growling ]
They're bigger, right?
Don't they all look bigger?
- [ Hisses ]
- [ Gasps ]
Oh, gross.
I think I'm going to be sick.
Hey, isn't that the plant
that tried to grab you?
The plant you cut your finger on?
Yeah.
[ Exhales ]
[ Shrieks ]
[ Squeals ]
[ Squealing ]
- [ Pounding ]
- Who's there?
[ Man Shouting, Muffled ]
Someone's in there.
- Or some thing.
- [ Pounding ]
This belongs to Dr. Marek.
He could be in there.
[ Man Groaning ]
[ Groaning Continues ]
[ Margaret ] Looks like just
a bunch of normal plants.
- Then what were--
- Those sounds?
- [ Sharp Grunt ]
- [ Margaret, Casey Scream ]
- [ Groans ]
- [ Margaret ] Dad?
- It's Dad!
- That's not Dad.
- No, stop.
- Casey, let go of me.
- What's wrong with you? It's Dad.
- It can't be Dad.
Dad left, remember?
- I've gotta untie him.
- No. Look at his head.
[ Margaret ] We already saw that.
Remember? It's a side-effect.
- [ Groans ]
- No, don't.
Okay.
I won't untie him.
I'll just take the tape off
his mouth, okay?
Mm-hmm! Mm-hmm!
[ Panting ]
Oh, kids,
it's so good to see you.
Now quick, untie me.
How'd you get in there?
I thought you left.
No, that wasn't me. I've been
locked up in that closet for days.
- Huh? But how? We saw you. You--
- No.
That wasn't me. It's a plant.
It's a plant copy of me.
- Wait.
- Look, I have no time to explain.
Just untie me. Quick.
You're saying the father
we've been living with is a plant?
Yes. Now just untie me.
How do we know
you're telling the truth?
I'll explain later.
Okay? I promise.
I'm untying him.
Oh, yes, that's it.
That's it. That's it.
[ Panting ]
[ Man's Voice, Muffled ]
- What are you doing?
- He's not our real father.
He is. I know he is.
Aren't you? Aren't you?
No, he's not.
I'm your real father.
He's not your dad.
He's not even human.
- He's a plant.
- You're the plant.
No. He's lying.
He's a copy.
He's a plant copy.
One of my experiments
that went wrong.
I put him in there because
he's dangerous. Now spray him.
No. He's the copy.
He's the dangerous one.
He's trying to make plant copies
of us all. Spray him!
I don't know what to do.
Give me that.
Get back, both of you.
Margaret, listen to me.
He'll destroy us all.
He had me locked up.
- But I escaped.
- You're a liar.
He was the one that tried
to feed you the food.
- He attacked Marek.
- No, that's not true.
He has Marek locked up
in the other cupboard.
Don't listen to him.
Attack him now.
Before it's too late.
Destroy him.
Please,
Princess.
Princess!
[ Screaming ]
How did you know?
There's only one person
who calls me Princess--
My real dad.
[ Dr. Marek ] We can study these
better at the university lab.
Oh, by the way,
the board wants to know
when you can come back, full time.
Well, as soon as I get over
all these side-effects.
[ Chuckles ]
Uh, listen. I appreciate everything
that you have done for me.
Oh, and I appreciate you
getting me out of that closet.
Well, you should thank
Margaret and Casey for that.
I still don't understand
how the whole thing started.
[ Exhales ]
Well, it was an accident.
I cut my hand on a slide,
and some of my blood mixed in
with some plant molecules,
and I ended up with something
that was part plant and part human.
- You never told me any of this.
- Yeah, I know. I should have.
But I was wrapped up in my work.
Then I went too far.
I created a plant that was
an exact copy of me.
- [ Margaret ] Except that it was evil.
- Well, to us, yes.
But like most organisms,
it wanted to dominate its environment.
It overpowered me.
I think that it wanted
to make plant copies of us all.
Oh, man!
When Aunt Eleanor was getting better,
she asked me about you two.
I said you were both
growing like weeds.
I never realized how close
to the truth I almost was.
- Well, I'm just glad we're all okay.
- And all human.
- I'll call you tomorrow, Dr. Brewer.
- Okay, thank you.
Okay. Bye.
[ Truck Door Closes ]
Well, listen.
Anybody for lunch?
I got a great mixed salad
and some garden vegetables.
- [ Groaning ]
- No, I'm only kidding.
I got hamburgers for everybody.
Let's go. Let's go!
I'll be right there.
[ Dad's Voice ]
Psst! Margaret.
Margaret, help me.
Please help me.
I'm your father.
- I'm your real father.
- No, I'm your father.
- I'm your father.
I'm your father.
No, I'm your father.
No, he isn't.
I'm your father.
[ Voices Echoing ]
Captioned by Grant Brown