[ Wind Whistling ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Man ]
Goosebumps.
Viewer beware.
You're in for a scare.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Wind Chimes Clanging ]
[ Girl Narrating ] I love to scare
my little brother Randy.
I tell him scary stories
about monsters...
until he just begs me to stop.
And I'm always teasing him by pretending
to see the monsters everywhere.
I guess that's why no one believed
me the day I saw a real monster...
until it was too late.
Randy! Haven't you ever heard
of the razor-toothed toe biter?
- What do you mean "toe biter"?
- It got Becky and Lilah next door...
while they were playing
in their wading pool.
- Couldn't they see it coming?
- Toe biter can camouflage itself as anything.
- Even water.
- [Gasps ] You're lying.
Ask Becky to take off her shoe.
She'll show you. Ask her.
- Don't use your foot!
- Do it real quick.
[ Screaming ]
Get it away!
[ Screams ]
- [ Screaming ] My toe! My toe!
- [ Screams ]
My toe!
[ Screams ]
- Mom, the toe biter got Lucy!
- [ Timer Beeping ]
Oh, Randy, calm down. You know
there's no such thing as a toe biter.
Yes, there is!
All her toes are gone!
Lucy, would you please stop
scaring your little brother?
Oh, Mom, it was just a joke.
How did all of your toes
grow back?
Haven't I asked you not
to tell him monster stories?
Actually, the toe biter gave me back my
toes, 'cause I promised to cut yours off...
- and give them to him tonight.
- No!
- Lucy!
- What's the point of having a little brother...
if you can't torture him?
Lucy, don't you have
Reading Rangers at the library?
Why don't you go and bother
Mr. Mortman for a while.
Well, what did you think?
Two thumbs down.
But, Lucy, Black Beauty
is a classic.
It would have been better
if the horse had two heads.
- [ Sighs ]
- And big, old, gnarly fangs.
Why don't you go
pick another book?
- Hey, Lucy, what you getting?
- Frankenstein.
Cool.
Are you sure, Lucy?
- Frankenstein is a classic as well.
- Yeah.
But this one's got a monster.
Wouldn't it be cool
if there were real monsters?
I'm not so sure, Aaron.
Most people like to be
frightened in movies or stories--
not in real life.
Aaron, you ever notice
anything weird about Mortman?
- Like his creepy, beady little eyes.
- And his sweaty little hands.
When he gave me my book,
it was so slimy I almost dropped it.
Yeah? Echh!
Oh, my blades.
I forgot 'em at the library.
Ah, man, I gotta get home.
Oh, no big deal.
I'll see you later.
[ Creaks ]
[ Cat Screeches ]
[ Man Humming ]
[ Humming Continues ]
Probably a classic.
[ Mortman ] It's time,
my plump, little beauties.
My, my, my little friends.
I do believe we've put on
a little weight.
Coochie, coochie,
coochie, coochie.
Don't be shy.
Ah. [ Chuckles ]
It's dinnertime,
my furry friend.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Clicks Tongue ]
Oh. Aren't you hungry?
Munch, munch.
[ Chuckles ]
Some crunchy crickets,
my little friends.
[ Slurps, Chuckles ]
Mmm!
[ Chuckling ]
[ Chuckling Continues ]
[ Grunting Loudly ]
[ Chirping ]
- [ Cricket Crunching ]
- [ Chuckling ]
[ Chuckling Continues ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
Mom! Dad! A monster!
- Huh? Where?
- At the library!
- Don't you say hi anymore?
- Hi, Dad.
There's a monster at the library!
- Lucy, please.
- What kind of monster?
Could you give us
a hand here, please?
A big, slimy, disgusting one...
that eats bugs!
Oh, I'd hoped this monster thing was
just a phase you were going through.
Life is a phase
I'm going through.
Well, could you go through it,
please,
after you've washed your hands
and set the table?
- Dad, this is no joke!
- Larry, you're making them too big.
-I happen to like big meatballs.
-Doesn't anyone here believe me?
His eyes popped out of his
head and he was eating bugs!
And everyone here
thinks I'm making it up.
- [ Aaron ] Hey, I wonder why.
- What? You don't believe me either?
Calm down, Lucy.
You're totally obsessed.
- [ Computer Game Bleeping ]
- Ooh, big word.
Well, you'll believe me
soon enough.
I'll prove it to you.
Didn't you think that
the monster was
the most sympathetic character
in this story?
Do you believe in monsters?
Perhaps we all have
a little monster in us, Lucy.
Why don't you go pick
another book while I tidy up.
- Okay.
- I'll see you tomorrow then?
Yeah, right. See ya.
[ Mortman Humming ]
- [ Light Switch Clicks ]
- [ Humming Continues ]
[ Knocking ]
It's dinnertime,
my furry friends.
Don't forget to chew.
[ Clicking Tongue Rapidly ]
[ Slurping ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Growling, Chuckling ]
[ Growling Continues ]
[ Chuckles ]
[ Sniffs ] My favorite.
[ Kissing Sounds ]
[ Chuckles ]
[ Chuckling Continues ]
[ Slurping ]
Mmm.
[ Smacking Lips ]
[ Grunting ]
Who's there?
[ Whispers ]
Stupid.
[ Growls, Chuckles ]
Lucy!
[ Chuckles ]
Keep running, little one.
I love fast food.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Panting ]
Oh, my mouth is watering.
Lucy!
I know you're in there.
- Ahh-- Aah!
- [ Screams ]
[ Chuckles ]
You're just making me hungrier.
- [ Chuckles ]
- [ Panting ]
Dinner is served.
[ Chuckling Continues ]
Come back! Come back!
Oh, come back!
[ Chuckles ] You can't get away
from me, you little cricket.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Mortman Grunts ]
Lucy! Why don't you stop?
Lucy! Come back!
Come back!
Come ba-a-ack!
[ Panting ]
If Mortman's such a terrible
monster, how'd you get away?
- [ Computer Game Bleeping ]
- I think the flash blinded him.
But I got the picture.
I got my proof.
You're forgetting something, Lucy.
Your library card
has your address on it.
- Mortman knows where you live.
- So what?
He could be on his way
to your house this minute.
- That's not funny, Aaron.
- If I were you,
I'd get out of there right now.
Good evening, Lucy.
May I come in for a minute?
No.
My parents aren't home
right now.
I mean,
they'll be home any minute.
they're in the bathroom.
Mom, is Dad still
cleaning his rifle?
It's okay, Lucy. It's really
you that I've come to see.
You left your backpack
at the library.
I have it right here.
- [ Whimpers ]
- This is yours, isn't it?
Could you maybe just
leave it on the doorstep?
Please?
Um, wouldn't it be easier if you opened
the door and let me hand it you?
- I'll just set it down here.
- Thank you.
Oh, it's no trouble.
It's on my way.
I look forward
to our next little chat.
[ Whimpers ]
Dad! Mom! He was here!
Mortman was here!
We gotta get this film
developed right away!
I took a picture that proves
he's a monster.
- Calm down, Lucy.
- He followed me home today.
He followed you home
for no reason?
Well, I forgot my knapsack at the
library and he brought it over, but...
Well, that was very nice of him.
He lives all the way across town.
- It wasn't on his way at all.
- Come on. We're wasting time.
- The photo place is gonna close!
- Now, Lucy.
- Please!
- [ Sighs ]
- Let me see! Let me see!
- I knew it.
Let go! Nice work.
- Randy, get into the car, please.
- You heard your father.
[ Car Door Opens ]
[ Car Door Closes ]
You're quite the photographer.
Mr. Mortman,
what are you doing here?
Have you been thinking
about monsters again?
Mr. Mortman.
Thanks very much for bringing
home Lucy's backpack today.
Oh, uh, it was nothing.
Uh, it was on my way.
Ah.
Mr. Mortman, why don't you come
over for dinner tomorrow night?
Lucy's been talking
a great deal about you.
It'd be nice to get
to know you better.
Well, that would be lovely.
Thank you.
It's been so long since
I've had a home-cooked meal.
[ Chuckles ]
Don't you see he's a monster?
The fact that he's not
in this picture proves it.
I don't care if he's a drooling
werewolf. He's coming for dinner.
- [ Doorbell Rings ]
- [ Gasps ]
Remember.
Your best behavior.
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
- This is very kind of you.
- Oh, it's nothing. Our pleasure, really.
[ Chuckles ]
Good evening, Lucy.
Nice to see you again, young Randy.
Will you be joining us
for Reading Rangers next year?
Can I sleep on it?
[ All Laugh ]
Of course.
My what a--
a lovely house.
Lucy?
Offer Mr. Mortman a meatball.
Mmm. Delicious.
Mm-hmm.
What's for dinner?
Well, it was going
to be a surprise, but--
Since you asked, you are.
[ Coughs ] Excuse me.
I thought you said--
That's right. You.
You are.
[ Hissing ]
[ Screeches ]
[ Dad]
Now that was a close call.
[ Sighs ]
Now listen, both of you.
You can never, ever
let anyone know...
that we are monsters.
We know that.
And we can't have any other
monsters in town either.
- [ Hisses ]
- And do you know why?
Because they might tell
other people about us.
And they'd be frightened,
and they'd chase us away.
Or worse.
Mr. Mortman's the first monster
to come around in 20 years.
Besides us, of course.
That's why it took us
so long to believe you, Lucy.
And when you two get bigger,
you're gonna get your training fangs.
That's right. Before long, you and
Randy will be able to transform...
just like your father and me.
[ Clattering ]
[ Randy ]
Oh, no! Another one!
- [ Mom ] Not another Mortman.
- What are we gonna do?
Better let him in.
- [ Mom Snarling ]
- [ Hissing ]
Hey, what's up?
Just finished dinner.
[ Aaron ]
Aw, man. Talk about timing.
Well, what's for dessert?
Well, it was going
to be a surprise, but...
since you asked.
You...
like cherry pie?
Sure.
[ Belches ]
Pardon me.
Captioned by Grant Brown