The reason why King Ming of the past was the originator of marriage
The way of repeating the continuation
Lonte at home
The rise and fall of the country
Yu Siyan
Free at kisskh.me
within the boudoir
The teaching of self-cultivation
That
teach it
Xu Shenzhi
don't move
you are too small
Stuttering
ruminant
blazing fire
Come out every night
don't you think
The imperial palace sends envoys to various places every year to collect
Thousands choose one for the grandson
Since he didn't blame
don't bother
Crickets take green as the best
You are half purple and not yellow
small
Can't fool people
you really want this
Let's go back
gone
adult
Zhang He recruits new words
Although it has nothing to do with the prince
But also a big event
He worked in the Ministry of Rites before he served in the Ministry of Households
At that time, it was the emperor's order to negotiate the positions of women in the palace officials.
When the imperial eunuch went to the selection
accepting bribes
Calculate the time
People have entered the palace
check
Yes
so small
Purple cricket again
Used to supplement the original bug king
It's too much of a joke
try
Okay
to lose
Your Highness, wait a moment
Give you three days and you can't win
Congratulations, Your Royal Highness, His Royal Highness
Your Highness
where does joy come from
this little thing
Win six games in a row
It's all a win
don't you don't look at it's ugly
Take that prince, that hussar general
Bite in one bite
Maxima often has but Bole does not often have
Even if the real bug king is close at hand
Who can know
This game has come to an end
admit defeat
hurry up
go faster
Free at kisskh.me
keep up
What happened
Sister Yin
Jinyiwei found out that someone entered the palace by impersonation
Not that someone was arrested yesterday
Why do you need to check
such a thing
one thing has two
Many people who were selected to enter the palace
unwilling to let his own daughter
Entering the palace as a maid
They spend a lot of money to buy people instead
It was implicated in the imperial eunuch and the Ministry of Rites, not to mention
Now this Miyashiro
I'm cooperating with Jinyiwei to check one by one.
And this kind of thing
That's
Sister Yin
go
Do you think she's weird?
where is strange
born so beautiful
Yu Nude cooks have experience
that day
I saw her give Fang Dianshan the account book
Beautifully handwritten
This guy can do anything
The royal family selects concubines from the people
Many families have carefully nurtured their daughters
Virtuous words and meritorious deeds are prepared
have a chance to be elected
She is soft-spoken and elegant
It looks like the daughter of a good family
Don't say she's a culinary girl
Even if you are proficient in piano, chess, calligraphy and painting
rhythm
what's strange
But a boudoir woman
Also know how to identify crickets
you really don't think so
what's the matter
tomorrow's exam
I will wait and see
Meng Shang food
The princess told me to come down
The weather is too dry after autumn
The emperor's grandson suffers from sore throat when he is slightly infected with wind and cold
you prepare some light food
Yes
Sister Yin
Jinyiwei found out that someone entered the palace by impersonation
Hidden set
Today's meal of the royal grandson
Can you give it to me
Yuan Gonggong
how are you here
Your Highness today invites Lord Yang to appreciate the chrysanthemum
hot pot for lunch
get ready
But the princess has already ordered
The emperor's grandson has to eat very lightly recently
line line
What does your highness say, how do I pass it on?
without a word
what happens is your own responsibility
and
I'll let her deliver the meal later
Yuan Gonggong Yuan Gonggong
Zijin
how can this be done
The prince is half incense stick
Prince
Half a stick of incense
hold on for a while
You are fragrant, fragrant prince
Prince Prince
Your Highness
I
It is really
I really can't run
Your Highness
my prince
You say
How can this be done
You now
Just put a knife on my neck
I can't get up either
hurry up
I used to wonder
Why did His Highness abandon the Huadian and use the thatched cottage?
Now look at this elegant scene
just understand
Free at kisskh.me
Master Yang did not say
Raise the spirit of heaven and earth
Then it is enough to take care of the world
and world affairs
than your father
no healthy body and mind
Why are you loyal to the father of the country?
father is here
Father
I
i want to dine with you
His Royal Highness
The princess is still waiting to accompany you to dinner
Are we going back?
The people are the foundation of the country
Disaster relief food previously allocated to Yingzhou
Must send someone to supervise the implementation
Previous cyclone flooding in Guangzhou
The granary of the cottage was destroyed
and
Yingtian Yangzhou Jinan House
Gee rain destroys crops
Has the person sent by the Ministry of Housing to question them come back?
Just arrived in Beijing yesterday
I have seen the emperor
That's good
The father emperor returned from the northern expedition
I don't care
But Zhili North and South
And serious floods in Shandong and Henan
people suffer
Dispatch immediately
Notify Fuzhou County
stop tax
Your Majesty has a solemn purpose
Want you to practice riding and shooting within three months
If this is to let the princess know that you are staying for dinner
Slaves can't afford to eat
Father naturally understands
Do I still need your reminder?
talkative
It doesn't hurt to break an occasional case
mother won't blame you
only
If the grandfather knew
Good news from the cottage
Can't spread the Qianqing Palace
Why is my father staring at me so?
Not Fengyang Hot Pot
Your Highness
Kikuhana Kiyohi Akime
Soothing wind and calming liver
Put it in this hot pot
don't have a flavor
Your Highness
The delivery person has left
It's alive
add dot add dot
It is said that Mr. Jingjie regards chrysanthemum as a friend
cooking with chrysanthemum
taste it slowly
This chrysanthemum pot is fragrant and elegant
Unique
so-called elegant
But if so
Prince
Last night, the King of Han spoke to His Majesty
It is said that not all the places affected by the disaster are not harvested
Prioritize things
avoid indiscriminate use of grace
nonsense
local disaster
Whether true or false
Always rescue first and then verify
This is the ancestral teaching of Daming
Saving people from poverty is like saving people from drowning
No matter how difficult the country is
Are there any people suffering from disaster?
The emperor is the lord of the world and the father of the people
How to be sympathetic to the people
How to be lenient to the people
How can this be compared with the common people?
indiscriminate grace
to say such a thing
so stupid
I'm going to my father
Your Highness must not
Father
if you go now
In case grandpa asks you what you had for lunch
with whom
how do you answer
yes yes
Prince
The King of Han slandered
you go rashly
Afraid of attracting the wrath of the emperor's thunder
bad for the people
Are you exaggerating?
What Wei Chen said was by no means intimidating His Highness
you go
The consequences are unimaginable
Is it as serious as he said?
It's as serious as he said
But I can't ignore the people's suffering
Is this good?
The emperor does not like to see me
don't want to listen to me
Then why don't we find one
To persuade those whom the emperor likes
how
Your Highness
The maid of Shangshi Bureau who delivers meals every day
He is a native of Suzhou Prefecture in Southern Zhili
I don't want to know anymore
What is the first sentence of Qian Shanzhang?
I just didn't remember anything
You are still silent until Qian Shanzhang
I'm just silent
It seems that this time I can't be a female talent.
Zijin
thank you
I will definitely pass this time
I've recited it many times, but I can't get it out.
It's too quiet.
I can't carry it
Free at kisskh.me
The ghost is at the door again
Zhang Gongzheng
This year's newly naturalized palace maid of the Shang Food Bureau
they're all here
thank you
Apart from checking the list
Mr. You still have a few words to ask
no trouble
Even if it is a hero, an honorable royal relative
Jin Yiwei can also be arrested and interrogated
What's more, my little food bureau
Mr. You wants to ask about the trial
please do it yourself
But what?
They also give to the masters of the harem
prepare dinner
missed the hour
The Food Bureau is also not good at explaining.
that's nature
stay away
Who is the surname where is the origin
Zhao Jiamin
seventeen
Originally from Yiyang County, Guangxin Prefecture, Jiangxi Province
Three generations of the family run the restaurant
Wang Shuhua
sixteen
Originally from Xiushui County, Zhejiang Province
My grandmother was the maid of the Shang Shi Bureau.
I learned cooking from her since I was a child
Best at making pastries
i don't know anything
I entered the palace according to the rules
adult
Do you have
Someone will
Check your household registration one by one
Next
Su Yuehua
eighteenth year
Renhe County, Hangzhou Prefecture, Zhejiang Province
Miss Su seems to be not only proficient in Hangzhou cuisine
back to adults
When Su Dongpo was the governor of Hangzhou
A year of heavy rain
West Lake flooding
He ordered the people to build embankments and bridges
survived the flood
My ancestors represent Hangzhou elders
I sent the braised pork and bean soup as a thank you
The ground is like jade
Sand Bottle Boiled Beans Soft as Crispy
I mean, this bowl of bean soup
Later, our Su family ran across the country
Famous chefs from generation to generation
I've always been by my father's side
Cook dishes in and out of famous mansions
If Master You thinks I'm an impostor
You can ask someone
You come
Yin Ziping
seventeen
Southern Zhili, Suzhou Prefecture
Grandfather served in Guanglu Temple
After his death, his family fell into disarray
how about you
migratory adults
Zijin is the same age as me
worldly delicacies
There's nothing she's not good at
No worse than her Su family
What can you find out?
Check it out soon
We're going in to make dinner later.
You adult
Roughly corresponds to the inventory and portrait
I'm going to Shanggong Bureau today
Let's go
It's amazing
what is the adult suspecting
The chefs of Guanglu Temple specialize in one dish all the year round
To be the ultimate can be condescending to others
let's go
Food Bureau in recent years
Famous for connecting all major cuisines
In order to suppress the name of Guanglu Temple
But their respective masters
It's still a dish from my own family.
This Yao girl's directory
Clearly written her grandfather
It's the imperial supervisor
Father is a poor inspector
He learned cooking skills from his biological mother since he was a child
A homeless woman
not a cook
How to be the same as the profound Su family
Are you good at cooking the world's delicacies?
This
Your Sichuan restaurant in Beijing
Can I get Dongpo Pork?
Immediately rush to Suzhou Fu
Who recommends who teaches
Who was sent to the palace?
One by one to verify and report
Yes
Grand Concubine
Your Highness heard that you are ill
I came to see you specially
who allowed you to tell him
Your Highness' forgiveness is my moment
please get up
are you still ill
sit
sit fast
don't pour tea
Yes
Xuan imperial doctor
Let the doctor come to see and treat
Yes
Your Highness
Ancestral family law has strict orders
The concubine in the palace was ill
Do not call a doctor easily
Besides, I'm just not eating right
Later, let Jinshu go to the pharmacy department to talk about the symptoms and get the medicine
Or invite the pharmacist
go please
Yes
Your Highness, you forgot
My grandfather was a famous doctor in Jining
I was weak when I was young
It's all done by him
I also learned some fur.
Strictly speaking
Those medical women in the pharmacy department are not as good as me.
believe me
Okay
everything depends on you
But if it gets worse
not reluctantly
seek medical attention immediately
Thank you for your concern
It was picked early
still sour
Your Highness
this is what i used
Your Highness, if you want to use it
take that box back
Preliminary
Do you remember when you first entered the palace?
I take the word for you
do you understand
When my grandfather went to the battlefield
Grandmother stays in Peiping
Soldiers approaching the city
Grandmother personally went to the city to supervise the battle
Guarded the rear for grandfather
that battle
Grandfather tried his best
Heavy casualties
Later he said
when he was on the brink of desperation
He thought of a word from his grandmother
come back no matter what
Grandfather became emperor
Sitting on the beauty of the world
But when he is angry
No one in the imperial harem dared to persuade
Only grandma dares to persuade
so-called hair couple
Regardless of life or death
hand in hand for a lifetime
grow old together
Preliminary
I wish you peace forever
I don't know what your knot is
but i want to ask
Free at kisskh.me
Are you the one who is willing to accompany me for the rest of my life?
Your Highness
I
recuperate well
I go first
Your Highness
You've been coughing all day
This is Tai Hospital
Feelings specially made for you
The doctor told me
this medicine
Best to drink hot
And this fairy porridge
Glutinous rice invigorates the qi
Scallion white to dispel wind and cold
And vinegar can kill evil poison
The doctor has seen it and said it is best for you
Your Highness
Do you want to suppress the scallion flavor?
sunny again
go
Are you going to see the grandfather back?
your highness
His Majesty
The grandson is here
grandfather
what to laugh at
i'm very busy
no lunch
You are good, your father and son
Eat chrysanthemum hot pot to enjoy the flowers
very comfortable
This
I am the king of a country
rich cosmopolitan
What about changing ten clothes a day?
just every time I remember
Queen Xiaoci lived a frugal life
so
I don't want this outside.
clothes
comfortable to wear old
later in the morning
I'm going to wear it for these ministers
let them know
The king of a country is so frugal
as a servant
should be more fortunate
I let them find this dress for a long time
How
grandfather
its not bad, right
I'm ripping a hole here
You ask someone to apply two more patches
Isn't this more like
no good words
Dismantled my desk since I was a child
Your word for a while
must be recorded on the daily note
passed on to future generations
Let future generations know
my grandfather
But the diligent and frugal emperor
This kind of reputation fishing
i disdain
This is to educate officials and officials
How come you are famous for fishing?
But it's not enough for them to see
Let them remember
Grandpa said
The foundation of the nation
This is why the sage king is to the people
Hengbao is like a child
Before eating, think about hunger first
Before you get dressed, think about the cold first
for example
Such as North and South Zhili and Shandong
And Henan Prefecture was hit by floods
The court should be smug
Don't dig, search, search everywhere
This can also reflect my grandfather
a person who loves and protects the people
You can tell at a glance
You are speaking for your father
how
What's up
fine
come come come
Huang Yan
Xuan imperial doctor
How
If the grandfather does not agree
I can't stand kneeling
Been here all the time
I
It was to take back his life as a guardian of the country.
what he did wrong
I also helped him deal with it one by one.
But such a big thing
Can you make fun of people?
get up
The grandson retire
grandfather
please use
What are you laughing at
Thank the emperor for the cake
Your Highness
Doctor Sheng please come
not allowed to speak
Yes
really poisoned
Please take this medicine, Your Highness
Your Highness
What poison has your Highness been poisoned with?
Not sure yet
but
poisoner
lest others find out
very small doses
Fortunately, His Royal Highness is blessed with profound blessings
Toxic onset early
If you don't notice
Dosage accumulates over time
But it's boring
Now His Highness has taken medicine
no problem
I take the liberty to ask
His Royal Highness's daily meal is
chrysanthemum pot
And fairy porridge
Your Highness
The slaves will go to the Shang Food Bureau now.
Bring back the poisoner
stop
Your Highness
It must be the little maid from the Shangshi Bureau.
I took her back
Let Jin Yiwei be interrogated strictly
Not afraid that she won't confess
shut up
Sheng imperial doctor
Grandpa Ruo asked about this
You said that the day you fell from the horse and suffered some skin trauma
come to you to get medicine
Rest assured, Your Highness
I understand
Your Highness
That little palace maid hides evil intentions
can't tolerate her
Go and call Chen Wulai
Yes
greedy cat
Is Jin Yiwei still investigating?
The palace has been checked
It was confirmed that there was an impostor who entered the palace.
Emperor Longyan is angry
Strictly investigate
absolutely not tolerate
Is it tasty
fragrant
adult
That house was a beggar
their woman
greased and powdered all day
Not a decent person at first glance
her husband
news from nowhere
Say it's an angel
I want to come to Suzhou Prefecture to collect crickets
moved my mind
go bankrupt to the countryside
Got a cricket at a high price
I want to please Shangguan and get rid of the low status
don't say
Really got him
The cricket in their house is brave and good at fighting
Invincible all over the world
What are you talking about?
who is talking nonsense
continue
Their youngest son is very naughty
Accidentally let the cricket go away
The news got out early in the morning
This county official
can spare them
I'll check it out the next morning
That's a miserable
The woman hangs the man and throws it into the well
Even the little son went with him
The family has one daughter
right
That girl looks like seven or eight years old
I don't know why she
she escaped
when collecting the corpse
Kneeling in front of her father and mother, crying to the death
no one can get up
It was later taken away
go on
who did she go with
Who else can you go with?
Where can this beggar go?
Many were taken away by the fisherman who ran the boat
When I grow up, I'll be a prostitute on a boat
but
That little girl is lucky
Spotted by the Yangzhou family
More than a dozen corpses were collected for her
Then took it straight away
be a skinny horse in the future
It's a way out, isn't it?
All selected eunuch officials
Relatives of all the maids
They all insist that no one is impersonating
how did you confirm
Free at kisskh.me
Lord Jinyiwei visits everywhere
It is said that someone from Suzhou Prefecture entered the palace under false names.
I look carefully at the eyebrows of her portrait
She does look alike
adult
Is there really a reward?
There are two people in Suzhou Palace entering the palace this time
The two pictures you say look like
which one
This seventeen-year-old girl
all look like flowers
you let me meet the real
I'll definitely recognize it
adult
Yao Zijin's inner school exam papers
He also interrogated the palace maid who was in charge of the upbringing
Said she was playing piano, chess, calligraphy and painting
flute and flute strings
Thin horses have been carefully trained since childhood
That's right
adult
There will be omissions in identifying people in portraits
But another witness also brought
take people
Yes
still have a headache
Hurry up
take a break
turn around
I'll give you a rub
feelling better
okay
I'll pour you some water
you say you
Obviously not feeling well
be stronger
The seat of the meal is for you
is it really that important
important
Very important
Ziping
I treat you so well
You are for the seat of the meal
want to kill me
why are you being so nice to me
Blame yourself
you shouldn't be so kind
shouldn't be so stupid
good
no bottom line
Can't raise tigers
you shouldn't
should not
put someone who truly treats you
be a fool
you
I beg you
You do not want
do not want
someone wants to see you
see clearly
is that her
picture
It's been ten years since
looks like
Haven't seen each other for over ten years
can recognize
It seems that the charm of the bounty is really great.
You, look here
adults are here
bring up
Yanniang, you can see clearly
The girl who ran away from your house
is that her
Adults
Eyebrows are three-pointed alike
you look carefully
adult
The girl came to my house when she was eight
I teach her to play the piano and sing
But she's born stupid
eccentric
can't teach anything
I'll spend money to buy someone else
Just teach her to do chores
In the end, he was negligent and escaped.
I searched all over the docks and alleys and couldn't find it
It's not hard to know if
little women dare
please forgive me