[English subtitles are available]
[Nothing But You]
[Episode 5]
[Congratulations to the Initiation of "The Tour of the Youth"]
Please rest assured.
I, Director Wang is here.
Everything is OK.
Stay fine in the future.
You must have opportunities for acting.
Thank you, Director.
That's all right.
You are Director Wang, right?
Who are you?
Who am I?
I am the boss who offered investment for you.
The young boss is here!
I didn't expect
you to be so young and promising.
I am certainly young.
It's rare to see the little boss.
Let's take a photo together.
Come...
Together. Together.
Come. Take a photo together.
Come, still photographer.
Take a photo.
Come. Wish us...
Godspeed and blockbuster.
[Congratulations to the Initiation of "The Tour of the Youth"]
[Congratulations to the Initiation of "The Journey of the Youth" from Hengyuan Hotel]
You guys
are too unreliable.
You even didn't go to the launching ceremony.
I will fire you sooner or later.
Are you kidding?
Only you didn't go to the launching ceremony.
OK?
Nonsense.
I've been there!
I also took a photo.
Are you drunk?
Who saw you?
Fine.
Today I will make you sincerely convinced.
[Congratulations to the Initiation of "The Tour of the Youth"]
Who is this?
Your poor film crew
is really poor.
A formal launching ceremony
even didn't have a backdrop.
You just hung a banner.
Mr. Lai Jr.,
you went to the wrong place.
The name is "The Journey of the Youth",
not
"The Tour of the Youth"
What?
Impossible.
[Congratulations to the Initiation of "The Tour of the Youth"]
I'm not going to the launching dinner tonight.
Have a good time.
Why?
I have to return to the company to deal with my business.
Do whatever you want.
If you come, you will be my eyesore.
Xiao He, you stay here.
Help me look after her.
[Congratulations to the Initiation of "The Journey of the Youth"]
Yes.
Right. Mr. Lai Jr.,
don't go to the wrong place
for tonight's launching dinner.
Don't look down on me.
Mr. Lai Jr.,
if later
you still have meals for free at others' places,
you will actually lose your face.
Hey. You...
Right.
Where is the launching dinner?
Nobody told me the location.
[Appreciation Dinner of "The Journey of the Youth"]
Thank you. Thank you.
Have a drink.
This is delicious.
[Appreciation Dinner of "The Journey of the Youth"]
Since Lai Zhengyi is not here...
Have a drink.
What are you doing?
If you want to marry into a rich family like our Lai family,
unless...
What?
Unless you can drink me under the table.
[Tipsy]
Who will drink with you?
That's too good for you.
The person I will marry is Mr. Lai,
not you.
Why do I need to get your recognition?
You refuse to drink with me
because you are afraid of drinking too much
and making yourself drunk, huh?
Coward.
You and Lai Zhengyi
are a couple of cowards.
You actually said that about him!
Do you know why Mr. Lai didn't come?
Because he doesn't want to see you.
When he sees you, he will feel angry.
You are thoughtless.
It isn't that he doesn't want to see me
or feels upset
or angry.
He is just afraid of me.
He is avoiding me.
So, he is a coward.
You are a coward as well.
You are well-matched at this point.
It's suitable for you to be together.
Double cowards.
Coward. Coward. Coward. Coward.
You are a coward.
Just have a drink.
I'm not afraid of you.
Come on.
Come.
Drink it all, coward.
Great.
Good.
Let me take a break.
Take a break.
Then I'll also take a break, too.
The second half begins.
Drink it all. Drink.
Who fears?
Together. Together.
[Tipsy]
[Working Group of "The Journey of the Youth"]
[Respect for Xiaoran who has a high tolerance]
[Appreciation Dinner of "The Journey of the Youth"]
She even dares drink out of the bottle with poor drinking capacity.
Bi Xiaoran, listen.
-You must hear
-Mr. Lai Jr.
very clearly
what I am going to say next.
All right. All right.
What to do? Mr. Lai came.
Listen to me.
-I advise you to break up with Lai Zhengyi.
-Xiaoran.
Stop.
-Let me tell you.
-Xiaoran.
You don't know who he really is.
He is a double-faced person.
You are still saying that about him!
He acts one way to a man's face
and another behind his back.
I am telling you that
he has strong masculinity.
-Nonsense.
-He...
[Appreciation Dinner of "The Journey of the Youth"]
-If you continue to shout at him...
-Xiaoran.
I will fight with you.
Don't point at me.
What?
Are you OK?
Xiaoran
was drinking with Mr. Lai Jr. all the while.
We just couldn't stop her.
I am
very capable.
Don't be sad anymore.
I have avenged you.
This guy.
Stay here.
Don't point at me, coward.
No.
Am I capable?
Don't be sad.
You little fool.
I'm fine.
I can walk.
Come. Sit down.
Thank you.
Right.
Lai Zhengling said you were a
double-dealing
and two-faced man.
I don't believe him.
Why?
Because I don't believe
what others say.
I have to see it with my own eyes.
You are a good person.
I believe it.
Because you don't know me well.
Why did you say that?
When my sister had an accident,
you arranged the best sanatorium
for her.
When I made mistakes at work,
you didn't blame me.
Instead, you helped me.
Besides, I am actually a little careless.
You take special care of me.
I think you are
the best person in the world.
What's this?
Abdominal muscle!
Do you have abs?
Let me take a look.
Take a look.
Don't move.
What are you doing?
Just let me take a look.
Can't I just take a look?
Just let me have a glance.
You don't let me look at it...
No.
OK.
Lie down.
I think
you are really the best person.
I am not as nice as you think.
If you still don't
lie down,
you will suffer a loss.
What?
You took advantage of me.
I'll never suffer a loss in my life,
and only taste the sweetness.
Taste the sweetness.
Am I kidnapped?
What's the matter?
You woke up.
Yes.
Have some congee to warm your stomach.
When I woke up,
I found my hands were bound.
I thought I was kidnapped.
Who did that?
Did that hurt you?
You did that?
Yes.
Last night,
you were actually a little rude.
Rude?
You are really the best person
in the world.
No.
It isn't my imagination.
Sorry. Sorry.
I'm wrong.
Never mind.
You are sweet.
It's more exciting than my illusion.
I didn't do it deliberately.
Forget it, please.
[Lemeng PIctures]
I didn't expect that just a few glasses of wine
had such a strong delayed effect.
Let me have a look.
You.
The sheet you made...
Come to give me a head massage.
You pretend to be deaf?
Lai Zhengling.
Mr. Lai.
From now on,
you are under the leadership of Xiaoran.
You'll work as her assistant.
Why?
I can't do that.
How much money does he still owe our company?
72658.32 yuan in total.
No. You.
I'm telling you
I can't do that.
How much asset does he own?
Only a car.
Sell it.
OK.
Wait...
Just an assistant.
I am capricious.
Today I'll show you
how to do that today.
Everyone.
This is the script newly revised by Mr. Qin.
I like it very much.
Some contents were removed.
But it becomes fast-paced.
Very excellent.
Take a look.
My parts were all removed.
What will I act?
Qingyan,
it doesn't matter whether you play more or less.
It matters whether your performance is outstanding.
Even a clever woman cannot cook a meal without rice.
Director Wang,
I only have several scenes.
How can I act?
Besides,
The blockbusters in recent years
are all the plays centering on heroines.
Who wants to see rough men?
Otherwise,
can we try to make the play center on the heroine?
Qingyan,
The Journey of the Youth
is different from other IPs.
I think as long as I strive to do it,
even though it doesn't meet the market demands,
it will also receive recognition.
Right?
Those sweet love dramas
are not the only way out.
Last year, the TV series
called Qing Man Nian
also made an all-around success.
But I...
Qingyan, stop.
I am the director.
Listen to me, OK?
Do exactly what I say.
Execute according to the new script, OK?
Contact me any time if you have any problem.
[The Journey of the Youth]
A rubbishy script.
The heroine's scenes are even
fewer than the third male character's.
I can't let it go on like this.
What's wrong?
How can the script be revised casually?
The script is the joint painstaking effort
of the director and the scriptwriter.
It can't be revised casually only because of you.
I don't have many scenes originally.
They have even been removed now.
I become the unimportant supporting character.
Before cutting my parts,
can you ask me for my opinion?
You show no respect to me.
We didn't remove the scenes causally.
We did it for...
Whatever the reason is,
I am unsatisfied with the present script.
It must be revised.
This TV series draws much attention.
Even though you don't respect my opinion,
you have to respect the audience's opinions.
It's not easy to revise the script.
A slight move in one part may affect the situation as a whole.
It will affect the whole project's
shooting schedule.
How difficult can revising a script be?
The sooner the revision is completed, the earlier we can start shooting.
If the matter lasts too long,
nobody will benefit.
No...
Is she intended?
-This...
-My phone.
It broke down.
Be careful.
Help.
It's me.
How can you be so cruel?
How can it be you?
Didn't you go swimming in the Maldives?
You have already lived together with a man.
How can I be in the mood to swim?
You didn't answer my phone
and even blacklisted me.
The crank call was made by you!
You made such a remark.
Jiangjiang?
What?
I am Bi Xiaoran.
No.
You kicked me just now.
-We grew up together.
-Let me go.
I can recognize you even when you become ashes.
Say. Where is your sister?
What's the matter?
Let her go.
Stop.
What are you doing?
Mr. Lai. I know him.
This is...
I am her boyfriend.
Nonsense.
Say it again.
I'm not your boyfriend?
He's my e-ex...
Ex-boyfriend.
When did you have a love affair with others?
Why didn't I know that?
That is over-past.
Let me introduce him to you officially.
This is the original author and scriptwriter
of the Journey of the Youth,
Qin Yanfei.
This is...
I know. Mr. Lai.
Nice to meet you.
Qin,
actually, there is a matter
I've been hiding from you.
Say it frankly.
As long as it isn't that your sister is nurturing the fetus,
I can accept everything.
It isn't a bad thing.
It's a good thing to contribute to the country.
In fact, she is working for the country.
When she disappears,
she is participating in
a space project.
Soon she will land on Mars.
This... This...
Is it
the Mars-crossing project?
You also know this project?
You are quite a great writer.
You are well informed.
That's it.
No. Jiangjiang.
Do you treat me as a three-year-old child?
You photoshopped the picture like that. How can I believe it?
When I was traveling abroad,
I heard your sister
was living together
with Lai Zhengyi.
Tell me!
Where is your sister?
Calm down.
Put your gun down.
My sister...
Do you still treat me as your brother?
You don't believe me.
Say.
Sorry, Qin.
It isn't that I don't want to tell you.
Mr. Lai told me to keep it secret.
I...
My sister...
Bi Xiaoran is going on a business trip to Australia.
Her work is confidential.
So, her tracks can't be known by others.
What kind of work should be kept confidential?
It's our company's confidential information.
I can't tell you.
Right.
The company's confidential information.
You can't know that.
Well.
Don't think too much.
She will come back in a few days.
Where is she in Australia?
I am going to find her now.
No. No.
You don't need to find her.
There is something more important
waiting for you.
What's wrong with your sister?
Someone made trouble in the film crew.
You need to deal with it.
I am just a scriptwriter.
I only need to write a good script.
Deal with the matter of the film crew by yourself.
It has nothing to do with me.
There is one more important thing.
Is there something wrong with your sister?
Not my sister.
It's me.
Sorry, Mr. Lai.
It's all about the company.
I live with Lai Zhengyi in place of my sister.
A man and a woman
stay in a room together.
I doubt...
See the way he looks at me.
He absolutely has an improper thought on me
and wants to misconduct himself with me.
No.
Have you ever
come across such a good thing?
You should feel happy.
I think it's impossible.
He doesn't look like
an unfastidious man.
Don't act like a snob.
You are not choosy.
I am so beautiful
and charming.
It's very dangerous for me.
Are you my brother?
Yes.
So, you can't go anywhere else.
Stay here to protect me.
Lodge?
Right...
The water pipe in his house burst.
He'll lodge here for several days.
I can book a room in the hotel for Mr. Qin.
He isn't used to living in the hotel.
He will suffer from insomnia.
Yes.
How about his friends?
He is of an uncommunicative and eccentric disposition.
He has no friends.
Since he is homeless
and so pitiful,
Mr. Lai,
please allow him to lodge here for several days.
Just a few days.
Since he is your friend,
I certainly welcome him.
You are magnanimous, Mr. Lai.
Let's have lunch.
Have lunch.
This is tomorrow's schedule.
Have a look.
No.
As for the matter of adding your parts,
we can discuss it later.
But you still should complete your work.
After all, you've signed the contract.
I have had a cold and a fever.
I can't work.
[Lemeng Pictures]
Wait for me.
Sit down.
Sit down, please.
Sit well.
Just a minute.
This is the cake for you.
Why did you suddenly
buy a cake for me?
Because I bothered you again.
One more person is living in your house.
I allowed Qin Yanfei to live here
just for the sake of silencing him.
Otherwise, he'll always ask
to find my sister.
Right?
Yes.
I know.
You take the whole situation into consideration.
You understand me.
Open it.
Open it to have a look.
What's wrong?
I know. I know.
I bought it for you.
I should open it for you.
I know you like blueberry.
I specially chose this kind of cake
with the most blueberries.
It's hard to choose.
Is it OK?
Do you like it?
You don't have to thank me.
What's wrong?
Did you quarrel with Lai Zhengyi?
No.
No?
Then why did you send him the blueberry cake?
He likes blueberry
and then I like sending it to him.
Any problem?
Yes.
There is a big problem.
I don't know whether he likes blueberry.
But I know
he suffers from trypophobia.
When he was a kid,
I often frightened him with a seedpod of the lotus.
He was frightened
out of his wits every time.
So, you put the blueberries in that shape.
Wasn't it to disgust him?
I know you like blueberry.
I specially chose this kind of cake
with the most blueberries.
Well...
I think he likes blueberry.
So, I sent him more
and put them in a lovely shape.
Who knows he suffers from trypophobia?
Now you know that.
Wait...
You have been with him for so long.
How can you not know that?
I attend to numerous affairs every day.
I am so busy.
It's normal for me to neglect that.
Xiaoran,
Ren Qingyan disappeared.
What?
What happened?
How's it going? How's it going?
Look.
I have phoned her many times.
No one answered my call.
What's wrong?
Ren Qingyan disappeared.
And she didn't answer the call.
Could she have an accident?
It's impossible.
She and her car both disappeared.
Well.
Find a stunt actress to act first.
Mr. Lai.
It happened suddenly.
It's hard to find a suitable
stunt actress.
Xiaoran,
can you come to help us?
What?
Me?
Director,
the stunt actress is ready.
OK.
Let me have a look.
You are pretty
in the ancient costume.
But I don't look like
Ren Qingyan.
Will the audience find it out?
It doesn't matter.
We won't expose your face.
Please feel at ease.
Go inside...
Where...
Where should I go?
No one told you?
This is a scene
where the hero and the heroine take a bath together.
You'll flirt with him in the water.
What?
Seduce him in the water?
Seduce?
Yes.
All right. All right. Come.
Ziyi, help her.
OK. Director.
In the water?
Every department, get ready.
We'll start soon.
Be ready for real scene shooting.
Three, two, one.
Action.
[They two are in complete harmony and kiss recklessly]
In complete harmony.
Kiss recklessly。
Director Wang,
let's find a professional
stunt actress.
I'll make the arrangement.
Give you one more day.
No.
The scene will be gone tomorrow.
And you can't restrict
Xiaoran's development.
This is acting, acting.
It's false, false.
Cut. Cut.
Well.
Xiaoran,
be more devoted.
One more time.
OK?
OK.
Restart.
Again.
Be ready for real scene shooting.
Three, two, one.
Action.
Cut. Cut. Cut.
Xiaoran,
be more devoted.
OK?
Let's try one more time.
You did well just now. Not bad.
One more time.
Cut. Cut. Cut.
It isn't OK.
Xiaoran,
this is a scene of seducing the hero.
You must be more devoted.
Be more charming and enchanting.
All right?
Enchanting...
Director,
let's remove this part.
Ah?
No.
It's very important for the whole TV series.
If you can't do that,
don't force yourself.
I can't give up halfway.
Let me try one more time.
One more.
OK. It's the last time.
If you can't do that,
I'll find another person.
OK.
Come on, Xiaoran.
OK. OK.
Get ready, every department.
Come. Be ready for real scene shooting.
Three, two, one.
Action
Cut.
OK. Perfect.
Perfect.
Xiaoran, well done!
Great.
Thank you.
What's this?
Didn't I get clean?
So many.
What's this?
Lili!
Look!
My skin broke out in a rush.
What's this?
It's definitely because the water in the barrel
is too dirty. You are allergic.
Ah?
It is very itchy.
Will I die?
Don't worry. It's OK.
Let me fetch some medicine.
OK.
What's this?
[UNA Life]
[Balm]
Apply some medicine.
Your fingers are so cold.
Don't move.
Sorry.
Why did you apologize?
The cake I sent to you
brought you the psychological shadow, right?
You don't know it, so it's okay.
I don't blame you.
You are so nice to me,
but I don't know you at all.
So, in the future, you
can only fix your eyes on me.
I have warned you
not to seduce me.
I...
I didn't.
I am
You are still disputing.
Tonight,
I will let you know who I am.
In this life,
you can't escape.
No.
We can't do that.
What?
Nothing. Nothing.
Sorry.
I'm not intended.
Give it to me.
I'll do it by myself.
Just go take a rest.
Go!
Bye.
I did that again.
It's too embarrassing.
Jiang Lili,
you are an idiot
contaminated by novels on overbearing presidents.
What am I thinking about every day?
It's too embarrassing.
My God.
I am really...
[Qin Yanfei]
Hello?
Bro, get started.
OK.