[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode One]
[The sixth year of Yongjia]
Your Grace,
Be careful, Your Grace.
It's too dangerous.
Come down.
Besides marriage,
there's no other way?
Your Majesty,
if we don't avoid war by marriage,
the Northern Zhou army will soon
invade our territory,
or even
our capital Lin'an.
Your Majesty,
please do think twice.
So beautiful.
[Win-ever Gambling House]
Why my lady still hasn't come?
My Lady.
I'm here, my lady.
[Li Laoqi's Lantern House]
[Silk Cloth Store]
Be careful.
[Win-ever Gambling House]
Miss, are you hurt?
My Lady, get up.
Get up.
My Lady.
Are you okay?
My fruits!
Let's go.
Your Majesty.
Don't bother me.
It’s about Princess Zhaohe.
Tell me.
Princess Zhaohe
made a flying bird,
and flew out of the palace through the gate directly.
A bunch of idiots!
Please forgive me.
Your Majesty, please calm down.
I'll send someone to get princess back.
Wait.
[Memorial to the throne]
This time,
just let her go.
[Pay us the back pay!]
Come out! Give me back the money! Come out!
Come out! Come out!
[Unscrupulous businessmen! Pay us the back pay!]
Come out.
Qingfeng,
[Thorough survey of curves and lines]
for you and me now,
it's still not the end of the world yet.
Brave young men,
take the first step bravly.
We must deal with it
no matter we step forward or step back.
Return the money!
Everyone. Everyone.
We are all educated people with good manners...
Everyone!
Please listen to me.
Listen to me.
I know I owe you money.
Don't worry.
For the money I owe you,
I will pay you back with interests.
To be honest,
[Pay back the money]
we have got great support
from the richest family in Lin'an, the Zhao family.
Zhao family? Zhao?
Really?
Everyone, don't worry.
Please give me three weeks.
No way!
Three days. Just three days.
After three days,
if I still owe you money, even if it's just one coin,
you can tear down my house and sell it.
What do you think?
Zhao family is willing to pay the money for you?
No matter it's true or not,
I'll give you three days.
A gentleman must keep his promise.
Everyone,
let's see.
Let's go. Please leave.
Please leave!
Just three days.
Okay, three days.
[Wood Feather House]
Three days. Three days. Three days.
Luo Ye, you're talking nonsense again.
Oh my goodness!
And we
have no contact with the Zhao family at all.
You shouldn't have
deceived them.
If I hadn't said that,
we couldn't have even left the house here,
letting alone borrowing any money!
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Go and find money.
Come on, let's play bet sizing [a way of gambling].
This is it.
[Fortune]
Miss, if you want to gamble,
I can do it with you at home.
Why bother coming here?
On my way back from the Ancestral Temple,
I was attracted by the design of this casino
and found it very special.
And then, the more I think about it, the more interesting it is.
Now seeing what's inside,
I come to realize that
this architect's really a genius.
So you came here
just to take a look at the design of the casino.
I think they're all built of bricks, tiles and wood.
It's not that simple.
Look.
At all four sides of the casino
lies doors with different hollow-carved design,
which not only helps with
the internal air circulation,
but also divides the crowded hall
into four well-organized areas.
And there are different flowers on each door.
Look at that plum blossom.
If I'm right,
every flower
is formed by 18 different petals.
What a strict and exquisite structure it is!
All parts of it blend into one integral whole.
For this kind of method,
I only read it in one manual before.
I've finally seen it for myself today.
This is not just a technology.
It's art!
I don't really get it.
But it does look pretty.
If you don't know what you're talking about, please don't lecture on it.
What?
Then tell me.
Do you understand
what I said just now?
The design here is too luxurious and rough.
It's full of petty techniques and is of such a bad taste.
It has nothing to do with art.
How can you speak so highly of it!
I really can't understand.
My Lady, don't be angry.
Okay. Tell me!
Who are you?
Do you know architecture?
Do you know house structure?
Do you know overall design and separate design?
Do you know the subtleties
of the arrangement?
False comments always come from those with poor talent and little knowledge.
That's really ridiculous.
Being short-sighted,
they see such a terrible design
as a treasure.
Besides,
even if I don't know architecture,
as a passerby,
I have the freedom to comment on it.
In my eyes, the design of the Golden House
is worthless.
What? Say it again.
It should be demolished!
I think you should be demolished.
My lady, he's mental. Ignore him.
Come back!
[Three Safe Bets]
My Lady.
Build a Golden House if you can!
You can't even build a toilet!
Calm down. Calm down.
He's not worth it.
He's running so fast.
Come and have a look.
[The Golden House]
Why are you out?
It's too noisy inside.
How are you?
Your last life-saving strategy
is the final payment of the Golden House?
No.
I'm just dropping by.
I don't care about this little amount of money.
Let's go.
I'll take you to find a large amount of money.
The small one, small! Listen to me! Small!
Hurry up.
Small!
This is it!
Big or small? Ready?
Big!
Wait.
Do you know how to do it?
No.
But I read a story
about a gambler who won from 20 taels
- to 3,700 taels. - Miss,
do you want to play or not?
The game is bet sizing.
Open it.
There are skills in the story too.
I learned some because it was fun.
- Let's have a look.  - Miss.
You... I...
Calm down.
Here's the money.
Okay, this is it.
One, two, three. Small.
My lady, you're awesome! My lady.
I’m a genius!
Sorry, sorry.
Thank you.
Bet sizing. Make your bet.
My lady, is it big or small?
Come on. This is it!
Small.
Me too. Small. Me too.
Small!
All right, there you go.
Don't move.
Ready? Open!
Small! Small! Small!
Two, two, three. Small.
This time we rely on our strength.
Again! Again! Again!
Clear! Clear! The game's over!
Come on. Leave here!
Clear! Clear!
Luo, take the money.
Okay!
It's too much.
Miss, are you here to make us go bankrupt?
You misunderstood me.
We can return all the money.
But I have a question.
Who built
this casino?
Miss Zhao is not an amateur,
but a successful investor.
Now our Wood Feather team of craftsmen is in a hard time.
There seems to be no hope.
I'm afraid no matter what tricks you use,
she won't invest easily.
So,
that's why I asked you to come with me.
Let's work together!
I believe we'll be a perfect pair.
And we'll definitely make it!
Can you put your hands down?
What's going on?
Return the money!
Wood Feather House
[Wood Feather House]
My lady, Li Qingfeng lives here?
Hello?
Stop shouting.
No one is inside.
May I ask who you are?
I'm the creditor of the Wood Feather House.
I suppose you're also creditors, right?
Creditor?
Li Qingfeng and Luo Ye have gone to the Zhao's Mansion
to borrow money.
Do they owe a lot of money?
[Pay back the money]
There are 30 creditors.
Do the math yourself.
[Wood Feather House]
How could the Zhao family
help them clean up such a big mess!
Anyway, I'll stay here today.
If they get the money, they should give me first.
Otherwise,
I'll tear down the house.
Wait, wait.
Calm down.
I'll pay you back the money they owe you.
Who are you?
I'm Li Qingfeng's disciple.
Old man,
you're still doing business
at this age?
Business?
I'm here to look for my daughter-in-law.
Your daughter-in-law?
Who is she?
Miss Zhao.
Today is the day on which she throws the embroidered ball each month.
You don't even know that?
Then why are you here?
I remember it.
The Zhao family has been worried about
Miss Zhao's marriage.
So they decided to let her choose a husband in this way.
From the beginning of last year till now,
she has thrown the ball for at least ten times.
Yeah, that's right.
But rumor has it that Miss Zhao has a high standard.
Everyone who receives the embroidered ball
has to be further tested
before someone can become the son-in-law of the Zhao family.
The Zhao family is a noble family.
I didn't expect they can also be so ridiculous.
Let's come another day. Let's go.
Let's keep waiting, please!
They can line up
and compete for the embroidered ball.
We can still talk business.
We only have three days.
Everyday matters!
Anyway,
we have to see Miss Zhao today.
Let's wait a little longer, shall we?
[Zhao's Mansion]
Wait. Wait.
Wait.
Excuse me. Is this...
the Zhao's Mansion? The richest family of Lin'an?
What are you doing here?
I’m here for a man named Li Qingfeng.
He's here for investment with Miss Zhao.
We...are together in this.
Li Qingfeng?
Are you Li Qingfeng's wife?
No...no way!
I'm not his wife.
That's good.
Otherwise, we'll be in troulbe!
You haven't told me
whether he's here or not.
He just went inside.
The Li Qingfeng you mentioned
is not here to ask for financial support,
but for
getting the embroidered ball from Miss Zhao.
The embroidered ball?
All right. Please leave.
[Zhao's Mansion]
Selection of a son-in-law?
My lady, the Wood Feather House in on the brink of bankruptcy
and is debt-ladden.
How could Mr. Li still be in the mood for girls?
I see.
Senior Li Qingfeng
must want to save the Wood Feather House,
so he came here to try his luck.
If he can get the embroidered ball from Miss Zhao,
then the Wood Feather House will be saved.
So,
the Wood Feather House hasn't received the Zhao family's support yet?
It's so sad.
Li Qingfeng is an old man,
but he still comes to fight for the embroidered ball for money.
Even if he gets the ball,
[Zhao's Mansion]
he'll have to move to the Zhao family.
I can't let such a talented man be bothered by money.
Luo, I must help him.
What do you want to do?
Let me see.
My lady, have you figured it out?
No.
Why can't we wait for him outside?
It'll be too late
if Senior Li Qingfeng gets the embroidered ball.
So,
I must meet him first.
My lady, you can't climb over the wall.
I'm not asking you to do it!
I...
If anything happens,
you have to come out quickly.
Don't worry.
Wait for me here.
Miss Zhao's here.
[Miss Zhao's here.]
[Gorgeous Vernal Scenery]
I wonder if I can get it.
[Gorgeous vernal scenery]
[Gorgeous Vernal Scenery]
I heard that Miss Zhao
is a bit unruly and willful,
but she's pretty.
If you don't go,
then I'm going to have a try.
Good luck to you!
Miss Zhao, here!
Here! Here!
This way, Miss Zhao!
Mr. Zhou.
Do you know the man over there?
Miss, that's Li Qingfeng,
19 years old,
from Lin'an.
I didn't know him before.
There she is!
She's going to throw the ball.
She's having the ball!
[Gorgeous Vernal Scenery]
Miss Zhao, here!
Throw it here.
This way!
Don't push me.
[Gorgeous Vernal Scenery]
Give it to me.
It's mine!
Mine!
This is mine!
Don't push. Don't fight with me.
My embroidered ball!
Embroidered ball!
Why is it in his hands?
Why did you keep throwing it?
You kept pushing me!
Bro, congratulations!
[Gorgeous Vernal Scenery]
What are you waiting for?
I can finally see Miss Zhao.
Where did Steward Zhou take him?
Why hasn't he come yet?
I'm not anxious,
Why are you so anxious, father?
Sweetie,
how can I not be anxious?
You are already 19 years old.
If you're still not married
when you turn 20,
there will surely be gossips.
I just don't want you
to suffer that.
My marriage is all up to you and my brothers.
My husband can be selected by the embroidered ball, or be your acquaintance.
I'm fine with both.
But I must find a man I like.
My Lord.
Go ahead.
He's outside the door.
Hurry up. Ask him to come in.
Yes. Hurry up.
Ning, be quiet.
Mr. Li, please come in.
This gentleman is really handsome.
Yes.
Not bad.
That's right. Yes.
I am Li Qingfeng.
It's my honor to see Lord Zhao and all the gentlemen here.
Hurry up!
Come on.
What's going on?
Please have some tea.
Nothing will happen.
Are you going to capture my brother?
I have no idea.
Bro, you lost your money, right?
Mr. Luo. What do you mean?
Just tell me everything you know,
then the money is yours.
You should keep the money for yourself.
[Yichun Brothel Level A Permit]
Bro, do you know this coupon?
Level A Permit for Yichun Brothel.
Only with this coupon
can you be able to
have fun with the best girls.
This is priceless.
This is
a test of your brother
from my Lord.
See?
Do you know what this is?
Yes.
I'll tell you the truth.
It's my daughter's idea to select her husband by throwing the embroidered ball.
I never agree with it.
So I ask you to give up my daughter.
And the gold in front of you
will all be yours.
But for this kind of test,
as long as you're not a fool, you can figure it out.
It's definitely not so simple.
This is just the first step.
I finally get what I want today.
I will never give up.
No matter how hard it is,
I'd like to sacrifice everything for my beloved,
even my life.
After hearing your words,
I'm really touched.
Please get up.
Mr. Li, please.
Don't be rude.
The Inspection Ministry comes to arrest Zhao Xian.
All the relatives of the Zhao family
will be imprisoned.
No.
I'm not from the Zhao family.
I'm not.
How could you say that?
I have nothing to do with the Zhao family.
Please investigate the case.
Your Excellency, please investigate it.
A serial strategy!
One trap after another.
It's really unexpected.
But isn't your Lord afraid that
those who have experienced the test may reveal it?
To reveal their stupidity, hypocrisy and fear of death?
Not only will they be ashamed of revealing it,
others will feel embarrassed about hearing it too.
Besides,
they all want to see others suffer this too!
That's human nature!
Lord Zhao
really knows humanity.
It's really not easy to be his son-in-law.
So you can have tea here.
Maybe Mr. Li will come out soon.
Miss, are you alright?
Who are you?
I...
Today is the day for Miss Zhao to select her husband, right?
I came with my brother.
Then I got lost.
I heard someone crying when I passed by,
so I came in.
I see.
Please point the way for me.
Where did Miss Zhao throw the embroidered ball?
I’m going to look for my brother.
The noise outside has subsided,
so I think it's over now.
Your brother has probably left the mansion.
It's over?
Has Miss. Zhao selected a man as her husband?
Miss,
don't cry.
You can tell me what's wrong here.
Sis, you don't know.
Every time a man gets the embroidered ball,
he has to be tested by Lord Zhao.
And the last test
will be carried out in this room.
This room?
You are Miss Zhao?
I'm not Miss Zhao,
But I have to pretend to be her.
I see.
The last test
is the seduction of the beauty.
You pretend to be Miss Zhao waiting here.
If the person who got the embroidered ball is seduced,
then he fails the test.
If he is a gentleman,
then he can see the real Miss Zhao.
Yes.
But the girls who did this before told me that
every man who entered this room
was a hypocrite.
No gentlemen at all?
Maybe he won't go too far in this room.
Lord Zhao asked us...
asked us to...
to lure the man on purpose.
That's wicked!
It's not like that.
I'm indebted to Lord Zhao and Miss.
They treat me very well normally.
It’s just that it sounds very horrible as described by the girls.
That's why I...
I...
Alright. Forget it.
A maiden like you
definitely treats chastity as life.
If he's a philanderer, you must feel miserable
even if you're only touched by him.
Let me help you.
How about this?
I'll do this test for you, okay?
I can't put you in danger!
No, we can't do that.
Don't worry.
If it's Senior Li Qingfeng here,
then everything's gonna be much easier.
But if it's a philanderer...
Don't think I can't see through you.
I know what you want.
Let me tell you the truth.
It's Ning's idea to select her husband in this way.
I've never been willing to accept it.
So today,
you have to give up
marrying my daughter here,
then this box of gold will be yours.
If you still have any other ulterior plots,
I think I've made it very clear.
It's up to you.
I'd like to give up.
You don't hesitate at all!
You just give up like this?
I won't take this box of gold either.
I just want to meet Miss Zhao.
You...
Mr. Li, do you not understand what I mean?
Or you just pretend you don't understand?
Mr. Li, if you're willing to give up,
why do you insist on meeting Ning?
I come here today
for business cooperation with Miss Zhao.
Unexpectedly, I got the embroidered ball.
Being in a panic, I came to explain myself.
Now I shall return the ball.
If I've offended you,
please forgive me.
You...
What?
Stop, stop!
The Inspection Ministry comes to arrest Zhao Xian.
Anyone who resists shall be killed!
No! No!
Your knife, your knife, your knife...
Put down the knife.
Your Excellency,
you made a mistake.
Didn't you just say...
It's my fault.
I made a wrong judgment.
So, Your Excellency,
sorry for bothering you today.
I shall treat you tomorrow
at the Drunken Immortal Restaurant
to express my gratitude.
He's coming out.
He comes out so soon.
Well... Mr. Li really passed the test?
I knew it.
This kind of test
is just a piece of cake for my brother.
Even if he passes these two tests,
there is another ultimate test waiting for him.
The outcome is still up in the air.
It's you?
Why don't you help me?
Why are you staring at me?
Mr. Li.
You... what the hell is with you?
My Lady, are you all right?
It’s okay.
You...
Mr. Zhou, I'm here
just to see Miss Zhao.
It's really unnecessary for you
to keep testing me.
Okay.
Then come with me to see Lord Zhao.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Don't worry. They didn't recognize me.
Why hasn't he come out?
My lady, why do you come out from here?
I certainly should come out through the front door.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Wood Feather House.
By the way, did you see Senior Li Qingfeng?
Let's talk on the way.
Let me tell you.
I just rescued a girl.
My Lord.
Stop it.
You may leave.
Yes.
Mr. Li.
You mean you came to talk business with my daughter?
But why did you enter my mansion in this way?
You even happened to get the embroidered ball!
It's a long story.
I did get the embroidered ball by accident.
But you have got the ball.
In that case,
you're still not interested?
Not at all.
Okay.
What business do you want to talk with Ning?
My friend and I co-established a team of craftsmen.
Because of the poor management,
we are short of money now.
So we'd like Miss Zhao's to invest in our team.
You need money?
Yes.
I just asked you to take this box of gold and leave.
Why did you refuse it?
These are two different things.
Don't beat around the bush.
Lord Zhao, the gold
belongs to you.
But I just told you that
if you gave up the embroidered ball,
this box of gold would be yours.
You also told me
you didn't want to marry my daughter.
You could have left with this box of gold.
But why do you insist on seeing my daughter?
Could it be that the gold
is not enough for you?
I also made it very clear.
I don't want to marry your daughter.
My friend and I just want to see Miss Zhao
to discuss the investment.
Please let me see Miss Zhao.
Leave!
If you don’t, my brother won't spare you.
Get out of here!
Leave!
Wait.
Ning, why are you out?
Mr. Li wants to see me.
And I also want to take a look at Mr. Li.
Greetings, Miss Zhao.
Please forgive me if I offend you.
Mr. Li, am I pretty?
Yes.
Ning.
Father.
I want to ask Mr. Li a few more questions.
You are a carpenter?
To be more precise,
I'm an architect.
You own a team of craftsmen?
My friends and I co-founded it.
I'm in charge of constructing,
and get 40 percent of the profits.
Since you have met me,
I want to know if I give you another chance,
will you still return the embroidered ball?
Yes.
You don't even think about it?
You dislike me that much?
Miss Zhao, don't get me wrong.
We don't even know each other.
How could I dislike you?
I just think
marriage should be based on love.
Only with love can two become each other's lover,
and make a good marriage out of their own will.
That's my humble opinion, and I'll practice what I believe.
That's also why I return the embroidered ball.
Please forgive me.
Even when 300 taels of gold is put in front of you,
you're still going to refuse?
Li Qingfeng.
You are the one!
You're the one I want to marry.
You...
Nonsense!
Miss Zhao,
I think I've made it clear just now.
I know.
But I don't care.
I want to marry you.
I won't marry you.
Am I not good enough for you?
It has nothing to do with it.
If you don't marry me, then you won't get my investment.
I shall leave now.
Li Qingfeng.
Stop!
[Happy Ever After]
How is it going?
It doesn't work. Let's go.
Li Qingfeng.
You're so attractive
and beautiful!
You must be Miss Zhao.
I’m Luo...
None of your business.
Miss Zhao, what else do you want?
Miss Zhao...
I like you.
It's our first meeting. How could you?
I don't care.
Anyway, I have a crush on you.
I just hope you can give me time.
I will show you what kind of a person I am
and give you a chance to fall in love with me.
What do you think?
Since we are friends now,
Miss Zhao, could you please offer us some investment?
Of course!
Senior Li Qingfeng.
Oh my god.
Come on.
Hello?
He hasn't come back yet.
Let's wait a little longer.
Your Grace!
I told you to call me lady.
My Lady.
No matter how well the house is built,
it's built by an architect.
You are a noble lady.
It's already degrading for you to come all the way looking for him.
Now you still have to wait for him here!
It's just inappropriate.
Let me tell you.
This time I come out of the palace
for joining a team of craftsmen.
So,
it's appropriate for me to wait here.
Do you really come out of the palace
for this?
Luo, you know it.
I love architecture.
My biggest dream
is to design constructions myself.
To start with the drawing,
and then to build houses step by step.
Then people can live in houses that I build.
If I don't leave the palace,
all these can only be empty talk.
Besides,
I don't know why His Majesty
always tell me to have music, chess, calligraphy and painting classes.
Auntie Zhao, Auntie Li...
Oh my god.
I was so busy but miserable every day.
Do you want
to see me cry every day?
No.
I know you're the kindest one.
Now that...
we're free,
let's go for a walk?
Yes!
Let's go!
Look.
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
Wood Feather Pavillion.
Luo, Luo.
Luo.
It's just a workshop.
You're going to join them anyway.
It doesn't hurt to see it in advance.
[Wanning Banking House]
Look at the bustling capital.
I'm still ambitious!
I...
Let's pay the craftsmen's money back later
and make some plans.
During this period,
I've really suffered a lot!
You can do it yourself.
I shall go back alone later.
First, everyone hates me,
so as long as you return the money, they won't care whether I'm there or not.
Second,
I just remembered that
I didn't lock the door when I left.
We have nothing to lose in the Wood Feather House anyway.
Wood Feather Pavilion was not locked either.
You have to go back now.
Your treasures are all there.
Go, go, go.
Be careful.
Be gentle with it!
Qingfeng?
Incredible!
Senior Qingfeng made a wooden kite!
Wooden kite?
This wooden bird?
Can it really fly?
According to this drawing,
it can fly!
My Lady.
Shall we give it a go?
But Senior Qingfeng is not here.
But I've never seen a wooden bird fly.
Try it.
We'll only fly it in this room.
There won't be any problem.
Hurry up.