[English subtitles are available]
[Jun Ji-hyun]
[Ju Ji-hoon]
[Sung Dong-il]
[Oh Jung-se]
[Cho Han-chul]
[Joo Min-kyung]
[Go Min-si]
[Jirisan]
[The show is an adapted fiction based on
stories of National Park Rangers.]
[All characters, events, regions,]
[organizations depicted in the show
are fictitious.]
You asked why I came back.
Someone's been killing people
on the mountains, disguised as accidents.
[It could've been a coincidence.]
[The yogurt could have gone bad.]
[It has to do with the mountain.]
[Why is the murderer killing
people on this mountain?]
We must find the person.
How can we? We don't know who it was.
[The murderer was wearing our uniform.]
It has to be one of the park rangers.
[Anyone can take the gloves
if they want to.]
If one is a national park ranger,
taking some gloves would be easy.
Jeong Gu-yeong?
[Gu-yeong was on the mountain
when Da-won got lost.]
Did you see Da-won?
He could've easily got
the commander's gloves.
So? Take Gu-yeong in?
We must take him ourselves.
Why did you go to the mountain that day?
The day Da-won went missing.
I had things to do.
[All the victims had something to do
with the mountain.]
Why are they together?
[Hikers, an old man
with a fractured leg and his wife.]
[Volunteer ranger squad Choi Il-man]
[All the victims]
[are related]
[to the 1995 flood.]
Hyun-jo knew about this.
[Hyun-jo knew who the murderer was.]
Did Hyun-jo tell you anything
before the accident on the snowy mountain?
After that incident last summer,
I haven't been able to see him.
Last summer...
A lot of bad things happened.
[Year 2019]
[Episode 12]
[Gwigam Rock.]
[Are you here because of that?]
Or is there another reason?
That's strange.
Doesn't the air feel a little heavy?
Help yourself.
Did you eat anything?
Have some of these.
It's good, right?
[Baemsagol Camping Site]
Watch your steps.
-Okay.
Haedong Ranger Station, control room.
Il-hae, what's your current location?
[Passing the 3.5km point
from Mujin Valley.]
Something's not right.
Check the situation at Yangseokbong Peak.
Wait here.
Commander, clouds on the ridge.
[Daily Precipitation]
Get out of the valley!
Quick! Get out of there!
Move!
[Daily Precipitation]
[Weather Forecast]
[Yangseokbong Peak]
[Daily Precipitation]
Get out of there!
Quick! Leave the valley!
Let's get moving!
Leave the valley!
The water's rising.
[Village Hall]
Call 911 and the township office,
and have all rangers stand by!
There's no time! We must leave!
Over there!
Quick!
Leave right now!
Get the children out!
You must leave now!
We don't have time.
We don't have much time.
Hurry!
Not much time left!
Let's move!
[There has been localized heavy rain
on Mount Jirisan.]
[Residents near the valley and stream,]
[please take caution.]
I repeat.
[There has been localized heavy rain
on Mount Jirisan.]
[Residents near the valley and stream,]
[please take caution.]
[All rangers,
please return to the office.]
[Warning: Falling Rocks]
It's dangerous.
Wait up!
It's dangerous here!
Go back!
-How's the situation?
-Illegal hikers are isolated.
Part of the road's damaged,
so things must be bad there.
There's a temporary office
set up near Mujin Valley.
Commander is already there.
Let's start.
Five people are isolated at Beombawi Rock,
three in Stone Chamber,
and a family of five
in Apricot Tree Valley.
Among them are seniors and children.
This road got drifted away
by the avalanche,
and a bus with 12 passengers and a driver
got isolated.
And the residents in the lower areas?
We made an announcement, but we'll do
a round of patrol and evacuate them.
[Commander, Il-hae speaking
from Bidam Shelter.]
Hey, Il-hae.
Where's the ecology research team?
Did they get to the shelter?
There was an avalanche on the way.
Mr. Yang and Chief Kim fell behind.
[It's almost impossible to rescue
from up here on the mountain]
[because the road got destroyed.]
The location?
Mujin Valley, Fox Hill.
Finished checking the equipment.
Let's begin.
-Go!
-Yes, sir.
I'll go to the damaged road.
[Emergency Rescue Operation]
[Bidam Cliff]
[911 rescuers, main station rangers.
Take the damaged road in Jingye-ri.]
We can't cross!
Oh, my gosh!
Help!
[Volunteer fire department,
take Stone Chamber.]
[Apricot Tree Valley]
[Mujin, Haedong teams, take Beombawi Rock
and Apricot Tree Valley.]
[Beombawi Rock]
[Fox Hill]
[Yi-gang and Hyun-jo,
take Fox Hill in Mujin Valley.]
Are you okay?
We're from national park!
We'll begin the rescue.
Please step back!
We're firing the rope thrower!
Step back!
All right.
Back!
One, two, three!
-All set.
-One, two, three.
Depart!
Pull the rope!
One, two, three.
[According to the weather forecast,
the atmosphere's still unstable.]
[More localized rain can occur.]
[We must rescue everyone before then.]
-It's just like last year.
-What is?
The two of us in the rainy mountain.
But something's different.
The black gloves you saw.
You said it was raining, right?
Yes.
Be careful.
The murderer's out to get you.
[Volunteer Rangers, Choi Il-man,
Lee Jong-gu, Kim Jin-deok, Hyun-su]
Why? What's wrong?
All of the victims...
They were
all related
to the 1995 Dowon Valley Flooding.
[Yoon Su-mi, female, 39, Dowon Valley]
[Seo Yung-jin, male, 39, Dowon Valley]
[Seo Yung-jin, Yoon Su-mi]
Hyeon-su's father passed away then, too.
I did leave a message.
I think the murderer has
something to do with the incident.
Did something happen back then?
A reason for anyone to do this.
Your son and daughter-in-law
had life insurance.
But in cases of deaths from disasters,
there are some steps to take.
You might not get the benefit
if it was suicide.
Flooding is a natural disaster.
It has nothing to do with crimes.
No one knew it would be pouring
on that day.
They just happened to be there
and made an unfortunate choice.
It's all coincidence.
And today's the same.
[Anyone can get into an accident
and die on the mountain.]
[No one knows what will happen.]
I found it.
I found it!
Who are you?
Are you all right?
See?
If we had cable cars,
this accident wouldn't have happened.
How can you say that in this situation?
If cable car construction started
and all trees were cut down,
we would have died.
We only survived
because the trees blocked the landslide.
Trees can be planted again.
Seriously.
You think trees are Lego blocks?
It can't be reversed
if you plant some trees.
Same as a village.
That town down there
is where I was born and raised.
But more and more people are leaving.
When everyone leaves one by one,
the whole village will vanish.
If you care so much about your hometown,
how could you do such a thing?
It's him! The cable car man.
You'll regret this.
[Black Bridge Village
is gone because of you.]
I'm not leaving!
You've taken the hometown
away from the villagers.
I said I'm not the one
who put the dead animal in the well.
I swear.
Yi-gang.
I don't think this is the way to Fox Hill.
The victim wouldn't be
where an avalanche already happened.
They would have gone somewhere else
even if they got injured.
To where?
Where there's
an emergency telegraphic repeater.
The repeater temporarily
amplifies the terminal signal,
connecting it to the base station.
In other words,
you'll be able to use a cell phone.
That phone won't work.
[Emergency Telegraphic Repeater]
Sir!
-Are you all right?
-Yi-gang.
What happened?
He's been bleeding for a while.
We need a support team.
He's too cold!
I think it's a hemorrhagic shock.
Haedong One.
Current location Clown Rock.
We have a critical victim here.
Can we get a support team?
[Site of road damage.]
[We're approaching via
an alternative route.]
[Apricot Tree Valley,
proceeding with the rescue.]
[Wind is slowing down the process.]
Is the rescue at Beombawi Rock done?
Yes, sir.
-Over here.
-Yes, right here!
-911, please!
-Coming!
-Well done.
-Be careful.
[Gu-yeong. Another SOS reported
at Clown Rock, Mujin Valley.]
Can you make it?
Yes. I'll leave now.
Gu-ho and Jin-hyung. Come with me.
-What a day.
-Let's go.
[Yi-gang.]
[The support team is on its way.]
Hyun-jo, you put him on your back.
I'll assist Hyun-jo down
and join the support team.
You stay with him.
-Got it.
-I'll come, too.
No.
We must get down as quick as possible
since he's in a bad state.
Radio me if anything happens.
Be careful.
There will be another support team.
Please wait here.
I can go down, too.
I must go down with them.
I'll come, too! I can make it!
Hold on.
Not with those legs.
There's a cave not far away.
Let's wait there.
But...
Help!
Over here!
-Wait. Did you hear that?
-Help!
Help me!
Over here! Help!
On the cliff!
Over here! Save me!
Are you okay?
Yes!
Jeong Gu-yeong speaking.
We found a stranded hiker
1.5km from Mujin Valley,
on the southwest cliff.
We don't have the gears to rescue her.
[Any support team available?]
Apricot Tree Valley
is still in the process of rescuing.
Ranger Team A joined
Jingye-ri at the damaged road.
Since the only way to get there
is a detour,
it'll take more than five hours
for the rescue.
Will you be okay by yourself?
You're going by yourself?
Dong-hyup, get ready to go up with me.
Yes, sir.
I'll go.
You must keep watch here.
I know you don't trust me.
But I've been training
with Gu-yeong for months.
I can do this. Please let me go up.
[Support team just left.
I'll take about two hours.]
Okay.
-Can you hear me?
-Yes!
Rangers with gear will come to rescue you!
It'll take a couple of hours.
Please wait patiently!
Okay!
All right!
Let's go.
Are you hurt anywhere else?
You should watch out
for hypothermia on a rainy mountain.
Let me know if you need anything else.
What is that sound?
Sounds like an avalanche.
An avalanche?
Mount Jirisan
mostly consists of land soil.
Heavy rain can easily lead to an avalanche
because the soil holds water.
Then this place can collapse, too.
Let's go down. Quick.
Don't worry. This bedrock area is safe.
Don't lie.
That's what they said then, too,
but the whole building was swept away.
What are you saying?
The building was swept away after we left.
You mean
Dowon Valley in 1995?
Yes.
[Those who've left all survived,]
but the rest all died.
I can't die here. I must leave.
-It's dangerous.
-Move!
Watch out!
The trees are slanted.
They can fall. It's dangerous.
-Let's go back.
-Move!
When there's a flood,
you must stay and wait for rescue!
That's the protocol.
Didn't you hear what I said?
They didn't die because they stayed.
They just made a choice.
And it happened to be an unfortunate one.
No! They gave up!
Because they were scared.
-They gave up!
-No!
They got scared, that's why!
How many times did I tell you
not to stand surety for anyone?
He didn't mean to...
Whatever.
So what are you going to do now?
You even got the house confiscated.
So what's the plan?
Gosh, this is frustrating.
Your son and daughter-in-law
had life insurance.
Here's the list of the payable
and the non-payable.
Here.
Please check their identification
and the insurance period.
But in cases of deaths from disasters,
there are some steps to take.
You might not get the benefit
if it was suicide.
What?
When the police are done
with investigations...
No!
My parents...
They didn't do that.
My mom and dad
would never do that to me.
Switch!
I'll take him!
Hurry up!
There's one more, near Clown Rock.
I'll go check.
Yi-gang.
Yi-gang. Can you hear me?
Kang Hyun-jo! You all right?
I can't reach Yi-gang.
It must be because of the rain clouds.
We'll go up. You head down first.
Kang Hyun-jo!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
You were right. The mud collapsed.
Had I gone down, I would have died.
I came here to die.
My business failed,
and my family's long scattered.
I had no reason to live,
so I came to the mountain to die.
I visited that place for the last time.
Then I realized I wanted to live.
The pagoda ground in Baektogol...
That was when I first came
to Mount Jirisan
in 1995.
Wow, I didn't know this place existed.
-Right?
-It's beautiful here.
Hey.
Let's ask them to take a picture of us.
One, two, three.
You're all so handsome,
so I'm sure it turned out well.
-Thank you.
Did you eat yet?
We brought rice balls. You want some?
Sure, thank you.
Of course.
-Go ahead.
-Thank you.
-Are you friends?
-Yes.
You're not dating?
-Oh, no way.
-Come on.
That's a real no.
-You came for hiking?
-Yes.
It's amazing here, right?
Does that really grant your wish?
How long do you think
this place has existed for?
I don't know. How long?
I don't know either.
Apparently, people have been piling
stone pagoda here since a long time ago.
Sometimes the flood
sweeps everything away,
but they get piled up again like magic.
If it's been a popular wishing spot
for this long,
maybe there's a reason.
What did you wish for?
I wished to become a good father.
The fact that you're wishing that
already proves you're a good father.
A good father doesn't ruin the
whole family by standing surety.
I'm all right.
I can stand strong again
as long as I have my family.
I'm sure of it.
I thought of that man.
"I can stand strong again"
"as long as I have my family."
-Yi-gang!
-Seo Yi-gang!
-They are here!
-Are you all right?
-Are you okay?
-Yes, I'm fine.
Jeong Gu-yeong speaking.
We found the stranded
in the cave behind Clown Rock.
We'll descend.
-Can you get up?
-Yes.
This way, please.
That's right.
-Watch your step. It's slippery.
-Okay.
-Be careful.
-Confirmed!
Are you all right?
What happened? Are you hurt?
No one knew
why my parents
went to the mountain on that day.
They left without a word to Grandma or me.
These flowers represent happiness.
Here you go.
I don't need these.
Why are you so angry?
You liked mountains.
I said I like mountains,
not I want to live near.
I have no friends here.
I want to go to Seoul!
There's no one there.
Your mom and dad are here.
Let's stay here together.
No!
I hate mountains, also you and Mom.
I just hate everything about this.
People wondered
if they went to the mountain and died
to leave me insurance benefits.
I denied it
and told myself
they'd never do that to me.
But...
What if they made that choice
because of what I had said to them?
I was scared if that was the case.
I wanted to forget.
[August Status Log]
[Mujin Station]
Are you sure you don't
want to leave a note?
Yes.
We'll survive and tell her face to face.
All of us will survive.
But...
I can't forget anything.
I miss them so bad.
I miss my parents so much!
Be careful, it's slippery.
-It stopped raining.
-That's good.
Oh, we saw a girl up there.
-What?
I found it!
Who are you?
Are you all right?
Go away!
I mean...
-Are you okay?
-Stay away from me!
-Go away!
-Are you hurt...
Hey!
You forgot...
You forgot this!
Take this!
Oh, gosh!
What is this?
They said someone would come.
How come no one is here?
It hurts!
My lottery...
It's all wet!
You're my life.
We're from national park!
Hello?
Over here!
I'm right here!
-Over here!
-We're from national park!
-Hello?
Over here! I'm here!
-Over here!
-Be careful!
-Be very careful.
-Oh gosh.
-Ma'am!
Get me out of here.
Wait up!
Help me!
[911 Rescue]
Sir.
Yang Geun-tak arrived at the hospital.
He's in a better condition,
so he went into operation.
Maybe I shouldn't have saved him.
[Rescue at the damaged road
has been completed.]
Great work, Fire Chief.
[Ranger]
[Emergency Rescue Operation]
Well done, guys.
Did you finish everything okay?
Everyone from Beombawi Rock,
Apricot Tree Valley,
and Stone Chamber was rescued safely.
We're lucky this year.
Go ahead.
-Gosh.
-Be careful.
Ma'am!
What brings you here?
What do you think?
You must have barely eaten anything.
We brought some food
from the ancestral rite.
You must be starving. Have some food.
Thank you. Move the food.
-Set the tables.
-Yes, sir.
-Thanks for your work.
-Thank you.
-Please get in.
-Okay.
Set the tables there.
Thanks for your work, guys.
Bring the food here.
[Emergency Rescue Operation]
Take everything out here.
And some water, too.
-What's this?
-Over there.
I'll bring the rest
to the fire department.
Okay. Go ahead.
-Thank you.
-Knock yourself out.
-Thanks a lot.
What? You're eating without us?
-Great work!
-Thanks.
-How did it go?
-We brought the injured hiker.
Well done.
Wait.
-Where's Yi-gang and Hyun-jo?
-They'll be right here.
Great work, sir. Have some!
-Sir.
-Nice job.
Hey.
Great work.
Go eat something.
Hey.
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
I'm not a child.
-Grandma.
-What is it?
Thank you.
What?
What's wrong with her?
My goodness.
Hello.
We briefly met up there.
I'm Kang Hyun-jo, a national park ranger.
I want to ask you something.
What is it?
I heard you were in the office building
during the flood in 1995.
Yes. So?
Do you remember them?
Well... Not really.
They were also in the office building
back then.
They must have been
with the volunteer firefighters.
I think there were people like them there.
Why do you ask?
Did anything in particular happen to them?
Maybe an argument
or common interest?
I'm not too sure.
It was a matter of life and death.
All I remember is that
we escaped the building together.
But...
I don't think they fought.
Have you seen Yang-sun?
No.
-Have you seen Yang-sun?
-No.
We can just walk down and take the bus.
Please get in. You have a lot of stuff.
It's really okay though.
Get home safe!
Take care!
Hurry up!
-Come help.
-Okay.
Did Yang-sun go to the main station?
-She mobilized.
-What?
[I'll shoot the rope thrower.]
[Please grab the rope
and tie it to the tree.]
Is that her?
I'll go first.
[Commander, we're at the cliff now.]
Good job. How's her state?
[A mild injury, but she's all right.]
[I'll bring her down right away.]
Okay. Keep the walkie on at all times.
[-Yes, sir.]
-Yang-sun, come down safely!
[Okay!]
You go, Yang-sun!
This is Yang-sun's first dispatch.
I'll save her more food.
[-Oh, gosh!
-Watch out!]
[Lee Yang-sun]
[Haedong Station]
[Jirisan]
Yang-sun!
Bring a lifebuoy!
[Seo Yi-gang, withdraw!]
[Going to the valley now is suicide!]
Gu-yeong! No!
[Could I see the daily log
during the flood?]
[It wasn't an accident.]
[It's all my fault.]
[You should talk to Yi-gang.]
What? What's going on?
[So what's the evidence you can use
to prove who the murderer is?]