♪Let the bygone be bygone♪
♪Let our intuition evolve♪
♪A firm resolution♪
♪Can't be easily crushed♪
♪A precise calculation♪
♪An invisible armor♪
♪A well-equipped chariot♪
♪Let's depart now♪
♪The goal can never be seen♪
♪How to realize the dream
of reaching the stars then♪
♪From the beginning to the end♪
♪How far is the horizon♪
♪The thrill in overcoming challenges
along the way♪
♪And breaking through every barrier♪
♪The future lies in the game♪
♪As it realizes one scene after another♪
♪Our dream is the driving force♪
♪It's a complicated world♪
♪A simple heart♪
♪Will respond to it♪
♪Taking one step at a time♪
♪The map points towards the end of the world♪
♪One day♪
♪We will arrive♪
♪At the distant road♪
♪Being touched♪
♪By every step we take♪
[GO Into Your Heart]
[Episode 10]
Hello?
Why haven't you come home
in the middle of the night?
I'm at my friend's place.
Yan Xiao is unbelievable.
Making you work overtime again?
The rain is torrential.
How about this?
Spend the night at her place.
Don't come home, but stay safe.
No, Dad...
My dad said
I shouldn't go home tonight.
Oh.
The place is leaking. Let's go somewhere else.
♪Like the encounter
between the stars and the night♪
♪You could see through my mind♪
♪The sweet pomelo candy
seems to be opening its mouth♪
Let me show you a magic trick.
Watch.
♪Let me guess in secret♪
♪Are you looking forward to it too♪
♪To those words in my heart♪
♪Nice to meet you♪
♪A confession through the eyes♪
Haven't you seen this before?
You've never watched "My Neighbor Totoro?"
♪Seen through it♪
No.
♪For you♪
♪You are behind me♪
♪Sensing but accepting♪
♪The gentleness released by the electric wave♪
♪Keeps transporting to my heart♪
♪Passing through mirages to arrive by my side♪
♪It is so beautiful♪
♪For you♪
I made the bed for you.
There is a glass of water by the bedside.
Thank you for the accommodation.
Rest well.
Good night.
It's still early.
Why not sleep in for a little?
I need to sort out the files at my office
and report to Brother Xu Chi.
Can you finally face him?
I've completely moved on.
Ms. Cheng
really is a great cameraman.
See? Xi He is shedding tears of joy.
I'm so touched.
This is very touching.
The image is overflowing
with emotions and love.
It hits me right in the feels.
To cease my flow of tears,
I must hold
my handsome face proudly
and stare at the walls of...
Not bad.
Master, do you have some time later?
I wish to have a game with you.
Sure.
Ke.
Let your master
take a breather.
He just came back and needs rest.
I did the same when all of you
first came here.
Ke just joined the family.
I must make it fair for him.
Okay?
Sure.
Allow me to brew you some tea.
Black tea or green tea?
The weather is too hot. I'll have some cold beer.
He gets more ridiculous by the day.
[Sheng Jing Chu]
It's too late.
I saw it.
You got 15 new followers.
Is this
what made you cry just now?
Lan.
You know me well.
The numbers
are nothing but an illusion for me.
I do know you very well.
You got all fired-up when you got one follower
over two weeks.
You got 15 new followers,
of course you would be moved to tears.
How shallow of you.
Sister-in-law.
You did an amazing job.
This will determine
the future of my career.
No!
How did she hear me?
Cheng Liao.
Do you remember
what you promised me?
I did my best.
Your best isn't enough!
I want results!
You wasted a great opportunity
and scoops.
Ms. Liu.
Think about it.
The bond of the group is inspiring.
The Go players are like a family.
They are working together
to pass down the legacy of Go.
How touching and inspiring.
I want the juicy scoops.
The juicy scoops!
But there are no scoops in the Jiuzhou Dojo.
You were filming all day.
What about Sheng Jing Chu?
He rarely goes back there.
What about Xie Han Zhou?
He was away.
Cheng Liao, listen up.
I know you are close with Mr. Xu
and also Sheng Jing Chu's girlfriend,
but I decide
what goes into our show!
I answer directly
to the chairperson!
If you fail at your job,
neither Mr. Xu,
Sheng Jing Chu,
nor your sister
can save your skin.
Just go.
That old woman went bananas on you?
Was my show really so awful?
It was good.
But it wasn't what that old woman wanted.
She wants the dirt
on a piece of white cloth
to get the views and attention.
Is this supposed to be
my entire career?
Am I going to spend my day
manipulating gossips?
I can't even post anything
that is real?
You will get used to it.
Learn to accept it.
This is unacceptable.
At work,
it comes down to resilience.
That means,
even if our boss scolds you a million times,
you must be resilient and stay.
These should heal your soul.
[Binhai Television]
I am aware that
Sincere Conversation is at the end
of the road.
[Star Host]
So I'm saving the last few episodes
for the Jiuzhou Four Seas Cup's
Go invitational tournament.
Of the four
traditional arts,
I have the most respect for Go.
It's the most complex and unpredictable
chess game
in human history.
A conversation with a great player
has been a goal
I want to realize
for my show.
You need not be worried
about the views.
Aside from the renowned players
from the Jiuzhou Dojo,
Zhao Yan Xun and Kato Kiyomasa
have quite a fanbase in our country too.
I believe this project
will give everyone
an enjoyable and memorable conversation.
The proposed project
is dubbed
"Showdown of Grandmasters".
I think the overall concept
is viable.
More people are interested in Go lately.
After "the Universal Challenge",
Sheng Jing Chu is all over the internet.
I like the idea.
If you need extra staff, equipment,
or funding,
I'll request from the higher-ups.
Thank you, Mr. Gao.
Cheng.
Don't be too pessimistic.
Maybe the "Showdown of Grandmasters"
is a turning point for your
Sincere Conversation.
I'll give it my all.
All the best.
We believe in you.
Sister Yi.
Bye.
Sister, stop!
It hurts!
It's me.
Sister,
you could have gone easy on me.
Don't you remember me?
How did you know I'd be here?
I know you are a TV presenter.
To see you,
I've been
giving out fliers for days.
Wait, where are we going?
What exactly do you want?
That day...
Enough about that!
Stop bothering me.
Sister.
I know.
You got it all wrong.
I'm here to pay you back.
But I don't have the money yet.
So, here is an IOU.
[IOU]
Forget it. Don't bother.
There is an extra zero.
I only gave you 500 yuan.
I know what I wrote.
Wait...
What is the meaning of this?
Lately,
I've never stopped working.
I did street performances,
I gave out fliers,
I delivered food orders.
I did every job I could.
But I can barely make any money.
I only have one meal every day.
I sleep in the cheapest room.
But I'm still short on money.
You gave me
500 yuan the other day.
After paying for the room,
I spent the rest pretty much instantly.
So...
So I wrote this IOU because...
I wonder
if you can lend me 4,500 yuan.
The total will be 5,000 yuan.
Do you take me for a fool?
It hurts, Sister! Please let go!
It hurts!
Stop fooling around
unless you want to face my wrath.
What is it that you want?
I only want to get some Go lessons.
How is it so hard?
I don't want to go home empty-handed.
I don't want my dream
to perish so easily!
That's the story.
I was so tired and sleepy
when I fell asleep.
Are you full now?
No.
Excuse me!
Another set, please.
Thanks, Sister.
Is it worth it
to work so hard?
I have no idea.
But one thing is certain.
Playing Go is the most relaxing
and happiest moment
of my life.
You remind me
of the time I just got graduated.
I was an intern at the TV station.
I didn't get paid. I am not an official staff.
I didn't get anything.
I barely had any hope
for my future.
But much like yourself,
when I set my eyes on a goal,
I won't give up so.
I tried to participate in every work
the station had to offer.
I edited videos, I wrote the scripts,
I carried the equipment.
I was even the assistant
of a host.
But I accumulated experience
over time,
so I acquired the skills a TV presenter
needs to possess.
Later on,
I finally got a chance
to be on the silver screen.
I used the experience I had
to convince the audience, the staff,
and the higher-ups of my worth.
That's how I made it here and became
a qualified TV presenter.
This is inspiring.
You really are amazing, Miss Goddess.
I can relate to your loneliness
and obsession
with your future,
so I thought my story could inspire you.
I hope this could
serve as a motivation for you.
Fear not.
Sometimes,
the hardship you live in
will unlock more possibilities
for your future.
This is by far the most uplifting thing I've heard
since I came back to the country.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Dig in.
Carry on.
There is something I must see to.
Where are you going? I can see you off.
Never mind. Finish your food.
I paid the bill for you.
Mr. Sheng.
Ever since you've fallen in love with her,
you started to take your life more seriously.
You make
your own meals now.
That's healthy
and remarkable.
But there is one thing
I just don't get it.
Since you can't tell the color,
how can you tell if the food
is cooked or not?
I have my ways.
But Mr. Sheng,
you might get food poisoning if the food
isn't properly cooked.
This is serious.
You should leave it to me.
Never mind.
Finish up and leave.
Fine.
I'll go after
I've sorted these bags.
Don't touch it.
Mr. Sheng, the competition is around the corner.
You should start practicing.
Leave the trivial chores
to me.
Don't touch it.
I can handle it.
Don't stand on ceremony.
Come on.
Mr. Sheng!
What did I do wrong?
What is it?
Does the flower have bug problems?
I don't know.
It hasn't been well lately.
I was hoping you could take a look.
I'll check it out.
These flowers
are doing very well.
Make sure you water them
regularly.
See?
The sprouts
look fragile.
But the truth is
they are extremely tenacious.
Don't forget,
they rose from the soil
one tiny bit at a time.
So don't worry about them.
Actually,
I was worried about you.
I wasn't
in a good mood today.
What's wrong?
The director doesn't like
the new show I produced.
But I was quite fond of it.
I got it covered.
When you get upset,
you like cooking.
Make yourself at home.
I have another favor to ask.
Do tell.
If I make a mess
out of this place,
could you not yell at me?
I will clean the place
until it's spotless.
However,
I'm a little frustrated at the moment.
As I said,
make yourself at home.
Then... I'll need some space.
It's done.
Do you feel better now?
My frustrations
dissipated like smoke.
But...
I made a mess out of your kitchen.
Sorry.
It's all right.
It's been untouched for some time.
It would be glad
to be of use for someone.
I'll clean it up later.
Dig in.
Sorry.
I think I pressed
the wrong button.
It's okay.
You just opened the garage door.
Your garage?
But you don't even drive a car.
I have a car.
Why did you buy a car?
I can't drive because I'm colorblind.
I won this from a competition.
This car is stunning.
The color is gorgeous.
This branding looks familiar.
It's a pony
standing on his rear legs.
What was it called again?
Ferrari.
I know.
Even though
I barely know anything about cars,
but I know
what a Ferrari is.
Give it a try.
I can't drive.
I'm not asking you to get on the road.
It's not illegal to test it out.
Well...
Press the other button.
This one?
Yes.
You don't drive.
But how do you know about the steps?
I know every detail I need to drive a car.
But I lack the eyes
that can see the colors of the world.
If there is a chance
I could see the colors again,
I would get my driver's license.
When you get it,
take me out for a ride.
Deal.
Pinky swear.
This car is awesome.
Do you like it?
You can have it.
Did I save
the universe in my previous life
to deserve this boon?
No.
I can't take this present.
I can't drive it anyway.
I did nothing to deserve this gift.
You made me food.
That's all it takes?
I'd have to cook
for you my entire life!
Why did the engine die?
Did I break it?
I think you might have to
cook for me for the rest of your life.
I didn't press anything.
Why did it die?
It ran out of gas.
Thank you, Eldest Senior Brother.
You really put some muscle into it today.
Slow down a little.
A little gentler.
It's you!
Why are you here?
Master.
Sit.
I'll give you a massage.
Let go of her!
Sit.
What do you want?
I...
I came to study under her.
I don't buy it.
You have no master here.
You have a decent look.
Perhaps I could
do him a favor.
No way!
I'm an eight dan for years,
I've never taken in any students.
You're only a four dan.
You have no right.
He came to me willingly.
So I don't mind at all.
Okay.
Master!
Please accept my worship!
Get up!
Get out of here.
Come on.
Master.
He is my student.
Hey...
This should be far enough.
Make yourself clear.
If you can't,
then let's settle it another way.
Is this supposed to be
a dance battle?
Stop playing the fool.
Plenty of people want to woo her.
Get in the line.
That's a lot of people.
She is a great person after all.
No one deserves to have her.
I don't want her.
But I want...
you.
Bro.
Does your hand hurt?
Shut up!
I'm warning you.
Stop playing tricks with me.
I heard everything you said.
She is a four dan.
And you...
You're an eight dan.
Let go!
So what?
You must be even greater than her!
Maybe you could be my master.
I...
So you're not here for her?
No way!
I know you have your eye on her.
Was it so obvious?
Of course.
I'm smart enough to notice it.
So don't take this the wrong way.
I want the greatest player around to be my master
and become the greatest there is.
I can't help you with that.
To become the strongest,
you must learn from the strongest.
Brother.
Who's the strongest then?
Golden Age Tianyuan,
Sheng Jing Chu.
Sheng Jing Chu?
(You have a new order.)
(Please see to it immediately.)
Is there more?
It must be delivered
before noon.
Brother.
What a coincidence.
It seems you deliver everything.
I must earn as much as I can.
Come in.
Are you sure?
Come on.
Keep it safe for me.
Thank you.
Sit down. Sit here first.
How are you lately?
Exhausted?
Not bad.
I'm a little exhausted,
but I'm happy.
Judging by the tone,
you've made progress
with your crush.
She gave me her numbers.
I can contact her now.
Good for you.
Brother.
How have you been?
Are things better now?
Not yet.
But I'm not worried.
I've known her for years.
I know her well enough.
I believe
with enough patience
and dedication,
I will win her heart someday.
I doubt it.
If you really like her,
you must take a proactive approach.
Do not take too long.
People might get her before you do.
Are you lecturing me?
No.
I mean no disrespect.
I'm giving you advice
based on my experience.
You should
focus on winning the heart
of your crush.
Sure.
I hope you succeed as well.
That's enough for today.
It's almost time.
I asked her out on lunch.
I envy you.
You actually got to ask her out.
I asked her out as well.
But she's busy tonight.
I should get back to my work.
I thought
you got your crush's number.
Yeah?
Silly.
Add her on WeChat.
Right.
Her WeChat!
Why didn't I think of that?
Brother.
You are my Polaris.
Thank you.
I'll buy you
a meal when I get the chance.
Forget it.
Let me do the honor.
I may be broke for now,
but I can still afford a bowl of noodles.
Right?
I thought
you'd refuse to see me.
Of course not.
As long as you keep a level head,
you're still my best friend.
My mind was perfectly clear.
Xu.
Cut it out
or I'm leaving.
Fine, I won't.
I have a present for you.
For me?
What is it?
There are only
a few episodes of Sincere Conversation.
I hope you can finish it
in the most beautiful outfit.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
You helped me out a lot
during "the Universal Challenge".
Your work went down the drain.
Don't bring that up.
Do I look so petty to you?
I've moved on a long time ago.
I did what I could for it.
The end result doesn't matter.
I know you care about me.
Do you?
Xu.
Fine. Let's not talk about it.
Have a drink.
[Friend Request]
[Yu Da]
[Verify Friend Request]
Brother, I have good news for you.
I got my crush's WeChat.
Congratulations.
You just got one step closer.
Thanks.
Keep up the good work.
I hope
you win her heart someday.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
I just made a donation.
To whom?
He's studying.
He's deprived of education.
Come on.
To your charity work.
Bless the kind souls.
To the kind souls.
Cheng Zhi Liao, are you awake?
Yes.
Come and get your breakfast.
Okay. I'll be there in a moment.
[Happy Birthday]
Good morning.
Dear Father
and Sister,
do we have any plans
for tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
There's a lot to do tomorrow.
Grocery shopping in the morning,
exhaust hood repairing at noon,
the junior Go lessons end in the afternoon.
Our shop will get really busy.
What about you, Sister?
Working overtime.
Dad, I'm headed to work.
Finish your breakfast, hurry up.
Don't be late again.
Eat your food.
I need to shop for meat.
Do the dishes for me later.
They don't remember my birthday.
No one remembers.
What is going on now?
Senior Sheng.
I've only been away a few days.
When did you get a greenhouse?
To make my life more colorful.
Don't be silly.
You can't see the colors.
I see with the mind.
As if...
Senior Sheng.
I bought you some fruits.
The weather is nice today.
Could you let me take
the Ferrari out for a spin?
I knew it.
You tried it every year.
Aren't you tired of doing it?
(You can have it.)
Did I save
the universe in my previous life
to deserve this boon?
No.
I can't take this present.
I can't drive it anyway.
I did nothing to deserve this gift.
Xi He.
If I were to give you
a very valuable present,
would you find it offhand?
Very much so.
Why would you give anyone present?
I thought you never let go
of anything
you got your hands on.
That depends.
That hurts my feelings.
I'm your best buddy.
If I couldn't get a present,
well...
It was Sister-in-law, am I right?
Why should I be
jealous of her?
But Senior Sheng,
I must say,
you have a unique taste
for lovers.
Ever since her show
was aired,
we've gained a great number
of followers on Weibo.
Then you should thank her.
That is for sure.
But how do I thank her?
I have an idea.
Hello?
Hello? Sister Cheng Liao?
We're going to the Karaoke tomorrow.
It's on Cao Xi He.
He assigned me the task
of inviting you.
So I look forward to your arrival.
I have plans for tomorrow.
Well, at least I think so.
I'm not sure yet.
Besides,
only the members of your institute are there.
I shouldn't ruin the fun.
Nonsense!
You are the most important
VIP of tomorrow.
We need you there!
Don't worry, just come with us.
Okay, I'll go.
Really?
Be there or be square.
I'll send you the address later.
Okay.
See you.
[The top TV presenter of Binhai
Television is a hypocrite!]
The main subject.
The category.
Talk shows.
You must pay attention
to these aspects.
[The top TV presenter of Binhai
Television is a hypocrite!]
Check your phone.
It's Cheng Yi!
It really is her.
They are having dinner together.
[The top TV presenter is a hypocrite!]
It's not having dinner.
They were dating.
Check your phone!
[Cheng Yi likes them young]
Isn't that Sister Cheng Yi?
[She is a debauched woman, get rid of her!]
It really is her.
[She visits nightclubs! How disappointing!]
Do you know who the guy is?
[The look on her face, she knows her way around!]
I don't know.
[She likes young brats!]
The man is quite dashing.
[She visits nightclubs! How disappointing!]
They had dinner together.
Not bad, Sister Cheng Yi.
I hope
you win the heart of your love.
you can win her heart.
This is new to us.
Yeah.
This picture is shocking.
Sorry.
The number you dialed is unavailable.
I just mustered the equipment,
funding, and staff for Showdown of Grandmasters.
I even got you
the mobile live-stream truck.
How could you make such
a grave mistake?
Cheng Yi.
This is outrageous.
The ratings on Binhai TV Station
are overwhelmingly negative.
We had to close the comment section.
Our chief just called.
You're no longer in charge
of the Jiuzhou Four Seas Cup.
We canceled your talk show
as well.
Sorry.
I never knew I would
garner so much trouble for our company.
For that, I will
express my deepest apology to everyone.
You should reflect on your mistake.
But I must ask,
how do this news thread
and the photo make me
the villain?
You're our most valuable host.
You should be mindful of your image!
I'm single.
I'm not married.
I'm not having an affair
or cheating on my partner.
I'm over 21 years old.
It's legal for me to have alcohol.
How is it wrong?
You're a public figure.
I am also a human being!
What do you think
the public will think
when you hugged that man?
Did you even check the photo?
See for yourself.
I merely
placed my hand on his shoulder!
That's all!
It's the 21st century.
So what have I done wrong?
You're the backbone of our company!
But am I treated like one?
You gave the influencer my show
and you cut
the funding for my show.
You must understand!
We are facing
competition from many platforms!
It's not easy for us to run the business.
We are planning to transform the business.
So why can't I
have a different image?
Why am I always
not being considered?
Over the years,
I never posted anything
on my Weibo page
or any social media
because I knew people might take a screenshot
to slander me!
Whether I was sad or happy,
no matter what I had to deal with,
I never took my frustration
out on anyone!
I couldn't even tell my father
anything at my work!
I don't want him
to get just as worried.
Mr. Gao, if you could just
read my mind,
you'd find it full of the anguish
and bitterness I've endured
over the years
I've worked here.
♪The wind blows, the moon
crosses the sea of clouds♪
♪The butterflies look like you, Zhi Liao♪
♪Awaken the bustle of a summer night♪
♪Black and white, and the faded colors♪
♪I reach out, but I can't touch it♪
♪Their beauty has long been forgotten♪
♪Because you are dancing again♪
♪Your presence lights up my world♪
♪Bringing warmth to my rainy night,
allowing me to see♪
♪That life is like a butterfly that can only
fly away after breaking out from the cocoon♪
♪Ah... Flying out of the desert of adversities♪
♪Ah... I want to respond to your kindness♪
♪The clouds drift past,
hiding the sun's brilliance♪
♪Waiting in the long rainy season♪
♪For the summer dialogues♪
♪Sweet and bitter, and everything unknown♪
♪Colors have appeared all around you now♪
♪I won't quit even if I have to go against the wind♪
♪It's you who have given me the new power♪
♪Ah... Finding the taste of memories♪
♪Ah... Let's pray for love♪
♪Your presence lights up my world♪
♪Bringing warmth to my rainy night,
allowing me to see♪
♪That life is like a butterfly that can only
fly away after breaking out from the cocoon♪
♪Your existence awakens my past♪
♪Embracing my future as you teach me♪
♪That no one is a lonely island and running
against the wind with me♪
♪Ah... The small dream is flying high now♪
♪Ah... You are my precious♪