Ya burning
you are born
Chunhuang, I did something wrong
Ya Ran, please tell me
who is this person
Ya Ran, don't be sad
Although you can't be with him
But you have to take good care of yourself
I know Bai Wei
By the way, Chunhuang?
how is he
since we parted
Chun Huang, he has changed a lot
In the past, he hated dealing with Quanxian's affairs.
Now I only care about those
But now Quanxian is prosperous and healthy
It is beyond the reach of Kongsang
This is all thanks to Chunhuang
But he only had Quan Xian in his heart
Never married a queen
He was born too
what kind of woman
the woman
He lost her after all
what a pity
But I really want to go to Longxiao Palace again
You will always be Quanxian's most popular guest
pure brilliance
we all miss you
Bai Wei, I'm leaving first
tonight
Just stay here and have a good rest
you're going to drink alone
It was sent by your maidservant.
Her Royal Highness said it was the Queen's favorite thing
I know everything, Alang
Bai Wei drinking on an empty stomach is bad for your health
so
How about I drink with you another day
Kings
How is Princess Yaran
she talked to the queen for a moment
I went to the side hall to rest.
nothing unusual
keep an eye on her
In addition, the envoy Izumi Izumi visited
What can be said inside and outside the palace
Envoys visit Mirror City
All the ministers and the people appreciate it
Said they had never seen it before
Quanxian has so many rare treasures
Eye-opening today
What can the six kings say?
The subordinates are attending the banquet today
Hear the Six Kings Talk
Among them, Qing Wang has quite a view on the alliance
Qing Wang determined that Quanxian was seeking peace on the surface
actually provocative
Quanxian's wealth far surpassed Kongsang
Kongsang has been built
But the treasury is empty
Although the king has a martial art
But not as wise as the sea emperor
What else did the king say?
King Qing also said
if you can agree with him sooner
To attack Izumi's request
the king the king
king queen she
what's wrong with her
The queen was poisoned in a coma
what
She treats you like a sister
You want to poison her
really vicious
Why are you laughing
I never thought of harming sister Bai Wei
all i want is your life
You gave her the poisoned wine with your own hands
you want to kill me
that wine
Yes
I regret saving you
Over the years, you have fought against the cloud
On the surface, it is for the tranquility of Yunhuang
what you do
Can't hide your wolf ambitions at all
After the sixth part, you have your eyes on Quan Xian
you are jealous
Sister Bai Wei has always had my brother Chun Huang in her heart
You are more coveted by Quanxian's wealth
you shut up
I jealous
i cove
You don't know it yourself
Your eyes have already changed
You are not at all
I know you
It's you who have changed
What do you want to take away my queen?
What alliance is trying to show my incompetence
Now you still want to kill me
I hate
can't die with you
I have ancient power in hand
In the seven seas, the cloud and the deserted six are my king's land
Then I'll let you take a good look
how do i
Stepping on Izumi first
The queen is bad
The king leads his troops to Biluohai
I'm going to talk to Quan first.
What did you say
the king said
The poison poisoned by the queen was poisoned by Ya Ran
he wants
nonsense
How could Ya Ran poison me?
go get my armor
Queen, you just woke up
go quickly
Yes
I have to stop Arang
must stop him
Neptune
King Kongsang has already killed the blue seaside
He said
He said that Princess Yaran poisoned Queen Baiwei
Said to step on Hiraizumi to avenge the queen first
If you want to fight
How can you send troops without a name
Neptune
Now is the last year of the Dragon God's transformation
Without the protection of the Dragon God
We can't fight back
Besides
Besides, he has the power of the emperor in his hand.
against
Yes
Langgan
you said that day
I just want the peace of Yunhuang
Why are you still fighting around
you are perfidious
kill him kill him
you are wrong
Possessing great power will not bring disaster
Quanxian has become where he is today
because of people's hearts
Because of
your desire
what do you mean
My spring ancestors have lived in Longxiao Palace for generations
Although the dragon god blesses
But never thought of being an enemy of others
but
you fell in love with the woman you shouldn't love
You even tried to take her away from me
Avi told me
She asked you to send me a letter
But
I have never received any letters
When I arrive at Longxiao Palace
You even let Ya Ran trap me
And this time
You even poisoned her
what are you thinking
Bai Wei asked me to deliver the letter
I did hesitate
But the letter has already been sent
And what you said about the burning and poisoning
i don't know
That's right
I really love Bai Wei
But
I never thought about taking her away
I didn't even think about hurting her
I didn't even express
my love for her
because I know
in her heart
She loves only you
If I hadn't arrived in time
You're going to keep her with you, right?
you can't get her
even less visible
I will spend this life with her in peace
These are all excuses for you to challenge Quanxian.
Langgan
I thought you were pure in nature
Can suppress the magic of the sign
you have lost your mind
You are not the same you used to be
kill him kill him
no matter what i become
I can do everything for Bai Wei
I can share the world with her
But I want to make her world
no more you
Avi
How can you point your sword at me
why are you doing this
I want to make an argument for you
make an argument for me
Are you referring to Ya Ran's poisoning?
Well I ask you
Why do you think Ya Ran will poison me
she
i ask you again
The cloud shortage has been pacified for several years
It will take time to get the whole army out
why am i poisoned
You immediately lead the army to go to Quanxian
Langgan
You have long planned to conquer Quanxian.
what ya burn poison
It's all your excuses
Ya burn is kind-hearted
would not do such a thing at all
shut up
alang
you do not believe me
if it was you
I will definitely believe
But now you've changed
Kong Sang can have today
All rely on Chunhuang to help
you do
You're doing this to avenge
his help
He's clearly thinking
how did you become like this
the world in your eyes
how can it be so dark
I am fine too
Ya Ran is also good
It's all an excuse for you to go to Quanxian.
When you hold high the sword
Do you remember this sword
It was originally given to us by Chunhuang
Let us pacify and protect the cloud
now
We have achieved our original intention
But what about you
You still don't want to put away this heaven-defying sword
You would rather listen to King Qing's slander
You even aimed your sword at Quanxian
Actually trying to seal the Dragon God
are you crazy
Without the blessing of the Dragon God
From now on
will obey from generation to generation
won't fight anymore
You killed Quan Xian today
another day
Kongsang must be destroyed by others
When will this back and forth stop
what are you doing
you are no longer what you used to be
the one i know
follow my childhood sweetheart
Good astrologer Ah Lang
It's the King of Stars that I don't know
The back soil ring
i give you back
Queen of Houtu ring
You can pick it up if you want
You are the queen of Kongsang
you are my queen
nowadays
Betrayed me for an outsider
this day and this place
These seven seas, this cloudless desert
I share everything with you
why do you do this
this day and earth
how can it be our everything
alang
You don't get obsessed anymore
let it go
Avi
why did you betray me
because of him
kill Chunhuang
all this will end
Bai Wei only belongs to me
how so
the phantom
Locked the three of us inside
if i don't wake up
The Heavenly Sword will look like it was 7,000 years ago
Killing Queen Baiwei
kill Bai Ying
i have to wake up
Bai Ying Bai Ying
wake up
Bai Ying, wake up
What's up with her
She should still be in the hallucination
Bai Wei
Bai Ying
Su G, you finally woke up
why are you here
not long ago
I was sucked in by a beam of light
result
This sword is in my hands
And I'm holding the Heaven-defying sword
With you in calming the cloud
you saw the vision too
things in fantasy
Did you not know
Previously in the tomb of Jiuyi Xingzunwang
I have seen the scene before Queen Bai Wei died
but i don't know
I am the one with the sword
wrong
Langgan
why didn't you tell us
You have seen the picture in the vision
And how did you come here all of a sudden
After you leave
I looked at the parchment repeatedly
what did you find
The parchment has these words written on it
On the same day we met in the trapped Longyuan
You give up your precepts and I go home alone
all day long
I can't wait for you to return
Clear tears and two lines of empty sadness
I didn't feel anything wrong at the time
But after watching it repeatedly
more and more uneasy
Especially those three words
You fade away
just expected
The past in this trapped dragon must be complicated
So I came over
Unexpectedly, it almost hurt you
that we have seen in visions
maybe not an illusion
but the truth
Did not you say
Have you always had a pair of eyes looking at us?
maybe the eyes
the one who took us into the illusion
you mean those eyes are
Queen Baiwei
phantasmagoria
Almost made the three of us kill each other
Or hurry up and find the sleepy dragon lock
Isn't that sleepy dragon lock right there?
Where is the sleepy dragon lock
Here is the Sleepy Dragon
How could this enchantment stop the fire formation?
Maybe this sleepy dragon cable is the same as the Xuanhuangjing
only you can see
then i try
Or let you go one step ahead
You are not too late
If it weren't for those few Quanxian soldiers to cause chaos
I'm already here
what did you do to them
Have you heard of the poison of the ghost red Yan?
It's now spread all over the waters of the county
no one is spared
And your left-right envoy Yan Xi
Guess he's dead or alive now
Including that spy Xiao
mean
Seriously, will I be deceived by you all the time?
Su G
you go to unseal
Give this man to me
Your Highness
Don't worry, it's alright
I'd like to see
How powerful is Prince Kong Sang
Dragon God who has been covered in dust for thousands of years
Finally see the sun again
This trapped dragon has been untied
Why hasn't the Dragon God come out yet?
Dragon God is at his feet
It turns out that the reef that was trapped in Longyuan for a week
the Dragon God
Why cut off the sleepy dragon cord?
Dragon God is not out yet
Dragon God
I am the emperor
I'm here to save you
Is it not enough to cut off the trapped dragon rope?
How can I rescue the dragon god?
I've been waiting for you for a long time
You only come when Kongsang is destroyed
Queen Baiwei
I can stay in the trapped dragon for seven thousand years
Thanks to this back soil ring on your hand
see you
It's like seeing us back then
What are the illusions we see?
What you see is real
That was seven thousand years ago
A piece of the past between me, Chunhuang Langgan
Whenever I think of what Lang Gan looked like at that time
I can't believe it
my memory is real
jealousy and ambition
will expand the dark side of people
make people crazy
Zhengquan seals Biluohai first
Ling Quan's ancestors left their homes for generations
fortitude becomes stubborn
Love becomes domination
The advantages of Langgan's original character
unknowingly become twisted
became that
people i don't know
Since he found you in Biluohai
Since then
Everyone's fate has changed
an irresistible fate
Let's go this way
What I want for Yunhuang is peace
And what he wants is domination, conquest
While we take our swords to the flames of war
We are destined to reach these two ends
Is fate really irresistible?
opened
this water mirror
Bai Wei
do you still want to come out
Avi
According to the Xuanhuangjing records
The seal of the Dragon God can be unlocked with the Heaven-defying Sword
But now the sleepy dragon rope has been broken
Why hasn't the Dragon God come out yet?
Dragon God has two seals on his body
One is set up by Alang
This is the sleepy dragon
for the dragon god
Trapped in the trapped dragon forever
There is another one that I set
At that time, Alang sealed the dragon god
I'm afraid the dragon god will be destroyed
Use half the power of the back earth
Created a seal for the Dragon God
protect it forever
And the other half of the power
left it in your back soil ring
Bai Wei
how so
I did not do it on purpose
Avi why are you
May I die without closing my eyes
see when you die
Bai Wei, stop talking
Avi, I didn't mean to
me
It's all Na Chunhuang
without him
you will always be my queen
yes he is
It's all his fault
I'm going to kill him
pure brilliance
I can't release the dragon god
But I will protect the Dragon God for you
As long as the Dragon God is there
Quan Xian will not die
don't fight again
He killed Avi
kill him
I can get everything in Yunhuang
Queen Baiwei
What do we have to do to free the dragon god
follow me
put your hand on
why can't i open it
concentrate
Concentrate mana on the Houtu God Ring
Be careful
I have endured so much suffering for hundreds of years
i can't give up
Quanxian's Dragon God
We finally meet again
seven thousand years
finally wait
The moment I unseal the seal for you
I'm here to correct the mistakes of the year
Dragon God is angry
it must remember
At the beginning, Chunhuang was the dragon's tooth to get for me
what should we do now
Unlock the seal and let the dragon god fly out
Queen Baiwei, please lend me your strength
let me release the dragon god
It's nature to lend you strength
Only you can inherit my power
you used to be half spiritual
Open the colorless city
But with your present body
wanna get my power
need to pay a huge price
give your most precious
Do you want to
Did you just hit a feather?
The poison of ghost red Yan
I promise you no matter what
For Quan, first for Su G
Don't let the past regrets and mistakes
continued
Queen Baiwei, I'm ready
good
my descendants
You've got all my power
Go and release the dragon god
Let the dragon god recognize the sea emperor
I should be gone too
Kongsang and Yunhuang
I'll leave it to you
Avi
You still want to switch to me
The seal of the Dragon God is about to be unlocked
Climb up and kill Su G
Why is it always me who is abandoned and hurt
Why
Bai Ying
What the hell did you just do?
To unlock the seal of the Dragon God
It's the only way
Back then when King Xingzun sealed the Dragon God
Now it should also be the descendants of my Kong Sangbai clan
to break the seal