[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode Fourteen]
The more I look at you, the more I like you.
Don't be shy.
Sooner or later, you'll be a member of the Meng family.
Yuanxu,
you should bring Luo home more often to visit me
so that I can communicate more with my future daughter-in-law.
Do you hear me?
Yes, mother.
Some of the plants can't be watered too much.
Be careful. Or you'll get them withered.
Luo,
stay here if you’re free today.
Tomorrow is my birthday.
All of my husband's friends will come.
They love Yuanxu very much.
So I'm sure they will like you as well.
Mother,
that's really not necessary.
There's a new project in the Wood Feather House.
So we're very busy.
We won’t join you tomorrow.
Since he met you, Luo,
Yuanxu has really become more steady.
He's filial and righteous.
As her mother,
I really have to thank you.
It's not like that, Madam.
He's always been a good man.
I truly helped nothing in that.
Look.
You're so humble.
Yuanxu,
it seems that it has been useful for me
to burn incense and worship the gods these years.
The gods really have given me such a good daughter-in-law.
I think you two
are really destined to be together.
Yuanxu, come here.
Great!
This is really great!
I'm really enjoying
this year's birthday.
Um... mother,
we still have work to do,
see you.
Bye.
Madam, take care.
You haven’t finished watering the flowers.
Luo, come often.
Such a plump girl...
She can definitely give birth to lots of babies.
Ning,
didn't you say you went to Wood Feather House?
I've been there.
Has Li Qingfeng changed his attitude towards you?
I don't know.
Maybe yes or maybe no.
Then at present, you should
stay in the Wood Feather House.
He needs to work.
Why would I stay there?
To make him get sick of me?
You are too careless.
I'm born to be careless.
Always being cautious these days
actually makes me
feel not at ease.
Why?
This may be my last chance.
So I should be myself.
Brother,
I want to race against you.
OK.
Come on, let’s have a race.
Let's go.
Miss Zhao.
Mr. Zhang, why are you here?
I brought this fine horse to Miss Zhao
to express my apology.
We were about to have a horse race, and then you're here with a horse.
What a coincidence.
Is this the seventh son of Lord Zhao?
Nice to meet you.
Forgive me for my ignorance.
Do we know each other?
Many years ago,
my father and I have met you
in a gathering.
Just one time.
It’s normal that you don’t remember.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Zhang,
do you think I lack horses?
Miss Zhao,
don't get me wrong.
I'm here to give you the horse to apologize.
When we first met,
I was in a rude manner.
So I feel sorry for that.
I hope you can accept this horse
and forgive me.
No need. Take it back.
Brother, let's go racing.
No hurry.
Since you're here to send the horse
to express your apology,
I can feel your sincerity.
That's right.
OK.
Let me have a look at the horse.
Sir,
I raised this horse myself
and it's my favorite horse.
Good!
This is really a fine horse.
We shall keep it!
Brother!
However,
our own racecourse
never lacks precious horses.
Since this horse is Mr. Zhang's favorite horse
and the Zhao family
never stripes others of their beloved things,
how about
leaving it in our racecourse?
We'll help you raise the horse.
In the future,
you can come visit anytime.
We would like to make friends with you
so that we can keep in touch.
That's great!
It's good to keep in touch.
Ning,
how do you think about it?
If you want to raise it, then do it yourself!
So it's to the satisfaction of all.
Mr. Zhang, you're just in time.
How about we have a horse racing together?
I only want to race with you, brother.
Miss Zhang, don’t worry.
I came here
just to send you the horse and apologize.
Thank you for your kindness, Mr. Zhao.
My sister is sick at home, so I need to go back and take care of her.
Maybe next time.
I see.
Then it's really inappropriate to keep you here.
Mr. Zhang, do as you please.
I'll take my leave.
This horse is really good.
Sir,
have you seen this lady these days?
No.
Have you seen my lady?
-No. -Think about it.
[Qian Fu Sugar Store]
I didn't expect that we really got the key information.
Let's go back and tell Qingfeng.
About Xu Qian's courtyard...
No.
This way.
Say it.
Lady, help me!
It's me.
My Lady?
Don't turn round.
Your servants are there.
They seem to have seen me.
If this goes on,
I think your father will soon
come to Lin'an himself.
Then I’ll leave if he comes.
Run!
Lady!
Catch up with them!
You come back so often.
Because I miss you.
Miss me?
You used to go out all the time.
Miss Han,
since he is with you,
he has become more thoughtful.
Mr. Luo,
we...
Honey!
Our son is back.
That's great.
Madam.
You must be hungry.
What do you want to eat? I'll cook for you.
It's okay. I don't want to eat.
Thank you.
What's wrong with her?
What are you looking at?
They are here.
Follow me.
This...
What happened?
Get in.
Officers,
what would you like to eat?
Please come in.
Have you seen this lady?
Maybe?
Really?
Maybe not.
Anyway, I think
she is pretty.
Why do you say she's pretty every time you see a girl?
Because she really is pretty.
You were somewhat pretty 20 years ago.
What 20 years ago?
I mean...
Let these officers take a look at you.
-She's an old lady now. -Go over there.
What old lady?
Look in the mirror.
You are such an old man.
Now I see every girl
is pretty.
Any other girl is prettier than you.
You're not even close to pretty. You're old.
What is this place for?
It's so small here.
Is this the place you used to live in?
This was my own little world
when I was young.
Your little world?
Every time when creditors came to ask for payment of debts,
my mother would hide me here.
Then I would hide here the whole day.
So in my childhood,
I spent most of my time here.
This abacus...
My father bought it
when he was still wealthy.
At that time, I wanted to study business with him.
But my dad told me
I could just become a deputy governor if I only learn abacus.
If i want to be a boss,
i have to forget the rules and principles for the abacus,
and accept the world's unjust
and unreasonable part.
Your servants are quite stubborn.
It seems that they won't leave for now.
Let's sit down and talk.
This carpenter knife
was given by Qingfeng
when my family was in straitened circumstances.
He didn't ask me to hurt people with it.
He just wanted me to protect myself with it.
In those years,
my only friend
was Qingfeng.
I think everyone in the Wood Feather House
envies your friendship very much.
Even I envy him
of having such a good friend like me.
God actually blessed me.
He let me have my best friend
and my best partner.
Niaoniao,
we can anyhow figure out a way to deal with them.
Since I was born
I've been facing problems,
and solving them everyday.
Don't worry.
As long as I'm here,
no one
can take you away from me.
I have no idea.
Architect Li, are you working?
I'm thinking.
Then give me something
and let me think about it.
You choose.
Is this
the little wooden horse
that Master Yu once mentioned?
Yes.
His cutting skill is quite different from yours.
It's of less sharpness but more smoothness.
Good skill!
It seems that you father is also a skilled craftsman.
This craftsman has been waiting for you all morning.
But you had no will to meet him at all.
It seems that he doesn't deserve your respect.
Don't get all sarcastic.
Why are you always
talking about this?
Because till now,
I'm still kept in the dark.
Then keep being in the dark.
You...
Why are you in this attitude?
What attitude?
Look at your attitude to me.
My attitude depends on you.
But have I ever asked you to yell at me?
Yell at you?
Of course you've forgotten it.
You always looked fierce
since the Zhongyuan Festival.
Am I also fierce now?
Is there any sweet talk now?
I can't tell.
You hid something from me first,
but now you're blaming me.
Is there any justice?
Then just do what you think is fair.
I don't care.
Okay, I won't argue with you.
I can strictly separate the work from my own mood.
Then tell me,
what have you come up with after thinking this time?
Nothing.
The sketches Mr. Zhang brought
include all kinds of architecture of the Xiao Dynasty.
But none of them
is the most beautiful house Miss. Zhang wants.
So we can only go to Zhang's Mansion tonight
to see Miss Zhang's mental condition.
Deputy Architect Chen,
are you working?
I'm thinking.
Thank you for your kindness.
You even invited a doctor to take a look at my daughter.
Of course.
Since we took this project,
then we should try our best to help Miss Zhang.
That's great.
But this doctor...
I have never seen him before.
I think...
I'm familiar with all the famous doctors
in Lin'an City.
This doctor is from my home.
This doctor specially takes care of Lord Meng's health?
Exactly.
Thank you so much.
No need.
Let Dr. Lin diagnose first.
OK.
Good.
Miss,
your pulse is stable and your body is fine.
But
I have a question.
Do you think you have forgotten something?
What do you mean?
I'm fine, so I have never forgotten anything.
It's safe. You can come out now.
Thank you, Madam.
Darling.
Don't worry. It's safe.
Father.
it’s getting late.
It's time for us to go back.
Where can you go?
They are all watching outside.
Listen to your father.
They may know you are nearby,
and they have people observing at all intersections.
You can't go out today.
Yes.
Then where can Niaoniao go?
There are so many rooms upstairs.
She can rest in any one of them.
Don't worry.
Niaoniao,
I've cleaned up a room,
and prepared new quilt and pillow.
Let's go up and have a look.
Go.
Madam, I...
Listen to me.
-Just listen to me. -Mother.
Let's go.
Stop looking.
Have a drink with me
and tell me
about you and Miss Han.
Come with me.
Dad.
You...
Let's go.
Go.
[Zhang's Mansion]
Who are you?
I'm Li Qingfeng from the Wood Feather House.
Please inform your Master.
Architects,
what brings you here at this hour?
Mr. Zhang,
Dr. Lin said
Miss Zhang was fine.
But she doesn’t remember Xu Qian at all.
So we are thinking
if her hysteria is related to memory loss.
So we came here at this hour.
Sorry to bother you.
Well...
It doesn't matter.
To be honest,
in our mansion,
it's not allowed to mention "Xu Qian".
Because we fear that she would get irritated.
Dr. Lin mentioned memory loss during the day,
and Fu had no response.
But don’t mention it at night.
If any accident happens,
the consequences will be disastrous.
OK.
Architect Chen is a girl.
So it’s more convenient for her to talk with Fu.
I’ll keep an eye on her.
Thank you, Miss Chen.
Don't worry.
Come with me.
It's the same every day at this time.
Every time I tell her to go back to her room,
she says that she wants to live in the most beautiful house in the world.
Fu.
Who are you?
My name is Chen Langyue.
Langyue...
Does it refer to the bright moon in the sky?
The moon is made of tears.
What?
Look, it's flowing.
It's flowing...
Is there a palace on the moon?
Moon palace?
Yes, there is.
Do you think the Moon Palace is beautiful?
Yes. It is.
Then... is it the most beautiful house in the world?
No.
It's not the most beautiful house in the world.
Alright, it's not.
In your mind,
what do you think is the most beautiful house?
Where is it?
What is it like?
Can you take me to the most beautiful house in the world?
Take me to the most beautiful house in the world.
Take me to the most beautiful house in the world!
-Fu. -Take me there.
Leave her to us. Go back to rest.
Take me there.
Take me to the most beautiful house in the world!
Fu! Fu!
Fu, calm down.
I’ll take you there.
Look.
Moon.
Don't worry.
Please.
Look.
Look at the moon.
The moon's tears are flowing.
Fu,
you want to live in the most beautiful house in the world, right?
I want to live in the most beautiful house in the world.
How many doors does it have?
Ten?
No, no, no.
One hundred doors.
What does that house look like?
What does it look like?
It's...
like...
like this.
What should we do?
What does it look like?
How about...
We...
No.
Mr. Zhang clearly told us
not to mention him.
But this is the only breakthrough.
This is the most beautiful house in the world.
Don't let go of each other's hands.
Or it won't be the most beautiful house.
You mean... this is the most beautiful house in the world?
Yes, the most beautiful house.
Fu,
Xu Qian and you...
Fu!
Fu! Fu!
What’s wrong?
My heart hurts.
What's wrong?
Xu Qian, who is he?
Nothing.
Who is Xu Qian?
Fu.
Do you remember him?
Who is Xu Qian?
Calm down.
Can you take me to Xu Qian?
I want to see him. I want to see him.
Can you take me to see him?
Take me to Xu Qian.
It's okay.
Calm down. Calm down.
Calm down.
Calm down, Fu.
It’s okay.
Your name is Chen Langyue?
What’s your name?
Li Qingfeng.
You must be together.
You must be together forever.
Otherwise, once you separate from each other,
you'll never be able to see each other again.
I'm going to find the most beautiful house in the world.
I'm going to find the most beautiful house.
The most beautiful house!
-I'm going to find the most beautiful house. -Fu.
-The most beautiful house in the world. -Fu.
The most beautiful house in the world.
I didn't expect that she came to Lin'an for escaping marriage.
That means
you haven't formalized your relationship?
We are sort of a couple now.
I mean getting married.
Do not worry.
I'll definitely marry her.
I'm afraid it's her father who will come.
Think about it.
If your mother and I keep trying to stop you,
do you think you can successfully get married?
You can stop me as you like,
and we can still get married, can't we?
But have you ever thought about Miss Han?
If your father were still wealthy,
you wouldn’t have had so many worries.
Dad,
didn’t you insist that
you wanted to stay at this small restaurant
and live an idle life?
And it was useless to persuade you to make a comeback.
It's just a feeling.
There is nothing
worth worrying about.
Fight for whatever you want.
It's not difficult.
Brat,
what you said today
is like what your father said in those years.
You said it yourself.
Fill it up.
[Making silk and satin garments all year round.]
I...
You first.
I think the most beautiful house in Miss Zhang's eyes
must have something to do with Xu Qian.
But now,
we can't stimulate her anymore with the name "Xu Qian".
At least we can't do it again
before there's improvement in her sleep.
[Meat Noodles]
That makes the two of us.
Let’s go back and ask Boss Luo
what information he has found.
Then we can find another breakthrough.
That's all we can do now.
It's raining.
Let's go.
Lady’s not back yet...
Luo, where are you going?
She hasn’t come back. I’ll go find her.
Let me go with you.
Why does the rain come so suddenly?
Move back a little bit.
My lady! My lady!
Maybe they're still in Zhang's Mansion.
Don't worry.
But it's so late.
They must have come out.
If my lady gets sick in the rain,
I really don't know
how many times I have to die to atone for my sin?
You are not the Dragon King.
How can you be to blame for raining!
Don’t worry.
Li Qingfeng is with her.
If my Master really gets sick in the rain,
I'll punish him first.
Let me hold an umbrella for you.
Let’s go over there.
What are you doing?
If you get a cold,
the project will be delayed.
Why would it have anything to do with you?
Go away!
If you get a cold, then we can only abandon the project.
Master.
Are they there?
Bastard, Li Qingfeng.
Sir!
You will catch a cold.
Meng Yuanxu!
-Sir! -What are you doing?
I did see that he conducted indecent assault on you!
How does he look like
he's conducting indecent assault on me?
Luo, did you see that?
I…
I thought you were
a righteous person.
I didn't expect that you're actually so shameless and nasty.
Master,
listen to me,
let's leave this damn Wood Feather House.
Haven't you heard what I said?
He was just blocking the rain for me.
Impossible.
If he was blocking the rain for you,
then why did you push him away?
I didn't want him to get wet.
He should get wet.
He doesn't match you for your identity is...
Meng Yuanxu.
Are you done?
No.
I have long wanted to make this clear.
I just don't understand,
I treat you so well,
but you chose Li Qingfeng!
He always makes you angry
but you refuse to give me a chance!
Don't you know
you can't have a relationship with him?
What are you thinking?
It's none of your business.
It must be my business.
Then leave the Wood Feather House!
Fine!
Sir!
My lady, I'm sorry.
I’ll apologize to you later.
Luo!
Sir!
She...
It seems that official Meng truly has affection for you.
What do you mean?
I used to think he was just on impulse.
Unexpectedly,
he has been so obsessed with you.
What about you?
[Spring Tea House]
Sir!
Leave me alone.
Go back.
Come back together with me.
Why should I go back?
Even princess wants to kick me out now,
then what's the point of me going back?
No one in the world cares about me.
Then I'd rather die on my own!
But I care.
Besides,
my lady didn't really mean to kick you out.
It's just that the one she likes is not you.
But she still regards you as her best,
and the most intimate friend.
Sir,
in this world, if you love her,
it doesn't mean that she must be with you.
Think about it,
has she ever done anything bad to you?
But you don't understand the pain
that the one you love doesn't love you.
How can I not understand?
You're finally back.
-My lady. -Come in.
Let me see.
You're all wet.
Are you cold?
Come on. Take off your clothes.
I've prepared some hot water for you.
Come.
My Lady, this is inappropriate.
Be good.
My Lady.
Silly girl, don't cry.
Don't cry.
Are you sure you want to leave the Wood Feather House?
Do you want me to stay or not?
I will, of course, respect your decision.
But maybe Architect Chen
doesn't want you to leave.
How can what you think be the same as what my Master hopes!
Let me tell you now.
I shall keep staying inyour damn Wood Feather House.
If Master and Luo don’t leave,
I won’t leave either.
It's useless for you to kick me out.
I shouldn't have fought with you.
The rain has stopped.
This issue
should be left in the past.
Li Qingfeng...
No one in the world cares about me.
Then I'd rather die on my own!
But I care.
Good morning, Master.
It's you.
Master, it was my fault last night.
Take this snack as an apology, please.
Luo is the one that you should apologize to the most.
I know.
I’ve given these to Luo.
Then about what happened last night,
you should also apologize to Li Qingfeng.
I have already apologized to him when I came back last night.
I told him...
Official, you got up so early.
You also come back early.
Where did you two go last night?
I...
I shall go back to rest.
What are you...
Official!
It's not what you think it is.
How do you know what I'm thinking?
Do tell! Where did you go?
We didn't go anywhere.
We were just at my home.
Your home?
Impressive!
I mean... my parents' restaurant.
Miss Han and I rested in two different rooms.
Nothing happened between us.
Official!
You have to be careful with your words.
If it's heard by others,
how should Miss Han face people?
Alright.
Even if you two got married last night,
I wouldn't be surprised at all.
No...
By the way,
Boss Luo,
did you find anything from investigating Xu Qian yesterday?
We've gained a lot.
Tryst in a yard?
Yes.
I knew it.
So our speculation proves right.
What speculation?
Last night,
Architect Li and I met Miss Zhang.
As Councillor Zhang said,
Miss Zhang indeed has hysteria.
And when it broke out,
she would always say she wants to live in the most beautiful house in the world.
She also reacted fiercely when Xu Qian was mentioned.
With the key information you and Miss Han found,
it’s not hard to deduce that
Xu Qian's house
should be the most beautiful house in the world in her eyes.
I see...
That makes sense, doesn't it?
Master, how impressive
you solved the case in such short time!
Qingfeng, do you have any problem?
I'm afraid Architect Li thinks
if the most beautiful house in the world
is the small courtyard where Xu Qian lived when he was alive,
it will be meaningless,
and not interesting.
Luo, tell Councillor Zhang
to communicate with the landlord.
Tell them we will take Miss Zhang there tonight.
If it’s really like what Architect Chen said,
that would be the best.
OK.
Slowly.
Is this the place?
Yes.
Go inside please.
This house...
I seem to have been here before.
Fu.
Is this the most beautiful house in the world?
No.
This is not the most beautiful house in the world.
You can take a look more carefully.
Are you sure it's not?
The most beautiful house...
No, no, no.
Fu! Fu!
-It's not! -Fu.
-This isn't the most beautiful house in the world. -Fu!
Fu.
Where am I?
You lied to me.
Fu.
This is not the most beautiful house.
What’s wrong with her?
This is horrible.
Fu, don't be afraid.
Fu, you…
Don't be afraid, Fu.
Everyone,
I'm afraid you have to keep working on it.
Please don't give up.
Don't worry, Councillor Zhang.
We won’t…
Fu! Fu!
Go home with me.
Fu, don't be afraid.
Go.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
Go home.
Fu.
-Let’s go home. -You lied to me.
It's all right.
[Wood Feather House]
Qingfeng.
Why are you still up so late?
There must be something
that we overlooked.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
This is life.
Difficulties abound, but I'm sure we can anyhow overcome them one by one.
I just think that many things don't make sense.
Why are you here?
I'm just here to take a look at you.
How's your relationship with Miss Chen?
Why do you ask?
Because I’m curious.
Have you talked to her?
Have you resolved your misunderstanding?
You said
she knew clearly that she couldn't be with me.
What does that mean?
But you two are already together.
Qingfeng, I'm going to bed.
Miss Chen, see you.
I think there must be something
that we overlooked.
But what could it be...
Is that the reason why you are here?
Of course I don't know either.
I couldn't fall asleep.
I passed by
and found your light was still on.
So I came to ask you about it.
Why are you looking at this?
I...
I shall also go back to sleep.
But I just came here!
You are doing it on purpose!
Stinky wood!