(All characters, places, institutions, incidents,)
(Episode 4)
(If you don't stop him, it'll be over for you too.)
(My One and Only Supervisor)
- What? - You rude punk.
Hey, do you want to have pork belly since it's raining?
- Supervisor? - What is it?
Why do you sound so down? What is it?
You will never give up, will you?
Give up what? What are you talking about?
You'll never give up on going after those jerks, will you?
Gosh, don't you know me?
Where are you?
Did you drink? Do you want me to pick you up?
The jerks running the illegal site you're after...
They are the Police University's...
Hey, Chul Jin.
Chul Jin. Park Chul Jin!
Chul Jin!
(Emergency Center)
Chul Jin.
Chul Jin!
Mr. Park. Mr. Park Chul Jin!
- Call Anesthesiology. - Yes, sir!
My gut feeling tells me that this case is dangerous.
That day,
you told me that you'd always be right behind me.
It still hurts on rainy days.
And I still turn around in panic mode,
thinking someone might attack me from behind. So please...
don't leave me alone.
I can't seem to stop the bleeding.
We'll move him now.
Chul Jin. Hey...
My gosh.
(Operating Center)
You were the last one he spoke to on the phone.
Is there anything you heard?
Hey, tell me.
The illegal gambling site.
Those darn jerks.
I'll catch them.
I will catch them no matter what.
Hey, calm down.
Because of those scumbags, Eun Ju died,
and even Chul Jin is hurt now. So how can I calm down?
How?
I must catch those jerks.
I'll catch them...
and make them pay for this!
Hey, Dong Man!
(I must...)
(I must protect everyone.)
(I believe that you'll do well.)
He's not here.
Why don't we meet up?
Yes. Will do.
(Do Not Enter, Police Line, Investigation in Progress)
(Do Not Enter, Police Line)
Professor Yu.
Kang Sun Ho.
Yes, sir.
You said you'll do anything for me...
if I help you out, right?
Help me.
- Pardon? - Help me...
so that I can catch those jerks.
- What are you talking... - With your hacking skills,
we can catch those jerks.
Yoon.
"Yoon"?
- Are you... - That's right.
I'm...
Bird.
What?
Wait, hold on.
You said you were in college.
A computer science major.
That's because hackers run away...
the moment I tell them I'm a cop.
At first,
I signed on to the Black Net to get some information.
But I met you, and we ended up chatting...
So you deceived me for a year?
Hey, I didn't deceive you.
I just couldn't find the right time to tell you.
When did you find out that I was Yoon?
That day at the police station? Or here?
You don't have to believe me if you don't want to,
but I only found out recently.
And when I found out, I was as surprised as you are now.
So I was going to pretend I didn't know it was you.
I was going to, but...
Chul Jin got hurt.
I think it's the jerks...
of the illegal gambling site that you hacked.
If you could help me out by hacking them,
I think I'll be able to get them.
Is that why...
you let me get admitted to this school?
You punk!
If I help you,
does that make hacking legal?
The first time is hard. It's easy the next time around.
And by the third time, you won't even feel guilty.
That's what you said to me.
That's why I promised you that I will never...
break any rules.
I made that promise to you.
I'll pretend you didn't ask me that tonight.
(Chungram Lounge)
One.
Two.
Hey, if you're not going to have that yogurt drink,
I can help get rid of it.
But then again, he should take some probiotics too.
Of course.
Probiotics are essential.
I'll get going first.
Our sweet friend...
looks edgy today.
You know how Professor Kwon...
put Sun Ho to shame in his class.
He didn't get any sleep last night...
and rummaged through books all night.
I feel lousy.
That's what your face says.
Honestly speaking, Professor Kwon was too harsh yesterday.
Who can answer him properly if he corners them?
I bet most of them would've gone speechless just like you did.
So don't be discouraged.
Thanks.
But I've actually never given it a thought.
What it means to become an officer and to protect the citizens.
What my stance is.
Then you can find your answer starting now.
We just got into this school. We just started this journey.
You're right.
We just started.
By the way,
about that thing you told me on the last day of the training...
I actually came to this school because of you.
It's you.
Sorry?
Which one?
Attention.
Professor Yu had an urgent matter to take care of,
so today's class is canceled.
Mr. Hyun over here...
will give you detailed information...
on the curriculum and the material you'll need for the semester.
We'll announce the date for the make-up class once it's decided.
We won't answer any questions.
How could he cancel his first class?
It must've been an urgent matter.
He notified us through a phone call.
He said he'll submit the report and the syllabus later.
Is he not feeling well?
He must teach his class even if he's not feeling well.
His students come to his class even when they're sick.
It looks like he doesn't qualify as a professor.
Why don't we start our meeting?
It's a cerebral hemorrhage.
His surgery went well,
but we'll have to wait and see whether he will wake up or not.
He will wake up eventually, right?
We can't guarantee it for now.
Hey, Dong Man. You haven't eaten, right?
Let me return to the force.
You punk, it's already over.
The paperwork has been processed already.
- Captain. - What is it?
Do you trust me?
Why are you asking me that? You're scaring me.
I trust you, Captain.
What are you trying to say?
I think Chul Jin found...
a lead to the gang running the illegal gambling site.
What?
So? Go on.
I think I should return to the force and investigate it myself.
I think Chul Jin found conclusive evidence.
How? What did he do?
I think it has something to do...
with the Police University.
Those jerks involved in the illegal gambling site.
I think they're at our university!
Was it you who hurt his head, not Chul Jin?
Come on, Captain.
If you talk nonsense with a serious face on,
it can be quite convincing. Thanks for teaching me that!
I'm serious! Chul Jin told me that over the phone.
Gosh, you pathetic punk.
Chul Jin is unconscious!
When will you grow up?
How dare you use a sick person?
You're insane.
And you call yourself his supervisor?
Gosh.
I'm telling you the truth!
Chul Jin said it!
- Don't follow me! - Chul Jin said it!
- Go away. - My goodness.
Stop following me!
(Tea Ceremony Club, Dahyang)
The best part of campus life is clubs.
Have you decided which one to join?
This one.
Scientific Investigation Research Club...
that Professor Seo Sang Hak leads.
It's also known as SIRC.
Others think SIRC doesn't have many activities...
because a public administration professor is leading it,
but if you think about it, it's the only club...
that deals with fingerprints, blood, and DNA.
No!
I heard there's a real goddess...
in the dance club.
A goddess.
Really?
Where can I fill out an application for the dance club?
Join the judo club if you want to see a goddess.
Gosh, you scared me.
You can see me if you join the judo club.
Right.
What? He has the face for judo.
What's your name? Sun Ho?
Kang Sun Ho.
I'm going to join the student council.
You're joining it too, right?
What? Yes.
The seniors wanted me to join, and I think it'll be fun.
But I heard there are only two spots left.
Are we rivals now?
We can both get in.
Here it is. Let's go check it out.
(2021 Student Council Recruiting a New Member)
- What about his number? - What's your number?
- Get his number. - It's 010...
- What is it? - You won't get this chance again.
Sun Ho.
If you want to win her love, then join the judo club.
Goodness, Professor Choi.
None but the strong men deserve the beauty.
You know that, right?
Why do you keep forcing me?
You said you want to increase your physical strength...
during your interview.
You can't change your mind overnight.
Keep reading it.
- And then... - Give me some time to think.
Did you write down his name?
Why didn't you?
(Student Council Room)
He's tall, and he has good grades.
I know.
Are you here to apply? You can put it there.
Oh, you know we pick new members based on their grades, right?
- Good luck. - Do you think you'll make it?
(Student Council Application Form, Oh Kang Hee)
(Student Council Application Form, Park Min Kyu)
Police officers...
shoot guns not to harm others...
but to protect them.
Remember that a bullet should only be fired...
to save people.
I hope you'll learn to shoot...
safely and precisely.
Please demonstrate it to us.
Take a deep breath.
As you breathe out, put your arms holding the gun...
in line with your sight.
Once your arms are in line, stop breathing,
aim your gun with the front sight with a rear notched sight.
Focus!
And shoot.
(Police University)
(Kim Koo Library)
(Miranda Rule)
This has the episode of Miranda of the Miranda Rule.
I thought it'd be good to take a look at it.
Thank you.
You don't need to read it all.
You just need to read this chapter.
Kang Hee's hand touched mine.
Kang Hee's hand...
Are you listening?
- Hey, Kang Sun Ho! - Gosh!
Get a grip.
I'm sorry. Can you explain it again?
If you read here...
It says you can't use the suspect's statement...
as evidence against him at his trial.
If you see the next page,
it goes on and on, but you must read it.
- You need to memorize it. - Okay.
There seems to be something going on with Kang Hee and Sun Ho earlier.
I knew it. Like attracts like.
Can't you see I'm studying?
I see. Sorry.
There's no more mercy or consideration for Cho Jun Wook.
Gosh, that's too much between friends.
There are no friends when it comes to love.
No. There's no fair play.
It's a war from now on.
I can do this.
Goodness. Are you guys going to be this childish?
If you're done eating, let's talk.
Do you like Kang Hee?
Yes.
You too, right?
Since when?
Before I got into this school. What about you?
Way before than you.
Witness, please come on in.
(2 years ago)
That wench...
(Witness)
I don't know it exactly.
But I remember people coming and going around midnight.
Then witness, have you seen the accused, who is your mother,
opening an illegal casino in a warehouse...
and gambling?
Yes, I did.
At night. Almost every night.
When I was studying for exams, and even before my judo competition.
That woman, that man, him and her!
Hey, mister.
(Accused)
Your Honor.
To those adults including my mother...
who renovated general housing into an illegal casino,
please give them the maximum penalty allowed by law.
Please, sir.
Then Kang Sun Ho, we can't be friends.
Okay, Park Min Kyu.
- There will be no fair play... - From now on.
- Gosh, really? - My goodness.
- Isn't this unbelievable? - Goodness.
What's going on? Why are you all suddenly so quiet?
Were you talking behind my back?
Keeping the dorm clean is essential.
Call the roll!
Evening-roll-call! Two in total, two present.
All clear.
Again.
Again!
Something amazing happened.
(Korean National Police University)
My gosh, unbelievable. Goodness.
Sun Ho.
It's unbelievable.
Did you hear about Oh Kang Hee?
Kang Hee's mother was convicted four times.
- And it's fraud and gambling. - What?
On the day of our interview,
she was arrested in front of the school.
- My goodness. - What's going on?
- I'm scared. - She's cuffed.
Everyone is talking about it since last night.
How could the daughter of a criminal become a police officer?
How can you say that, Jun Wook?
Hey.
Oh, my goodness.
Kang Hee must have heard everything.
My gosh.
No way.
Just for this week. This is an emergency.
What about the report and make-up plan from last week?
Did you bring it, Professor Yu?
Guidance Director?
I'll come back later.
As for the report,
I'll submit them together at once.
Professor Yu.
Are you canceling your class again?
Well, I got an urgent matter.
What's more urgent for a professor than teaching his students?
Gosh, I have nothing to say and all,
but I really have an urgent matter.
Then just leave.
You seem to lack ethics as a professor.
Don't disgrace other professors.
Just submit your resignation and leave.
I get what you mean.
But who are you to tell me...
to submit a resignation or not?
This is my last piece of advice...
to a loser like you in a polite manner.
Leave without causing any trouble.
Did you just talk down to me?
What are you doing in front of all the students, professors?
- Here, have some. - Thank you.
I thought you've made up your mind, Professor Yu.
The school and students...
I thought you've got some different plans now.
When field officers come to the school,
they often have a hard time adjusting.
But even so, you can't do this, Professor Yu.
My colleague is injured badly.
He's still unconscious.
After this week, I may not even be able to track them down.
This week is like the golden hour.
I know that I shouldn't be doing this,
but please understand just this once.
I get why you have to do this,
but it's time you made up your mind.
Whether you'll stay a professor or go back to being a detective.
Darn it.
Hey, you've been asleep for way too long.
Actually, never mind. Just sleep.
I'll work round the clock...
and make sure I catch the jerk who did this to you,
so just sleep and rest up.
To tell you the truth,
I was starting to be attached to the school.
It's fun to watch those clueless youngsters.
"I used to be like that too."
It makes me a little emotional at times.
But I promised that I'd always protect you.
That's why I'm here again.
What I'm saying is...
Don't sleep for too long.
What am I doing now? He's asleep and can't hear me.
Gosh.
(Get lost, Oh Kang Hee! Criminal's daughter!)
(Drop out!)
This is insane.
This crazy little piece of...
Who did this?
What?
Gosh, what was that?
(Get lost, Oh Kang Hee!)
(Criminal's daughter! Drop out!)
(Criminal's blood is flowing in you!)
Gosh, this still looks so messy.
(Bookstore, Convenience Store, Stationery Store)
Hey.
Chul Jin got injured a few days ago,
so I wasn't in my right mind.
I'm the one who needs to catch them.
What I'm trying to say is...
Just forget what I said that day.
Bye, I'm off.
Unbelievable, right?
She always acted like she was better than everyone else.
Is she seriously not going to drop out?
She wants to hold out because she has no shame.
Like mother, like daughter.
If she becomes a cop and her mother gets arrested,
will she just let her off?
No, I won't.
Even if she's my mom, she needs to pay for what she did.
And if you've got things to say to me, say it to my face...
instead of doing it behind my back like a bunch of rats.
Hey, watch what you say.
You're one to talk.
Your mom is a gambling addict.
No wonder you turned out like this.
Let's go, girls.
- Hello. - Hi.
(Leadership Room)
Oh, Ms. Baek.
You need to see this on our website.
Why? What is it?
Hey, look. Oh Kang Hee is really something.
- What? - What's going on?
She must really be out of her mind.
- Hey, look. - What?
Check this out.
Kang Hee must be so upset.
What do we do, Sun Ho?
What's going on?
My daughter tells me she wants to die before me.
You little witch.
(Did you know? Oh Kang Hee's mother...)
(was convicted four times for illegal gambling.)
(They say children are a reflection of their parents.)
(If Oh Kang Hee becomes a police officer,)
(it'll only tarnish the public's trust in the police.)
(Did you know? Oh Kang Hee's mother...)
I don't want you in my life!
When was this posted?
Where is Kang Hee?
[VIU Ver] KBS E04 'Police University'
"No Hard Evidence"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
I hope it helps you cool down.
(Get lost! Drop out!)
Do I make you uncomfortable?
No.
Yes.
Because of my mistake during the Chungram Training.
By doing that,
you're robbing me of the opportunity to solve the problem...
on my own.
It's not easy to befriend someone who humiliated you in the past.
I said that because of my mom.
Whenever I had an exam, she somehow got the correct answers...
and made me memorize all of them.
She told me to memorize the answers instead of learning to solve them.
So later on, I got to a point where I knew the answers right away...
without understanding why they were the correct answers.
Another family where the mom's the problem.
What?
Hey, isn't this our first time...
having such a long conversation since becoming roomies?
Well, people make friends even during wartime.
Oh, they get things done fast.
Did you see this?
(Freshman Oh's shocking secret)
(This post has been deleted.)
("Criminal Investigation")
(Korean National Police University, Oh Kang Hee)
Hey, Kang Sun Ho.
By the way, how did you know?
Who else would do that, if not you?
Why? Do you hate it?
A little.
It's so childish,
but kind of sweet at the same time.
Oh, have you thought about Professor Kwon Hyuk Pil's question?
Do you know your answer?
Not yet.
During the class that day,
you said that we should protect everyone when we can...
since we're police officers.
I felt a little guilty when I heard that.
When I was a junior in high school,
my mom's trial was held.
The prosecutor asked me to stand in court as a witness.
So I testified...
that it was my mom who did all that.
The people she was involved in the crime with...
hired lawyers.
But my mom was poor,
so I was afraid she was going to take all the blame.
That's why I testified.
I told the judge that they were all in it together.
That my mom was involved in it too.
I only said that to protect my mom,
but I think I only protected my mom,
not others.
Hey. Please do this for us.
A guy like me will never be able to make that kind of money.
But you can.
Please forgive them just this once.
I plead you, Detectives.
Help me.
Chul Jin got injured a few days ago,
so I wasn't in my right mind.
That must have been...
the best option you had back then.
And I don't think...
that's wrong.
Let's go. We need to get ready for the evening-roll-call.
Why don't you go ahead first? I need to stop by somewhere.
Where?
Yes.
It'll take me about ten minutes, so please wait for me.
(Do Not Enter, Police Line)
(Kim Dong Woon, South Chungcheong 90J 1398)
All right.
(Professor's Office)
Professor Yu, I have something to...
Later.
What are you doing?
I need to ask you now, not later.
Get out! Get off now!
I said, I have something to ask you!
Darn it. I'm not responsible for this.
Professor Yu.
I heard you met all the truck drivers within a week.
Yes.
This is where they park their trucks,
so you must've met a lot of them.
I can't believe you actually met all of them.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I'll check as soon as I can and return it to you.
It rained a lot that night,
so I'm not sure what got caught on my dashcam.
Goodness. The road there isn't paved,
so it was all muddy.
When it rains, the truck gets messy.
What are you doing?
It's 8:57pm, 14 seconds.
It's 8:57pm, 34 seconds.
It's a gray sedan.
What's the number? Four seven...
What's the last one?
Isn't that 41?
What?
Hey, it's me.
I'll send you a file, so can you analyze the video...
and get me the car model and its plate number?
Okay.
Where are we going again?
Aren't we going back to school?
Where did he go?
It's almost time for the evening-roll-call.
What's all this?
(Kang Sun Ho)
(According to the constitution...)
(The Miranda Rule)
"The Miranda Rule"?
Don't you know that I'll get a penalty for AWOL?
So why did you have to follow me? I'm so busy.
(Provincial Police Agency)
Are we going to a police station right now?
Yes.
Why?
I smell something fishy.
If you want to go up, just go. Why are you waiting here?
Be quiet.
Hey, Detective Lee. You gained some weight.
I guess you're only working from the desk.
- Gosh. - My goodness.
Hey, Detective Kim.
I saw that you changed your car.
Don't get any bribes.
I'm watching you.
I bought it on a five-year installment plan.
Don't shoot your mouth off.
I was just kidding. See you.
Hello, sir.
Hey, Senior Inspector Yu.
I heard you were going to appoint me somewhere else again.
Thank you.
But Captain Choi isn't the type to do that.
Right.
It's not Captain Choi who asked me.
I thought it'd be a waste to let you go.
I didn't want a competent officer like you to be stuck at school.
Oh, I see.
Anyway, what are you doing here?
Oh, my colleague got hurt,
so I came to pick up his stuff.
Oh, you mean Inspector Park Chul Jin?
- Yes. - I see.
They got the real culprit.
They're investigating him now.
They caught him?
Oh, right.
I mixed it up with the Seongsu-dong theft case.
Oh...
Gosh, how could you mix that up?
I know, right? Good night, then.
- Okay. See you. - Bye.
- Hey, let's get going. - Sorry?
Chief Han.
What's this about? Why are we here?
Didn't you see him earlier?
His face when I told him that the real culprit was caught.
I can tell who's guilty.
They can't hide their feelings in that instant.
But I only got circumstantial proof. I have no evidence.
- Gosh. - What are you going to do?
Well, we'll have to wait until Chul Jin wakes up.
Darn it.
What did you want to ask me?
Oh, I'll ask you later.
Is Chul Jin okay though?
I was really desperate when I had to get the money...
for my dad's hospital fees.
It looks like Professor Yu is desperate too.
So please wake up soon.
Oh, right.
You said you wanted to ask me something.
Are you not going to ask me?
I think I heard my answer.
What?
Why did you help the drunk in the emergency center?
What do you mean?
"We need to protect criminals too. They have rights too."
Is that what you believe in?
Beliefs aren't important. I just follow my instincts.
Why make it so complicated and question everything?
I don't have such beliefs.
It's simple. Protect them and catch them. Got it?
If you want to do that, you'll need to work out.
How can a weak man like you protect or catch anyone?
- Go away. - Hey!
Guys, do you want to win that girl's heart?
- Of course! - Of course!
- Here I go! - Bring it on!
(Leave your judo club application here.)
You have time to take care of your skin?
We haven't received a single application!
(New members wanted)
Just wait until you get to my age.
Sunspots scare me more than getting zero applications.
You can't see them now, but they'll become visible later on.
You pulled a bait-and-switch on me when I was a freshman,
so I still have to put up with this.
What? "Bait-and-switch"? What do you mean?
You said this would be the highlight of my campus life.
Where are the boys?
I hate you!
What if they decide to get rid of the club?
Gosh, this is crazy.
We'd like to join the judo club.
Here come the boys.
Welcome.
I'll teach you the breakfall technique...
to see if you're qualified.
Wait, there's a test?
Here I come!
Now that you've joined the judo club...
and will be learning from me,
you'll become the toughest cookies in the entire school!
Maybe it'd be easier to just drop dead.
Then she's mine.
Professor.
I want to try one more time. Here I come!
- I'm sorry. - He doesn't know it yet,
but I joined the PR club too.
- All right! - Eon Ju is a member.
I can handle two clubs.
No! I will try one more time.
- I won. - I'm okay!
Bum Tae can't beat me.
Look at that!
- My goodness. - I'm okay.
- Oh, right. - It hurts.
- I sent you those photos. - No, I want to try again.
I'm okay!
Jun Wook.
You call yourself Mr. Popular.
Everyone would agree.
- Right, sure. - That's right.
Can you send me the photos of everyone...
who tagged "Korean National Police University"...
on Monday night?
- Okay. - Thanks.
No problem.
(Kim Ba Da, Korean National Police University)
It was posted on Monday at 9:30pm.
And the person who posted it used the Wi-Fi...
in the lobby at the dorm.
What?
Hey, did you hear?
They caught the person who posted the video...
of Kang Hee's mother.
What?
So it was you.
What a nasty girl you are.
Everyone.
My daughter tells me she wants to die before me.
Why did you do that?
Darn it.
Then I'll go show this to Ms. Baek.
I did it to join the student council.
Darn it.
There are only two seats available on the council.
But they look at your grades, so I can only join if she gives up.
You did that because of something so petty?
"Petty"? Don't you know that the former council members...
have it easy even after joining the force?
If you want to "have it easy" as a police officer,
you should just quit now, you idiot.
You're not going to tell anyone, right?
Go to the student council's office and withdraw your application,
- Darn it. - or you'll be...
too embarrassed to stay in school.
Hold on.
How did you know it was me?
That look on your face.
I can tell who's guilty.
They can't hide their feelings in that instant.
Oh Kang Hee's grades are much better,
but with all those talks about her, we shouldn't let her in.
Totally.
She'll destroy the council's reputation.
We absolutely cannot accept her. There's no way...
Oh, she's here.
I'd like my application back.
Okay, here.
Wait.
Why?
I've decided to withdraw my application,
so you can't disqualify me...
for such unfair, ridiculous reasons.
Can I have my application back?
Here.
(Professor Yu Dong Man)
(Here's the video analysis result.)
(Here's the video analysis result, 384N 4178)
Hello?
What? He woke up?
How is he?
(Parking Reserved for Professors Only)
(Dormitory Rules)
I heard you joined the judo club.
Yes, I want to build strength.
Did you get into the student council?
No, I applied to join the PR club.
I'm a total newsmaker.
Who else would join the PR club if I don't?
So many freshmen will apply next year...
if you do the promotion.
I'll make sure it's more competitive than ever.
It's Professor Kwon's class.
That's it for today's class.
May I...
answer the question you asked me last time?
The answer had better be worthy of my time.
I stumbled upon a book in the library.
It was a book about Miranda...
of the Miranda Rule.
Ernesto Miranda was a serial rapist.
He confessed to his rape charges during a police interrogation,
but the court ruled his confession inadmissible...
because he had not been informed...
of his rights to remain silent and to consult with an attorney,
so he ended up being released on parole.
Ultimately, this verdict...
set an example that justice can only be truly realized...
through lawful means.
However, there are still many controversies...
surrounding this decision.
Personally, I don't agree with the verdict.
The rights of someone who kidnapped and raped an 18-year-old girl...
are not important.
But perhaps by following the rules...
and accepting everyone's rights,
we can protect...
those who truly need to be protected from such criminals.
So my answer to your question...
remains the same.
Be it an innocent civilian...
or a criminal.
I believe that everyone should be protected,
within the frame of laws...
and rules we must follow.
Because we're members of the police...
and a law enforcement agency.
The verdict wasn't made to protect Miranda.
The officer who caused an accident and led the criminal to die...
didn't get dismissed and punished because the criminal was innocent.
We shouldn't let our emotions do the judging.
We should leave it to the law.
Understanding the world through the law...
is the legal mind you must learn...
in the first class of the Constitutional Law course.
Kang Sun Ho.
Well done.
Wow!
Good job, Sun Ho.
(Hangang Medical Center)
I didn't know bananas were this good.
My gosh.
Chul Jin!
Hey, my head! I can't breathe!
Hey! Are you okay?
You punk. You made me worry.
Why didn't you worry about me when this didn't happen?
Look at him. He's back.
- He's back, Captain. - Dong Man.
Oh, right. You remember the jerks who did this to you, right?
What?
- Dong Man. - Oh, it must've been a big shock.
Then do you remember the phone call we had?
You said it has something to do with the Police University.
- What? - What?
What's wrong with him?
It's dissociative amnesia.
He's mentally shocked.
It looks like a whole part of his memory has been erased.
We'll need to wait and see if his memory returns.
Let's wait and see.
What do you mean?
You expect me to believe that?
You saw how fine he was.
What? Wait, Doctor!
Shouldn't we do an MRI scan again?
Hey.
It's possible to temporarily lose some memory...
when you're in shock.
No, that's not possible. That can't happen.
We can't catch those jerks if he doesn't remember!
(Yu Dong Man)
(Professor's Office)
(384N 4178)
(Here's the video analysis result.)
It's 4178.
Wait a minute.
Wait. Hold on!
Professor Yu!
- Excuse me! - Professor Yu!
Stop right there! Wait!
- Hey! - Professor Yu!
Stop right there! Hey!
Stop!
(Korean National Police University)
Hey, you punk!
Professor Yu!
I said, stop!
It's a gray sedan.
When it rains, the truck gets messy.
This is my last piece of advice...
to a loser like you in a polite manner.
Leave without causing any trouble.
Wait!
(Korean National Police University)
Hey! Darn it...
What? What are you doing here?
You asked for my help.
Do you still need my help?
What did you say, you punk?
You asked me to help you to catch those jerks.
Do you still need my help?
I feel like I can...
protect the hurt...
and catch the bad guys when I'm with you.
A way to protect my people.
The right way to protect them.
Not as Hacker Yoon but as a student of this school,
can I find the right way...
as I work with you?
(Korean National Police University)
(Police University)
This is all the material I collected...
while chasing the illegal gambling gang.
I'll come back in a month.
These are the culprit's footprints. They're 285mm.
Could it be Professor Kwon Hyuk Pil?
I can feel the stare. But hands are faster than eyes.
- I saw everything. - From where?
The moment you inserted that wire in the window.
That sly punk.
Let's go. I'm going to catch him no matter what.
What was that? You look like you saw a puppy.
If he looks cute to you, then you're already into him.
Hey, don't smile with teeth.
If a student here makes physical contact...
to show a sexual appeal,
they will be expelled instantly.
Oh Kang Hee, you're expelled!