♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
♪Moonlight flows in the night♪
♪Between poems and songs♪
♪It's my obsession♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
=My Queen=
=Episode 13=
(Who will be my close disciple?)
(Secret Chamber of Jing Yue Sect in Phantom Land)
(This trial will end if)
(one of you four dies.)
Zhe Xiang,
I'm the worst one of us.
They will definitely kill me.
Don't worry.
I will protect you.
I will get you out of here alive.
Why?
Sorry, senior.
Don't blame me.
I just want to be alive.
I, Zhe Xiang, from now on,
will never believe in
sisterhood anymore.
I promised that
I would get you out of here alive.
My lovely disciple,
you seem to have killed more than one.
One more useless person
is too many as well.
You're right.
I change my mind now.
I only want one disciple.
Go
and kill her for me.
Senior,
I just want to be alive.
Don't kill me. No!
Going through this kind of pain
once is enough for me.
I can't do it.
Xiao Ai.
Zhe Xiang.
I can't do it.
Wake up!
Zhe Xiang.
I can't do it.
Put it down.
Wake up!
I can't stand it anymore
if you don't wake up.
- I can't do it.
- Zhe Xiang.
Zhe Xiang.
Jiang Mengmeng, are you crazy?
You finally woke up.
Blood. Blood. Blood.
Thank you.
Why do I always get hurt?
Help! Help!
What's that sound?
Is it Song Che?
Let's go.
What is this guy doing here?
Song Che.
General, please wake up!
We have lost the battle.
We have to run.
Run?
Tell me.
Where should I run to?
Go away.
Mengmeng,
why are you with him?
Who else would I be with?
You want me to be with you,
who lost the battle?
It's been eight years.
Big and small battles
for over 50 times.
I've got fellow soldiers dying
next to me.
There were enemies as well.
I felt scared every day.
When I felt scared, I thought of my mom
and you.
I thought of
the days before we were 12 years old.
Mengmeng,
tell me,
why am I not as good as him?
Why am I not as good as him?
Tell me. Tell me.
Murong Chen is the 5th prince of
Cang Yun Kingdom.
He has a noble identity,
and he is handsome and rich too.
He is much, much better than you.
Look at you, Song Che.
You look so poor.
How can you compete with me?
And you dare to take Mengmeng from me?
I despise you.
Hit me. Come here. Come here.
Come and hit me.
Help!
Help! Help!
What's that sound?
Help!
I punch you.
Mengmeng.
What?
What? What happened?
Why is my face hurting so much?
You just lost a fight with Zhe Xiang.
Then, you went crazy.
You kept slapping yourself.
I lost the fight to her?
That's impossible!
My...
Where is my sword?
My sword?
There it is.
Let me go!
How did you get hurt?
Just small wound.
Why didn't you tell me?
I cut my hand on a branch.
And the wound was already bandaged
by Zhe Xiang.
How could I lose the fight to her?
It is impossible.
By the way,
where are Chang Kong and Xiao Ai?
Yeah...
I wish we could always be here.
That would be nice.
Yes, I like here.
If His Highness is here as well,
that would be nice.
If Her Highness is here,
Well,
we have to find the
5th prince and 9th princess.
By the way,
as for what happened just now,
please don't let others know.
OK.
Let's just pretend this never happened,
OK?
Your Highness.
Xiao Ai.
Are you OK?
- Yes.
Are you really OK?
- Yes, really.
OK, then.
The fog has lifted anyway.
Let's get out of here.
Yes. Let's go.
Let's go.
Let me go.
What are you doing?
It can't be true.
How could I possibly lose to her?
There was no way I lost to her.
Where is my scabbard?
Is anybody home?
It's safe.
Finally, I can enjoy a good sleep.
We can only stay here for the night.
Sorry to let you put up with it,
Your Highness.
Yes.
Your Highness,
you have to put up with it for a while.
When we arrive at Cang Yun Kingdom,
you won't have to
suffer with us anymore.
Mengmeng, he hit me.
Xiao Ai, he hit me.
Your Highness,
I'll go in and prepare a bed for you.
Mengmeng.
Why don't you two share a bed?
Again?
Who wants to
sleep in the same bed with you?
I don't want to
sleep in the same bed with you, either.
Sharing the bed with her
is better than...
I don't want to share
the bed with you, either.
Now that I know everything,
it's time to put an end to it.
Why do you have to do this every time?
Always by hurting yourself.
You don't care about
your life?
Sure enough, you are here.
Tell me,
why did you always
show up when my life was in danger?
Even if I didn't launch Tian Ji Token
or ask for help,
you knew exactly where I was.
The first time we met,
why were you in Ruo Shui Kingdom?
I just...
Just happened to walk by
and saved my life, right?
How about the second time?
How about the third time?
The palace was strongly guarded.
Even if you are a great warrior,
how could you just
come and go so freely?
(Does she know everything?)
When I was in Ruo Shui Kingdom,
you were there as well.
Then, when I'm walking around the world,
you too.
I thought it was the storyline that
kept you showing up again and again.
Now, I realized
you were always with me.
Mengmeng,
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to lie to you.
A Mu.
The first time we met,
you asked if I knew about Liang City.
You also said I look like
an old friend of yours.
At that time, I didn't know
where Liang City was.
I didn't know
I am the old friend you mentioned.
I didn't know it was not encounter,
but our reunion.
I didn't know
you've been with me all the way,
and protected me quietly.
You've been by my side all the time.
I didn't even know
your cold poison was because of me.
I took the liberty of
finding the blood night-blooming cereus
to make a deal with you.
I'm sorry.
♪Of all the waters♪
Don't be too sad.
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
I never blamed you for anything.
♪Of all the waters♪
So many things have
happened over these years.
Uncle Qi passed away.
You are the Master of
Tian Ji Pavilion now.
Before Uncle Qi died,
he was so worried about you and me.
We are now very good.
In the heaven, Uncle Qi
will feel happy.
By the way,
that she-devil,
did she ever come to you?
After Uncle Qi passed
me the Tian Ji Token,
I transferred all the activities of
Tian Ji Pavilion to underground.
Tian Ji Pavilion is
an intelligence-gathering organization.
Acting in a diametrically opposite way
and hiding.
But to the outside world,
Tian Ji Pavilion disappeared
ten years ago.
These years must have been hard for you.
Uncle Qi saved my life.
This is what I should do.
I have made a decision.
What decision?
You have your own responsibilities.
I have mine too.
I promise you
I will find blood night-blooming cereus
and cure your cold poison.
In this way, you don't have to
worry about that she-devil anymore.
You can live under the sunshine again.
By the way, A Mu.
Fine,
I call you Yun Ya.
Over these years,
you have been wearing
a mask all the time.
No one has ever seen
how you really look like?
Actually, the first time I met you,
I almost took your mask off.
Now I realized
it was lucky that I didn't do that.
Why?
Think about
how dangerous you are now.
If one more person knows
who you really are,
you would be even more dangerous.
If it were you,
it would be fine.
Me?
If you really want to have a look.
Your Highness.
Chang Kong?
Chang Kong,
what are you doing here?
I accompanied His Highness
to take a leak.
I found that you were missing.
Then, I came here to look for you.
I came here for that too.
By the way, where is Murong Chen?
His Highness is waiting for me
somewhere else.
Your Highness, shall we go back?
OK.
Then, let's go back.
Why did you stop me?
Chang Kong acts on my own way.
Your Highness, please punish me.
You...
9th princess has got her memory back.
She wants to get the blood
night-blooming cereus to save Yun Ya.
This is in line with our plan.
But if Your Highness
tells the truth now...
You're afraid that
I'll break up with the 9th princess.
She won't help me open the
blood night-blooming cereus.
I just don't want Your Highness
to ruin the final plan
just for the sake of love.
I lied to her over and over again.
But she took me so sincerely.
- I...
- Your Highness,
it is the last step.
Your Highness, why not
get along with the 9th princess,
just like you used to do?
After we find the
blood night-blooming cereus
and the big picture is decided,
it won't be too late
to tell her the truth then.
Your Highness.
(When I hugged Yun Ya,)
(why didn't my heart beat faster?)
(No. No.)
(We have such deep connection.)
(My hero must be him.)
(It has to be him.)
No way...
No. No. No.
No what?
(I must have been shocked by him.)
Murong Chen,
in the middle of the night,
what are you doing out here,
scaring others?
I didn't mean to scare you.
I'm here, waiting for you.
When you got back,
who knows what you were thinking,
you just walked right into me.
Oh, it hurts.
You said you were waiting for me.
Why?
Since you're OK,
I'm good too.
There is something.
Murong Chen,
what I am going to say is very serious.
Absolutely not joking.
I admit I did have a crush on you.
Really?
But that's as far as it goes.
All the time,
I think I'm just playing a game.
The storyline is a game.
The emotions are games too.
You know,
the men who are
inside and outside the palace,
I have checked them all.
They are all excluded by me.
So,
I am also excluded,
right?
I know what I said
does not sound good to you.
But if I don't tell you right now,
I think it will be not
good to you even more.
I've been
only caring about my own happiness.
I never thought
what I did would make other people sad.
So for this,
I want to apologize.
I'm sorry.
About what you just said,
I feel really happy.
But I have a question.
Just ask.
Why is he,
the one you like?
Actually, I don't know why it is him.
But I just know that
he is the reason why I don't
want to pick anyone else.
I can understand.
Now that we're both clear,
we're going our separate ways.
You won't send me to Cang Yun Kingdom?
Of course, I will.
I will send you to...
But...
You really don't want to see me?
What about what you said before?
"Merry meet, merry part"?
No. No. No.
I didn't mean that.
I mean
I have something else to deal with.
It's also because of him?
Do you remember that
we went to find the
blood night-blooming cereus?
Wait a minute.
(Egret Villa)
This.
Wait a minute.
(Egret Villa)
Since we want the same thing.
How about...
OK, this is a deal.
We are only teammates looking for
the blood night-blooming cereus.
Nothing else.
Only teammates.
Then, our next target is
Egret Villa.
Put out the fire!
Help put out the fire!
There's a fire. Somebody, please help.
Quickly. Quickly. Put out the fire.
(Cereus Villa)
What happened? What happened?
Help! Someone, please help!
Come and put out the fire.
(Liang City to Egret Villa)
(Egret Villa)
Wow, big mansion.
Yes, it is.
I thought
only Ruo Shui Palace has
such kind of big mansion.
The landlord must be somebody.
Well, you haven't seen
the buildings of our Cang Yun Kingdom.
This kind of mansion
is so normal there.
Then tell me,
if Cang Yun Kingdom is
so strong and rich,
why did you come to
Ruo Shui Kingdom for blind date?
You...
(Lu Feibai)
I'm not aware of your visit.
I didn't come to welcome you.
Please forgive me, three ladies.
La...
Who said we are ladies?
Such beautiful ladies.
You can't be men.
Moreover,
this lady looks familiar.
Maybe we have met each other
before somewhere.
Such a bad move!
Landlord, you are eagle-eyed.
You called me "landlord".
That's not close enough.
I'm Lu Feibai.
I'm a business man.
Ladies can call me Childe Lu.
If you don't mind,
you can call me Brother Lu.
Brother Lu...
Please call me Landlord Lu.
You are such a...
I...
Childe Lu,
I haven't had a chance
to introduce myself.
You can call me Jiang Mengmeng.
They are my companions in the journey.
We are passing through.
I am just wondering
if we can spend the night here.
Yes, of course, you can.
No matter how many nights
Mengmeng wants to stay here,
I will be fine with it.
Please.
Let's go.
- See...
- Mengmeng.
See that?
You...
If you want to stay, just stay here.
I won't stay here.
Let's go, Song Che.
Red coral.
Gold and silver vessels.
This is...
Childe Lu,
you have more treasures
than my 8th brother.
Do you have mineral
resources related business?
If you like them, just take them.
Wow,
that's so generous of you.
They're all fake.
That's why he is so generous.
Murong Chen, be polite.
Childe Murong is eagle-eyed.
No way!
Fake?
Let's see.
This luminous pearl.
It should be with pearl powder varnish.
Fake!
This coral
is dyed with red paint.
This golden vase is
plated with copper.
How about this one?
For this one,
the rubies on it are made of glass.
Take it. It's a toy.
Glass?
What Childe Murong said
is true.
They're all fake.
Oh, I know.
He is a counterfeiter
specializing in selling fake goods.
Mengmeng,
you have wronged me.
The "treasures" I have here
are all fake,
but the goods are real.
Childe Murong has a bright eye.
Your family must be grand and rich.
Everything in your house must be
made of gold, jade and precious stones.
That's true.
Everything in my house is real.
Have you ever thought about this?
If an ordinary family
wants to buy something decent,
they can't afford a real one
within their life time.
So you're selling these goods
to ordinary people?
Yes.
They just can't
afford to buy a real one.
So they buy a fake one
to be self-deceiving
and satisfy their own vanity.
Poor people don't deserve it!
OK?
Childe Murong, you're wrong.
Everyone is fond of beautiful things.
They are not rich,
so they should have nothing
but food and clothing
instead of quality of life?
Maybe you think these goods are
worthless.
To an ordinary person,
they have no need to collect treasury
and maintain their value.
But as long as it makes their life
more colorful,
that's the greatest value to them.
You're so right!
Compared with very few
upper-class rich people,
most of the people
are from normal families.
They represent the
vast majority of people in this world.
It's a huge market,
with huge potential.
But businessmen often overlook
this market.
They think that ordinary people
have no demand for luxury goods.
You're right.
This is called "light luxury".
Light luxury?
Xiao Ai can't understand.
But I can feel it seems
pretty good.
Childe Lu,
you really have extraordinary
talent in business,
and you are also commercially minded.
You even have humanistic concern.
You are handsome as well.
You're a great businessman.
Thank you, Mengmeng.
Then, can you
please tell me about
how these,
these, and these
goods are produced?
Look, this one...
- Oh no.
- Don't stop him. Don't stop him.
- Calm down.
- Don't stop him.
That's amazing! You are so brilliant.
By the way,
Landlord Lu,
why did you build such a mansion
in a place where a family
was slaughtered?
♪With the singing of girls,
I passed the South♪
♪The scenery has come into my painting♪
♪Who would understand
my unrestrained affection♪
♪But as time goes by♪
♪I know she is my only one♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪