You're watching amc's the walking dead.
All new episodes premiere
Sunday nights at 9.
And check out these other amc series:
Fear the walking dead,
Washington's spies,
and into the badlands.
Only on amc.
They need our help.
You are staying here.
Damn it, Maggie, let's go!
Not until it's done.
- Stop!
- Or she's dead.
Guns, knives on the ground
right now.
Nice jacket.
For a murderous bitch.
Well, we'll take it off her
before we shoot her.
It ain't on there right,
I can feel it. It ain't stopping.
I'm getting it tighter.
Jesus, give me a second.
Son of a bitch, you're cutting
off my circulation.
Well, sport, it's supposed to.
Hell was that?
It's primo.
Damn it, they've got him.
Give me the walkie.
Babe, what's happening?
Lower your gun, prick.
You, with the Colt python.
All of you, lower your
weapons right now.
Come on out. Let's talk.
How many we got?
Eight in sight.
Too many.
No, we can take 'em. We took more.
We're not coming out,
but we will talk.
Names.
Names!
I'm Maggie, she's Carol.
We've got a Carol
and a Maggie.
I'm thinking that's something
you want to chat about.
Now, we're gonna work this out
right now,
and it's going to go our way.
You can see we have one of yours.
We'll trade.
I'm listening.
First I want to talk to
Maggie and Carol,
make sure they're all right.
I'm gonna put you on.
You say you're fine.
I'll know if you try anything else.
Rick, it's Carol.
- I'm... I'm fine, but...
- now you.
Rick, it's Maggie. We're both okay.
- We'll figure thi...
- shut up.
You have your proof. Let's talk.
Alright this is the deal
right here.
Let 'em go, you can have
your guy back and live.
Two for one,
that's not much of a trade.
You don't have another choice
or you would've done
something about it already.
We have to get him back.
Primo can take care of himself.
He can patch me up.
I need him, thanks to that bitch.
You lost your balls, Paula.
You should've shot her in the
head so they could hear her die.
If you could just shut up,
I'll solve this.
Then make the deal or we go in.
She said shut up, so shut it.
You should be glad she doesn't have
a sack of gonads to trip over.
Look, I know you're
talking it over.
It's a fair trade.
Just come out, we do this,
we all walk away.
Smug prick.
He must think we're stupid.
That's a good thing.
Do we have a deal?
I'll get back to you.
Move!
Turn.
Wait.
Omega, omega, saviors down.
Go to gamma, code "fire."
Alpha channel is not clear.
We follow the protocol.
Where the hell are you guys?
Out west of the...
15 mi... on... way.
We're headed to the break point.
Switch to theta channel,
same code.
If I'm not there,
toggle to Alpha, listen in.
Copy that.
I hate this damn place.
Safe house.
There ain't nothing safe about it.
This place is gonna save our asses.
Get on the ground.
You there.
You, over there.
You're wondering if
there's a way out of this.
There isn't. Not unless I say so.
Paula, I need backup!
I want to kill you both right now.
It's taking all I have not to,
so go ahead, I dare you,
try something.
Just see what happens.
When's the last time
anyone checked this place?
It was fine a month ago.
Sweetie, that was a month ago.
Shit hards quick.
The guns have gone bye bye,
the food's gone bye bye,
and we got growlers
up and down the halls.
Means people can get through, too.
- Maybe we should get gone.
- Carol!
- Yeah, Where the hell to?
- Nowhere.
Got dead in the halls?
Free security.
Those assholes get here
before our people,
the cold bloods will
buy us some time.
Shut up.
Jesus, it's bleeding.
It's not supposed to keep bleeding.
- Molly, give me the rope.
- I'm not losing it.
- I'm not.
- So you grind it out. Jesus, Donnie.
Screw you, 'chelle!
We have to get him back.
He can fix it.
- We have to, Paula.
- No.
I saw them, you didn't.
They took the place down,
they got the guns,
they'll kill us, too.
Hey!
I'm not going down like that,
not after making it this far.
Hey!
What?
She's hyperventilating.
Somebody needs to take her gag off.
She's a nervous little bird,
ain't she?
Look at you.
Bitch how did you make it this far?
Honey, you need to take some yoga
breaths and calm your ass down.
I can't...
Oh.
You're one of those.
What are you so afraid of?
Are you actually afraid to die?
All this and you're scared of
getting your ticket punched.
It doesn't matter what happens to me.
Just don't hurt Maggie.
Don't hurt the baby.
Yeah, right.
She got a bun in the oven,
she doesn't look it.
I'm only two months, i think.
You're some kind of stupid,
getting knocked up
at a time like this.
You think that's funny?
When was it ever smart
to get knocked up?
Women used to just die in childbirth.
And they always thought
the world was gonna end.
Living through it, why would
you just give up?
But are you gonna live through it?
Anyway, that's cute.
Babies are the point.
Children are our future.
Making bite size snacks for the dead.
The point is to stay standing.
No.
Walkers do that.
I'm choosing something.
That's right.
You are.
You did.
The baby.
Honey, in case you haven't noticed,
you've got bigger problems
than a little secondhand smoke.
Molls.
Y'all are worse than a bunch
of Evangelical second graders.
Those things'll kill you.
They already have.
I'm a dead woman walking.
Which puts us in exactly
the same boat.
Ah!
My arm feels like it's on fire.
You pull that off,
you gonna be nothing but a spigot.
- Okay, hold on.
- Agh!
Scout crew is coming.
They're 30 minutes out, maybe less.
He doesn't have 30 minutes.
His nerves are dying.
If he doesn't get medical help,
he's gonna lose his arm,
maybe his life.
I'm not a doctor, but my dad lost
his leg, and I know that much.
Your man, primo, you think
he can help you?
It's time to end this.
Talk to Rick.
30 minutes.
You know my problem?
She did this to me.
She did it and she's just
sitting there
right as rain, fully intact.
- Hey.
- No, you're not gonna make the trade.
And we just do 'em both now.
No, we wait for the others.
We have to be smart.
We need insurance.
Then shoot her in the arm, too.
No.
You really gonna stick up for
some gutless bitch over me?
- God damn it!
- Shut up.
Don't push me, Paula.
Shut up!
Leave her alone!
No! No!
You dumb, uppity bitch!
You really are some kind of stupid.
Take her out.
See if she knows anything.
Should've done that before.
Move.
You got nice clothes,
time to make babies.
You're holed up somewhere good.
Tell me where.
Don't draw this out, bitch.
Just tell me where.
Help yourself and
the baby in your belly.
The way you stay alive
is you produce for us.
You're not the good guys.
You should know that.
He got you good, kid.
He's in pain.
Guys can't handle pain.
Excuse me?
Just wanted to say thank you
for helping Maggie,
for helping me.
My husband ed, he used to...
yeah? I don't care if your old man
used to ring your bell.
I see exactly who you are, Carol.
I know.
You're pathetic.
You wanna think we're just the same?
Go ahead.
You're wrong.
He's just a warm body for my bed.
That's it. I could kill him
in his sleep.
Do you really believe in that crap?
My faith got me through
the death of my daughter.
Hmm.
Well, the good news is maybe
you'll see her again soon.
What happened?
I stole something. Got caught.
What?
Gas, from this place.
- Why?
- To get a new car.
Look for my boyfriend's body.
Did you find him?
He was blown up.
Not much to find.
"Frankie."
- Was that his name?
- Hell, no.
I barely knew him.
He was a dick.
Frank was my dad.
And that's what I was gonna
name the baby.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
You aren't.
I'm not planning to die today.
Yeah, me neither.
Thing is, one of us is wrong.
Just tell me where.
Have you thought about it?
Talk to me.
You weren't listening.
I said I'd contact you.
Would it make a difference
if I said I was sorry about that?
What do you think?
I think we're gonna make the trade,
so tell me where.
We haven't agreed to that.
You will.
You know what? I'm not so sure.
We'd be taking most of the risk,
not getting much in
the way of a reward.
The other option
won't work out for you.
We'll take our chances.
You don't have to do this.
You don't have to fight.
Your people killed all of my people.
Of course we gotta fight.
- We didn't want to.
- But you did.
So tell me why.
Your people ambushed
my people on the road,
tried to take everything we had.
They were gonna kill them.
Well, damn.
So now we know what happened to T's group.
Those idiots.
Probably put on a big show.
Okay, fair play.
You were just defending yourselves.
But, see, your people killed
them on the road, right?
Blew them to pieces.
So, why not stop?
They said they were
working for Negan.
And what do you think
you know about Negan?
He sounded like a maniac.
We were scared.
We had to stop him.
Sweetie, sweetie.
We are all Negan.
What do you mean?
What does that mean?
Can I have one?
Well, look at you, little bird.
I didn't think you approved.
I don't.
You are weak.
What are you so afraid of?
So scared, you can't even
stick to your own principles.
You don't want me to stick
to my own principles.
I was a secretary before.
I fetched coffee for my boss
and made him feel good about himself.
I spent most of my days reading
stupid inspirational emails
to try and feel good about myself.
There was this one
that kept going around.
A young woman was
having a hard time
and told her mom
she wanted to give up,
so her mom went to the kitchen
and started boiling
three pots of water.
She put a carrot in one,
an egg in another,
and ground coffee beans
in the last one.
After they had boiled a while,
her mom said,
"look, all three things went
through the same boiling water.
The carrot went in strong
and came out soft.
The egg was fragile
and came out hard.
But the coffee beans
changed the water itself."
You're supposed to want
to be the coffee beans.
See, to me,
coffee was just a thing
that my boss would drink up.
No matter how many times I
refilled his damn cup,
it was just never enough.
I was at work when the
army took over DC.
We weren't allowed to leave.
They had to evacuate all the
important people first...
members of congress,
government employees.
So I was stuck with my boss.
Not my family...
my husband, my four girls...
My boss was weak and stupid
and he was going to die
and he was going
to take me down, too.
He was the first person I killed
so that I could live.
I stopped counting when
I hit double digits.
That's right around the time i
stopped feeling bad about it.
I am not like you.
I'm still me, but better.
I lost everything and
it made me stronger.
You sure about that?
I'm alive.
With those people, those killers.
Your people are killers, Carol.
That makes you a killer.
You... you're the one.
Excuse me?
You're the one who's afraid to die.
And you're going to.
You will die.
It's what's gonna happen
if you don't work this out.
Are you going to kill me?
I hope not.
Asshole, are you there?
I'm here.
We've thought about it.
We want to make the trade.
That's good.
There's a large field with a
sign that says "god is dead"
about two miles down I-66.
Good visibility in all directions.
We'll meet you there.
10 minutes?
10 minutes.
Mm..mm. Now, that was too easy.
Maybe they're just itching
to get their people back.
No, there was no static.
There should've been static.
They're close.
They're probably already here.
We were careful,
but there were tracks.
- There had to be.
- No...
They killed everybody back home.
They have the weapons.
They know what they're doing.
They're probably waiting to kill us
as soon as we walk out those doors.
- That's what we'd do.
- No.
You have to listen to me, please.
Rick is a man of his word.
He wouldn't put me and
Maggie at risk to attack.
Then he's just as stupid as you are.
What's your ETA?
A few minutes away,
- but the car is running on fumes.
- We have gas.
We'll fill you up and then we move.
Radio when you're back
in the perimeter.
Copy that.
We gotta get ready.
Pull 'chelle out so she
doesn't get stuck in a fight.
We have to be ready to
move at any second.
What about the girl?
Leave her for now.
If we leave, we travel light.
And if the pricks are here,
we pick 'em off at the door.
Molls, we need this hall clear.
Just a sec, sugar.
Are you okay?
I have to be.
They've spread out, but I think
we can make it past them.
- We have to try.
- We can't leave them alive.
No, we should just go.
Carol, we have to finish this.
We have to.
He was already dead.
- He's turning.
- We should go.
We need a gun.
Give me that.
Eat shit and die, Donnie!
Where are ya, magnolia?
I wanna bloody up that nice...
agh!
Let's go.
They're using them to keep us in,
keep the others out.
Come on.
We have to find 'em.
Just run.
Shoot her.
Go on, do it.
You've killed Donnie,
you've killed Molly.
Your people have destroyed my home.
- Get outta here.
- Carol.
You have no idea.
The things I've done,
what I've given up,
what I had to do.
- Just run.
- Carol, shoot her.
Go ahead. I've already
lost everything.
Paula?... Paula?
Molly?
You lying bitch!
I'll do it.
You're good.
Nervous little bird.
You were her.
But not now, right?
Me, too.
I told you to run.
If you could do all this,
what were you so afraid of, Carol?
I was afraid of this.
Paula, we're approaching
the perimeter.
Are we a go?
Do you copy?
Meet us on the kill floor.
I think I might have
killed 18 people.
20.
I should've killed Donnie,
too, in the woods.
I had a clear shot. I didn't miss.
None of this would've happened
if I had just killed him.
- Don't think about it.
- I can't stop.
We're almost done.
Careful. The floor's slick.
You sure this is it?
She said kill floor.
Hey, this one's locked.
What the hell?! Agh!
Maggie.
You okay?
We got your trail.
- You start a fire?
- Yeah.
Hey, you good?
No.
Come here.
They're dead. They're all dead,
the ones that took us.
They're all dead.
Hey, are you okay?
I just...
I can't anymore.
It's okay.
Your friends are dead.
No one's coming for ya.
So you might as well talk.
Let him burn.
I'm gonna ask you one last time...
How'd you get the bike?
- We found it.
- Like hell you did.
We found it.
Was Negan in that building last night
or was he here?
Both.
I'm Negan, shithead.
There's a whole world of
fun that we can talk about,
so let's have a chat.
I'm sorry it had to come to this.