no more
How
Han Wang always liked meat
It is my fault
adult
Free at kisskh.me
We also just received the order
Mr. Wang
Even the soldiers of the five cities are dispatched tonight.
Who are you going to take?
counterinsurgency
Come with me
don't keep looking at me
It's hard to eat a piece of meat
What's the fun of being a man
Father, don't forget the business
Winter moon crucian carp with thick meat
Delicious
This road was created by Mr. Yun Lin, a painter of the previous dynasty.
Crucian Carp Belly Soup
Only take two pieces of meat from the belly of the fish
Made with pepper
extra fresh
Unique flavor
Fresh and smooth
melt-in-the-mouth
When I was in the boudoir
My mother often cooks crucian carp soup by herself.
What's up
Hidden set
Let Ziping replace Yuxuan
no
Can not
If we lose to Supervisor Shang Shan tonight
everyone will be punished
Row
Next dish Ding Hu Shang Vegetarian
I know
Needle to Maimang
Bird's Nest vs Snow Fungus
just right
You accompany her to bandage
Okay
go
let's go
go hurry up
hurry up
His Majesty
This dish is based on white fungus and yellow otolithiasis
Made from six ears of fungus, elm and sweet-scented osmanthus
Served with nostoc and bamboo fungus
Fresh lotus seeds and other precious ingredients are boiled together
Rarely made smooth and delicious
again
Fresh and elegant
walk away
not withdraw yet
Yes
no fuss
Just a moment of neglect
prince
I can not wait anymore
when can i see him
Just wait until after the family dinner.
emperor
Wan Zhangyin's dishes are here
It seems to have a refreshing aroma
come on
His Majesty
This dish uses abalone, shark fin and ginseng
Twenty-eight kinds of ingredients including scallops and deer tendons
It is simmered in an aged flower-carved wine jar
The finished dish has a slight aroma of wine
oily but not greasy
Three things about the dish name Fushouquan
Meat and incense around the tongue
Soup is rich
Unforgettable
I have never eaten such delicious food
Okay
Good luck, good luck and longevity
grandfather
this is a good sign
Emperor Pucha
very delicious
that is
Free at kisskh.me
Grandpa Emperor has a rare appetite
It seems to be the credit of the crab soup
crab paste
Yes
Crab meat is the freshest thing in the world
only Beng Dajia
Can compete with Fu Shouquan in three matters
But now is not the best season to eat crabs
Can't get the best out of the soup
I use crab paste to make tofu soup
The world's lightest and most delicious
Combining two ingredients
The freshness of the crab is neutralized with the clearness of tofu
to be just right
Crab sauce is still so effective
That's no ordinary crab sauce
The fattest hairy crabs in mid to late September
Forget the crab meat
Only take crab paste and crab roe
Crafted Bald Butter
Crispy and fragrant
The taste of the world
Where can ordinary crab sauce be compared?
and
that tea
No wonder
Get rid of fishy smell and oiliness with common tea
tongue to taste
The fragrance of tofu and the deliciousness of crab sauce
Zijin
you are really awesome
So how many wins and losses do we have now?
What happened to our first game?
They won the first game
they won
What about the second game?
What's up with the second game?
I do not know either
Why did it come back intact?
Princess Han has asthma
Do not eat chicken clear all the year round
To avoid angering the princess
So I called people to withdraw.
What did you say
Can you say that again
What's up
Princess of the Han Dynasty
Shuei
princess
Princess Xiuzhen
what happened
Yuehua
What's up
can't eat chicken
But I made fried walnuts
each waist flower
It's all dipped in chicken.
not good
The princess is suffering from a recurring illness
Xuan imperial doctor
Quickly announce the imperial doctor
Yes
Slower
Lord, please stay
Mother
The princess is suffering from a recurring illness
no delay
To hurry up to announce the imperial doctor's diagnosis and treatment
Mother
You first bring people to your palace
Invite the pharmacist too
Slave, please go here
go
prince
back off
father emperor
What does this mean?
bring up
go
quick
kneel down
His Majesty
Changshan guard commander Meng Xian
Yulin avant-garde Peng Xu
Qintian Supervisor Wang Shecheng
And the servant Yang Qing and his son
All the rebels have been captured
what crime
grandfather
Qin Tian supervisor Wang Shecheng plotted against Meng Xian
Said that he has been watching the sky differently recently
The world will be replaced by a king
And conspired to offer poisonous wine at the banquet
Poisoning Your Majesty
Bing Jie Neifu Weaponry and Talismans
Then win the six ministers of the five palaces and six ministers
A fake edict has been found
Free at kisskh.me
Amulet to be stamped
Can abolish the crown prince
Support the King of Zhao
Really my good son
I'm just a little sick
can't look towards
why do you remember
This dragon chair and his big brother's head are gone
third brother
third
wake up
third brother
third
You really colluded with people to poison your father
conspiracy to usurp the throne
I'm greedy
big brother
what do you say
what to say
what's wrong
Why are you making such a slander
My loyalty and filial piety to my father
That is where the sky and the earth can be seen, the sun and the moon can be seen.
How can I collude with people
Conspiracy
Who said that
is it you
Who instructed you to frame this king?
To shut up
go down
Yes
I said the third
Chang Shanwei is your escort
Who can mobilize it but you?
Everyone was detained and still refused to recognize
no
father emperor
I just had a drink
fell asleep
I don't know what happened
But someone must have framed it
I want to trap my sons and ministers in injustice, father and emperor
let him drink
emperor
go
His Royal Highness Zhao Wang
Since you know nothing
why not drink
father emperor
There are no elite soldiers and generals in the hands of Erchen
More selfless friends in the military
Sonny is really alone
Stayed in Beijing for a few years
That's half a step, don't dare to go wrong
that formed partisans in the army
adored by warriors
who is it
The third one hurt me again
Son-in-law is wrong
in the early years of war
Erchen has a lifelong friendship with many generals
But it was a tough battle.
Since Erchen went to the fief
I will never have any dealings with these generals.
I don't even know where to start with the so-called support.
To be favored by courtiers
Who in the world is better than Big Brother?
Those sour civil servants in this court
That's not a mouthful of Prince Rende
father and father
The son and the minister wronged the father and the emperor
Okay don't say it
father emperor
today's drink
Erchen is willing to drink
but before drinking
Sonny must swear to God
I have no intention of committing chaos
What happened today must be someone trying to frame it
There must be someone trying to do the oriole behind.
father emperor
If you insist on using this glass of wine today
Words of Innocence
Erchen is willing to do it
father emperor
Can't make the father
The third brother has always been humble and wise
Never act against
This time it must be wrong
If this is a glass of booze
Son-in-law is willing to take the place of himself
I come
big brother
third brother
okay
They all want to drink poisoned wine to prove their innocence
Don't you dare to be alone?
I'm innocent too
come to me
Give me
enough
grandfather
My grandson hasn't finished speaking yet.
Meng Xian Peng Xu
Just a mere commander
How many soldiers can you have?
To hijack the heavily guarded inner vault
just nonsense
The two uncles are extremely smart
How can you do such a stupid thing
grandson already found out
It's just the conspiracy of those ignorant subordinates
Nothing to do with the two uncles
Zhanji
you said earlier
Uncle San is timid
You scared the third uncle to death
two uncles
You are too quick
Don't wait for me to finish
Even if they weren't behind the scenes
It is also arrogant and indulgent on weekdays
Make a bunch of subordinates greedy
usurpation of power
Your Majesty, rest your anger
edict
Wang Shecheng is seductive with celestial phenomena
punish
The rest of the accused, etc.
Xiazhen Fusi Prison Rigorous Trial
slave servant
you two
Zhao Wang closed his door to self-examination
Yes
and you
Go back to your fief to me tomorrow
Father Xie
Hanwang arrives
sister in law
Mother
Princess Han suffers from illness
Why not take care of the sick
Just stay in the fief and rest.
Dishes prepared by eight famous chefs of Shangshan Superintendent
how did you know in advance
And that walnut kidney flower
who reminds you
Specially cooked with chicken clear
Chicken Qing
Free at kisskh.me
The Princess of Han is known to have old illnesses
Take poached eggs in the morning to nourish your body
The walnut kernel fried kidney flower in the food list
Cooked with chicken broth as usual
It's him
Daughter
You believe me
I really didn't do anything
I don't know the princess of Han
I didn't know she had asthma
Daughter
You believe me
Of course you don't want to murder Princess Han
you just wanna frame me
What did you say
You clearly know that Princess Han has relapsed and died
The palm print of my Shang Food Bureau
Escape from negligence
This is not intentional framing, what is it?
dereliction of duty
You are so angry
Not because Princess Han died
I'm afraid of losing your place of honor
You just said him
who is it
tell me
Say
who is instructing you
no one instructs me
I did it myself
I did it all
You are the stamp of the Shang Food Bureau
New Year's Eve killed
Of course you can't get away
I am anxious
just want to see
You look like nothing at the end
Look at you, a woman who has abandoned her husband
What will happen in the end
I did everything
I did it all
you are satisfied
you are so disappointing
Meng Shang food
The princess summoned
Don't be too polite
grandfather
the traitor's mansion
Finding out the edict of treason is really child's play
third
usually meticulous
How can you leak the wind ahead of time?
Catch all at once
a Washington
if any
A greedy treasure
The thieves naturally keep
on the contrary
A ruined temple outside the city
Except for the spider web
nothing
even
Mice also don't want to patronize
Emperor Dragon Chair Power
how tempting
your uncles
While I am old and sick
colluding with eunuchs
Exchange messages
I don't even hear them, I think
I am deaf and blind
who told you to scare them
grandfather
You are clearly scaring them
bold
Grandson never wrongs anyone
I have fought many times in my life
kill decisively
Strict precautions for parents and children
The world often scolds me for being cruel and violent
What do you think
Say
grandchildren's childhood
Grandpa used to say
What is the leader
originally when people hunted
elect the bravest man in the crowd
as leader
and this person
The one who took the most lives from the beasts
Take up arms and organize an army
Protect tribes and food
This is the leader
tribe still
let alone a country
Ordinary people want to be a good person
Doing good deeds is
But for the emperor
Blindly adhere to the path of righteousness
will only become a mediocre emperor
What do you think is a good emperor?
for the people
for the country
benevolence and righteousness
close relatives
Even if you are scolded by thousands of people, you have to endure it
Adhere to the right path of the country
Defend your territory and people
This is the king
You always take care of your family
Leave room for them
Is that glass of wine poisonous?
Although highly toxic
Only poisonous and rebellious heart
Poison can not defeat the real dragon emperor
Come
walk with grandpa
princess
What Happened at the New Year's Eve Banquet
It's all the slave's fault
The slaves are willing to be punished
don't defend yourself
Slaves are humble people
Relying on the protection of the princess
Only have a place to stand today
This should have been tied with a ring of grass to repay your kindness
New Year's Eve banquet because of my momentary negligence
Let the villain take the opportunity to make trouble
at this point
What face is there to justify in front of you?
Meng Shang food
Who do you mean by the villain?
People who know the righteousness in the world
Should understand the ruler, the minister, the father and the son
The principle of superiority and inferiority
I won't commit a crime with respect
Slaves and servants are not strict
Blindly forgiving
Actually let the villain have an inch to wait for an opportunity to make trouble
this one
Meng Shang food
Hu Sishan
Slaves serve the Lord wholeheartedly
Forget about the dangers that are close at hand
Did not check the food list again
Give the villain a chance to frame
It's the slave's fault
this second
It's just that the slaves are deeply grateful
have to be bold
A man who can betray Shangguan so easily
how to be trusted
How can you stay by your side?
The Imperial Physician has diagnosed and treated the Princess of Han
Said she was suffering from chronic diseases
This time, despite the dissuasion to come to Beijing for a long distance
relapse of old disease
no recovery
There is nothing wrong with the proposed food list of Guanglu Temple
There is nothing wrong with the food bureau making meals according to the order
Besides, His Majesty appreciates that crab soup very much.
The right to make meals still belongs to the Food Bureau
Ruoshang Food Bureau has nothing to do with the death of the princess
why
someone tipped off
You send private messages to the King of Han
you can plead guilty
This is a false accusation
Hu Sishan
How dare you speak ill in front of your master without any evidence
Slaves meet the princess
That day at the Qianqing Palace
Witnessed Master Yuan being expelled from the main hall
Meng Shangshi once said that His Majesty was taking elixir
Poor dragon body
It is even more asserted that there will be a change in the palace
Slaves think about it later
fear
dare not report
Meng Shang food
If it wasn't for a private message with the King of Han
How can you know that something will happen in the palace?
Pay attention to everything
micro-knowledge
princess
Zu Xun has long said
Concubine and female official in the palace
Don't interfere in any affairs outside the palace gate
Meng Shangshi's private peeping on the Lord is a grave sin
Not to mention repeated messages with the vassal king
Besides, she used to repay the grace of King Han
against your will
Meng Shang food
Anyone who writes privately posts privately and communicates messages outside
Writer and receiver
You are the chef in the palace
knowingly
what to blame
If you want to add guilt, there is no excuse
princess
You are wise and wise
I actually believe this provocative statement
Doubt my loyalty?
over the years
you serve your majesty
Host the Food Bureau
Do your best
princess
But you privately peeped at the Lord and talked about palace changes
Words and deeds are really out of line
unforgivable sin
According to palace rules
Take away the post of Shangshi
Go to Gong Zhengji yourself to get guilty
Do it yourself in the future
The slaves say goodbye
The Princess Wanwang cherishes
Congratulations
Meng Shang food
It's not a food anymore
how will i call you from now on
I'm curious
I trust to reuse you so much
why would you trust her
Entered the palace since a young age
We are inseparable friends
Later, he entered the Food Bureau
Because you are domineering and suspicious
anyone who doesn't like you
Always try to suppress eviction
we're blinding you
I've been pretending to be discordant
ten years
You pretended to be in front of me for ten years
Impressive
A Wai
don't be softhearted
I know
In addition to acting domineering
Fair enough
But as long as she is there one day
I'll never get out
these ten years
She has been covering the sky with her hands
We are obviously best friends
But always pretend to be discordant
Are you having a hard time?
from now on
no longer needed
wake up wake up wake up
everyone is fine
safe and sound
great great great
it's fine
Great
it's finally okay
it's alright it's alright
I was just scared to death
what happened
Are you still to blame?
come come come
Come on
I wish you a healthy body
All things are
auspicious star
Everything goes smoothly
hurry up
Come
thanks
Thank you thank you thank you
be careful
Come
Really tasty
Come on
get me some vinegar
Zijin
Happy new year
good luck
reward you
Thank you Your Highness
All the blessings of this Forbidden City
It's all in this bowl of flat food.
I eat first
Your Highness is worried
some things
I am confident
Do it with ease
some things
I haven't tried
I don't know how to deal with it
Your Highness
Not a single luck
It's empty
But I follow Your Highness
is my greatest fortune
It's you
why did you frame me
We are innocent
How can you
it's fair trade
you did something for me
And I also got the meal order from Shangshan Supervisor for you.
do you know
Because of you I became a murderer
it was all your fault
do not come
go away
who hurt you
what happened
Are you deliberately not happy?
Just like your murderous mother
My mother didn't kill
daughter of a criminal
How dare you talk back
you see i don't hit you
you come to me
see i don't hit you
My mother didn't kill
Tell you to talk back and not kill
i told you to talk back
you fight back
you're right
I'm not unaware
pretending not to know
i just want to know
if i am in danger
Will anyone notice
I've always followed the rules, if I do something wrong
Does anyone understand
Even one person is fine
I just didn't think of it
this error
at the cost of human life
It's my own choice
nothing to do with others
you go
you can hate me all you want
just in the future
don't put others
as your hope of living
how did you come out
walk into
what are you doing
Yuehua hasn't come back yet
you care about her
It's freezing, come in
you know
except you
Who has the courage to openly attack the princess?
too presumptuous
I said
Never let go of the initiator
She regrets it to this day
This time I'm here to see you
you bastard
Looks like you won't go back with me either.
Accompanying the king is like accompanying the tiger
But now our king
The worst thing is to be smart
hello do it yourself
After I leave Beijing
no message
Just take care of yourself
The father's teaching, the son remembers
And official business
one step ahead