[English subtitles are available]
[One and Only]
[Episode 3]
All the zithers here are handed down from ancient times.
And one of them
was used by His Highness when he was young.
It was sent to Chang'an
after the late emperor passed away.
His Highness said that
you can choose one yourself.
Which one did my master ever use?
Are you asking me which one
did His Highness use?
This one.
It's called Chang Feng.
The waves rise as the distant wind comes,
like a single filed on a high mountain.
I'll take it.
The reason
you are unwilling to get together with me in Pingqin Commandery must be that
you have kept a beauty
inside your house.
Is he one of master's friends?
[Pince of Pingqin]
You are?
Whatever.
I am just gonna salute him first.
Are you Zhousheng Chen's concubine?
No, no, I am his disciple.
I see, I see.
I get it.
I knew it the moment you waved.
He can't marry you in a public manner.
You see, he'd
rather take a serious oath,
what a nuisance.
You two.
Yes, sir.
What you saw today
stays in this room.
Do you hear me?
Got it.
I should call you sister-in-law.
It should be.
What's the name of your mansion?
No, no, you misunderstood.
Not sister-in-law?
If not, then.
Whom?
You, you go out and ask
someone in the mansion,
and you will know who I am.
Me? Go out?
No, my dear,
why are you driving me out?
Did I say anything wrong?
Don't take it personally.
Though I am one of the princes.
I am actually,
I am just a vassal prince, bestowed for the counter-insurgency.
I am not a member of the royal family,
I didn't read a lot.
Please forgive me
if I said anything offensive.
I, I will apologize.
Don't be mad, don't be mad.
I am a man with little schooling.
I am really not...
You scared my disciple.
You little...
Disciple?
The Cui family sent her over here?
But I had no idea.
Sorry, my dear sister-in-law.
All right.
You may go.
I have put my foot in my mouth again.
Come on.
The people of Pingqin Commandery.
came along with Prince of Pingqin.
And they brought a lot of harvest from this year
to show their gratitude
for the great kindness His Highness showed to send out troops and save the city last year.
May I know if she is the princess?
No.
This is His Highness's disciple.
I heard that Prince of Nanchen's disciples
are all generals.
She is new, she is new.
The people in your jurisdiction
are so you.
You all love to see someone as someone else's wife.
Stop calling without knowing.
This is not concubine.
I was mistaken just now.
I mean...
Come on.
Apologize to His Highness and Miss Cui.
Please excuse me, sorry.
Not a problem, it's ok.
You are also to blame for this.
If you, the Prince of Nanchen, take someone as your disciple,
you have to let all the people from the Western State,
and the Royal Army recognize her.
Tomorrow, I will take you
to see the Royal Army.
[The Western State]
Secular conduct my guide, remain integrity for good.
What's her dreaming about
that makes her smile like that?
She is not too old,
nor too young.
It might be inappropriate
to just carry her back.
What happened to master?
To cover Shiyi with a fox fur
on such a hot day.
Maybe it's for avoiding body contact.
How can you be doing this?
Please let me.
She's too heavy for you to carry.
Open the door, please.
This fox fur...
It's from my room.
Just leave it here.
Am I not in my master's study?
My Lady, morning.
Did you know that last night,
it was His Highness who carried you back in his arm?
You mean
I fell asleep in my master's study?
Though His Highness is not
someone to be easily fussed.
But you should always remind yourself of
the etiquette between a master and a disciple.
Especially because His Highness is the uncle of the emperor,
even the emperor himself
has to show some courtesy to him in the future.
I know.
But I didn't mean to fall asleep.
I get it, My Lady.
You were simply too tired at that time.
But here we are, at the royal mansion.
Nothing like that of Cui Mansion.
We must be careful all the time.
Master,
you are finally back.
Shiyi locked herself up in the yard
for no reason.
She refuses to eat or come out.
And she's been copying books all the time.
Cheng Xi said she is pondering over her mistakes behind the closed door.
Master.
Did she make any mistake?
I will check it out later.
Master,
why don't you go there now?
I am afraid she's starving.
Not everyone
is the same as you
who would starve to death without having a meal.
I...
Master.
It's a bit inappropriate for you
to crack a joke at this moment, isn't it?
You need to go over there now.
All right.
I will be on my way.
I heard that
you are pondering over your mistakes behind the closed door.
Is it because last night
you fell asleep in my study?
Master, I have realized my mistake.
I forgive you now.
Though you have forgiven me,
I can never rest easy.
I need to review as many times as I can.
And keep everything firmly in mind.
In my opinion, rather than wasting your time
and doing the same thing over and over again,
it would be better to open your eyes instead
and look around you.
Xiaoyu
is now freaking out
because you refuse to step out of the yard.
Soon,
if she still can't see you,
I am afraid
she is going to tear the whole mansion down.
Make sure you get that.
I understand.
I gotta go then.
Counsellor,
do you know anything about aphasia?
As far as I know,
if it was a usual aphasia,
the most common way
is to stimulate the acupoints through acupuncture,
along with the support of some medicine.
It will take effect as time goes by.
But I see Miss Cui
is very clever and quick-witted.
She can hear while remain silent.
In my humble opinion,
the root cause lies in her heart.
Her mother ever mentioned
that she had aphasia
because of her father's departure.
Have you heard about this,
Counsellor?
I only heard that
the Cui Family searched everywhere
for a good doctor for their daughter.
As for the rest,
it seems that no one dared mention anymore.
Your Highness,
if you really can't bear to see her unable to speak,
I can help you search for some good doctors in the Western State
and ask them to come to our mansion for treatment.
However,
if what Mrs. Cui said was true,
as far as I am concerned,
the root lies in Miss Cui's heart.
We must seek her salve where she got her sore.
[The Chonghua Palace]
The secret letter making a false charge against me
should be tore on the spot.
How could you even hide it?
You misunderstood, mother.
I...
Your Highness.
[Liu Zixing]
His Majesty has not yet to read the letter,
as it was opened by me.
Oh, yeah?
What's the content of the letter?
Recite it to me.
You don't dare to speak but to read?
Zhao Teng.
Take him out. Give him 30 strokes of the cane.
Don't be angry, Your Highness.
Prince of Guangling has been in a poor health since childhood.
30 strokes...
I am afraid he won't hold it.
[Liu Hui]
Then 20.
Got it.
Your Highness, please.
Mother.
Why would you punish my brother
every time I made a mistake?
On your knees,
now!
Your Highness, here is your medicine.
[Meng Luan]
Everyone says
Your Highness has taken a huge advantage,
but no one knows your grievances.
You love birds,
and then death was granted by the empress upon your birds.
You had several fish,
and they were also poisoned by the empress.
Apart from the daily torture,
you have to take all the blame and punishment for His Majesty.
Enough.
I am simply airing your grievances, Your Highness.
In this place,
not to fight, not to grab,
not to take by force and not to think
are key to survival.
Zixing.
Your Majesty.
Don't move, Zixing.
It must hurt.
I got you into trouble again.
I am the reading partner of Your Majesty.
I deserve your punishment.
Your Majesty, don't you have a present ready as your apology
to give to the Prince of Guangling?
Yeah, bring it over here.
What's this?
Your crown princess.
His Majesty has given an imperial edict
to document Miss Cui's daily life
in the mansion
and send the records to the Eastern Palace
once they are transcribed into volumes every year.
Cui Shiyi.
Your Highness.
What are these?
My Lady's birthday is about to come.
Here are things from the Royal Palace,
including rewards
from the Empress, His Majesty and Prince of Guangling.
These are all birthday gifts
from the Cui's clan in the Beichen.
That many?
They have got a big family.
The Cui's clan has six branches.
Even for our branch alone,
there are three little branches.
And branch to which my lady belongs is called Wushui.
It got prosperous because of our chief.
My Lady is the only girl
in her family,
also the future crown princess.
That's why she's got lots of birthday presents.
Did you forget what I said?
No formality inside the mansion.
I forgot.
Cheng Xi said
your birthday is coming.
I have never prepared any birthday presents
for anyone.
After thinking it over.
I think this
might be suitable.
Open it and take a look
before you decide whether you want it or not, okay?
These are all the seals from the generals who surrendered to me
after I left the Central State.
I was gonna give it to my royal brother.
But it's fine if I give it to you,
so that I don't have to think it over and over
for your following birthdays
year after year.
Are you sure you want to give me
such an important item?
So long as you don't hate it.
This is the proof that my master
once fought for his people in different wars.
I will make sure it's well-kept,
and protect it with my life.
We are about to send out our troops.
Get ready.
This is going to take months.
The army provisions and the defense of the Western State
must be taken into consideration.
Yes.
Your Highness.
There is one more person to concern.
Oh, and Shiyi.
When we went for a battle before, we went without delay
and our mansion became an empty house immediately.
This time,
we have this little disciple in the mansion.
We can't simply go at our free will.
Well, bring her along then,
so that everyone will feel at ease.
That's impossible.
If Mr. Cui ever finds out that
we brought Shiyi
to a battlefield,
he's definitely going to
put up a desperate fight against master.
[Library]
[Charm]
Did you forget the next line?
I used to recite it.
But somehow,
I forgot when I took the brush.
May I?
[Love]
[the female exerts her charm while the male becomes intoxicated...]
What are you thinking about?
Mom once told me,
the sentence is saying
the female exerts her charm while the male becomes intoxicated,
soon they hit it off and fall in love.
Fill in the blank
when you finish your studies here.
I have to go.
And I am here to tell you that.
Where are you going?
I don't live here normally.
Around 8-9 months in a year,
I will be leading troops outside.
It will be the same in the future.
You need to get used to this.
After I leave.
You and Cheng Xi will be the only ones
living here except the guards.
Take care of yourself.
That's all.
There are no other things
I need to tell you.
News of victory.
Okay, wait for my news of victory.
From now on,
there will only be news of victory for the Royal Army.
[the female exerts her charm while the male becomes intoxicated]
♫Like a gust of wind gently brushing♫
♫Like a cloud waiting for the rain to fall♫
♫There is a corner in my heart♫
♫Where my expectation is glowing♫
♫It's the shooting star lighting up the night sky for you♫
♫There are so many wishes I want to say to you♫
Master.
Senior sisters and brothers.
♫There is still a hidden sore of longing♫
Take care.
♫My thoughts stained three feet of white snow♫
♫Counting the days for your return over and over again♫
♫Flowers blossom and flowers fall, my heart only clings for you♫
Like master said,
he is always fighting on a battlefield
year after year.
♫My obsession is silent♫
And I always seem to be the only guest
♫I use all my life to guard only one person♫
in the Nanchen Mansion.
♫I say nothing, only hoping to spend my life with you♫
♫I'm full of love for you♫
♫Waiting to unlock the years of time♫
♫Our eyes will still be full of stars when we reunite♫
[the female exerts her charm while the male becomes intoxicated...]
[they hit it off and fall in love]
♫Renewing our relationship♫
Master is used to breaking his words.
The time he promised to come back,
is not going to the real time nine times out of ten.
♫We used to be inseparable♫
He did, however, only one thing.
The Royal Army was never defeated.
♫Heartfelt thoughts are written on a piece of paper♫
Only the news of victory.
♫A heart full of thoughts overflowing into the heart♫
♫Who shall see through the deep sorrow on the paper♫
Mas-ter.
♫My obsession is silent♫
Master.
♫I use all my life to guard only one person♫
♫I say nothing, only hoping to spend my life with you♫
My Lady, His Highness is back.
♫I'm full of love for you♫
Watch out.
♫Waiting to unlock the years of time♫
Are you injured? Let me see.
I will go get the medicine.
♫Our eyes will still be full of stars when we reunite♫
♫We will still promise with each other when we reunite♫
What's up?
You thought I was your master?
Your master is in the military camp.
Why didn't he come back to his mansion?
He is wounded.
In case of information leakage,
he is temporarily recovering in the camp.
Where are you going?
The military camp.
Did you forget it?
Your master doesn't allow you to go there.
That's what he told me before he left.
Now that he's back.
Those words don't count.
All right.
I'll take you to the camp.
We just won a victory.
He shouldn't blame you.
I'll take the bamboo slips.
You take the books.
You're breaking into the military camp without permission.
You do have the guts, don't you?
Xiaoyu.
Here.
Follow me to get your “punishment”.
Watch your step.
Is the letter from Shouyang here?
Eleven.
What? You can't recognize me?
It's another year you haven't seen each other, isn't it?
How long have we been away?
Since we left the Western State,
it has been 19 months.
Your wound.
It's okay.
You don't need to worry about that.
Master.
I have prepared the provisions
according to your order.
Great.
So tonight,
you set out with the provisions
to Shouyang.
Please leave it to me, Master.
I know the place better than he does.
All right.
Then you send the news of victory back to the Central State.
Got it.
Glad Shiyi is here today.
Even if all of us were gone,
there's still someone looking after our master.
I'll be honest with you.
Master fell off his horse
because he was shot by a poisonous arrow
and hurt his arm.
Although he was detoxified,
his symptoms will come back now and then,
and it feels like breaking a bone.
Master won't allow us to make it public.
It will get worse at night.
So, you need to be extra careful.
Now Master is all yours.
I'll also leave my brother to you.
Don't worry.
He will be okay as long as I am.
Our master and I will be the same.
Please take a good rest, Your Highness.
Why are you here?
I worry about you.
Go take a rest in Xiaoyu's camp.
You won't be of much help here.
I can handle this.
Go ahead.
Anything wrong, My Lady?
Well...
I am afraid His Highness will blame that on me.
Please.
All right, all right.
If he keeps sleeping,
the medicine will get cold.
Why are you here?
My Lady, what brought you here?
His Highness finished taking his medicine?
No, no, the medicine was spilled out.
It's all gone.
You are being too kind, My Lady.
Actually, I could
take the bowl on my own.
No, no.
I spilled it.
Spilled it.
My Lady.
What on earth happened?
Medic.
Your Highness.
I was being careless
and tipped over the medicine just now.
I am gonna have to bother you to cook another one for me, will you?
Yes, I will cook it immediately.
Nevertheless,
I'm afraid you'll have to wait for another two hours.
Okay, no problem.
Just a bowl of medicine.
It won't kill me with two extra hours.
Why are you so worried?
What do you want?
No matter what you say,
I am staying.
You have made up your mind?
These days,
I am afraid
the news of me having a relapse would get out,
that's why I am only keeping Xiaoyu and Tianxing
with me.
What they can do,
I can do just the same.
All right.
If you get tired,
you can sleep over there.
Today,
Xiaoyu and Tianxing were both wrong.
The day after tomorrow
marks the full 19 months.
♫Snow of pavilion gently kisses the window pane♫
The 19 months you are away from your mansion.
♫My love for you won't dive deep into my brow♫
♫Singing whispers while I'm slightly drunk♫
♫Hearing it, can you see that I'm thinking of you♫
♫Watching your shadowy form disappearing in the heavy snow♫
Master.
♫If I were a lyre, how would I be able to harmonize with you♫
Allow me a few more days till I get used to this.
I will pay a solemn respect to you by then.
♫If I took the brush, how should I portray you♫
♫With the floating tea fragrance, how should I drink with you?♫
♫Under the moon at the city gate, we enjoyed the lanterns and boats together♫
♫Pity that the feelings cannot be expressed♫
♫The snow in front of the yard keeps falling♫
♫Looking at your smile, I don't want to wake up♫
♫How should I greet you in the four seasons of the world?♫
♫With a sincere heart, I believe♫
♫One day, we will enjoy this picturesque world together♫
♫Even if it's millions of miles, I'll run to you willingly♫