[English subtitles are available]
[Nothing But You]
[Episode 17]
Lili!
Why are you coughing so much?
I feel so cold.
So hot.
You're having a fever.
Maybe because of my heavy work pressure,
I suffer from low immunity
and have fallen ill.
Let me send you to the hospital.
Don't bother.
Let me just rest at home.
There's no time for me to go to the hospital now.
If I still can't handle
that Zhang Xueying tomorrow,
then all the effort will be in vain.
We've paid
so much desperate effort,
and it's all futile now.
Right.
It's a pity, indeed.
Maybe it's an act of God.
No way!
My fate can only be decided by me myself!
This stuff...
is quite warm.
I often feel cold and weak,
and this is used to warm my body.
Now that you're okay,
I'm gonna leave now.
Mr. Lai!
Please give me three more days!
Yiyi...
My darling! Please...
Call me one more time.
Mr. Lai.
Not this.
Yiyi!
Not this one, either.
Forget about it since you're reluctant to call me that.
My darling!
Please!
Then I'll give you three more days.
You're so nice!
My darling...
I love you so.
Guys...
There's good news for you!
Through my consistent efforts,
I sacrificed myself,
and finally convinced Mr. Lai
to give us three more days.
We must keep working hard
and break through the obstacles.
Why...
Why do you all look spiritless?
Did something happened?
Something big did happen.
[Zhang Xueying: Fight against the dark. And I finally see the light of hope.]
[Thank you for accompanying me during the battle.]
What...
[But it's about time to put an end to everything.]
[I've received apologies from Lemeng, as well as their compensation.]
What?
[A company which dares to admit its mistakes and shoulder the responsibility is worth forgiving.]
What does she mean by "a company which dares to admit its mistakes
and shoulder the responsibility"?
What mistakes did we make?
Wait...
That's complete rubbish!
Who gave her compensation?
Why didn't I know about it?
No one knew.
After she posted it this morning,
it seemed to have confirmed Mr. Qin's stigma of plagiarism.
Now on the Internet, everyone says
our company is afraid of getting into trouble
and has settled this thing with money.
What on earth is this?
We also just saw it.
Good morning.
What are you doing here?
Why are you still so happy?
Didn't you check Weibo?
What are you looking at?
Zhang Xueying has made a statement.
Has she?
Then she has kept her word.
Come on, let me see.
What's this?
She talked nonsense.
She took my money and still threw mud at us!
I'll beat her up!
What do you mean?
She said it!
She said,
so long as I gave her five million yuan,
she'd stop making trouble.
Five million yuan?
Are you crazy?
Why didn't you discuss it with us?
We were short of time and the task was heavy back then,
so there was no time for discussion.
Do you know
what a great loss you've caused
with your reckless action?
The efforts made by everyone is now in vain.
My reckless action?
Lai Zhengyi,
didn't you say it?
You said, if it was not settled within three days,
you'd cancel this project.
I did so to save it!
Save?
Then what about now?
Have you saved it?
Did you ever think of the consequences
when you gave her money?
Did you discuss it with any of us?
I didn't think so much at that time.
I did it all for the project.
You...
Aren't you cash-strapped?
Where did you get the five million yuan?
I sold my car.
Lai Zhengling!
You're no longer a child!
Can you be even a little cautious when doing things?
You sold your car,
but have you settled things?
Alright.
I'm foolish,
and I'm reckless.
You're the only smart person in the world!
Satisfied?
Now I've sold my car.
What else do you want me to do?
No one forced you to sell your car!
You're the fool who did it!
Okay...
I'm the fool.
Are you crying?
Nope.
Impossible.
I've never cried even once since my childhood.
It was the first time
I saw Mr. Lai so angry.
He's just a double-faced man!
He hides it so well normally.
Ding Dong,
do you also think I'm foolish?
You did so for the good of our company.
I know it.
I gave Zhang Xueying money,
because I wanted her
to clarify and explain.
I didn't expect her to post that!
You know what?
I really don't want to see this project canceled.
This was the first time
I wanted to do a good job seriously.
I don't want everyone to look down on me.
I don't want to always pale in comparison to Lai Zhengyi.
But Ding Dong, you know what?
Ever since our childhood,
Lai Zhengyi has been better than me in every respect.
I am my parents' biological son,
but they both favor him.
And you guys also favor him.
There will be someone who loves you.
Forget about it.
Don't comfort me.
I know.
I can only screw things up
rather than do anything right.
Ding Dong.
Mm...
Thank you.
This time, because of me,
everyone's effort is in vain.
You trusted me so much.
Sometimes I feel
my heart is filled with...
You didn't let me down.
You were just too naive,
and fell into Zhang Xueying's trap.
Don't worry.
We'll figure out a way.
Right?
I hope so.
[Zhang Xueying: Fight against the dark. And I finally see the light of hope.]
[Thank you for accompanying me during the battle.]
[But it's about time to put an end to everything.]
[I've received apologies from Lemeng, as well as their compensation.]
[A company which dares to admit its mistakes and shoulder the responsibility is worth forgiving.]
I'm pissed off!
Zhang Xueying has gone too far!
I must find a chance
to teach her a lesson!
Lai Zhengling is also an idiot.
He paid five million yuan so easily!
What a rich man!
Maybe this...
is not a bad thing.
What?
Lai Zhengling gave the money personally.
What's it got to do with Lemeng?
What do you mean?
Anyway, you go meet Chen Tang first.
Leave the rest
to me.
I've used Qin Yanfei's account
to send messages
and clarified to have nothing to do with it.
I don't have to say too much about what the company should do, right?
We are already drafting the statement.
The press conference will be held half an hour later.
Though I dislike you,
I have to admit
you and I
have the best cooperation at work.
Same here.
[Lemeng Pictures: Lemeng didn't give Miss Zhang any compensation.]
All of them have denied it.
Then where on earth did Zhang Xueying get the money?
Out of nowhere?
Jeez!
It's a completely different story!
No way!
Did Zhang Xueying stage this play by herself?
Things are getting bigger now.
It's really interesting.
Here I confess.
I gave her that money.
Sorry, the subscriber you are dialing cannot be connected now.
What are they doing?
[Lemeng Pictures: Lemeng didn't give Miss Zhang any compensation.]
Chen Tang!
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say
can be used against you in court.
Why are you targeting me?
I told you it was not me!
I didn't take your draft!
Chen,
you know me pretty well.
Today I asked you to come here
not to hold you accountable for anything.
If you know anything,
come clean now.
Things have been really serious now.
The truth matters a lot to us.
I've been your editor
ever since you started writing books.
We've cooperated for so long.
Don't you trust me?
Zhang Xueying is your ex-girlfriend.
If she didn't see the manuscript before,
why is her book
exactly the same
as “I'm a Maid in an Evil Cult”?
How would I know it?
You're so stubborn.
Next, please feel free to ask questions.
[Lemeng Pictures]
Let me say something.
-Mr. Lai Jr.! -Mr. Lai Jr.!
Please tell us!
-What on earth happened? -Right!
Please say something.
Where on earth did Zhang Xueying get that money?
Please tell us.
Could you please explain it to us?
Right, Mr. Lai Jr.!
Please reveal a bit.
Do you know any information?
Do you know the story behind?
Zhang Xueying's money
was paid by me.
-What? -Really?
Because she blackmailed me.
What?
Why did you give her money?
Right!
[Lemeng Pictures]
Mr. Lai Jr.!
Please wait.
We'll have the Q&A section later.
Now let me first tell
the real story to you.
We've put great effort into this project.
How could I just stand by and see it being ruined?
So,
I went to negotiate with Zhang Xueying.
But she
just asked for 5 million yuan as hush money.
Five million yuan.
If I didn't give it to her,
she would destroy our Lemeng Pictures.
And she also wanted to ruin
Qin Yanfei's reputation.
So I had no other choice
but to
sell my personal car
to give her five million yuan.
Then, Mr. Lai...
Then how was it
settled later?
After I gave her that money,
she promised me to make a statement.
[Lemeng Pictures]
The next day,
she did post a statement
on her Weibo.
But her statement
completely distorted
the truth.
She was telling lies.
So, my friends,
what you read before
has also been distorted by Zhang Xueying.
Today we hold this press conference
just to explain the real story
to you guys.
Please don't be cheated by her!
So, I had no other option
but to
[Lemeng Pictures]
sacrifice and give her money.
They should have met each other.
Excuse me.
Hello?
How's it going?
He's really tight-lipped.
He's reluctant to tell anything to us.
Zhang Xueying is done.
If they still refuse to cooperate,
just wait to receive the court summons.
Really?
Look at the Trend now.
[Zhang Xueying is suspected of extortion. Lemeng called a press conference.]
Sister made such great plans!
Nice!
I have something else to do.
See you.
Stop there!
Before we make things clear,
you can't leave.
Sit down!
Let him go.
Zhang Xueying is already done.
She's suspected of extortion.
Lemeng has called the police.
See? It ranks first on Trend.
[Zhang Xueying is suspected of extortion. Lemeng called a press conference.]
What?
About the detail of how she wrote the book,
the police will investigate it.
As for you,
you can't get away with harboring her.
I didn't mean to do it.
On that day, after Yanfei and I finished the meeting,
I took his outline back home by accident.
When Zhang Xueying knew about it,
she just badgered me to let her have a look.
I really had no other way
but to give it to her.
I didn't expect her to so such a thing.
At first,
I did think of
clarifying it for you.
But leaking manuscripts
is a taboo to editors.
Not only will writers hold us accountable for it,
we could also be banned from the industry.
So I dared not say it.
I'm sorry.
-Come on... -Come on...
-Together, together. -Come on...
-Cheers! -Cheers!
Bro,
this is a toast to you alone.
Now you're finally proven to be innocent.
It was really a hard road.
The truth will always come to light.
But I didn't take it seriously.
But I must thank you all.
This is pretty good now.
I'll drink it up.
Please feel free to drink yours.
Come on! Here we go!
-Come on! -Cheers!
Here we go...
Actually, we didn't help too much.
It was mainly Xiaoran who made great efforts.
Were it not for her persistence,
this project
would have been canceled long ago.
Right, Xiaoran!
You're so great!
Zhang Xueying had schemed for so long,
and you just turned the tables in one fell swoop.
Actually, it's not just me.
No...
I also did a good job,
but it was mainly because
there was a skilled person helping me.
-Oh! -Oh...
So it's the couple's joint effort!
Then Zhang Xueying's really unlucky!
Well...
What skilled person...
Forget about it.
You were going to give up this project back then.
Right! Yes!
Don't forget Mr. Lai Jr.'s efforts!
He's also done a great job!
You're right!
-If Mr. Lai Jr. didn't give the money, -Yes!
this project
couldn't be saved so easily!
Right!
Listen,
it was all part of the plan.
Everything was a decoy.
It would be hard to catch her if I didn't sacrifice something.
You know?
It was just a test for you!
Come on... Together!
-Mr. Lai Jr. is both brave and resourceful! -Come on...
We really lucked out
to achieve our success this time.
In the future, we shall do things
more cautiously.
We're all reckless.
We're a group of fools.
Only you are the greatest.
You're the only smart guy,
and the only sensible man.
Only you're the major contributor!
Satisfied?
No...
Mr. Lai didn't mean that.
All of us are the major contributors.
Thank you, Mr. Lai Jr.
Come on! I propose a toast to Mr. Lai Jr.
-Come on. Thank you! -Thank you for your hard work.
I'm gonna leave now. Bye-bye!
Listen...
Listen to me first!
Do you know why
he treated me so arrogantly today
and accused me implicitly
and condescendingly?
You know...
He's drunk!
He's just jealous of me!
Mr. Lai Jr.!
Ding Dong,
please send him back.
Okay.
-Let's go back. -Listen.
Don't move me!
Stop moving me!
I'm okay.
I'm really okay!
Why are you looking at me?
You! Why are you looking at me?
Go back now.
How vile you are!
You're so vile!
He's really vile!
He asks me...
He asks me to go back now
just to let my parents
scold me.
Am I right?
Wait!
Mr. Lai asks you to go back because he's caring about you.
You're so drunk now,
so you must go back home quickly!
Am I?
He's caring about me...
Nonsense.
Listen,
he looks like a good guy on the surface,
but in fact, he's always stabbing you
in the back.
-You're really drunk too much. -This is who he is.
-Let's go. -I'm okay.
I'm really fine!
Don't...
-Don't touch me! -Let's go... Okay!
I won't touch you!
I'm fine!
I'm really all right!
Lai Zhengyi.
Mom and Dad have thought highly of you since our childhood.
They have treated you, a man from another family,
like their biological son.
I've always been neglected.
And you're been a genius since childhood.
But why?
This time, you helped Lemeng
get through the hard times.
Mom and Dad are really exhilarated.
But what about me?
If I go home now,
I'll surely be scolded.
Like, "You can only screw things up
rather than do anything right.
There's nothing you can do.
You're a loser!"
They'll definitely say so.
As a member of the Lai family,
shouldn't I be
the chosen one?
But, listen, Ding Dong.
Ding Dong, Ding Dong!
Listen.
In the first year...
In the first year of our junior high school, you know.
I tried really hard
to get 98 points.
I really...
Do you know his score?
He scored...
He scored 100 points!
It was okay to me whether you
scored 96 points
or 69 points.
It was okay!
But he got 100 points!
You...
Were you targeting me?
Tell me the truth.
He was not!
Bi Xiaoran, listen.
Now...
Break up with him right away.
Enough!
Break up!
Or your youth will be wasted.
Really, really!
How could you say so?
He's your elder brother, after all!
I see you as my elder brother,
but do you see me as your younger brother?
Of course, I do.
Why hasn't he come out yet?
It's been a long time!
-Don't move! -Come over!
It's said the boy called Lai Zhengling
in our primary school
is your younger brother.
No!
I don't have any younger brother!
Cut the crap!
I know it all!
Hey!
Do you know
what happened at that time?
what happened after he
finished that talk?
No response at all!
And...
I even gave
my little toy car
tied with rope
to him to play.
That was my only
toy car without electricity.
Pull,
and slide.
Pull, and slide.
Really interesting.
Pull, and go.
Just the one with strings...
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
I just think,
Lai Zhengling is quite a poor guy.
Not at all!
Actually,
after I heard what he said,
I can understand him more or less.
He and I are both
siblings of the geniuses.
Sometimes,
we're quite stressed out.
No matter how hard we try,
we always
pale in comparison.
This is also true for me.
But I'm luckier than him.
Al least I know
my sister cares about me.
But he
is under the pressure from you on one hand,
and can't
get your recognition on the other hand.
What do you want to say?
Actually, after this time spent with him,
although Lai Zhengling is impetuous
and unruly,
I find
he's not a bad guy in nature.
He doesn't say it openly,
but every action he takes
is to get your recognition
and attention.
I've been on bad terms with him
for a long time.
He was just drunk and talked nonsense today.
It'll be fine after he wakes up.
But I think
he really cares about you.
But what about you?
Do you
see him as your younger brother?
All right, it's late now.
Time for bed.
Time to go to sleep.
I'm okay.
Sit down!
Sit still!
Wake up!
I feel uncomfortable.
Sit well.
What a double-faced,
ungrateful
and hopeless guy!
Sit well!
In fact, Mr. Lai
does care about you.
He's given you opportunities
at work both openly and secretly.
He's training you,
and helping you improve.
Though I don't know
what has happened between you,
there must be some misunderstandings
which remain unsolved.
Don't try to convince me!
I didn't!
All right...
He's not helping me improve!
He's...
abusing my cheap labor.
I feel uncomfortable.
That's your bias!
So of course, you...
I feel uncomfortable.
What are you doing?
Let me sleep for a while.
Just five minutes.
I can't fall asleep.
Sing a song for me.
♫Are♫
♫Are you sleeping?♫
♫Brother John?♫
♫Morning bells are ringing♫
♫Ding, dang, dong♫
♫Are you♫
♫Baby sleep, gently sleep♫
We're finally home!
The foreign ladyboys are really different.
Oh my goodness.
Finally, we're home.
This...
Babe, be careful.
Dad! Mom!
Xiaoran?
Hello, sir and madam.
What happened?
Hello, Mom.
Come back now!
Wait...
I'm still working.
It's improper to go home.
What work?
Quit it!
Hello?
Quit it?
Gosh!
Something bad happened!
[Luchi Xianting]
What did you do as her younger sister?
I was scared!
What?
Your sister...
Your sister has become like this!
And you didn't tell me!
I...
You brat...
She didn't allow me to tell you!
Calm down!
Calm down.
Mom,
I'm okay.
That's just an accident.
I'm really fine.
Are you kidding me?
W-what do you mean?
I just...
I just went out...
I went out
to play just for two months,
and you have become lame!
If I really went out
for a year or more,
could I still see you safe and intact?
Relax...
She's safe now!
Right! She's safe and sound.
You brat!
Your sister has become like this,
and you still went out to play, huh?
Were you in the mood to play?
I didn't go out to play!
I work in place of my sister every day!
I've worked so hard!
I'm pissed off.
Right,
what happened between you two?
What happened?
You lifted her up when you just walked out.
Right!
This is also an accident.
I'm her boyfriend!
What?
Sir, Madam, don't worry.
We're in a relationship
aiming for the marriage!
Being in a relationship without a goal for marriage
is too irresponsible!
We've already decided the date of marriage!
Qin Yanfei!
Date of marriage?
Have you really decided it?
N-no...
When?
Mom, where are you going?
Mom, no...
You've already decided the date of marriage, huh?
Mom...
-Mom! -Wait...
Do you wanna die?
You two!
I didn't lie!
What are you talking about?
Do you want to die?
I...
Wait...
-Mom! -Mom...
Calm down!
Easy, easy!
Sir, Madam!
We really love each other!
What are you doing?
I'm...
going to peel an apple
for my future son-in-law!
I was freaked out, Dad.
I was really scared.
Then...
what's the date
that you've decided?
April 4th in the next year!
It's a good day for marriage.
April 4th...
No!
April 4th,
doesn't sound like a good day!
It's not auspicious!
Choose another one.
You're right.
Then what about March 3rd?
How about it, Dad?
How about March 3rd?
March 3rd!
I think
it should be February 18th!
February 18th!
February 18th...
Brilliant, Dad!
Mom!
I also have a boyfriend now!
Wait!
We're talking about your sister's business.
Get married on February 18th...
Dad!
I've found a son-in-law for you!
Just February 18th! It's good!
Go away...
Besides...
I was talking!
Come on! Stop messing up!
We're talking about your sister's business.
Come on, take some grapes.
Thank you, Mom.
Nice.
Eat some!
I want grapes, too!
There's nothing to do with you!
I...
Zhengyi,
Come back to have dinner after work, all right?
Mom,
I have a meeting in the afternoon.
It may end very late.
It's okay.
I'll wait for you.
I miss you.
-I really can't go back, Dad!
I still have
several meetings later.
I'm so important in the company now.
They all need me.
Cut the crap!
Your mom has prepared so many dishes.
Come home on time!
I see, Mom.
All right, Dad.
Mom?
Dad, Mom,
why did you call
both of us back?
You brat,
do we have to
call both of you back for any business?
The four of us
haven't had a meal together for a long time.
See?
Zhengyi has lost weight.
He must be too busy to have meals on time.
Come on, eat some shrimps.
Thank you, Mom.
There are so many things to settle in the company recently.
You've worked so hard.
Well done.
What did he do?
And you just praised him.
Things are not done by him alone!
There's so many employees in the company!
How dare you say that?
You've just made so much trouble
in your brother's company.
You didn't help at all!
See?
There you go again!
I've heard nothing!
Blah, blah, blah.
Whatever.
It has been long enough
since your suspension of schooling.
Go back to your school now.
Start having classes tomorrow.
Dad, Mom.
I want to tell you that I
don't want to go back
to study in that business school.
I want to be a racing driver!
What racing driver?
It's useless!
Right!
What if you have an accident?
What should we do?
I don't care!
I've dropped out of school, anyway.
What did you say?
I said,
I've dropped out of school.
It's not a trifle thing!
Why didn't you
negotiate with us?
I did...
tell it to you.
But did our negotiation work?
Did you listen to me during our negotiation?
You...
Why do you
make trouble for us?
Why can't you
learn from Zhengyi?
Learn from Zhengyi?
I learn from Zhengyi.
I learn from you.
Okay?
Zhengyi,
Zhengyi.
You only have eyes for Zhengyi.
Was I adopted by you?
I really don't understand.
You already had Zhengyi back then,
so why did you give birth to me?
I'm nothing, all right?
Come back!
Leave him alone!
Mom!
Mom, Dad,
don't worry.
He's just childish.
I'll go persuade him later.
Okay.
Then I will count on you.
Don't fight against each other!
Yeah.