You are awake
How are you feel?
Is it uncomfortable?
You shocked me
If not, Li Dai Xi, tell me
I didn't even know you fainted
What happened?
It seems that my electricity is now gone
You look
My electricity, it's gone
Your electricity is gone
I went to see Dr. Jiang
Dr.Jiang had already taken the electric out from me
This child...
Dr. Jiang's equipment was not completely tested
What if it is harmful to the body?
Here is the complete test here
It really works
Electricity is gone
That's  great
You come with me
So I gonna go
I'm going to pour water to you
I'll go with you
Sit down
Your name
Uncle, did you know?
Don't argue
Name
Mai Si Chong
With our Weiwei
How are you guys related?
Huh...
He hesitated
A man who hesitates, is it reliable?
I didn't hesitate
I like Weiwei
He said he like you
I think
By now you should be studying
Now is school age
Drink water
Why hurry?
Follow me to the kitchen
Not finished speaking yet
This is like you say
Age of learning, so go to learn cooking
Now you still have time to confess
I'll go see you
It's hard to back down
A man playing in the water
After a while, it sinks from the surface of the water
What's wrong with you guys?
Have something to say, just say it
It's like this every day
It makes us stressful when practicing
You don't understand
Breaking news
Weiwei solved that problem
Now, even if Xia Rui would release a video clip
Nobody believed him
This crisis has passed
Chong will go for a drug test soon
At that time
Let's wait and see
Really?
ตกลงมันเกิดอะไรขึ้น?
Yes, yes, tell us quickly
You don't have to ask
As long as you remember
Do your best to practice
Learn a lot from brother Chong
Dr.
Sorry, you guys are late. Tomorrow will come again
Doctor
He is a provincial team athlete
Have come to check for drugs
Can you give us certification today?
Mai Si Chong
In you case
Must have a examination request from the university
Examination request
Tomorrow the university opens and will come again
What should we do now?
Forgot it
Let's talk again tomorrow
Let's go
Drug examination site, why is it so far?
Last time it was very difficult to come
At this time, I couldn't call for a car
No cars at all
Weiwei
Did the car come?
Haven't come yet
You sleep like this will catch a cold
Otherwise
Let's find a place to stay
Let's go
Took a small hotel room, isn't it better?
This one is too luxurious.
No
How can I put you in such a pitiful state?
Here is fine
Welcome, Can I help you?
Two rooms
Ok
Sorry, there is only one room left
Only one room left
Not a standard room?
I will go ask
Well, it's late now
Don't ask
Let's talk again tomorrow
I'll take a shower first
Can I help you blow?
Weiwei
I will ask if there is any additional room
Hello, please check again if the room is available or not
Guests just check out ,please wait a moment
What do you plan to tell Master Mei Ling?
Speak truthfully
Why do you look so happy?
Someone will be able to join the province team. Of course, I must be happy
So
Waiting for me to join the provincial team
When children's day
So you can travel with me
You have grown up so much and will still go on a children's day trip?
Why I can't?
Are you going or not?
Look at my mood first
No
Must go
Professor Mei Ling
I would like to consider about drug testing with the provincial team
I am not cheating
So
No matter how rigorous the drug testing is
I am pleased to do
Mai Si Chong
Hasn't your coach told you yet?
What?
Overdue for drug testing
And
You have been eliminated from the province team
But your coach still believes in you
She believes you are not a cheating boy
Therefore, the university has been discussing for a long time
The decision is final
Let you be punished with criticism
Ok
I understand, Professor Mei Ling
So, excuse me
Let's go
Why? Coach
This is...
I still can't figure out how to tell Mai Si Chong
But it cannot be delayed any more
This one be announced today?
Tomorrow
Announced with the list of provincial teams
You and Mai Si Chong are in the same dormitory
Please comfort him
Anyway, this year our team has you participating
This many days
You also have time to rest and practice
After you entered the province team
It doesn't get any easier than in the university team
Just fighting
Come on
You don't have to think about it
Just not joining the provincial team
Not a big deal
Next year will continue to break the record
Look if he will let me join the team
But because you wanted to protect me, so you didn't go for a drug test
Otherwise, you have joined the provincial team already
Weiwei
Didn't I tell you?
My past life
Swimming is the most important thing
But after I met you
I just discovered that
In life there are many possibilities
There are many beautiful things
That makes my heart beat
So
Whether you can conduct electricity or not
You are the cutest to me
It's the happiest Pikachu
Don't be sad
Smile please
Not enough
Quickly
Let's go
Go
Where's Weiwei?
She was called by Yu Xi Sin
Just can't enter the province team
You guys are like this
Do like going to my grave like that
Not an ideal grave?
Rui
In the afternoon, why don't you go to practice?
You're really stupid
Brother Rui has already gone to the provincial team
In the afternoon, he asked to leave to adjust his practice schedule
Rui
Sit sit sit
Chong
Rui
We are all brothers
What's going on, why can't we talk well?
Haven't you heard that saying
If someone suggests you to be generous
You'd better stay away from him
Otherwise, when the storm comes
He will also hurt you
Why are you talking to Brother Rui like this?
What are you shouting at her?
enough
Xia Rui
Don't you have anything to say to me?
All that should be said, I have already said it
Rui
Dad
Yu Xin
Come here
Uncle, Hello
You are Weiwei, right?
Hello
Why must you be so formal?
เวยเวยไม่ใช่คนอื่นซะหน่อยWeiwei is not someone else
Come on Weiwei
What do you want to eat? Just order
We can eat it all
Or should we talk about business first?
Weiwei, you want to know, right?
About Mai Si Chong
Yes
I called to ask
The provincial team leader
Nothing but worry about that
Mai Si Chong
is going the wrong way
But only need someone to prove
He is talented
Can do it for sure
So we came to you, dad
Do you know anyone over the years?
Who is a leader and speaks well
Stupid girl
Think about it
If I look for someone to defend him
Like that, others would think
Mai Si Chong
use connection
so
so, what should we do?
You have to find Lobbyist
And
This Lobbyist
It must be reliable
And
With Mai Si Chong famuly
There must be no personal relationship with each other
Sun Yang
Xia Rui
You admit to confess your mistakes
Everyone is ready to forgive
Xia Rui
Are you there?
This one be announced today?
Tomorrow
Announced with the list of provincial teams
Why is there no announcement?
Coach Pei Pei
Hello
Coach
Welcome
Here. this way
This time is the provincial team selection playoff round
How important is it? I won't have to say much
For equality
You have to pass a drug test before the competition
Hope that you guys
Will show your full potential
Got it?
Prepare well
Finished and go have a meal together
Ok
Thank you for the previous story
You're welcome
Let's go get ready
I bet Chong will win
What if Rui wins?
No way
If he win
I'll be drinking water in the pool for a month
Where's Xia Rui?
What time is it, and he hasn't come yet?
I'll go and see him
Mai Si Chong
I accept
You are an excellent swimmer
I'm jealous
So I did a lot of things that hurt you and Mei Weiwei
Game between us
I lost from the start
So this competition is meaningless
I owe you guys, sorry
Sorry
Why you don't take it and see?
Why me?
This might be good news for Xiao Chong
I am a generous person
Let you see first
Glad?
Lao Mai, why are you so serious?
Don't you shock me
Mai Si Chong in this playoff round
Hit a record at 50.35 seconds
Successfully entered the provincial team
Congratulations
This old man
Fool me?
Really unthinkable
Open the first week of semester, people will register so much
Finally, our physical therapy club can survive
Who made our bosses become jokes?
Hello Everybody
Welcome everyone to my live
I didn't think the physical therapy club would be this hot
Right now, our President Lin Bai Hui is teaching everyone Tai Chi
You don't take me, I don't take
Ok
Let's see where our Weiwei is
Very similar
Similar what?
Just 199
Will get Mei Weiwei electric eel back home
This kind is too cheap
Steamed fish is more expensive than her
Our Weiwei
How will it be compared with the money?
How did you come?
Where's Ding Yi?
Don't know
After class, just ran away
Why are you so happy?
Of course
Well, your boyfriend is so handsome
Others must be very jealous
Right?
I gonna go
Why are you still wearing this?
You don't have to use it
Anyway, I'm used to
Wear it and I feel comfortable
Ok
Did you have anything you want to do, but did you dare to do it?
I haven't swam yet
Swim
Your boyfriend is a great swimmer. How did you...
Do you want this?
I teach you
Go
Otherwise
Forgot it
I...
It's ok
During practice
Not many people
Let's go
But...
I've never swam before
Weiwei
Got me what are you afraid of?
Trust me
Let's go
Come on
You have not yet entered the pool, so what are you afraid of?
But
Last time you said
Last time I was almost drowned because of you
Be careful
So you don't let me go
Yes, I don't let you go
I'll be by your side
Don't take advantage with me
Why is it me who takes advantage?
Obviously, you're the one who takes advantage
All right
Come on, hold this one and let's try
Trust me, I'm on your side
So you take me
Really unthinkable that I would have a day to swim in the pool
How is it?
The days when there is no electricity
So happy, right?
Before I
Tend to worry about my own conductivity
So these things are really hard to think about
And never thought of my own future
So now you can start
Plan your future
Also have
Our future too