It's time to perform plan B
Help!
I don't believe anyone could drown in such a shallow pool
Mei Weiwei
What have you done to me!
I bought all the throat medicine in the market
You can have a try
I still sounds funny!
Are you done?
I can't breath!
What did you do last night?
What have you done to your throat?
I was kissed by Mei Weiwei last night
Mei Weiwei!
What have you done to my throat?
Just make me normal
Are you stressed out recently?
Don't take it out on me
I am not...
I am not angry, I just want to be normal
Stop laughing
I am telling you
You are the one who get best of things
You have to be responsible...
Alright
I will be responsible to you
From now on, you follow me around
I will take care of everything
But, don't talk to me again
Maybe this is helpful
Why are you following me
I am here to buy groceries
Wow, you are so special
Shot! He must assume I am a lady
who needs a razor!
So embarrassed
Okay
Let's move on to chapter 2
the sports industry structure
First of all, you need to know a concept
Interpreted literally
the industrial structure
can be interpreted
as the problem of corporate relationships within a certain industry
but also as the relationship structure
between various industries
In the 1970s
I attended to sit in the first row
to give a good impression on Ms.Meiling
You want the first row? I can go...
Since you seem to be a little sleepy
Don't let anyone notice we are sitting together
-Or things will go wrong -I would like to call the roll
Stop talking to me
Zhang Yuxin
Mei Weiwei
Here
Since you are so curious
and this is a theory lesson
the homework would be a presentation
You rehabilitation class could do first
and you would be the team leader
Sit
Are your brains clear now?
Let's continue
Some economists in Japan...
Why are you keeping your head low?
You said you wouldn't want people to see us together
You and me are not a couple!
Sooner or later
Anyway
Things are much more complicated than you think
I can never imagine taking class with you
Can we have lunch together?
Can I have your number?
Can I?
I want your number too
You can have my number first
Then I will form a group
You and him will all be in there
Here is my number
Take me to lunch!
Ms.Meiling is calling us
We need to go now
-Let's go -Okay
Sit there
You guys are here
Weiwei
When will Sichogn be normal again?
Maybe tomorrow
You..
Will you be uncomfortable of eating so much?
What do you want?
Weiwei's electricity shocked me so hard
-Daixi -I don't want to talk to you now
Daixi
What happened to them
No idea
Give me a chicken leg
I am starving
You sounds normal now!
How come?
Really
I need to tell Weiwei the good news
Wait a second
Weiwei is having a cold war with you
You tell her now
She won't speak to you any more
That makes sense
Daixi is really angry with me
Peng Yan?
Are you available now?
We need to talk
Sorry but I am busy now
Maybe next time
Don't turn around
How is it going
Do you like the life here?
You freshmen have so many classes
I have been here for two months
Oh! I forgot
I have been so busy in my internship
outside the campus
Actually in high school,  I was thinking if there is a possibility
that you will choose South China Sports University
and become a  track athlete
I don't do track any more
-Is it because of me? -Peng Yan
Can we stop mentioning the high school stuff?
Fine
Right
What are you majoring in now?
Rrehabilitation
My first thought is the sports economy but I am 1 point short
and I am considering switching majors
Switch to my major?
Why are you study here?
I heard you have gone aboard
and you changed your name
Remember the no high school stuff rule?
Let's not break it
Right
There is a meeting of seniors
I know a guy who had switched majors
You can talk to him
I don't think I can make it
I have other stuff
You still don't want to get close to me
Can I at least have your number?
Text me anytime you are in trouble
Daixi
I will move
You don't treat me as your friend
I can explain
Explain?
Are we really friends?
First, you lied to me, that's fine
If I didn't see you guys together today
You are going to hide it from me forever?
Or, you also fall in love with Mai Sichong?
You can totally tell me
if you like him
I would give in without another word
I wouldn't fall in love with Mai Sichong unless I am mad
Fine
You have your Peng Yan in your hands
Why not cast a spell on him?
Then you have two!
Am I being mean?
That must sound harsh
I am leaving
Such an idiot
Weiwei, I know you are in the dormitory
I would shout out loud
if you don't come downstairs
Mai Sichong
Can't you leave me alone?
Why don't you go training?
You can't leave me alone
You said
You will take care of me today
Hello monitor
It's rare to see you in the library
About that presentation
I can help you
Are there ways to get extra points?
Extra points?
Give me a minute
Starting a club!
I am thinking of starting a massage club
But I need at least 10 members
If you join me
That would be wonderful
How many members do you have
including me
Two
Fine
I am in
We would be the founders
to gain the extra points
Let's go for some surveys
Now?
Slow down
What are you doing!
I can't stand you and him being together
Your voice!
You lied to me
Wow, I am normal!
Come on
You said you need to do survey
It's none of your business
You are my girl...
my...
girlfriend
I need to take care of you
Fine
Give me some minutes to go through everything
You don't need to! Just follow me
Let's go
Wait
Let's do this
Excuse me, if there is a massage club
Are you interested joining in?
You are? Good!
Excuse me?
Can I ask you some questions?
-Sure -Thank you
Excuse me
Would you mind doing me a favor?
Okay let's talk
You can tell me everything
Mai Sichong
I am thinking of
separating for couple days
You go back to your life
and then we could hang out again
Is it a no to me?
What do you mean?
Think twice
Your feeling about me is such a sudden
What do you like me about?
Maybe when you wake up tomorrow morning
You will regret liking me
and think you are crazy
Right?
No!
I really mean it
This is all my fault
What happened?
Is there anything borher you?
I told her how I feel but she blew me off
Who? Mei Weiwei?
You have told her?
And she turned you down?
Correct
That's not possible
Did she not understand what you mean?
Maybe
She turned you down because you have never been in a relationship before
Have you been in love before?
Of course
I admit that you are genius in swimming
But when it comes to the love part
I am the only genius
You are too staight
Girls wouldn't respond to you even in games
You are nothing but a pretty face
You gotta a lot to learn!
Girls need flowers, music and ceremony!
You have to create an atmosphere
Done!
Is she able to find Avatar Square
according to this picture?
You have found it
The only reason
that I can locate this place is because I am with you
What's the plan?
If she said yes
We need to go on a date
and I will drive her
I am thinking of
decorating the car with roses
You don't even have a complete plan
Meet me here
I have something to tell you
What's this all about
What's this
Cheers
Peng Pai
Are you not going to introduce that girl to me?
Which girl? Can I meet her?
She is very important to Peng Pai
You better be kidding
Is she your girlfriend?
Look at his face!
Cool
Peng Yan?
-Are you having dinner here? -Yes
Since you have been here, why not join us
Thank you but I am good
I insist
I can introduce you to my classmate
who had switched majors
Let's go
Trust me
Excuse me
This is Mei Weiwei
Nice to meet you
This is the one I told you before
You can call her Qiaoqiao
-Nice to meet you -Hello
Sit here, please
Let's sit
Thank you
Let's drink
Peng Pai told me that
you want to switch majors?
Yes
My point is
Switching majors is to better achieve your life goals
not to hide from things
I know
Thanks for noticing
May I know the specific reason
why you want to do this?
Is it because Peng Pai?
No no no
I am not in a relationship
with Peng Pai
Don't freak out, I am just kidding
But Peng Pai
always mention you
Sichong
There is a notice
saying that there will be a power failure
End of the plan
Has Weiwei picked your phone yet?
Peng Pai's resume
is better than some experienced people
Sichong!
Mei Weiwei
Don't do stupid things!
Weiwei, listen to me
Peng Pai is my friend, he is perfect
These four years
I still can't figure out what he wants
He sometime is like a fake people
He drank too much
I am sober!
I have a question for you Weiwei
-Enough -Mei Weiwei
Why you stood me up?
I didn't
Leave her alone!
It's none of your business
Let's go!
I am so sorry about this
Are you Okay?
Mai Sichong
What are you doing?
This is for you
A shabby car?
What about now?
Am I clear enough?
Can you please listen to me?
I am enough with waiting
and doing nothing
I have been thinking this for a long time
For no reason
I just can't stop thinking about you
All I ask for is an answer
Can you accept me?