Give it back to me
Why would you steal a medical report?
You soften your voice
Who is the thief?
Just borrow it
This is call borrow?
Don't care
If the last time it wasn't for you I would have taken it back from the beginning
You told me honestly
Why do you have to do this?
I don't want anyone to see my medical history
If the university
especially if the provincial team knows that my knee has a problem
Until I have to withdraw, what to do?
Your knees...
Better now, you don't have to worry
Go with me
What will you do?
However, the medical report must be returned
Go
I'm still sick
So the more you have to return
You have to come right now?
Of course
Do you know that this is very serious?
But I don't have the key
Ding Yi is not here
You tell me how to enter?
Open
Can you like this?
So what should I do if broken?
It's ok
Last time reported the repair
Last time?
This isn't the first time you've been here, is it?
Not at all
Last time I heard someone at the Student Council talking
Really
It seems like she's gone
I'm so shocked
We hurry to return the medical report to the original place
You were in the storage report room that day, right?
No, I'm not
Good, it's not someone else
Your porridge
Thank you
Why are you staring at me?
Eat
Mai Sichong
Don't you want to know?
That before, why did I have to follow you?
Then you know my secret, will you unfold me?
Of course! No
Then don't care
You choose to believe me
and tell me about your electric power
Then I have to choose to believe you anyway
All right, this...
Just end today
You don't have to think again, okay?
Let's eat
This one is delicious
I said...
We have two more weeks to have a college sports event
We only have 4 people
There are a few team events that can be entered
The only entry to be entered is the 4x100m relay
Will all of you join?
I...
Of course, I didn't participate either
But this is a good opportunity to show the power of our Major
Weiwei
What do you think?
I don't go
Boss
Do you have time?
Why?
Could you give me a special tutoring?
I want to know about rehabilitation
Especially the knee meniscus
But...
Knee meniscus, are we going to study next semester?
I'm just trying to study it, just trying
So I'll go back and prepare a lesson plan
We can study many people
so we can talk about sports events as well
Sports meeting, don't count me
But I can treat everyone with coffee
Thank you Yu Xin
Hurry and eat
Thank you, Yu Xin
I know you shouldn't take sugar
What is this?
This's....
Don't you want to learn about the knee meniscus?
So today let's start with the basics first
Today, I'm going to teach you some useful points for knee recovery
This is the Wei Zhong point and the Wei Yang point
These two points are very useful. It is often an acupuncture point for knee restoration
Except at this point, Let me think...
Should still have here
Cheng Jiang point
Do not overlook it, even if it is not knee position
But actually....
If these 3 points are acupuncture
Shao Chong Point
Should be like this
Not correct
Oh my god!
What are you doing?
More concentrating on studying than before
You have to learn all the time
But don't you want to transfer Major?
Why, do you know your own mind?
Transfer or not?
As I see
You just
Will be a representative of athletes together with senior Peng Pai
It's not good?
I don't think I'm suitable
I've been to his company
Every woman at his company like ...
It's all like this
I can't
I think studying physical therapy is good
Like our boss, Lin Bai Hui
Will it not be successful?
Just...
I don't know if I can do it or not
It was brainwashed by your boss, right?
Hey!
Brainwash what?
People have a dream, and where is it bad?
Another thing
The career of a physical therapist is pretty good
The professionals are greatly reduced
God!
Lin Bai Hui is really good
When the semester starts, I think that no one wants to study
Now so good
Everyone is determined to be a graduate
I plan to do sports news
Can work and also meet so many handsome man
and watched various competitions as well
Shoot one hand with 3 birds
How about Jun Jun?
What does Jun Jun want to do?
I...
I never thought it before
Should be taken according to the parents' arrangement
But I don't want
Anyway, now we're only in 1 year
It's too early to think about it
Now let's go to bed
It's true
Otherwise, tomorrow you will surely get swollen eyes
Good night everyone
Good night
How are you, recently?
Your eyes have gone dark
Drink this
Because it uses too much electricity, right?
For your legs Recently I ...
I have to read until late at all
I'm also learning acupuncture
I don't believe it
Really
It's a full pinhole
Just kidding
Do like a kid
Even though I didn't learn acupuncture
But for you, I really read until late
But because of love
I just know you can't do it
I can't
But I know one person can do it
My boss, Lin Bai Hui
His family, do business in rehabilitation center
he will definitely help you
Can not
What if he kneaded me and realized I had an injury?
Anyway, that's true
Hello
Chong, where are you?
Convenience store, why?
Something happened
Xie Rui
You come to me
What's the matter?
I just...
On the way, I found this one
So...
give you
No need
This is not a special gift
just go eat some food with me later, that's ok
Thank you
Jun Jun
Hello Auntie
It's great that you are here
Help me find Xiao Mai
I made an appointment with him to go see your mother
Last time he didn't go
Today I called, he didn't answer the call
I'm so anxious, you hurry and help me find him
Aunt, don't be frustrated
I heard Ding Yi say that Ma Sichong was in the Master's room
I'll take you there
What did he do at the Master's room?
I don't know too
I will go in first
You are waiting for me
Mei Ling Professor
About your health examination report
You have nothing to tell me?
That the university did not check and monitor
just want to give you one more chance
You still haven't thought to explain
Professor
I know I was wrong
But I want to beg you
You can can punish me
But do not unfold about my injury, can you?
Mai Sichong
I hope now, you will clear all of this
Tell me all
You must understand That this is not a small matter
What if the situation is serious?
The university has to punish you
You know?
Mai Sichong
You really let me down
How did you guys come?
The children told me, so I hurry come here
Xiao Chong, how is he?
This's son make me really frustrating
You guys...
Mom, how did you come?
Why would you dare to do something stupid like this?
This kind of serious matter, you dare to do it!
You know all
What did the professor say?
Not a big deal
Just being punished, Inevitable
Chong bro
You borrowed the storage report room key. To steal medical reports
This big deal, why did you keep me off for so long?
All right, now is not the time to talk about it
Hurry to the hospital with me
Checking the body this time, I made an appointment for a long time
Thank you you guys
Weiwei
Hurry, go with me
You are with him, so he can be sane
Let's go
Quickly
Go!
What's going on?
How is it?
Mom
I don't know, will it work? Why do you need treatment?
Be obedient, don't move
During this time what you do is only a matter
Finally, this time I can take you here
I will definitely heal you
I will take a photo of the good condition of my child now
Send it yo your dad
What's good? mom, don't be a kid
Don't move
No need to take it
Why? don't move
Got it
Doctor, how are my symptoms?
From the results of this examination
Symptoms are not very good
If you want to go back as before the injury
Would be really difficult
But you don't have to worry
We are...
It's okay
No need to comfort me
I know
Otherwise take it like this
You just treat him well first
We will not disturb
Okay
Weiwei
So let's go out first
Be a good boy
Let's go
We add a few more sets
You will feel it
Tell me if you feel hurt
Auntie, here's your water
You think...,my son...
American experts, come here a few days only
It's not easy that I can make an appointment for him
But when the time comes, can't be contacted
When asked, he said that he was meeting Sun Yang
You think, I should be angry or not
If you don't want me to notify the police, so calm down!
Auntie
Is it very difficult to treat the symptoms of Mai Si Chong?
It seems that the symptoms are not very good now
He was terrified that others would know his injury
The more people know, he was even more pressured
Weiwei, important things like this, he can tell you
Obviously, he trusted you a lot
My son
His whole life has been swimming all along
If one day really can't be an athlete
No way
Auntie, I studied physical therapy and rehabilitation
Our boss said
Knee injury
If you do a good physical It can be cured
really, Weiwei?
Then it's great!
The province team is close to accepting applications
Please take care of him
Don't let him freak out
Auntie, please trust me
My dear son
Be a good boy and Intend to practice
And don't forget drink health tonic as well
I know
Go quickly
After a while, the car is stuck
So I'm leaving
What did my mother talk to you?
Secret
Anyway, I don't want to ask
Have something to say, just say it
Aren't you awkward?
That day, because you went to help me at Peng Pai Company
So didn't go to see the doctor, right?
It's okay
However, it cannot be fixed
Why before, I was able to call you
But suddenly I can't call
Secret
What are you going to do?
No matter what it is
About swimming I definitely won't give up
Do you really think so?
That only thing I can think
Here's your cake
What do you think, Mai Si Chong think?
To steal medical reports
How do I know what he thinks?
Even me, he still didn't tell
I'm very angry
But...
Even Bro Chong has things that are not perfect
Sometimes heaven opens a window
But closed the side door instead
So your house is underground. Not has even a door
What do you mean?
This time does not count
Come another game
Hey!
We agreed, who loses that person pays
Mai Si Chong : You have 1 new message.
Chong bro come back
I don't play anymore
I'll go and comfort him
Aren't you angry with him just now?
Do you think I will be like women like you?
Said that angry and just angry
Cake, you pay too
Hey!
insane!
Really don't understand
OK, what is he going to do?
What kind of brain does this have to be?
Hearing that he didn't want the professor to know the injury
Afraid that the provincial team will not take him
But he's a college representative, isn't he?
That's right!
Weiwei, where are you now?
Like this, he's finished
Thank you
It's okay
Today I came here, I have something to ask you
Mai Shicong's knee, what happened?
You probably know a long time ago, right?
I just guess
Actually about his injury, I don't know how much
He never told me anything
But he likes to swim that much
He's gifted
I just feel that he's very unfortunate
Yes
He's just this age
It is a big problem
Are you guys still going to sign a contract with him?
This hard to say
If he does not sign into the province team
There must be no serious problems for sure
But if he lose the selection first
The value will not be very high
Why?
Doesn't sound like real?
If it were you?
How do you choose?
I don't like taking risks
And you?
I don't know
I still have a class, so excuse me
Weiwei
You try to let Si Chong think again
There is still another month
Thank you
Boss
You say that I have started physical therapy now
When is it okay to start acupressure for someone else?
Soon it should be 3 years
So long
What do you think?
I started learning acupressure with my father when I was 5 years old
Age 13 to actually do it for the first time
Still have to wait 4-5 years that my dad let me take care of the patient
Looks like this
Can't rush
All right
Boss
I have one thing, I want you to help me
What matters?
Would you please go to Mai Sichong' dorm?
Why?
If you're free, I want you to help giving him a physical massage
Help massage to Mai Si Chong
That's great!
I'm working on a new massage project recently
Still worried that I can't find research
If Mai Shi Chong agrees, it will be of great help
Weiwei
Mai Shi Chong, he ... will you agree?
Yeah
Of course
Let me do it
Really
Yeah
I have one thing, I want you to help me too
What?
Join our relay race
Okay
I'll join
Yes!
Weiwei
I think so well
Until then, I will take the first one
No no no
You take the first one
Or let Jun Jun leave first
Then I will run as a 4th person
Why?
Are you ok?
Coach Li from the provincial team Just call me
Ask me what your symptoms are
Everyone keeps asking me
Now they are very worried about you, what are you going to do?
Mai Si Chong
If you treat me
Trust others a little more
Tell me early
This would not be the case now
The number of universities that can compete, at first there was a limited quota
If they are not satisfied with you, they can not let you join
Until then, I can't help you
Coach
He's...
Mai Si Chong
Do you still respect me as a coach now?
I know what you are thinking
You think this, as long as little is known
The pressure in your heart is also less
You care or not
Who are you?
You're just a coward
You are just a runaway man
You...
You try to think carefully what I say
Mai Si Chong
I don't know if I can tell you this now
But there is something I have to say
You can feel comfortable
First, I promise
we will still sign a contract with you
will not forsake you
Second, if you give up the provincial team selection
Contract signing directly
I can convince the board
can double the value
I understand how you feel right now
But there is only one thing I can do
Hopefully this will make you more comfortable
You can think carefully
In the end, it is your own life