Your knees?
Is it okay?
It's ok
Hello Ding yi
My cell phone is on me
Why didn't you tell me?
Hello
The signal is not good at all
Mai Sichong, Wait for me!
Zhang President
This is Sun Yang's schedule of activities
Finished, please confirm
Okay
These two days must have been difficult for you
When this event done
You can take a break for two days
Thank you
Take this opportunity
Try asking the Mai Si Chong. Does he has time?
Just come and look around
and visit the company
Okay
I'll go back to the university in a moment
Go
Hey Chong bro
Where did you go last night?
Noting
Did nothing
I knew
Brother Chong, you're really shy
Jumping not enough last night?
Swim for the whole laps
Pei Pei coach is not here
I could swim less
Missing just one laps
Coach
Coach, I'll swim right now
Brother Chong, you lied to me
Ready?
The qualifying team at the provincial level is about to begin
To encourage everyone
The university
prepared to host
In the friendly competition of the university
Even if it's just a friendly match
But as long as it's a game
I hope that...
You will show your potential
Strive to be the first
Understand?
Understand
Coach
As it is a friendly match
So can I do it for friendship?
Withdrawing from competition
I think
for friendship
You still have to compete
This will give everyone an advantage
All contestants
Must be involved
Go to practice now
Tomorrow the hospital will have an expert from America meeting
You have to go
Brother Chong bet with me?
Last position
I must be the first
Will I get first place? I don't know.
But anyway, Ding Yi got the first place
Keep level
Bro Chong, don't be humble
I bet with you
Brother Rui, did you take it with him too?
I bet, I and Brother Rui for sure
Brother Chong, are you still kidding?
How could number one have two?
You keep the first from the end for yourself
Sichong
Peng Pai
If tomorrow can't come
Then it can be next time
Weiwei
Mei Weiwei
Bro
Bought it for me?
Just...
I am afraid that you will tease me
Am I that kind of person?
Or not
Err...
Tomorrow, at company have a Sun Yang meeting
But Si Chong couldn't go
Do you want to go?
Sun Yang
Yes
I can go?
Of course
Why are you going?
Are you a fan of Sun Yang?
You think
Before Sun Yang leave I have never watched every match
I will tell you
The meeting was a lot of people
You should be careful
Trust me
I will protect Weiwei well
Then see you tomorrow afternoon
When you come, call me
I will come down to pick you up
Okay
I still have to study, so excuse me
See you tomorrow afternoon
Okay
Bye bye
Weiwei
Junjun
No need to sleep
Next Wednesday, has a massage exam
We need to find a massage exam partner
Massage partner?
Lin Bai Hui
Can Tai Chi be used to protect yourself
Next Wednesday, come study with me
During this university there are psychopaths
Psychopath
You don't know yet?
Psychopaths stalking people at night
Secretly filming in the bathroom
They come in disguise
Put on a hat, put on a mask
CCTV cameras cannot see the face
This is too bad
Weiwei
Junjun
Recently, we have many activities.
You guys go back late
For safety
Otherwise
You guys bought a spray for protection
No
Like this
Sorry Weiwei
Wednesday I have a live broadcast
I have to go
Wing Chun is the original fierce martial arts of China
It is an attack block technique
Forget about it
Could you be a partner for a massage exam next Wednesday?
No problem
Welcome
Yu Xin
Are you busy?
Large cup 35, small cup 30, what kind do you want?
I don't drink coffee
In coffee there is a lot of caffeine
Drinking a lot is not good for the body
It also causes insomnia
What kind of coffee tastes good?
Yu Xin
I come today
Because I wanted to invite you
Join our physical therapy club
This is the first club in our field of physical therapy
Without you it's like a lack of spirit
And also, I really like you
You like me?
Cold outside but hot inside like you
If you were there
Everything must go well
Wait
If you want to use ...
a club
Come follow me, I will say
Not necessarily
No no no ,I'm not...
You're not, that's good
Today, in class...
You left this
this one
How much?
Do not pay
I buy you
Thank you
Err...
Our shop is closing. So you ...
You hurry back
So
About club activities
You can consider it again
Thank you
Weiwei
Sorry, I couldn't take the exam with you
You...
Can you find someone?
I've found
That's good
So...
You have to be very careful
Your power, don't let others know
To compensate you
Tomorrow I will take you to eat something delicious
Tomorrow I have an appointment
Have an appointment
What's the matter?
I will meet Sun Yang
Sun Yang
Where did you meet him?
FT Company
Is that a company that Senior Peng Pai trainees?
He brought you to meet?
The two of you are back together
No
Weiwei
When she was bullied
He walked away
This thing
Can you let it go?
I'm just going to meet Sun Yang
Not going to see Peng Pai
Mei Weiwei, Mei Weiwei
You're...
Why is your little brain so bad?
All right
I don't talk to you
Look
Sun Yang
Actually, my first gold medal was from Sun Yang
Even though he's leaving the industry now
But he is still my idol
So why don't you go with me today?
What are you going to do?
I...
Go...
I go to practice
Yeah
Go practice
Don't lie to me
Have you ever obeyed that?
Anyway, I have something to do
Don't ask me anymore
Okay, don't ask
Keep it well
May be in the future
You might only see me on the poster
You keep it well
So will you run?
run
Are you back?
Let's go eat.
Okay
Why are you and Li Dai Xi being together so often lately?
Just go to eat two times together
How about Wei ?
She's gone
So are you going?
Okay, let's go
Why hasn't Sun Yang come yet?
How do I look?
You're a lavender? (Fan's group name) , stand here
Sun Yang was close to come
This is not so bad
Sun Yang has arrived
Sun Yang
Who is she?
Why can she enter the FT company?
Go
This is our office space
Qiaoqiao sister
You come already
You...
At FT, do you have to dress formally every day?
Actually, it doesn't have to be
But every Friday is the company's Free Day
Today is free Day
Sports agent
It will be more informal compared to other artists
Oh
Let's go
Will take you to the meeting room
Okay
Then, we're going
Go
Why are the two of you so sad?
Weiwei has gone to meet Sun Yang
Why do you know And why I don't know
Mai Sichong
Why don't you take care of Weiwei?
Or will you really let she go with Peng Pai?
I...
Do you feel that She is like an old grandmother who is strict about the children's friendship
Keep eating
What reason do I have to stop she from going?
Sun Yang is her idol
Why does Weiwei want to meet other men?
You also like Sun Yang, isn't it? Why don't you go too?
Keep eating
You guys don't know
When Weiwei was in high school, gossiped until she had to quit
Moved to another school
At that time, the person she trusted most was her senior named Peng Yan
But when Weiwei was bullied
He just disappeared
Wait
Peng Yan
Now is Peng Pai
I think
He must be afraid of confronting the past, so he changed his name
Actually, using Sun Yang as an excuse
Brother Chong, where are you going?
You sit here
Peng Pai told me all
Thank you for supporting me
Before, I had been in Nanti
You can call me senior
Senior
Oh yes
Today I brought with you a present
Senior
I have been preparing for a very long time
Inside here I gather...
The achievements of you over the past 5 years
I also posted a photo
Please be careful
Hope you like it
I left the industry
The competition has nothing to do with me
However, I have to thank you very much
Brother Yang
Weiwei has always admired you
Can you bother taking pictures with her?
Can I?
Sure
Come on
Why are you with Sun Yang?
Was that guy an FT employee?
This woman is so ugly
Secretly approached our man
Thank you
Err...
This one...
Can you sign for me?
Thank you
Err...
I will give this signature to my friend
He is also a swimmer
He admires you very much
Would you please write to encourage him?
What's his name?
Mai Sichong
Si from Si Yi
Chong from Ling Hu Chong
Mai Sichong
This name is familiar
What about your own signature?
I have enough photos. Thank you
All right
You can give it to me
Thank you brother Sun Yang
I have got something to do
So, excuse me
Good bye
Thank you
It's okay, you don't have to send me
Be careful when you go back
Thank you
I will go send him
Wait for me for a while
What is lavender?
Actually sneaked into the back door
Relying on a boyfriend who is an FT employee
In order to meet Sun Yang, right?
Who are you? Do this again, I will call the security guard
You are really shameless
Don't you know that Sun Yang is our person?
My hand
Why should you hurt people?
You have no reason
How do you hurt?
No, I'm not
It's all red, you still say no
Help me
Still will say you didn't do
You guys look
It's all red
Weiwei
Sister Qioaqioa
Who are you?
I'm staff here
You guys, calm down first
Just an apprentice
Go get someone who can handle this
Should you guys calm down first?
Has anything? you can tell me
Sir, you can't go in
Sir
I think your employees are really unreliable
Not allowing fans to enter
Let only the girlfriend enter
Shameless
No, I'm not
This is misunderstood
I didn't hurt anyone
You take advantage of connection
And also pretending to be pitiful
I said I didn't hurt anyone
You didn't hurt anyone?
Then I will teach you
Don't you know what the consequences will be for the chaos in the company?
Don't want me to notify the police
Just calm down!
Who are you?
Let's go
She hurt us first
Right
You come back and explain this first
Weiwei
Are you ok?
I'm okay
Why didn't you answer my phone?
I might have turned off the sound at all
In the future, if there is something like this
Have to tell me
We have to rebuke
Damn not enough
Must defeat them
Never mind
Little one like you
I will protect you
All right
I'm really okay
Peng Pai
Weiwei Bag, why is it here with you?
Just a moment ago, two fans had invaded
Said that saw you take her to meet Sun Yang
That you came to create problems at the company
So where is she going now?
Went with that man already
You hurriedly followed her
Weiwei
Your bag
You still dare to come again
You take Weiwei came to the company
Why you leave her alone?
Weiwei
Sorry
I have something to talk with you
You dare to say it again?
Just now
When I send Sun Yang, meet Zhang President
I really don't know. That the company ...
Don't know?
Saying that you don't know is like warding off responsibility
Because of that, she had to transfer school. Do you know?
Peng Pai
You're just a two-faced person
Mei Weiwei was in a lot of pain because of you
I warn you
Stay away from her
Go
That day, my father had an accident
You can take it
What are you doing?
Mom
Your homeroom teacher called me to meet
Because of this girl, right?
This is not about her mother
You look
Where does she look like a student?
This is not really about her, mom
Go, back home
This is not about her
Mom
Why are you like this?
Peng Yan
Your father can't stand it. You quickly come back
When I arrived at the hospital
Doctor said...
My father couldn't handle the wounds
Then my father passed away
My mother sold the house
She can't live alone
So I stopped going to study abroad
After I graduated
I didn't want to contact my relatives again
So, I change my name
Later...
When you change QQ
Phone is broken
I tried to contact you
I send messages to you every day
But you did not reply
Now
I want to find it, I can't find it
Today is the same
Not on the side to protect you
Sorry
Sichong
Thank you
Today if it's not you, come catch up
Nothing already
So, I'm leaving
Let's talk
He...
He's been looking for you for so long?
4 years have passed
He had always wanted to explain this to you
What this means?
That means I'm very stupid
I didn't know before so I deleted the QQ message
Meaning he still cares for a fool like you
How happy are you stupid?
I will sleep
Your little stupid brain
There is no way to deal with such a difficult problem
Good night
Even though you've waited for her many years
But people are not in the same place
I've been waiting for her for 4 years
You just know her, not too long
Are you close with her?
Do you know what kind of person she like?
What do you want to say?
At that time I knew
That she has feelings for me
She and Peng Pai were in a relationship?
Now still not
But in the future, it's unlikely
Tomorrow I will compete. Will you come to see?
Tomorrow is my birthday
You probably won't leave me alone
Wait until I won
You will be the first physical therapist of the Olympic champion
He left the track slowly, right?
So what will you do if you lose?
I'm not losing
I won't
Mai Sichong
Thank you so much
I will always be by your side
Weiwei
I like you