It is raining outside
How can I get to the classroom on time?
I can't pick you up now
Find a way here by yourself
Why are you so late?
I was playing video games when you called me
There are many memorable moments in our life
It can be a warm hug
a romantic eye contact
a tempted heartbeat
or
a sudden touch
a kiss that you will never forget
These precious memories
that hide deep down in our mind
are sparkle love
Are you alright?
I will leave you here if you are fine
My name is Mei Weiwei
Since I was born
The static electricity in my body
is  extremely active
If my heart rate runs over 110
I will turn into a living Pikachu
and release electricity to all the people near me
The faster my heart rate, the stronger the voltage
However, my super power
haven't really hurt anyone yet
If you accept my electricity by accident
you will fall in love with the one you first see
but the fake love like this
it won't last too long
After 24 hours
the fragile bond will break up
Except this
If you ask me
what else
my lousy super power can bring to me
There is only one thing
which are endless troubles
Our experimental class is...
Mei Weiwei
Our group meeting will be over soon
and here you are?
I am so sorry
I had an accident on my way to the classroom
Just sit
We have taken classes for 3 weeks
since the military training ends
and I haven't met Zhang Yuxin yet
She is living in your dormitory, tight?
Go and ask her why
Okay
Alright, let't move on
In our rehabilitation class
There are only 4 students
But we are still a group
-Lin Baihui -Here
You are the monitor
so it's your job to organize some activities
so that everyone here can get along well
Okay class dismissed
Ms.Meiling excuse me
Can I have a word with you please?
I am in a hurry to a meeting
Find me in the lecture hall this afternoon
A cup of Americano please
Thank you
A cup of matcha latte please
Thanks
Hello Yuxin
Ms.Meiling asked me about you in the group meeting
she wonderer why you didn't attend classes
She had already called me
and I've told you that
I need to do the part time job in this cafe
which occupied most of my time
Enjoy your coffee
Alright
Why don't you pick me up today
Where did you go
Weiwei
I think I have a crush on a guy
Another!?
He got the first prize of the swimming competition
I met him when I am doing a interview
-Are you in the swimming team? -Yes, I am
Can I ask you a question?
What do you expect from the swimming team
Nothing special
I can be satisfied
if I can make some progress every single day
What are you dong here?
Are you doing interviews?
I can be your guest
What do you
expect from the swimming team
I am here to be the bottom of the team
so that my teammates can be more confident
I am sorry
I am here to interview the champion
not you
Fine, your champion is here
His name is Mai Sichong
His highest grade
on 100 meter freestyle is 5 minutes 35 seconds
He have been so popular since his high school
Nice to meet you
I am a journalist from school TV station
My name is Li Daixi
My major is sports journalism
Your job is to interview our champion
Why are you introducing yourself
Sorry
Mai Sichong, I have a question for you
What do you expect from the swimming team?
Winning the golden medal
But you are already got one
That's history, it means nothing to me
I am talking about my next competition
Cool!
Are you in a relationship with someone now?
I mean
Being in a relationship may affect your training
How do you get balance?
There is no such a thing like romance in sports
I am supposed to compete for my nation
My girlfriend's name is competition
Cool!
I have a feeling that Mai Sichong
will be my one and only
-Can you help me to get him? -No way
I have promised to my mother that
I won't use my super power again
How about this
I will replace you to take the massage class
The professor don't know you
You said you are busy
If you go to the massage class yourself
Your super power
will hurt people
No one can survive from your hands
Ms.Meiling I am assigned to this school
My attention is to go to the economy school
and I am not physically suitable
to give people massage
Could you pleas...
I am sorry?
Physically disabled?
What a lousy excuse
You think you can do whatever you want?
We have rules
You can go to the economy school
when your average grade is above 90
-Final offer. -90?
Stop
There is no negotiation
Your final grade will speak for you
Ms.Meiling!
Jesus
Is it so hard to open a door?!
So, you are the one who knocked me down in front of the library
Are you the one who block my way?
Your apology is accepted
Hey!
Kiss! Kiss!
Sichong
Girls are so open nowadays
Hello
everyone
I am Li Daixi from the TV station
If you want to know about the information of the freshmen
Feel free to ask me
Is Mai Sichong single?
I am sure about this
He is now but he will not very soon
Alright
It is so late
Although we are young
we need to get enough rest
Good night everyone
How is it going?
Did Ms.Meiling promise you?
She said that my final grade must be
90 or above
and she will approve my request
I don't think this is possible
Don't you give up!
You can help me this time
and in exchange
I will take your massage classes
I promise it is the last time
and I promise your massage grade
is above 90
Okay fine
You promise?
You can't change your mind
I promise
Thank you
Are you sure she is not a mute?
Is she angry about me because
I moved to your dormitory without her permission?
Don't over think
The only word I hear her saying
is "here"
On my marks, get set
You are 0.4 second faster than  last week
Mai Sichong
Come on!
Coach
You don't have to worry about him
He won't give up until he is able to
get the same grades when he was in high school
Just wait and see
Look at him
and look at yourself
So you are planning to time Mai Sichong
forever?
Can I?
How dare you
There are only two months left
We don't have enough spots for everyone
But it doesn't mean that the rest of you
don't have to take trainings
You need to be aware of your ultimate goal
I don't care about your future plan
But as long as you are here
You can't stop training
Which one is Mai Sichong?
The one on the seventh track
You can tell?
Of course!
Let's go
Alright
Rest for a second
Excuse me
what's your emergency?
Hello
We are from the rehabilitation class
Sometimes we take the same class with the swimming team
I am not so clever
and I need practice
Can I practice on one of the team members?
This is my student card
Right
I will find you someone
Mai Sichong, come here
and the rest of you, dismiss
This is one of your classmate, she will practice on you
So yesterday, you are in purpose
Coach
You are training right now
It's so rude to interrupt
I can come next time
Our training is over
But we are practicing massage
Is it a good time to practice here?
I don't see any trouble here
Sit
What are you waiting for?
You need help?
Swimmers are most likely
to hurt the joints
on their shoulders
and secondly
the knee joints
I'm a swimmer
how could I hurt my knee?
Stay away from me
Don't!
Watch out!
You are so weird
like a ghost around me
I am telling you
You are not my type
Please leave me alone
What?!
So what's your type actually?
Don't even try
His only lover
is his swimming glasses
Ding Yi and Xia Rui, Let's go
Wait! In our last interview
I am not done yet
I want to know
Since when ddi you start learning swimming?
Why are you so passionate about it?
and, is it real that you haven't fall in love with a girl?
Hello
Let's go back to the dormitory
Why did you stop just now
Daixi
I think I have seen a old friend
Maybe not
But anyway
The one you fall in love with is
that rude guy who knocked my down before
Your taste is terrible
yeah, horses for courses
But how could you stop your magic
for a random guy
Give me Mai Sichong's Wechat account
I can handle this
I bought some new lipsticks
-Wanna try? -Sure
I am Mei Weiwei
I am so sorry about today
Can I meet you some time
No need
and I don't think everyone can talk to me in Wechat
Son!
Yes
I have told you that don't come here with your fancy car
It embarrasses me
come on
I was going to drive that nanny car
But I have it washed
Fine
Are you thirsty?
Drinking beverage is not good for your health
remember?
But you just ignore me
You are messing with me?
aren't you?
When I was little, you held me in arms
played with me and gave me back to dad
when I cried
How dare you judge me like that
I suffered so hard
to give birth to you
Fine your ingrate son is leaving
Wait
Are you moving a supermarket here?
Share with your roommates
I am leaving
Why are you in such a hurry
I am not finished yet
What do you want
speak now
I met your Professor Liu the other day
She said all the files are well packed
which means your report is still in the school
-What? -Don't worry
She said it is only privacy
-No one can see that. -No
I need to get it my own
Don't over think
I promise your dad not to tell you this
But I think
it is your own business
You have the right to know
Right?
So here I am
-Keep it as a secret -Okay
I got it
You can go now
Tomorrow is my birthday
-I will pick you up -Okay
Focus on your training
Who is this girl, is she so fond of me?
I am going to lose the game
Did any of you sell my number?
I didn't
I am going to take a jog
I gave your number to Li Daixi
Who is that?
The girl who interviewed you before
looks pretty
Sichong, focus!
I met your Professor Liu the other day
She said all the files are well packed
which means your report is still in the school
Sichong
Why do you want the key of data room
It's my own business
It's also my business
I am responsible for this
it's my job to keep them
-Calm down -Give me back please
Just one hour
I am begging you
please
What do you hiding from me?
You're not coming to school under an imposter, are you
Of course not
I will tell you some day
There are cctv in the corridor
Watch out
Don'e blame to me if things go wrong
Hello Daixi
I will send you location
Come here soon
Now?
Yes
Daixi, come to the data room asap
Where is he?
He can't be far away
Wait
Daixi
I have an idea
What?
I have things to do
Mai Sichong
Are you alright?
Did we make it?
Probably
Great
When he looked me, I saw stars in his eyes
Why he left in a hurry?
Did he get shy?
Dingyi
What's wrong?
Is coach Peipei here?
What's that?
I got  this
from Avatar square
Don't forget
to put that thing back to the data room
I think I am ill
My heat beats so violently