During this university A dangerous person appears
Please all students to be careful
If you suspect being stalked
Immediately notify the police
I'll take care of you
Why do you seem so worried about Weiwei?
Are you jealous?
If you want someone to protect you, come see me
I give you 20% off
You can do it?
If you don't keep following me I will be very grateful
I followed you?
There are many beautiful college students
I have good things, why am I interested in people like you?
You remember what you said and what you did to me
Why?
I'll say. Why?
You...
Weiwei
You think...
Do you think other people will see my strength last night?
Trust me
Even if others see
He might have dreamed of it
Don't worry
So I go to study first
So
After finish class, I'll come to you
Why you have to come to me?
There are a lot of things in the university lately
So I can protect you
Physical condition like me
You don't need to protect me
That's right
Can't you just want to protect?
Give  you
Ding Yi told me that...
Every time after he was scolded by Coach Pei Pei
Will eat this candy
You eat
Maybe it will make it better
Okay
So I'm going
Finished class, will come to you
Junjun
Let's go out on Saturday. There is an exhibition
Invite him to come out as well
We all at the same university
It's a destiny
You don't have to invite
About the letter
If you don't have time, it's ok
Next Saturday I would like to invite you to have afternoon tea together
Are you free?
Junjun
Why are you still at the dorm?
Where are you going?
I'll go and see if there is a CCTV in that area
Not sure that the villain might be captured
I'm going with you
Let's go
Weiwei
There are CCTV
Yes
Not sure that all images may be saved
So let's hurry and go look at the CCTV in the control room
Hurry up
Not in time to attend class
Go
Come in
What's the matter?
Hello
We are...
Something happened last night, so we wanted to see it
CCTV on Zhi Xing Road
So let me see it for you guys
Thank you
Zhi Xing Road
CCTV cameras on Zhi Xing Road last night a bit problem
Repairing
May not have been recorded
So...
When will the repair be completed?
I'm not sure
I still have to submit my application for study
This is late
Otherwise you will go back first
I'll check it again
Err...
But it is really important
Go
We just want to see...
I'm really busy
เราไปกันเถอะ
Let's go
Go
Weiwei
You just...
Found something?
Junjun
Why are you coming quietly?
I just...
Like I met a guy last night
So...
Or that the security guard is ...
I was just wondering
Because of his figure and also his legs
Very similar to the villain I met last night
Mei Weiwei
What are you thinking?
Two women investigate
Think heaven will protect you?
I know you don't have to say it
What do you know?
Be careful about safety
I told you if there was something, you have to call me
I don't want to bother you every time
Give me a mobile phone
Don't forget next time
Have to call me
Weiwei
I suddenly realized that...
I made an appointment with a friend to see a cartoon exhibition
I will be back too
You can message me with anything
That you bought, don't you eat?
I am full
This evening, don't forget to come to the swimming pool
Weiwei
Can you pay attention?
That we tried many today, will affect the competition on the day after tomorrow
Again
Mai Sichong
How are you?
The neck is not okay?
Was the shock too much?
It seems...
Nothing
I was wrong
Just kidding
Now, you were electric shocked, is it useful? I don't know
Why do you have to do this?
What if I can't control electricity?
In the past, it was not well controlled
It's still alright
All right
Time
Ready
Go
Fight
Quick
How much?
51.09 second
Faster again
My statistics have always been international level, right?
In the future
Wait for me a little more
when I win
You will be the first physical therapist of the Olympic champion
So what will you do if you lose?
I'm not losing
I won't
Weiwei
With that security guard, how are you going to deal with?
Otherwise, should we notify the police?
But what if we find the wrong person?
Investigate a little more, we will know
Now
Just luring a tiger out of the cave
Chong bro
Can you say something that is the language of the athletes?
But he is a security guard
He won't know how to deceive people?
Why are you saying another idiom?
You really are a creature that talks a lot
Can you talk about your family later?
Who is the same house?
Junjun
There is something I want to disturb you
What?
We can use beauty
Lure him
Not like this
I didn't tell that Jun Jun to be the lure
So what you mean is ...
What do you guys think?
This woman is not bad at all
Stop tease now
Smile
Don't take it
I think
Still missing something
Missing what?
Which one do you want?
Ok stop
Come on
All right, stop
We have to keep thinking that
Where to catch this psychopath?
Of course, it must be the place where you meet him most often
Brother Chong, don't pretend to be playing
Stop
Go in
Sichong
Xie Rui
Li Dai Xi
Let me out
Din Yi
Can you be a man?
Go, hurry up
Hello, Chong bro
We have grown to this size already. There is no other way?
Ting Yi started speaking with an idiom
Sister
Now you are facing humiliation
Wait to catch that psychopath. Will definitely make a name for the family
Wait, Li Dai Xi
Wait for me to catch that psychopath first. I'll teach you how to say the right way
Where will you go?
Stop
You go away
He is a security guard
Student
Let me go
I just made a mistake for the first time
Next time I don't dare to do it
It doesn't matter if you do it the first time
We called police, take him
Please don't
Let me go
Very dedicated
But even if you are a man, you shouldn't catch the culprit yourself
Now men are insecure
Everyone
Being brave is good
But when in danger
The first thing to do is notify the police immediately
Understand?
Okay, so we're going
So that CCTV
Should be able to capture the villain, right?
I've watched that CCTV already
No scene can be used at all
Don't think
We...
Shall we celebrate?
Of course, let's celebrate
I put so much effort
It's everyone's work, isn't it?
What
I didn't help?
Let's go
Trust me
CCTV has a limited time
When the time is over, it will automatically delete
Cheers
Today we do a big thing
Should universities give us a banner of praise?
Yes
Should give us
Actually
I prepared
To everyone already
Really?
Not joking
Put it in our dormitory
Why put it in your dorm?
Building B Room 517
Our room
Yes
Is it a love letter?
The two of you couldn't have ...
Junjun
You don't like me, right?
Insane
Like you?
She must have taken the wrong drug
Then someone likes you? Li Dai Xi?
Junjun
You look at these 3 people who do you like?
No
Just say it
I will recommend
You like Mai Sichong
I drink for you both
Why drink for us?
Everyone let's celebrate
Come on, everyone cheers
Cheers
Li Dai Xi
You are so heavy, who is going to support?
You like me
So you won't let me lose weight, right?
What practice should you go to?
Build muscle
What
Continue?
Muscle
That means your waist is not good
You are!
Sis Wei
Why does she like to say I like her?
Li Dai Xi
I see you like me
Obviously, I'm the one you like
All right, Junjun, help me
Junjun
Come on
We're going back
Be careful
Xie Rui
Jun Jun is my childhood friend
Do not bully her
Have you ever seen me bully anyone?
No
Here
There is another crazy person
Let's go
What are you watching?
This time is a warm-up match
To see the work of everyone
You guys can relax
Except Ding Yi
You guys don't need
to be pressured
Coach
Go practice
Don't linger
Tomorrow I have a competition
Will you come to see?
Senior, do you wait a long time?
Not at all
You have no something to do, right?
No, I don't
All cleared
Even if the psychopath has been caught
But walking at night have to be careful, you know
I knew
Thank you
Why are you free today?
Before, I was very busy
So these two days were stopped
Have a little time to rest
Tomorrow is my birthday
Our appointment, you have not forgotten, right?
Tomorrow?
Not the day after tomorrow?
You remembered my birthday wrongly
You've something to do tomorrow?
Tomorrow I have a competition. Will you come to see?
That we tried many today, will affect the competition on the day after tomorrow
I reserved a delicious restaurant
You probably won't leave me alone
Okay
On the way, haven't eaten anything yet?
When you haven't come yet, I ordered a strawberry cake that you liked
Thank you
The competition is about to begin.
Invite the contestants to the track
The staff will test each person's body
To keep the competition going smoothly
You intend this
Wei Wei saw, that she must be happy
If finished, we will go out first
I wish you success
Thank you
I go out to help
How are the windows and doors?
Junjun
How did you get here?
Come see you guys
Why are you in such a hurry?
Anyway, you can't get 1st place
Don't run to me
This time I got another last place
Coach Pei Pei will definitely take me to death
Fight
Where's Weiwei?
Has been out since morning
Should have gone to Peng Pai senior's birthday party
But she left me telling you that
Fight this time
Start the competition
Everyone
Ready
- Is that he ...
- Is it late?
Let's watch the university swimming competition live
This's Mai Sichong, right?
Yes
The person behind will overtake him
How does he swim?
Quick
Fight
Quickly
What's happened?
Fight
What's going on?
God, why is it like this?
Before this was not like this
Will lose
Mai Sichong , fighting
Weiwei
Sister Qiao qiao
Didn't you go to Peng Pai's birthday party?
My friend on the swim team had a little accident
I'm going to see him
Weiwei
Why?
Did you know that Peng Pai ,he...
He, what?
What's happened?
Chong bro
Coach
I go see him
Go
Peng Pai, today he...
He will confess his love to you
Confess love
Hello
Hello Mr.Peng
Ms.Mei Weiwei sent you a gift. Now it's on the way
Almost arrived
Bro
Sorry
Today I have a really important thing to do
Probably can't go
Don't wait for me
Have fun with your friends
Happy Birthday
Weiwei
You...
You didn't go to the birthday party?
Is Mai Sichong win?
He's...
Lost
Not just losing
It's also the worst result since joining the team
54.57 second
Where's Mei Weiwei?
Should have gone to Peng Pai senior's birthday party
Mai Sichong
What's wrong with you guys?
Sis Wei did not go to watch Bro Chong compete
Two days Chong Bor kept swimming and not going anywhere
On the results of your health examination
You don't want to tell me?
I heard he had an injury. But did not let the Professor know
He's a college representative, isn't he?
He must have really finished
Will his sports career end?
Mai Sichong
Mai Sicong wake up