The spirit of a good man
Really comfortable
Should have a bath with more bubbles
This will help the blood circulation in the body
We haven't taken pictures yet
Let's take a photo
Exactly!
Okay
Come on
Rui
Stand on top
You stand in front
Your face is so small
I can't shoot
Come on
Is there me in the frame?
What did you take? Give me
Okay
1 2 3
eggplant
Okay
Like I'm closing my eyes
So
Where do we go next?
I'm not going
Err, I...
I will go home
Already bought a car ticket?
Yes
I gonna go
Okay Bye bye
Bye bye
I will be back too
I made an appointment with my friends
I am going too
At the coffee shop, I have something to do
Bye bye
So
I gonna go too
Tell us to go and just go
So?
Why go all together?
So
Dai Xi
So let's go shopping
Go
Err...
Do you have any wishes?
I...
Previously had
Now...
And you?
I...
At first there was no
Now there is...
Err...
This place seems far from the station
Otherwise let me request a car
Drop you off at the dormitory
No need
I can go by myself
And...
You trust me
Next I ...
Will not interfere with any more chaos
Story of you with Mai Si Chong
You handle it yourself
I...
You buy shoes for training at a provincial club
one pair, is it good?
If I've gone
Don't you think?
I have to be alone
Now your thoughts are very dangerous
I can't always be with you alone
Otherwise you are thinking of ...
What does Chong bro want to do?
Have lunch
He want to have lunch
So hungry
Go find your Dai Xi
Go
How is it?
Weiwei
Last night, you and Mai Si Chong
Say it
What did you guys do?
Nothing
Nothing, why does your face turn red like this?
Student Mei Weiwei
You and Mai Sichong
Just recently dating
Why?
Or have to date each other for a long time
So can do such thing
Like that ...
You guys
Can you help me keep an eye out for Mai Si Chong
Is he doing anything too much?
This is Weiwei's first love
First love
Don't let I watch
People who are in love are not really the same
Get out
What do you think every day?
How far has you and Meiwei developed?
Dai Xi said that you have done too much
You guys have..... done, right?
What?
Student Mei Weiwei
Is the way of showing your love, it's too much?
Why did you let him lead like this?
You have to learn to control the game
So how do you control love? Master Li
The most important point is...
Women say that is not willing, is not willing
The man has no right to say anything
No matter what
But I'm willing
You're so obsessed with sex that you've been deceived by him
Our Weiwei
Yesterday was a clear girl. Who still don't wear a complete set of underwear
Today, you have been fooled by him
What?
Wait, like that as you say, we haven't done
What are you and Li Dai Xi thinking?
Come here
- I and Mau Si Chong
- I and Mei Weiwei
Just hold hands
Not too much
One kiss
Just this
So?
Just that makes you so happy
I think what are you all doing?
What can I do?
Then, Li Dai Xi, let me watch you all day
Then you guys are at the university. Do you only hold hands on days?
Too sweet
I already told you that I will go to see Mei Ling Professor
This winter holiday, you and Bro Xia going to keep practicing with the provincial team
Hui Hui has moved out
How to maintain a long distance relationship?
There are no pros to play online games
Left me alone
Thanks
You...
Why come to my coffee shop again?
I just want to find a place
read a book
Yu Xin
Do you have time?
Uncle, hello
I am her college friend
And also the head of the room
Even though I don't know what you are thinking of doing here today
But...
This is a public place
You just please
Don't hurt other people
Or not able to curse
You trust me
She is my daughter
So I'll go wait in the shop
Why did you come?
During the winter holidays, you didn't come back home
I miss you
Therefore stopped by to visit you
Over the years I have been very busy
Not taking good care of you
But now it's okay.
I've resigned
resigned
I decided to leave FT
Open a coffee shop
So I can have time to take care of you
Yu Xin
That day, I was a little flustered
I'm very sad
I'm really sorry
Many days ago, I...
Been home and thinking for a long time
In the past, I spent too little time with you
Even if you are free
Still have to pay attention
Need to take care
The past cannot be solved
But I swears
I will start from now on
Do my best to be a good father
Dad welcomes you home anytime
I'll go back
I will visit you often
Are you ok?
Why did you go so long?
Manager, I'm sorry.
I haven't finished the conversation just now.
This is also a working place
You have to fight
This project must be negotiated by tonight
Manager, I vomited three times
I can't drink anymore
I really don't understand
You followed Chairman Zhang for many years
What did you learn?
I will recommend one more time
Don't try to act like him
Today it is out of date
This chance
Not that anyone has
Mr. Li's team looked at you very well
You drank a drink to make him happy
So it end in one meal of this meal
Otherwise
Definitely had a second meal
Come cheers
This kid is not bad at all
Not bad
This semester, you do not bad at all
I asked the secretary
Your GPA has reached the threshold for transfer Major
Go fill out the form and send it to me
Professor, what day must I return to you?
Must be as soon as possible
Weiwei
Do you think well, that you will transfer Major?
No
Why?
You don't want to transfer Major?
Mai Si Chong is a swimmer
You are his personal physical therapist
Like this, you can follow him everywhere.
So happy, right?
This is my personal physical therapist, Mei Weiwei
And become the best physical therapist in the world
Of course
She is also my most favorite person
Can you stop imagining?
You are not afraid of your electricity
Will someone know it?
Not like that
Are you back?
About transfer Major
Weiwei, actually, I didn't always understand
Now you can go to this major very well.
Why do you still want to transfer Major?
Or think that our major
Is it too old?
No no no
I have another reason
Mei Wei is in this room right?
Below, someone came to see you
I go see
Auntie, let me go to meet Weiwei
How old are you?
Why does the smell of the liquor are so buzzing?
Can't
It's very late today
Today I must meet Mei Weiwei
Go back and talk later
Go back and talk tomorrow
มีเรื่องอะไรกันคะ
Auntie
I'm sorry, he's my friend
So drunk
Now you are students
Can't drink alcohol too much
Sorry
Okay, send him back too
Ok
Why are you drinking so much?
Watch out
Are you going to find Sis Wei again?
You guys are too sweet.
In the evening, she doesn't eat enough, so she can get frustrated
Watch out
There are steps, be careful
Why are you drinking so much?
I'm ok
Are there any people in your room?
I will have him pick you up
Are you ok?
Hello, Weiwei
Hello
Mai Si Chong
Peng Pai , he's drunk, now I ...
I'll tell you
Weiwei is mine
She's nothing to you
Do you know?
What are you doing?
Take it
This is the key chain that you gave me
You keep it
Take it back
Ok
I'll take it back
I didn't want you to get it back
I just want you to be by my side
You are so drunk
I'm going to buy you a bottle of water
You obviously like me
Why has it changed now?
Why can't we be together?
Weiwei
Only I am honest with you
In Mai Si Chong's heart, it was only a matter of swimming
Let me go
Forgot it
Mai Si Chong
Don't come let me see your face again
Just now
Does it hurt to get caught like that?
I'm ok
Mai Si Chong
Are you still angry?
Are you angry me?
I'm angry
but not you
I'm angry that...
Why can't I run faster?
Why can't I be by your side all the time?
I'm angry that I'm your boyfriend
But still makes you sad
Weiwei
I will have to go to training camp soon
I hope
You will tell me anything
I will support you fully
Why?
Intend to come to the company. will you come to punch me?
Do not find another reason to deal with Mei Weiwei
Otherwise, I cannot guarantee
For her, I can do anything
You know it
I have many memories with her that you don't know
I didn't come to listen to your nonsense
I just want to tell you that
From now on
Stay away from Mei Weiwei
Did you hear it?
Who determines that I can't like her?
Like?
What does your "like" mean?
You don't have to let juniors like me teach you
Xiao Mai
When you get to the provincial club
You have to be nice
Meeting for the first time, you have to be nice to match with other people
You know?
I know
Then at night
If turn off the light already
Just sleep, don't secretly play your phone
I know
Your mom is planning to let you carry it all over the house
Okay mom, that's enough
This one, I don't want
The college friends saw me all laughed at me
Laugh what?
All right
I gonna go
You don't like eating durian candy, right?
Actually, now I feel that...
It's pretty good
Enough
Go
So, I'm leaving
Safe trip
Bye bye
How do you know I'm here?
Innocent that I couldn't hear
Some people are old like this and still eat durian flavored candy
Not too naive?
Just know that you like to eat
You don't like it?
Yeah
Durian candy is this delicious
Let you eat, it so waste things
I gonna eat it
You're so innocent, okay?
I gonna go
Go
Why?
Don't forget to make video calls with me every day
Must be reported every day
I know
Eat more
And sleep more
Intend to practice
But, are you going?
All right
Go
Bye bye
Don't worry
I will hurry to come back
So, I'll go
Go
Bye bye
I represent the coach to inform everyone that
During training sessions
It is necessary to cut off all kinds of communications
Every day after training is finished
We will return the mobile phone
Give you an hour
Go contact
Relatives and girlfriend
The rest
Do not be distracted
Take out the mobile phone
Your cell phone?
I didn't bring a mobile phone here
Did not carry a mobile phone
Take out the mobile phone
Mom
Take it out
Everybody
Go back to bed early
Quit line
Are you at the provincial club yet?
How are your teammates?
Is Xia Rui in the same dorm with you?