Why did you bring me here?
Just go, then you'll know, hurry up
Today I am not in the mood to practice
Not going to practice
There is something to surprise you
Senior, we are here
Weiwei
Sichong
Where is he?
Mai Sichong
Sun Yang
Hello
Why didn't you tell me before?
Surprise
Sun Yang bro
Thank you for coming this time
I returned to college this time
It's a secret
Why don't you say something?
What can I say?
Sichong
You just talked to Sun Yang
Me and Weiwei are going to buy something to drink
Let's talk
Sichong
Do not know that this place has changed?
Can you take me in and have a look?
ok
Sun Yang came to university today
In order to meet you guys
I didn't think that Sun Yang Bro
Will accept the requests of a small fan club like me
Mai Sichong must be really happy
Peng Pai Bro
Thank you very much
Weiwei, are you so worried about Sichong?
Who's going to be worried about a crazy person like this?
Bitter coffee
I'm going to add some sugar
This place is still the same
You have changed quite a bit
This kid doesn't look like before
You know me when I was as a kid?
Thank you
Oh yeah, bro
I will give this signature to my friend
He is also a swimmer
He really admire you
What's his name?
Mai Si Chong
Si from Si Yi, Chong from Ling Hu Chong
At that time I realized that...
Previously, I've gave you an award
Bro
Actually, I have always had one regret
You retire too quickly
So I did not compete with you
Otherwise
Let's compete
Now?
Bro, aren't you there a waist injury?
Just for fun
Don't be seriously
Can't like that
I have to do my best
Are you ready?
Come on
You count
Count to 3
It's okay, Mai Si Chong
Thank you bro
How is it?
Do you think well?
Senior means ... swimming
Otherwise, what will?
Today I'm on a mission
Mission?
Mei Wei said to me
About your situation
So now, what do you think you will do next?
Said not to hesitate Would have been a lie
You don't have to look at me
How I choose, you can see
The way of life. Was defined
Different paths The view is different
There is no right or wrong
Until today, you're asking if I regret it
I regret
But I'm not sorry
Because this is the path that I chose
I can just keep walking
Before, I thought
Everything I think will be come true
But now I am not as confident as before
I really don't know
I will win or lose
But...
I still want to try it one more time
Thinking to try
There must also be time
Actually, if today I did not come out
You won't give up
Because in your heart you already have the answer
But you just don't want to say
You...
Worried that it would not be able to come true
In the past I had not joined the province team
Can swim faster than you
The little girl said that you were always confident in yourself
Pretending to not hurt Even though I am still hurt
Even though
Still have to hide the medical report
Although it looks very funny
But isn't this an important matter for athletes?
Why is there anything, she tells you all?
Is she your girlfriend?
No
No?
So I can flirt
Look at her too cute
Can't
I mean...
Not yet
I'm not teasing you
Not having love is good
Having a girlfriend will make your heart insecure
Until then, You will feel that
Gaining experience in swimming
It would be more fun to hold a little girl on this path
She is not the same
She is my inspiration
All right
Let's go
Yu Xin, you've arrived
You come to practice quickly
Otherwise it will be easily injured
You called me
because...
Right
Meeting about activities
Even now we are missing one more person
But we have all signed together
However, you should prepare yourself
You look at Wei Wei
During this time she intends to run every day
You can practice by yourself
Practice yourself
Practice yourself, it's ok
What's the matter?
Furious that big tree
Big tree?
Sun Yang
Sun Yang came to Nan Ti
Bro
It looks like Sun Yang was secretly filmed
Yang bro
Someone took a picture of you at the university
And posted on the internet
Right now, there were people in front of the door
What should we do?
I have a way
Everyone, don't take pictures
Sun Yang came personally, okay?
Don't take pictures
All done
They followed Mai Si Chong
But he could not be able to resist for long
I think this kind of thing is fun
Yang bro
Now is not the time to joke
Let's hurry
I had the driver wait at the university gate
Sun Yang Bro
Today I really have to thank you
Make you in trouble
It's ok
Never mind
Take good care Mai Si Chong
I have no problem
Ok
So, excuse me
Hurry
Where's Sun Yang?
It's all because of you
Missed the big news
I...
Sun Yang
Don't have to go
What are you doing?
That's not Sun Yang
That's Chong
How do you know?
I sleep with him every day
Just seeing one of his hair, I can see it
Let's go
I will take you to eat...
Strawberry cake
Really?
Sun Yang
I think it must really be you
Can you sign your name?
Sun Yang
Do not take
Sorry
Thank you everyone
Can't take pictures
Sun Yang
Sorry
If all done, don't forget to tell me
The story of Mai Si Chong is very interesting
If he has signed a contract with our company
Would be very fun
My heart really wants him to sign a contract
I watched
He has a passion for this career path
He was probably better than me that year
Not having to mention his inspiration
Yang bro
You looked very enthusiastic just now
If the company knows you and your fans
What is it about?
Or do you want me to make a stressful face? In front of a fan?
You shocked me!
They're all gone, right?
Should be
Thank you
To find a place like this
I'm tired of dying, do you know?
If not, come a bit far
How to get away from the fan club?
Come on
Let's go
People are gone
Umm
Is it ok?
I'm hungry
Let's go get something to eat
Let's go
Yu Xin
Dad bought this for you
You don't have to fool me with food
Have anything, just hurry to say
You haven't been home for a long time
Can't you just go home to eat with me?
Who are you like?
To be so stubborn
You just can't accept Mei Yun
The three of us, let's stay together as a family
Who is your family of three?
live well
Zhang Wei Xin
You go back to your mistress
How can you speak like this?
I am just going to say this
My mother died, the bones were not cold yet
You went to live with this fox lady
Are you guys not ashamed?
What the hell are you talking about?
Who are you?
You dare to hit her
I am her father
Even so, it can't hurt other people
Being a man can't hurt a woman
Even without saying that Yu Xin is your daughter
Hello
President Zhang
There were some students secretly filming Sun Yang at the university competition
It looks like Peng Pai take him to there
How could this happen?
I will hurry now
Yu Xin
We will meet again
Are you ok?
Yu Xin
Why did you follow me?
Don't you think I'm embarrassed enough?
Do not let a cold
Come on
You guessed, today I am competing with Sun Yang
Who win?
Must be Sun Yang
Isn't there me in your heart?
Or is it you who won?
Why are you so good?
Of course
So I decided
From now on, I will practice well
Join the province team
Win the championship
And
If not you
Maybe I would have given up
Actually, I didn't help you much
It's you who thinks by yourself
Whoever it is today
Ding Yi
Xie Rui
Or even the boss
They all help you
You are not the same
Actually
You have helped me many times
Do you remember when the car crashed in high school?
Did you save someone?
Student
You finally recover
I'm so shocked
Be patient, I'll call 120 for you
Hello
120 or not?
I disturb you guys, please send someone to urgently
Please send someone here now!
The person I helped was you
Right
At that time I thought where the angels flew down, help
Unthinkable
It was actually a Pikachu
Why?
Are you disgusted?
No, I'm not
Mei Weiwei
Thank you
Thank you what
Thank you for coming into my world
You keep talking, food all cold
Let's eat
Oh yeah
Almost forgot
Why did you tell Sun Yang that I stealing the medical report?
It's embarrassing, you know?
Who made you do this stupid thing?
Pikachu got up
I'll go back to the dorm
You wait for me
Peng Pai
I've always looked at you well
Why would you break the rules like this?
You took Sun Yang...
Meet friends
And also let him go into the water to compete with others
How do you let me protect you now?
Sorry, Mr.Zhang
It was my mistake
This is a company
Not a place for you to show your personal courage
The situation of your family
I knew
You have always done very well
But why this time...
You think about your future. To exchange the future...
Until you have to lose everything?
Mr.Zhang
Thank you for training me
This will not affect you
So as a result, I'll be responsible
Excuse me
I trained you, I don't need you to thank me
After Lin Bai Hui came to our dormitory
Ding Yi changed to another person
Every day urged Lin Bai Hui to give him a massage
Pikachu
Have you shut down?
Your face
Why is it so hot?
I'm okay
Yu Xin
Weiwei
Let's go back to the room
A wristwatch, you have it to measure your heart rate, right?
Most of the time, the body's reaction won't lie
Sichong
Brother, about today, I haven't thanked you yet
If you really want to thank me
There's one thing you can do
At grade 12
Weiwei joins the relay team
At that time I was the captain
She is the most devoted and lovely person on our team
Day 7, month 7 in that years
She secretly gave me a gift
Since then, I knew
She has feelings for me
Bro
What do you want to say?
I've been waiting her for 4 years
You just recently got to know her
Are you close to her?
Do you know what kind of person you like?
Have you ever played the game?
Players who keep letting the other side relent
Finally, you will hear the word
Defeat