You said yes to me
You won't regret it later?
My electric
It's ok
Whether you conduct electricity or not
I'm the same
Okay, isn't there a race tomorrow?
Let's go back quickly
I won't go
If you still don't return it will be late
Do you really want me to go?
I won't go
Hurry back
You can catch a cold
I returned to the dormitory
Are you awake?
Would you like to drink some water?
Thank you
Where's Weiwei?
Stayed out with Mai Shi Chong all day
But today they really are...
Using Nanti as a love scene
Jun Jun
Actually, I have always wanted to ask you
The one you like
Not Xia Rui
Right?
You guys are here
Jun Jun
Here for you
Today is difficult for you
Thanks
Eat more
This is Yu Xin's
Thank you
What do you want to eat? Just take it
However
Mai Si Chong bought it
A while
Show your true potential
Make the best swimming record
understand?
understand
But this is a competition
How will it be like in normal practice?
Ding Yi
You did not participate in the competition
Why are you still here and telling me what to do?
Fighting
Get on the car
Thesis Examination Results
You only do 1.2%
There should be no problems
Actually, professor wanted me to change the topic as well
This is just a university pre-examination. There is still a lot of time
Weiwei
Sis
Where are you going to hurry?
I have something to do outside
Qiao Qiao
We have to see the professor to get the paper exam results
Let's go
Okay
So, we gonna go
Bye bye
You guys
Not talking well
The matter has passed
Big brother, I've known you for 4 years
No need to tell how well I know you
Are you happy? I can see
I know the feelings you have for Mei Wei are not the same
But she must not know for sure
I think...
You have to tell her
FTI Company
Sheng Yu: Did you hear the news yet? Zhang Wei Xin will resign
President Zhang will resign now
Fighting Fighting
Nanti will win
How did you guys come?
Why is this ...
Can't see?
Come and cheer you guys
Also here
With cheer flags
It's over
You guys do this If we lose, where will we put our face?
Bad mouth, how can you lose?
Just...
Why haven't you entered the field yet?
All right
Provincial teams allow friends and relatives to attend the races
But everyone still has to register
Okay?
Okay
Let's get into the field
Let's get into
So crazy
You don't have anything to tell me?
Fighting
That's it?
Wait and see
I will show you one place
Let's go
Brother Chong hurts again, right?
It's okay, he'll be able to do it
Are you ok?
I'm ok
I've been doing physical therapy for him all this time
He told me it was okay, then trust me
Weiwei
Uncle, auntie
Darling, hurry up
Trust me, Mai Si Chong will definitely win
There you are, must win
Where is he?
Fighting
Mai Si Chong, fighting
Fighting, Mai Si Chonh fighting
Fighting
I'm not your boss any more
You don't have to be that cautious
About resignation
At first I planned to wait for you to work
At least
I can protect you
But now...
President Zhang, you're very good to me
Since I started working, I have always followed you
I am very grateful
About FT
There has never been a place for useless people
You are talented and ambitious
Just try one more time
President Zhang, don't you try one more time?
I want to take a temporary break
I would like to divide the time
to my daughter
At first I thought
This kid is tired
To take care of herself
But now looking back
Over the years my daughter needs me the most
Instead, I threw away the opportunity
Come on
Bless you
Bright future
Eat it
Very good, right?
We win
I can brag fully
Today before my mother go back she said
Tonight, let me take everyone to rest a little
Everyone
Bro Chong would like us to spend the night too
Why are you excited?
Of course I must be excited
Chong and Rui grabbed the 1st and 2nd place for us
You have to be respectful, understand?
To celebrate Chong and Rui
Because of my intelligence, so we make the practice complete
I decided
Let Chong bro feast for dinner
How about this?
Tonight, I invite everyone to take a hot spring bath
Open a private room
VVIP, is it ok?
Great
I haven't been in a hot spring yet
Really?
Chong bro
I really want to marry you
Marry with your head
Li Dai Xi's head
Like a ball
You...
Say it again!
Look, what games are there?
King of Fighters, is it good?
Here I can choose what I want, right?
Professor Lin gave a very good description these days
You don't have to
Jun Jun, you choose
What do you want to watch
BLEACH
BLEACH?
Otherwise
I take you outside
Go
I'm a little excited
Sorry
It's ok
You will get used to
Next
I will do this to you often
First time just ever
The second time was used
And many times
Better then
Lots of mosquitoes
I gonna go
mosquito?
Where are the mosquitoes?
Are you guys back?
Finally back
Oh year
What is this for?
Here, write the name
Write down the name of the person you like
Like that
Will be fulfilled smoothly
Really?
Fortune sticks
What is this?
Younger Sis, our fortune sticks are very accurate
really?
I will meet my soulmate
won't I?
Among the crowd
So flattering
What is it written about?
Like enemies
face to face
Nothing
Let's go, what else are you going to randomize with?
Go
Why are you randomly picked?
What wishes do you have? I can help you
I...
I'm still thinking about transfer my Major
I want to know what the future will be like
Why?
You don't want to transfer?
Still hesitating
It's ok
however
Where is the future going?
I will support you
Come on Weiwei
These give you
Why did you buy so many strange things?
You just eat, it's ok
This little raccoon. You have to put it on, too?
You eat
Wo ju (Lettuce)
Xi Gua (cucumber)
Hwan Xiang (Raccoon), Ni Chew (Carp)
Wo Xi Huan Ni (I like you)
You are outdated, Mai Si Chong
Chong bro
You are crazy too
too sweet
Where did you learn these from?
4 spades do make up
to 4 hearts
Kiss
All right
You guys turn your face away
Oh, it's so dark
Don't look back
Okay okay
We don't look
If I don't say
Don't turn back
I don't want to just be a game
Commonly done
Real kiss must be more serious
Chong bro
I'll say
Your kiss
I didn't say to kiss my lips
So, kiss one more time
You are...
Next turn
This turn, let me do
Ok, your turn
This turn
I'm a king
So
A hearts and A spades
Must hug 1 time
Jun Jun
So who is the other person?
Not me
Sis Wei
You're not angry, right?
Just hug, isn't it?
Go
Hugged
Childhood friend
What's going on next? Come to me and Xia Rui
We will protect you
Next turn
Come on, next turn I'll do
Ok, your turn
Next turn
I'll go to the bathroom
Err...
I picked up the phone for a while
Go
Come on
Wipe the table
Jun Jun
Are you ok?
I'm ok
You don't have to do this in the future
The person whom the Mai Si Chong likes is Weiwei
Weiwei also like him too
They are a good match
So what?
You have liked him for a long time
Why doesn't he care about you?
I...
Don't want him to know
It's not you don't want, you just dare not
You have been protecting him for a long time
But you're just going to back off
What would mean like this?
Like this, what is your advantage?
First
I don't like it at all
Finally accept the result
You're just too cowardly
I hope that in the future you will not do this again
I'll feel
Very uncomfortable
Ok, I got it
I won't do this again
I conduct electricity, can't go into the water
Weiwei
Feeling of the first kiss
How is it?
What's first kiss?
It's like a CPR
Have you had a CPR as well?
At that time, Mai Si Chong was sick
Fainted at the pool
I just...
Meaning that it was not your first kiss
Do you want to play together?
Forgot it
Weiwei
She wants to spend her life in this world with me
So you two are together in the world
I'll be with Jun Jun in the worlds too
Never thought that
In college, I will have good friends like you guys
Me too
This room...
The one is Jun Jun, and one is you
If not because I moved in
Probably no one talked together
actually
Actually, I like to talk a lot
You are Jun Jun?
Probably not wrong, right?
A while
See you in the garden
Okay
Just go
Fighting
How is it?
Is it fun to today?
The hot spring is very comfortable
Why call me out?
I have something want to give you
What?
Just this one?
I...
Actually, I want to buy big fireworks
But...
I can only buy nearby
But this one is very beautiful
Ding Yi told me that
Girls like you love things that
beautiful
Sparkling, isn't it?
I made you see
How is it?
It's beautiful, right?
You...
Really don't like it?
Weiwei
Actually
I just want to give you special memories
But actually I...
I don't know what to do to make you happy
Before I met you
Each day I spend my life with swimming
My world is a monotonous blue
But when I met you
My world has become colorful
You are like fireworks
Bright and dazzling
In the pool
Even if meeting a strong opponent
I was never afraid
But in front of you
I'm afraid that I'll do something bad
You know that
This is the first time I have been in love
Has many things
That I don't know what to do as well
Don't know that...
You'll...
Can you accept a boyfriend like me?
Mai Si Chong
I like you