I am a former student council president. Fan Zheng Xiang
Misappropriated funding of the council
Misconduct
Was removed from the position of student council president
Considered as a punishment
All right
About the student council president, I knew
You are doing very well
So fighting!
Thank you professor
All right, I have class
I'm going
Thank you bro
Why haven't you answered me yet?
See from the report of this examination
Symptoms are not bad at all
But will return to normal as before the injury
Still considered difficult
It's okay, Auntie
I have my way
Is this Jun Jun?
Right
Our little girl grows up very fast
I remember that Xiao Luo was still very small before
Yeah
You don't know
Mai Sichong and my Jun Jun
study at the same university
What field of study are you in?
I...
Physical Therapy
So...
You and Mei Weiwei are in the same dormitory
Um
When you were kids
Be together every day
When they moved home
our Junjun
Even playmates don't have
Why can't I remember?
When?
What do you remember?
Remember only the dog?
So...
Mom, auntie
I'll go back to the university
Xiao Chong, aren't you going to go back to the university as well?
Go together
Let's go
Be careful
Ok
Safe back
Byebye
Junjun
Your cell phone is upside down
oh
Junjun
Do you have any lessons this hour?
You...
Want to know the schedule of Mei Weiwei?
Are you guys really close?
I...
I am not close to her at all
I and her ... How could that be?
Close?
What is this?
This
Give you
give me?
Thank you
So cool!
It looks almost like me
right?
Passed
Why are you here?
Return your gloves
Thank you
Very good
Weiwei
I heard that the Student Council Chairman's embezzlement was exposed
Do you do it?
No not me
Long story
I'll tell you this time it's not me
Now tell him
OK, so who helped you with that four-eyed guy?
All right
Actually, it is Peng Pai senior
Open this club successfully. He has helped us a lot
really?
wait
Who do you say?
Peng Pai senior
Let's not say it again. Let's talk about club activities
I thought it all
Mei Weiwei
Why
Weiwei
What's happen?
Nervous
Come on
Look
I'll give you look
I typed 3,941 words
You look
First topic
All right
Today we have enough
Done
Don't just walk by
Friends, let's take a look
The first physical therapy club
Teaches all skills
This is the course package
Take a look
Friends, take a look
Weiwei
We almost gave away
Let's go out
Guys
The first physical club Let's take it and see
It's free
Student
Give me one
Come on
Bro
You guys give out here, it doesn't work
You guys should go to the gym
There are many people
Weiwei
Buy milk tea for you guys
Thank you
Senior
Drinking a lot of milk tea is not good for your body
Because it contains a lot of sugar
Peng Pai
Haven't thanked you for the last time helping us with the club
What club
Are you Weiwei's senior, Peng Pai?
Hello
So let's go give out leaflet at the gym
Thank you bro
Bro
Thank you
Good luck
Free, no need to pay
Friends, let's take a look
Take the details of the club to read first
Free
No need to pay
Not reply to my message
Actually, here comes for give out leaflet
You are very busy
The class was really busy
Thinking of replying
You're probably not angry because of such a small thing, right?
How can I be like that?
I didn't think you'd even come and give out leaflet
Why are you so stupid?
Say like you have a better way
Easy to say, hard to do
do not have to be distributed
Like this would have been waiting until graduate
Wait and see me
Quickly
Mai student
Thank so much
If I can do it like you say
Then physical therapy club
Was not too far away
Little thing
I just don't want to delay my training
Weiwei
Are you going to practice with my Mai?
Can you swim?
Isn't Ding Yi busy these days?
I just helped him record the time
All right
We don't talk about this again
Thinking of club activities first, it's better to think about it
Right
Club activities
What can your physical therapy club do?
About this
I already thought
Did you think it?
Yes, I did
Okay
Weiwei
Peng Pai senior helped us to successfully open the club.
Wait
What is Peng Pai about opening the club?
He helped expose Fan Zheng Xiang
Allowing us to successfully open this club
He exposes
Well, it was he who exposed Fan Zheng Xiang
Clearly that...
Yeah
Today, our Mai Shijong helped us a lot as well
It's the number 2 hero, so clap your hands
You guys can make your own club
I'm leaving
Mai Sichong
I'll give you a free massage coupon later
Don't want
Yu Xin
Is there still strawberry cake left?
Sorry
The last piece he bought
Why is it you again?
Stole my strawberry cake to eat
Your strawberry cake
You call it
Will it answer you?
You...
Why is the mood so bad again?
Are you still fighting with my sister-in-law?
You don't want to talk crazy here
She's not your sister-in-law
How about you?
I advise you to stop bothering Chong bro
You're so ugly
No chance
You are the ugly
Shaped like a frog
In addition, your face was a squirrel.
You...
What
I'll tell you
Princess like me, had not been interested in Ma Sichong for a long time
It's just that Weiwei doesn't like being gossiped
So, you'd better not be talking here like this
She will not be satisfied
This fork ... You haven't used it, right?
You used it all
Why do I use it?
Consider giving you a reward
What time does your club break up?
I left work and I will go and see
Okay
What are you doing?
How can you get a shock?
Then what?
How do you want to hold hands again?
Thinking of taking advantage of me, right?
Who's going to take advantage of you?
Aren't you asking me to help?
Why?
People let you do what, you just do
Others let you form a club, so you form
Others let you drink milk tea, you drink
Can you be yourself?
You asked me to come and help you. You're still acting strange here
Never mind
Bored
What are you angry?
What else can I be angry with?
Mei Weiwei, I'll tell you
About club opening, actually the truth is ...
What's wrong with you?
Nothing
It's just that day for a girl
Come up
Come up, quickly
Why?
Let me down quickly
I'm not feeling well
Watch out
It seems to me ...
Not so uncomfortable
Weiwei
Dai Xi
What are you doing?
She...
Not feeling well
So I brought her here
Thank you
Weiwei
You sit first
I'll help you brew brown sugar
Dai Xi
You are back here
Why did you change the bedding pattern?
Look at this one and it's cute
So change
Come on
Bring boiled brown sugar to drink quickly
Thank you
It's hot
Actually the feeling of being shock is unreliable
Shock to love you
It's reaaly...
Jun Jun, you're back?
She...
Will hear what I say?
No, I shouldn't have heard
Are you sure?
Of course
Trust me
No way
I didn't get shocked by her
Stop thinking and sleep
Weiwei
You didn't tell me
What is the theme of today's work
You still can't see it?
Dance for health
But we can't drink alcohol
sparkling water
How did you come?
I came to see if I can help
Isn't this syrup?
I will tell you
This is not very good for the body
There are both sugar and food coloring in it
I'm going to hang the lantern first
Mai Sichong
You try it
Adding a little goji berry is fine
Goji Berry
Why don't i think?
Send to me
Thank you
Short and do not show off
Who is short?
You're short
Li Dai Xi
Why do you have to let me carry this?
You're forcing me
You wrong
Help princess move things
It is an honor for you
You...
Now you can see clearly
How's mood of princess like me now?
So
You don't have to try to do anything for me to like you
What am I doing to you?
Do you know Zhang Ziyi's daughter? What's the name?
What's the name?
Xingxing (it's mean wake up)
Wake up, you
You...
Not bad
No more
All friends
Next is...
To welcome you to a healthy party tonight
Activity highlights are
Health lectures
I want volunteers to come forward
If any friend voluntarily
Please come to the front
Who will voluntarily
He...
Ding Yi, please come
Good
Come on
You lie down here
What I want to tell everyone today is
Xen Yu point massage
It lies between the ribs
Find the location of this point
And then look at how his kidneys are
Just look at this point
At this time, Master Lin was pressing this student's Xen Yu point
This student shouted loudly
Apparently Kidneys are not very good
Who's the bad kidney?
Li Tai Xi, you mean, right?
Relax
Anyone interested in this technique
Very useful too
How did you come?
Let them share with you
After a while, I'll go back to doing OT at the company
Thank you
Actually, you don't have to come
You're so busy
Everything about you must be important
If not because I have to work
Will be with you all night
oh really
About club opening I haven't thank you yet
Thank you
It's okay, that's what I should do
So, I'll go now
Okay
Bye bye
Have something to talk with you, follow me
What
Talk about what
Why have to come out?
I ask you
What happened to you and Peng Pai?
What matters?
Look at my face and answer me
What answer?
What do you want?
Chong bro
We don't see anything
Please continue
continue
Insane
It seem that...
She must like Peng Pai for sure
All right, Ding Yi
Thank you everyone for joining us today
To keep our activities going
Let's get started
Great
Master Lin's skill is fine
Really?
Okay
Then you can continue with me
Li Dai Xi
Can I press the point for you?
Press your big head
Err...
Let me help you
You're in the physical field, right?
Hello, my name is Xia Rui
Thank you
The physical department has a dance party for health
I'll go too
hurry up
come quick
Will you come too?
Okay
I look at you, it's not that busy
There is still time to come back and pick up things at home
Didn't your mom teach these things when she was still alive?
Wang Mei Yun
Don't mess with my mom
I've come back and have something to eat?
How about a dining table?
Thief up the house?
Or not because your daughter?
The mahogari table was just bought
This money just let it go
You wanted to destroy this house
Zhang Yu Xin
What are you going to do?
You threw my mother's dining table first
You want to protect her
Okay
So just throw me away
Weiwei
Leave with you,ok?
Weiwei, we'll go now
Okay, bye bye
Safe back
Bye bye Wei sis
You're go back
Mai student
Weiwei
Not hurry to get up yet
There is still someone inside
What's wrong with your knees?
Door?
The door has been locked
So what should we do?
I'll call Dai Xi
My phone has left with Dai Xi
And you?
Mine...
Left with Ding Yi
So what should we do?
Wait for a while
Maybe someone will come
All right
Oh
Li Dai Xi
Aren't you hungry?
Why do you eat that much?
I did it to take care of you
You're an athlete should pay attention to food
Can you not quote me?
I brought a lot of food for Chong bro
They are okay, right?
Your knees
okay?
Almost healed
No problem
You had been injured before
at your knees, right?
No
Just a bump just now
Don't lie to me
That you want me to shock you
Just hoping that the knee injury will heal quickly, right?
How do you know?
Just...
Just know
You haven't told me, how does your knee hurt?
Then I will tell you
Don't tell anyone else
Umm..
In the past
To save the life of a child
So there was an accident
At that time I fainted
Later someone told me that...
has someone helped me
At that time my knees moved
I didn't think that you would be brave
Do you have any secret?
Actually, it's not a secret
You know that
My body has a very special electric power
But I can't tell others
I've always felt that
This body only creates problems
Because it never brings me any luck
But there was one time, did you know?
I use my electricity to save someone
Since then I thought having electricity is good too
Before, you ...
You keep following me
Talk about my electricity
I was a little embarrassed
So I shouted at you loudly
Sorry
Thank you