Peng Pai senior
Weiwei
Why are you at the university today?
I'm coming to the topic of thesis work
Afternoon back to the company
Err...
Bro...
I have something I want you to help me
Just say it
Is it possible? ...
That you will help manage Sun Yang and Mai Sichong meet together
I think...
If Sun Yang talk direct with him
He will definitely be able to help Mai Sichong
This's...
I'm afraid it will be difficult
Actually, I just tried asking. For good luck
You don't take it to pay attention
So, excuse mw. I've to go to study
Ding Yi
Sis Wei
Mai Shi Chong hasn't come to learn yet?
Chong asked to take a break from home
Been home several days ago
He said he did not dare to come to the university
The phone turned off
His knees
Still not getting better, right?
I think
If you want everything to be as it was before
It's no way
But if physical recovery goes well
I think
Should be able to join the provincial team, no problem for sure
Ding Yi
Do you want to help him?
Follow me
Why are you moving so fast?
Boss
Did you not say?
Just I join the relay race
You promised to help massage for Mai Si Chong
Yeah
But...
We moved suddenly like this. And did not tell the Professor
It's not good
What's not good?
Anyway, you don't like the seniors in the dorm
Now, you moved to the Mai Sichong's dormitory
There are more swimmers waiting for you to heal
It's so good
Made new friends
Show off one's skill
Shoot one hand with two birds, right?
And you, Ding Yi
Selection of the coming province You have to cooperate fully with Master Bai Hui
Care to impress
Roger that!
Guaranteed work success
Hui
Then I will ...
Take good care of you
We can...
Name change
So what do I call you?
Bai Bai
Hui Hui
It's up to you
You just lift up quickly
I'm going to register
Then I called on my own
Up to you
All right
So, let's carry things up first
I'm leaving
You hurry back
Now your son keeps himself in the room
Who called it did not open
Darling, don't be impatient
This isn't your idea?
You know I will talk to him
You will also explain to me
It's all my fault
The child is already growing up
You just let him calm down a bit
Who's coming again?
I'll hang up
Auntie, hello
Weiwei
Come in
Do not call Auntie in the future
Call me Mai's mom
Is Mai Sichong at home?
You came just right time
This child kept himself in a room
What ever I call, he would not come out
Can you help me talk to him?
Quick
Auntie
I cam suddenly
Don't bother, right?
How can disturb this? I'm so glad you came
You hurry to help me talk to him
Locked himself in a room for two days and refused to come out
What I said, it did not work
Also let me go to the university, bring him something
Said to be at home for a while
I Anxious to die already
Go in quickly
Then I will try talking to him
Book "A Brief History of Humanity"
Weiwei
You talk to him
I will go get some fruit for you
Okay
Thank you
You read understand?
It's not difficult
How can I not understand?
Why are you free to come?
I asked Lin Bai Hui to move to your dormitory
He is very good at rehabilitation
He will definitely help you
No, don't want
Why?
Block yourself?
What?
The one who is embarrassed is not you
What's embarrassing about this matter?
Anyway, this isn't the first time you've been embarrassed
Not everyone has any interest in you
Trust me
What kind of person are you? Saw people falling and stepping over again
I'm not go
Get up and go back to college with me
No
You will not get up?
Won't get up, I'm going to drag you
No, I'm not go
You get up,now!
I told you, not go
Mei Weiwei
Why you...
Still hugging me
You're not embarrassed?
You obviously pulled me down
What's the reason?
I...
Come on
F...F...Fruit
Sorry
You guys can continue
Xiao Mai
You go downstairs, help me throw away the trash
I can't lift
This child...
You're so fast that I can't keep up
Mom, don't think about it by yourself
What is it that I thought?
Why are you two playing sumo?
Auntie, I'am leaving
Weiwei
Please stay
I still have something fun for you to watch
Fun?
You look at him as a kid, was he fat?
Belly like a baby watermelon
You look, this is like a big head doll
This picture
I remember it was 5 years old. You look. he still eat his hand
Keep watching
I am most impressed with this picture
It was probably the first time he won a gold medal
He was red-eyed as well. You look
He had to put swimming goggles to cover his face
Mom
Mom, can you respect my privacy?
What? It's so cute
This picture is not shown to Weiwei, so anyone can see it?
Here is 3 of our family
All right
Isn't there a yoga class in the afternoon?
Hurry to go to class quickly
I'll talk
Okay
So you guys talked
What's so laughable?
Is this the medal you got when you were a kid?
Just a gold medal
Do you still have a silver medal?
Of course not
I remember not knowing who had it. When swimming competition at the university
Why do you like to swim?
It was a long time ago
The real reason
I couldn't imagine either
But as a kid I was on the swimming team
Yang Master caught the eye of me
Yang Master
At high school, Yang Master
is my coach
He is also a professional athlete
When he saw me swimming, he felt that...
In the future, I will definitely get a gold medal
So later he decided to pull me over
But...
My situation now...
Mai Sichong
Let's go find Yang Master
Yang Coach
Sichong
You...!
At last you appeared
Haven't seen each other for a long time and still do like this
You still know that called for a long time
I didn't see you coming to visit me
And this hasn't come yet?
This person is...
your girlfriend?
No
College friends
Do you want...
to go to see inside?
It has been for many years, so what's worth seeing?
Let's go eat
Go
Yang Coach
I haven't eaten with you for a long time
Oh yeah
On the way, you said that...
Didn't audition for the provincial team, because of the pain in the knee
How did this happen?
Before
There was a little accident
Knee meniscus injury
The doctor recommended that I have surgery
Therefore was unable to audition for the provincial team
You're...
As a swimmer
Why do you let your knees fall like this?
Coach
I know, I was wrong
In the future, I'll be careful more
You know well
And now
Can you still swim?
I can swim
But just...
Why?
You probably haven't thought of giving up, right?
Oh yeah
I have a gift for you
You look
gift?
Yang coach
Why are you carrying this?
Why can't I carry?
What's not good?
I'll told you
I also liked your commitment as a kid
Determination that will not give up
Xiao Chong
You listen to me
You are a very talented person
Also trying hard
It's been 10 years now
I have found a good seedling like you
I believe that you will definitely be able to step on the podium
And
Not just in the country
But also abroad
You will definitely go a long way
Got it?
Got it
Thank you
Be careful
It's ok
I'm not drunk
watch out
All right
Xiao Chong
Remember
You must...
Take good care of your girlfriend
I...
Your thoughts
You can't lie to me
Be careful
Safe back
Bye bye
Just a moment ago you drank quite a bit
I'm going to buy you yogurt
Cure the hang
Today I lost to the fat boy in the team
And also frantic in the team as well
I know I was wrong
But this does not mean that I have given up
I, the Demon of the Pool, Mai Si Chong, swear by
I won't cry anyway
I don't care what rank I stand in
I won't say I give up again
If I say give up again, I'm a dog
Yang coach
Don't be angry me
I guarantee
That I have to do it for sure
Mai Sichong
Thank you
So...
I sent you back to the university first
Let's go
Yang Master looked at you really optimistic
Sure
Coach that I have ever met ,who doesn't see me as good?
And you?
Do you see me a good person?
I...
Is that difficult to answer?
At least
I'm probably the best swimmer you know, right?
Mai Sichong
That you are like this Isn't it because of confidence?
By the way, Mai Sichong that I know
When being with the swimming that he like
Will be enthusiastic and confident
If you give up now
So before, I had looked at you wrong
I sent you just like this
Go back on your own
Excuse me
Wait
You don't go to university with me
Probably not afraid or embarrassed by people
I...
What's I have to be afraid of?
Is it not because I am afraid of someone
to walk with me
will be gossiped by those around her
and male her unhappy?
Take it like this
I sent you back to the dormitory
But let me choose a path
Dare or not?
You choose, then choose
Who doesn't dare?
Why did you have to come on this secret route?
Close to your dorm
and
Weren't you in danger last time?
So I have to come and send you back
I think, you were just scared
to go to a crowded place, right?
How is that possible?
I am Mai Si Chong
What is there to fear?
Just kidding
Then you can take off your hood
No way
Like this, I feel cool
Ding Yi
We're here
Has he gone?
Has he gone? Ding Yi.
You're afraid you'll meet Ding Yi
And also say that you are not afraid to be embarrassed
Who said I was afraid to meet people?
Is there anything I have to fear?
So why do you have to take a shortcut?
I...
Is it not because I can be with someone a little longer?
I am back
You back?
What is the matter to be so happy?
I successfully persuaded Mai Sichong to return to the university
What's so glad?
It's great
Oh yeah, Jun Jun
You and Madam Sichong were friends as a child, right?
He...
Was he like this in the past?
Everyone said a few words and just ran away
Actually it is because of him...
Too proud of hisself
The first time when he won a gold medal
He was red-eyed
So he refused to go up for photo group when receiving the award
I am most impressed with this picture
This was probably the first time he won a gold medal
He was red-eyed as well. You see
He had to cover his face with swimming goggles
Because the eyes are so red
Are you sure that...
that this is called self-esteem?
Not a narcissist
You guys...
Why do you have to pay attention to the Mai of Sichong?
Probably because he grew up handsome
But looks like our college boys when growing up is so handsome
Except Ding Yi
Also has
Your guys boss
Lin Bai Hui
Journalism student
You talk about Ding Yi, just say it. Why came about with our boss?
Yu Xin
You look strange
What is strange?
What strange will I have? There is nothing strange.
Tomorrow, class time is changed to 7:30 a.m.
We have already signed the 4x100 mixed relay
But still missing another woman, what should I do?
Yu Xin
There are still others missing
Please help
I...
Actually I...
Not signed
I can't really run
Yu Xin
Let's join the team together
Okay
What do I need to do?
I have to really want to try it
I will sleep
You guys sleep
I go take a shower first
You go
You keep staring at me for 20 minutes, what are you going to do?
You changed
I know
I become more handsome
You have changed
I am like the best sibling
But now what do you have, you only talk with Mei Wei?
Do you feel the conscience in your heart?
Is it painful?
You do it yourself
How are you and Wei Wei the same?
Shallow excuses
All right
Buy a game for you
Don't think you can take a game to destroy my soul
Next month, add allowances for another half month
Am I the type of person who bends to eat?
So...
The game and the allowances are no longer available
Okay
I forgive you, okay?
I can't remember
Forgive you
Are you finished talking?
Weiwei let me do you rehab
So...
Let's start now
Fight
How is it?
Get better
That's good
Look at your heart rate
Take this to collect electricity
No problem
Take a break
Why haven't mom come yet?
Don't talk about her to me
You said the weather like this
So that she could save electricity
Won't let me use the electric mattress
Really angry
Every day she has to bring cold feet
Put on my belly
You think she's not annoyed?
Dad
Your stomach is not small
This is not because of you?
Came out early for a run with you
Will eat or sleep, they are all confused
Then can the belly be small?
Weiwei, you think...
In future
With a body like this, if you want to find a soulmate? What should you do?
Dad, I was just in Grade 10
Right, that's too fast
Besides studying
All day you just ran
Why do you like running?
I and your mom still think
We gave birth to a running machine or something
Running makes me comfortable
The Flash can still save the world
Pikachu can still help Xiao Zhi
As for me, running makes me happy
Make myself happy, it's wonderful
Wonderful
I wish only my daughter to be happy
Dad was happy
Go home
Let's go home
How did you come?
How long have you been running?
To get tired like this
What does it have to do with you?
I promise to practice with you, isn't it?
I said it and I have to do it
I finished practicing
And are you still practicing?
If you don't practice, just go
I don't practice anymore
Tired to die
come on
Be comfortable
I give a special price
80 each time
You...
Friends should be free
So add more 20
Hurts
You be careful
Good morning, Yu Xin
Good morning
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet
You look this
The chef at the cafeteria makes
I had him add 5 eggs for me
Help me open the lid
I'll find something
Lin Bai Hui
Your eggs smell
It's too strong
Please, please stay a distance from me
Yu Xin
Are you okay?
I'm okay
Then please call Weiwei
Why hasn't she come yet?
Why?
Go to the pool with me
There is a surprise for you
Mei Weiwei
Why did you bring me here?
Go and know by yourself. Hurry up
Today I am not in the mood to practice
Not going to practice
There is something to surprise you
Bro
Weiwei
We are here
Sichong
Where is he?
Mai Sichong