Tomorrow I have a competition
Will you come to see?
Tomorrow is my birthday
The appointment you have not forgotten, right?
Tomorrow?
Fight
That's Mai Sichong,right?
The person behind will overtake him
How does he swim?
Mai Sichong, fighting
Chong bro
You look, I'm sleepy but have to come and play with you
Just give up today, don't make yourself unhappy
What bullshit? keep playing
Front left, you look irritated
The right one is like a broken heart.
Because today, sis Wei didn't come, right?
No
What is it about her?
If I let you talk, don't argue
Because today Sis Wei didn't come
So you are not in the mood to compete
Otherwise, you wouldn't take this much time away from Brother Rui
Chong bro
Today you look in a bad mood
Otherwise ...
It's okay
Today
Haven't congratulated you yet
Lose once, it's okay
The future wins will be better
Forget it!
Tomorrow, just apologize by face to face
Don't come to watch me compete, not reply to my message
Going to Peng Pai's birthday party, it must have been very happy
Mai Sichong
This's...
It is sports equipment that I bought for you
Take it
No need
What's wrong with you?
Are you sick?
You don't have to care
I know that you lost it. Must be sad
But still have a chance to win, isn't it?
If nothing else, so excuse me
I intend to come to you
You act like this
Be careful, I won't help you next time
Then you don't have to help
Chong bro
Are you guys okay?
Sis Wei did not come to see Pee Chong compete
During these two days, Chong kept swimming and not going anywhere
The competition still lost
Shut up
Weiwei
I say the truth
See from the examination report here
The symptoms are not bad at all
But will return to normal as before the injury
Still difficult
Where's Weiwei?
She...
He had been out since morning
Should have gone to Peng Pai senior's birthday party
Senior Peng Pai is not a kid like you
Can you please be an adult?
Weiwei
Bought you milk tea
Thank you
You are Weiwei's Peng Pai senior
Wait
What is Peng Pai about founding the club?
He helped expose Fan Zheng Xiang, so we successfully founding a club
Oh yeah
About founding of the club,I'm not say thank you yet
It's okay
It's what I should do
Journalist friend
Would you call Weiwei for me?
No need, she already has a senior Peng Pai
She and Peng Pai are in a relationship?
Now not yet
but in future it's not sure
Tape
What are you doing?
Hello
Err...
We are now preparing a new event
Forget about recommending
This is our new student council president, sister Jia Yi
Hello sis
If you guys have any problems
You can tell us all the time
We will adjust accordingly according to suggestions as well
Mei Weiwei
Your boyfriend is not bad
Exposing the mistake of the previous president
He's not my boyfriend
I'm still amazed
Why is Mai Sichong so dedicated to you?
Mai Sichong
Err..., we still need to check that way a little more
Excuse me
Wait
What is Peng Pai about founding the club?
He helped expose Fan Zheng Xiang
So we successfully founding a club
He exposes
Well, it was he who exposed Fan Zheng Xiang
It's clearly that...
You guys do it yourself
I've something to do
Yu Xin
This one that the teacher said in the class, do you understand?
What we discussed in class today
There is still here
I remember like having this picture too, right?
Err...
I suddenly realized that I had something  to do
SO excuse me
Okay, so you hurry
Well, then I will go first
Bye bye
Yu Xin
Junjun, let's go
Still have this...
I remember
The person who plays as Kurosaki Ichigo today so handsome
Junjun
Did you not say that today you will invite him
I haven't told him yet
Junjun
Hello I'm Xia Rui
Jun Jun, is this person is Kurosaki-kun?
Last time we saw your picture too
Not very clear
I didn't think the real one would be very handsome
Uh ... do you guys want something to drink?
I will buy it
No need
You guys go, I go too
Then we...
Go to a convenience store to find something to eat?
Okay
Let's go
Thank you
Do you like the god of death?
That day ... sorry
I...
I like...
Not...
I know
That day...
Too many people
Everyone teases
You don't know what to do
So you pointed at me instead, right?
It's fine, there's nothing to apologize for
At least this story really made us known, right?
Actually I...
Before, I was like you
At that time I was more boring than you
I'm just ...
I don't know how to communicate with everyone
When I saw you and I felt
See myself earlier
So I want to be your friend
Friend
Just
Common friend
I heard that you are sick
This is a drug and a supplement, you take it
Medicines and supplements
Take it
I heard that you were sick
Just right
Here are drugs and supplements, so take it
Forget it!
Mai Sichong
Mai Sichong, wake up
Anyone here?
Is there Anyone?
You wake up quickly
Mai Sichong
Mai Sichong, wake up
You...
be patience
wake up
Actually it is you
I'm really sick
All of them are hallucinations
Hallucination ...
Mai Sichong
Wake up, don't frightened me
Anyone here?
You...
You
You finally get conscious
You shock me to death
Just wait
I'll call 120 for you
Hello
Please send someone here
Fever is gone
Waking up and pretending to sleep again
No, I'm not
Why are you so sick of being such a child?
No, you're always like a kid
Not me
Or are you not ...
You...
In high school at 12 grade, you saved someone, right?
How did you know that in Grade 12?
Because I ...
Sichong, You already wake up?
Brother Chong is awake
We brought some juice
Are you still feeling sting right now?
Much better
Hello senior
Wei Wei Are you at University?
In the afternoon, I'll return to the university to take my thesis papers
Otherwise go have a meal together?
Just talk together
Ok, then you wait for me for a while
I will go now
I'll go to meet Brother Peng Pai at canteen
So excuse me
I will order food back for you
Then I'll go now
Chong bro
Do you think Mei Wei and Peng Pai have some somthing?
What about you, shut up.
Err...Junjun
Otherwise you go to eat first
What is the matter with Chong, I will tell you
Do you eat bananas?
Is your thesis not finished yet?
Peng Pai
Your birthday plan I told her
Sorry, I just...
I'm leaving
Bro
You last birthday party, I didn't go
Sorry
I sent a gift You've got it, right?
Got it
But...
Why send books to me?
I saw inside it about sports economics
I think it is very suitable for you
But what I want is not a book
Also, I...
Bro
Actually, having adjusted my understanding you and let's be friends again
I am very happy
That day was not going to my birthday
Is something happen with him?
That day...
Went to watch Mai Sichong compete?
Umm
You...
Like Mai Sichong?
We are...
Nothing
Err...
The food that I ordered is finished
I go get it
You guys are here
Rector
Pei Pei
You look
Mai Sichong's score when in high school, can be attached to the provincial team
But this time, why is it so bad?
Actually, it shouldn't be like this
You have to pay attention to him a little more
Coach Li of the provincial team has always been interested in him
Last year's selection, why he not join?
I still have another meeting
You guys, consider it again
You look
When examining the body, there was no abnormality in Mai Sichong
I can only check the original files
Where's Mai Sichong
Chong seems to hurry back to the dormitory, I don't know why
Is he ok?
He's...
Still not recovered, right?
There may be serious matters in the dormitory
Otherwise
You go to look after him
But how can I enter the male dormitory?
We have a way
Rui, today...
Is it cold today?
Rui
What are you guys doing? This is ...
Nothing
Chong bro
Why are your clothes is on my bed?
Ding Yi
Coach Pei Pei called us
What?
About practicing
Buy it for you, eat it
You first
When I was in the hospital
You went to eat with Peng Pai
What are you talking about?
I didn't go to his birthday party
So I went to apologize to him
You didn't go to his birthday party
Isn't it that I have to go see you for a match?
In the end, I couldn't keep up
What are you smiling at?
Nothing
You lose swimming competition
So frustrated, right?
Also get sick
It doesn't matter
I don't shed tears because of all this
I think our electro therapy is useless
Otherwise, do we find another way?
It's okay
I thought for a long time
That I swim faster, not because you shock me
Next time, you just come and watch me compete
I must win
Why?
Because I like ...
I'm going to buy two bottles of mineral water
I will tell you a big secret
What?
Weiwei is taking care of Mai Si Chong at our dormitory
Weiwei takes care of Mai Si Chong in your dorm
Turn down the sound
No way
They are...
Wahy?
I will tell you
When Chong bro at high school, he makes a very good time record
But when he entered the university he couldn't do it
But every time that he saw Weiwei
Immediately swam faster
This power of love
Mai Sichong
Probably didn't really like Weiwei, right?
Why?
Are you jealous?
That's you who jealous them
Dai Xi, then let's go for a walk
No
They are in the room I can't go back
Not go
That ... brought it back to me