Good morning
Morning
Dingyi
Get up for your breakfast
Sichong, where did you go last night
Dressing like Pikachu
You really scared me last night
Do you know the girl
who came to the swimming pool yesterday?
Which one? That journalist?
No, the other one
Right, the one from rehabilitation class?
What's wrong with her?
Nothing
Is there something you're not telling me?
I think he is being weird, Xia Rui, do you agree?
I get something to do, excuse me
So weird, fine, let's go
Over 600 yuan?
That's unbelievably expensive
Weiwei
I have been waiting for Sischong's message for the whole night
Why he didn't text me?
He must be sleeping
Calm down
When he gets up
your phone is going to be busy as hell
But it has been so long
Your super power
is going to be valid tonight
Sweet heart
Are you feeling alright?
Don't keep secrets from me
Relax, I am fine
Don't worry about me
Let's find the Pikachu's head
Fine
Hello Weiwei, can I have my Pikachu back?
I will wait for you on the third floor of the teaching building
The student union needs it for an activity
Daixi, I don' have much time left
I gotta go
-What to do with the Pikachu? -Forget about it
Are my eyes deceiving me？
Where is the head?
I can't find it
Are you kidding me?
I lent to you last night
because you look like an decent lady
Why do you act like a rude girl?
I need it now!
How about this
I would like to for the head
Fine
-How much is it? -6000 yuan
6000?
The Pikachu is a special edition
You won't get it
even if you fly to Japan right now
Fine
But could you please
give me a 50% off?
Is 3000 enough?
No way
Is this made of gold?
Can't you read a book before scamming people
Can you?
Who the hell are you?
Mai Sichong from the swimming team
Don't you know me?
She said she would pay for it
Here is your Pikachu
Don't you dare bully people again
Alright
Your Pikachu is safe and sound
My debt to you is over
Thank you
Let's go
Why are you stealing my Pikachu head
I find it for you
and now you blame me, how grateful
You want my attention on you?
What do you want?
I have no idea
I just feel like to being around you
Are you falling love with...
with whom?
Nobody
I gotta go
How about dinner tonight?
I don't think it's a good idea
What can I do?
How can I face Daixi?
I used my super power on me!
I am sorry
I thought I am the one only one in the dorm
That's alright
I won't tell Daixi about this
I am going to grab my take out downstair now
Okay
There is a good news
and a bad news
I want the good now first
The good news is that I found the Pikachu head
The bad news is that
My super power on Sichong failed
The Pikachu head is so big
I can't figure out where he exactly was
I told you so
He should have dated me this morning if you succeed
Relax
I can charm him again
Are you sure?
Don't make yourself be pressured
I have promised you
and I have come up with a new plan
Alright
Let's talk about
something you may concern about
Roger Federer looks more handsome than in the pictures
He would take off his wedding ring
when he grabs his tennis racket
Which means, he is single
when he is playing games
I noticed that all the ladies are so excited
But the guy who
sitting in the middle of the third row
What are you excited for
Mr.Peng Pai
I like you a lot
I appreciate it
Mr.Peng
Is there much pressure during our daily work?
This tournament has its own systeem
every individual has their own work part
So we as the volunteers
also have own tasks and goals
In the meantime
We need each other to make a good team
Take me as an example
My job is to
assembling you guys and assign work
Thank you for answering
Mr.Peng
My name is Ai Ning [Love you]
Because I love you
Wow, thanks
But I think this could happen between you and me
I will be very pleased
to answer questions about volunteer work
Mr.Peng
Actually I want to know
In this tournament
Only you followed the whole process
Does this experience help you
get a job tin FT since it is the best sports management company
I am a lucky person
I was supposed to be responsible for the beginning
but they are suddenly short on staff
So I can follow the whole project
You are so busy
Do you need my help as a good wife?
I think this is my mom's business
I won't waste your time here
right?
Good
Let's go on
What else do you want to know about Federer
Okay
You
Excuse me
I am here to pick up
the psychological test
made by sports management class
Okay
I will bring to you from the data room
Thank you
Madam
there is something wrong with my body
Can I use the thermometer?
Hello
Excuse me
Which class are you in?
The Swimming class
My name is Mai Sichong
Mai Sichong?
the exceptional admission?
Sir
I think I am on the edge of madness
Since I met her
She has occupied my mind
I can'c control it
and I always think about
getting close to her
Are you feeling sick?
Find a doctor if you are feeling wrong
Anyway, there must be something wrong with me
Based on what you have said
I assume you may have fall in love with her
My advice is to
ask your friends
and figure out what she wants
I may have scared her
Will she hate me?
Girls won't hate a guy like you
This makes sense
Thank you sir
Actually I am not a "Sir"
I am back
Here you are
You are also a student?
I am Peng Pai, a senior from Sports Management Class
Sorry
I can't find a proper time to tell you this
But don't worry
My month is zipped
Thanks a lot
I know what should I do next
You are early today
I will never be late
Alright
Guys
I will call a roll first
Mei Weiwei
Here
I am here
What's your problem
Louder please, haven't you gotten anything to eat?
Madam
We all heard her
Pardon me?
He said he didn't hear me too
Sorry madam, I have a sour throat today
Fine, I will continue
-Peng Wanli -Here
Gao Dashan -Here
Stop talking to me
Find me
after class
Okay
This is all about today's class, dismissed
Finally
I almost can't breath
Can I talk to you now?
What do you want?
I think I have a crush on you
Can you be my girlfriend
I am a grown up
I don't have to deny anything
What's your answer?
Say yes
Weiwei
You said I can talk to you after class
Mai Sichong
I think you need to rest now
This is illusion
When you get up, you will forget me
This isn't illusion, I have thought for a long time
There has never been a problem
that can make me think for more than ten hours
I can't explain now
Just leave me alone
I am so sorry
Mom!? Didn't I tell you to wait me outside the school?
Who is this?
-Mei Weiwei, My future girlfriend -Really?
-I'm not... -"Future" girlfriend, I understand
You are so pretty
Are you available this afternoon?
Yes
That's great!
Would you mind having dinner with us?
Today is my birthday
Let's go
Let's go to my place
Keep up!
Hello
Sichong is doing great
He is not only good at swimming
but also good at getting along with girls
Let me see it
That's Sichong, really
Is she meeting his parents?
That's a big step
Amazing
Yes, unbelievable
Indeed
We need to put some effort into girls
Learn from Sichong
Another crazy woman
Here is the roasted chicken
Do you like it?
This is Sichong's favorite
I like it, really
Right
Ms.Mai
Happy birthday!
Thank you!
You are so adorable
Is this the first time?
Weiwei, Sichong has never
brought a girlfriend home before
I am not...
What are you talking about?
Weiwei is a
very close friend of Sichong
Not his girlfriend
Watch your language
I am sorry
I hope you don't mind
But everyone in this family is very easy-going
Make yourself at home
-Have anything you want -Yes, don't feel uncomfortable
Come on
You are embarrassing her
No no no
What do you want to eat?
I can order take out for you
Thanks, but I am good
Order take out?
Every dish on this table is better than take out!
Absolutely!
Your dad is really good at cooking!
You are doing a great job
Thank you
I will get you some water
No need
What happened?
I am fine
Are you okay?
I am good, I will get you some water
Excuse us, come with me
Are you training too much
these days
No
I know you best
It's been several months
You still hurt so much
I have told you so many times
If you don't care your legs now
The damage will be permanent
You just won’t be able to look a cow in the eye for a while
Why did I sent you to the Sports University?
My attention is to give you a break
Yes, you are right
Bu it doesn't matter
As long as others won't notice I am injured
If our coach knows it
How can I be admitted to the Province team
Although I am in a university
I can't go easy on training
The competitions
in the second half of the year are very important to me
Alright, you are making sense
So listen to your doctor
Fine
I will be careful
Let's go eating
Go
You little bastard
Give it to them
We are leaving
The driver will drive you to school
Weiwei, come by next time, will you?
Sure
Thank you a lot
Good bye
Bye bye
Be careful on the road
It is not my attention to
invite you for dinner
It's my mom...
Mai Sichong
Send my greetings to your mom
and I can't accept these snacks
Take them back
Why
Am I rushing to fast?
It's not
Tomorrow is another day
I am leaving
Keep the snacks
I don't need...
Sichong
Peng Pai?
What a coincidence
Do you know each other?
I didn't expect to
meet you here
Long time no see
Peng Yan
Peng Yan?
His name is Peng Pai
I will leave you two alone
What about the snacks?
Pang Pai?
Excuse me?
She is angry with me again
Girls are unpredictable
Sichong
Is she the one
You are talking about before?
Yes
I called you so many times
Why wouldn't you pick up?
and can you explain this?
What is going on between you and Mai Sichong
Daixi
I ran into Peng Yan just now
Did he go aboard?
He has changed his name
Now he is Peng Pai
The Peng Pai?
Did he say anything to you?
Nothing
Do not tell me you just left
I was so shocked that time
I didn't think much
and left unconsciously
You don't have to be afraid him
If he doesn't behave
You can shock him with your power
No no no
If he falls in love with you
Things will be more complicated
Explain this, now!
Are you two together now?
It's a long story
The story is that I used my super power on myself
So he falls in love with me
Why didn't you tell me the truth
when we were at the cafe?
Why did you lie to me?
I am afraid that you will be mad at me
Anyway
He will forget me
After couple hours
Then we start our plan B
And I am sure it will work
-Are you sure? -Of course
Fine
Peng Pai
You have knew about Mei Weiwei
since high school
right?
-Are you courting her right now? -Yes
But things don't go very well
She is hiding from me
She used to be a professional track athlete
She runs like a leopard
Really?
I need more
Share with me
I just have no idea how to please her now
How did you first meet Weiwei?
It's not so long after first day of school
Actually I don't have much impression on her
Then I met her in the school
She became clingy
Right
Why she turned me down
when she is the one who loves me first
I think you may have misunderstood her
You need to calm down
That's what she told me
I just think she is clumsy
But later in that night tour
She looked at me
and I felt something changed
What changed?
You mean fall in love at first sight?
Anyway you don't need to rush in
Take some rest
Cheers
Pleas eat
I believe you will love back
I won't give up
Stay calm!
Stay rational!
Come on
Ding Yi
Let me sleep
Good morning
Get up!
Don't bother me
I want to sleep
I believe you will love me back
I won't give up
Stay calm
Stay rational
Why you always turn me down
I won't stop loving you
no matter what you said to me
What's this
What did I do yesterday?
Weiwei. are you in bed?
I am thinking of you all the time
I want the whole world know
your cuteness
-Ding Yi -My sister in law!
Call me Mei Weiwei please
Can you do me a favor?
This is for you
Did you take training tonight?
The coach didn't ask us to
But Sichong mush be there
You want to surprise him?
Y...es
Forget me?
Peng Yan
We should have talked that night
And I want to apologize for
what I did before
-I was...-Peng Yan
Let bygones be bygones
I can hardly remember it
I need to leave for
my classes
Sichong
Why are you so happy today
-You and Mei weiwei -Shut up
What happened
Yesterday you were just fine
Why you behave like this
She is right
Falling in love at first sight is stupid
What would you react if she come to you
It depends on my mood
Let's go training
Weirdo
Mai sichong
Somebody is drowning
-Help her please -Drowning?
Pleas help her
Can anybody drown
in such a shallow swimming pool?
Come on
She is drowning, for sure!
She was seized with cramp
Go and help her
You are such a lousy actress
I am leaving
-Good evening coach! -Coach?
I cramped!
Grab this
You are safe now
It's you
Are you okay?
I am fine
What are you doing?
Mei Weiwei
What have you done to me!