If able to control the voltage
Electricity can also help heal exercise injuries
50.30 seconds
Good job
0.4 seconds slower than the statistic you were in high school
Mai Sichong
Why you call me out?
Help me record the time
Ready
Go
How much time?
54.46 seconds
That's 54 seconds
Why do I need you to come and order?
Okay, so call me what's the matter?
Mewi Weiwei
Please Shock electricity on me
I say
Are you crazy?
Stop
I am not crazy
I'm seriously
No, I'm not okay
Why?
What?
If I make you...
So, what should to do?
You make me what?
Make me fall in love with you?
Mei Weiwei
Never known before
That your brain has such a problem
Okay
I'm wrong, are you satisfied yet?
So, how about...
When you shock electricity on me
I'll close my eyes
I promise
I won't make the same mistake twice
That still not okay
I do not guarantee my electric
I can't be responsible for you
Trust me
You don't have to take responsibility
He is Mai Sichong,right?
Go go go
That's enough, you don't have to say
Hurry back to practice
Go
Do it by yourself
Forgot it!
There is not much time
Anyway, you have to shock me
For what?
Why is it so important?
You don't say?
You don't say, so I go
Okay
I'm wrong.
I will tell you all
That is...
Please shock on me
Maybe I might swim faster
I'm not sick
You will also say that you are not sick
Hello Bunchang
Hello Weiwei
Where are you?
Everyone has arrived, only you are left
Okay, I'll go now.
So, I'm leaving
Don't talk about this anymore
Just find someone else
Mei Weiwei
Besides you, who else can I go to?
Sorry I'm late
Weiwei
You told us to come here
For...
To announce a particular issue
I and Bunchang are preparing
A big plan that will help everyone graduate quickly
This plan is...
Established a physical therapy club
Clap your hands
Conclude that all
It is a club that is suitable for our profession
Not only makes this knowledge popular
It can also help students recover from physical exercise
And then?
So
Everyone
Would you like to join the club together?
Cooperate together
Weiwei
Even though last time you helped me present my work
I have to thank you very much
But what kind of physical club is this?
I'm not free
And also not interested
Yuxin
Actually we care about you
Will get retired for missing school often
That's not good
So I can find a matter of handing over the letter
Has anything else?
If you don't have, I'll go back and sleep
Yuxin
Weiwei
Club
I don't join too
The owner of the bar is still waiting for me
I'll go now
Jinjin
Weiwei
Don't give up
This is the way of the revolution
A hundred times a thousand times The road is still a long way
You say is right
I won't give up
Bunchang
I have some question want to ask you
The last time you spoke in class
Electricity can help restore the body
Then is it possible that...
That electricity stimulates the body's potential
For example
Makes it run faster, something like that
Electrotherapy is the most basic type of therapy.
That I have learned is...
It helps the muscles to relax and control the nerves
But as you say
Stimulate potential
I've never heard of it before
Electrotherapy
Who said that only Mei Weiwei would have to help?
I can do it by myself
Mei Weiei
You come to study by yourself today?
Yeah
Don't unfold me
This student...
Who
Hello Professor
I'm Meiweiwei
Mei Weiwei
Why don't you look like the last time?
May be because...
I just cut my hair
So you...
can't remember me
Stand up
I teach physical therapy
You probably think I'm old now
Your appearance, I would never remember
The height is this different
Still say that you two are the same person
This kid is so stubborn
Tell me
What field do you study?
What's your name?
Professor
I'm Mei Weiwei
If you really are Mei Weiwei
So last week it was a fake
There is no reason to come to class
This moment
Let's start
Weiwei
you...
Are you ok?
I'm fine
Very fine
Just didn't check the name of the class
Next time, we can dress up for class again
It's good that you can think like this
About that content
you don't worry
I will help you
Thank you Bunchang
Then I'll go to work
Weiwei
Bro
Thank you
I'm really sorry for that day.
Which makes you guys must not be okay
Never mind
You and Mai Schichong
What's wrong with that?
No
I and he just
Don't mention it
In fact, a good person like him
Did not join the provincial team
It's really a pity
Our company has always wanted to sign a contract with him
sign a contract
It's like Sun Yang?
Yes
Weiwei
Did Sichong ever tell you?
Why he didn't join the provincial team
Never
What reason could he have?
My seniors said
It could be due to a serious injury
And it might be because
Want to go to a club abroad
But they just guessed
I am a swimmer How can I hurt my knee?
Please shock on me
Maybe I might swim faster
I'm not sure either
Don't reply to my message anymore
No answer
Hey you...
I can remember
Are you Weiwei's classmates?
You are Mai Sichong?
Yes
I'm Linbaihui
I'm her classmate
Hui student
Ask you something
Where is Weiwei?
Weiwei went to the coffee shop of the university
Ok thank you Hui student
Hui student?
Weiwei
Are you free tomorrow?
Why?
Let's go see a movie together
Compensate that day, did not say goodbye
okay?
okay
so,I'll buy ticket
Okay
Mei Weiwei
Why don't you reply to me?
I...
Bro
Sichong
I'm thinking of going to the pool for you.
I'm currently an intern at FT Sports
It's a company specializing in sports brokers
Are you interested in participating?
In addition to training There are still other contests
What do you mean?
You take advantage of your appearance and height
Can be a super star
Besides being a professional athlete, this is probably the best choice.
You know
Athlete's career is at high risk.
I understand
Thank you
But in my heart I have only one goal
Be the first of the provincial team
Compared to being a super star
I think
The pool seemed to suit me better
Becoming a professional player
Would be much better
But this walk is like a gamble
But if injury occurs during games or practice
There is still another option
Is it really considered to have a break, right?
It's not necessary, senior
Still have breath, Life has to be at risk
A blessing is not a curse. Bad luck is inevitable
No matter what happens
Why bother
I still have another practice. I go first
Mei Weiwei
Bro, then I will go first.
Will you stop calling my full name next?
Do like me as your servant
I haven't said anything yet
It's only you who follow me
I'm lazy to talk to you already
Senior Pengpai made an offer to you
You haven't thought so well, why hurry to refuse?
Let me stop swimming
No way
Who made you stop swimming?
Stupid
What did you say?
You say I'm stupid?
What right do you have that I am stupid?
I just said so
You...
Do you have anything to hide?
How can I have something to hide?
Overthinking
Go
Let me go
Why are you taking me here?
I've researched many times
So brought her to shock me
Yeah
I begged Dr. Wu Tang several times to use this electrotherapy room
Give it to me
You don't think that you...
Actually, you are suitable to be a physical therapist
No, I'm not
I just want to change a major
You...
Look
Shock with a little electric
My knees move more smoothly
If next, you give me an electric shock every day
My fitness
Will definitely recover quickly
Mai Sichong
Why don't you join the province team?
That's...
Just don't want to enter
Don't ask anymore
What are you doing?
Based on your appearance
When you lie your heart will beat faster
So now
You look in my eyes and tell me
That your body is not a problem
My heart rate is normal
I told you to say
That your body is not a problem
My body is not a problem
You can't look
Can't look
Deceit
I didn't mean
Weiwei
I'm wrong
I'm really wrong
Seriously, you shock me
No way
Err...
I will give you everything
I didn't want you to take responsibility
If you talk about it again
I'm going to shock you
Okay
Let's shock me
Shock me
Give it to me
Unless you shock me
Shock me
Give it to me
No
You've stepped on my shoes
Can you...
Can you forgive me?
Give it to me
Mai Sichong
You can borrow the keys to the electric treatment room, right?
You can also shock yourself
Why you have to come and ask me to help?
But only you that can shock me
And my training statistics have improved
Who knows why it must be you?
But...
The problem is not that it cannot be helped
From time to time I have never been shock continuously
Last time I shock you 2 times
Your voice is still like that
I don't dare to imagine
Weiwei
I won't let you take the responsibility
I will take responsibility for myself
Only the heavens know this story
You know, I know
Even if...
Even if there is a problem
I promise you no one will cause you trouble
But what if the problem happened?
No
I am going to have a problem
I don't agree
Weiwei
When I was in high school
I used to hit a record at 50.35 seconds
With this statistic
I can stick to the Olympics
Seriously
I, Mai Sichong, this life...
The most important thing is swimming
So...
No matter what happens
No matter what the consequences will be
I will bear it
Trust me
Okay?
oKay
All right
Let's go
Okay
Now no one here
Let's start
Come on
Start
Okay start
Do you feel it?
No
How about this?
Mei Weiwei, are you done?
I feel it
Hurry up
Hurry to practice quickly
My bag
Hurry up
What do you mean?
Isn't it because I'm trying to recharge you?
I'm afraid that you'll turn out of energy
Next, there is no power to shock, what do I do?
You can doubt me
But you can't doubt my electric power.
So why don't you eat?
I'm just afraid that you have something to ask for me again
So don't dare to eat
How can I do that
Then I feed you
I have hands, I can do it myself
What do you do again?
Can you eat by yourself?
Stupid
I just really wanted to thank you, so fed you
Hurry and eat
Really delicious
Try this
Who believes
Sichong
Recently, new movies are just getting popular
We go to see together, okay?
What movie?
What's the title?
You check it out
Electric shock
That's the name of the flash
Also, that's not Marvel's either
That's an American movie
Chong bro
You're not going to book tickets, right?
Xiao Chong student
You're not going to pay movie for me, right?
Like that, I'm shy
Don't be shy
Didn't invite you
And watch you look at me
Is it too cruel?
I...
I just look at what it is
Weiwei
Why are you here?
Do you not practice today?
No, I don't
To thank you, I want to pay a movie for you.
Weiwei
Bro
How long have you been waiting?
Not long
Sichong
So let's go see a movie
Go
Wait
Which movie?
Incidentally, I want to watch movies too
Let's watch together
However, I haven't bought a ticket yet
Let's go
Let go with us
Thanks
What are you doing?
Aren't you hungry?
If you are hungry then you can eat a lot
So irrational
Weiwei
I go to the bathroom
You look at this villain
So stupid
Weiwei
Is it over?
Not yet
Are you sleepy?
No
Keep watching
Err...
I'm sorry
Just half movie, I fell asleep
Half
In just the first 10 minutes, aren't you sleeping?
No, I'm not
So you tell
In which scene did the villain appear?
Enough, Mei Weiwei
You don't seem to understand
You understand?
Only look at the climax scene
Do you know a lot?
You're asleep, aren't you?
Come on, Sichong
Usually Weiwei doesn't like to watch movies like this anyway
She just likes the environment
It makes her relax
So
Would be inevitable if going to sleep
You don't take too much thought
All right
Tomorrow morning at 6:30 a.m.
Don't forget
Is there a queue tomorrow?
Recently we have studied
Bro
I'm leaving
Then I go to send you
No need