This time is the provincial team selection playoff round
How important is it? I won't have to say much
For equality
You guys must first undergo a drug test
Hope you guys
Will show your potential to the fullest
Understand?
Where's Xia Rui?
I'll go to see him
I owe you guys, sorry
Sorry
Mai Si Chong was the first of a university team swimmer
Who have been selected into the provincial team with excellent results
I said it, right?
Mai Si Chong must not have a problem
Weiwei
Now you're happy, right?
Why do you have to hurry to take pictures for him?
Women in love are really messed up
The Provincial Swimming Team Really awesome
No, you have to go back
Forgot it, ok?
No
How could the culprit not go?
Make the victim run away
You're willing to meet me
So now we...
Are we still friends?
You should go and apologize to Mai Si Chong
In your mind
There is only a Mai Si Chong, right?
This is not an important point
I...
Hope you don't
Throw away your conscience
I can't apologize
Everything has a price to pay
No one forgives me
I just have to pay back
Also, the Mai Si Chong chose to do drug testing
Unfolding about Mei Wei electricity
He must pay
Xia Rui
You cannot destroy other lives like this
It will also destroy yourself
If you insist on saying this
So
This will be the last time we meet
So have you ever worried about me?
You should go back to the dormitory
Everyone forgives you
I don't want to go back
Xia Rui
I know you are not a bad person
Please just admit it
We are happy to accept you again
Actually
I...
I want to thank you all the time
Because...
You are the first to see me
And you...
Willing to walk into my heart
Jun Jun
Thank you
All right
Go back to the dormitory
Where are you going?
I want to...
Be quiet alone
Think after this
How to go next?
Xia Rui
Actually
You are never neglected
You are in my heart
It shouldn't
I shouldn't have taken electricity anymore
My heart rate was not increasing
Probably static electricity
Come on
Trust me
By the way, the electricity has disappeared
It will not be repeated
About Xia Rui
What do you think?
And you?
Should I forgive him?
In your mind, you have the answer
From the day that I first got to know him
I think he is a man of great effort
Never lose hope
Even though a lot of things have happened recently
But I think
He's not what the outside shows
He's not that mean
I believe he is a good person
Our Mai Si Chong
Since when was the generous person?
I've always been a generous person
Let's go
Completed
Ok
All steps have been completed
Your documents will be sent directly to the provincial team
You don't have to think too much
Before
I think a little too much
When you go to the province team
Do your best
Don't make our university embarrassed
Did you hear it?
In the future, I have won the Olympics
I will hang a photograph here
Famous alumni
You hurry and go
I'll wait and see if you can do it or not
Err...
This year
Thanks to Mei Ling Professor
Go
So excuse me
Take care of your knees
I got it
Sorry
Are you ok?
I'm ok
Sorry
End of this month, have an international university championship
You remember to come and cheer me on
You have gone
The dorm will be just me and Bai Hui
He woke up at 6 o'clock to boxing every day
9 a.m. start meditating
How do I live?
Just follow him
Don't keep playing games all day and night
How will you do if you bald head?
Until then, Li Dai Xi had definitely left you
Here for you
When you don't see me, just look at this
Chong
I'll miss you
Enough, just haven't met
Where did Xia Rui go?
Xia Rui seemed to be preparing for another college entrance examination
But his grades are good
With his hard work
No university can not take the exam
Good
Chong
Are you still thinking about what Xia Rui did?
Forgot it, the matter has passed
Are you free for a moment?
I just want to come and tell you face to face
I talked to Coach Pei Pei already
That I was the one to frame you
Also, I have already handed out my resignation certificate
You trust me
About Mei Weiwei
I didn't tell anyone
And also
Sorry
Xia Rui
You know? First time I met you, what I feel?
Sober
Discipline
And also very talented
First group stage
Your score is not good
Coach Pei Pei asked you
What's your goal?
You said that you will try hard by yourself
Win the national championship
Since then
I consider you a real opponent
Xia Rui
Let's compete
Fair and honest
Will them officially compete?
Otherwise, what will?
Looks like a match
But the truth is for harmony
Who will win
I think
Lose, win, it doesn't matter
Start the competition
Get on track
Ready
Fighting
Mai Si Chong fighting
Xia Rui fighting
Fighting
Chong fighting
Mai Si Chong
Thank you
All right
Everyone just send me here
In the future, we will meet again
Bye bye Xia Rui
Bey bey Rui
Bye bye
It's very late
So...
Everyone, go back and relax
Such a long night
It's too late to go to sleep and have a sweet dream
Cheers
Mai Si Chong
We come like this, do we bother you?
Trust me
I've been stepping on
Tonight, my parents are not at home
What are you stepping on?
My house or your house?
Your house
In fact, the taste of wine is like this
My parents did not let me drink alcohol
Afraid that I'm drunk then shock people
In the future, you can drink comfortably
Anyway, there was me by your side
Chong, where did you learn this?
Fluently
Look at you
You don't learn to learn
Why do I have to learn?
Mai Si Chong student
Your knees get better
This is a medicine that we specially packaged
You use it in the morning and evening
The most important thing to recover is timing
Also has the intention
Thank you
You're welcome
Boss
This gift bag, you didn't choose it yourself, right?
Yu Xin helped me choose
Yu Xin, what is this?
Knee pads
Can also insert medicine sachets
Yes
It fits in my medicine bag
Come on
Let's have a few more drinks
Wish Chong have a bright future
Victory from the start
Cheers
Why am I here?
Should be...
Ding Yi take us here
Chong
We back already
You use this opportunity wisely
Fighting
Where're they?
Should have gone
Even the room was kept clean
So I go back too
Don't just
Are you hungry?
Otherwise, do you have something to eat?
You told me what you want to eat
I will make you eat
Cooking must be done often
Even though I haven't tried what it tastes like
But still looks fluent
Very professional
You just wait
Oh yeah
This is...
Specially selected for you
Congratulations on joining the provincial team
Electrostatic
Open to look
You ... This probably doesn't look too young, right?
No
Who would dare say that I was a little kid?
I, Mai Si Chong, definitely won't let him sat that
Trust me
In addition to training I will always wear it
So today, do you have any other plans?
Today
All day today, all time is yours
Where do you want to go? I'll go with you.
Officially congratulating new colleagues in 2020
Peng Pai
Lin Kang Kang
Jiang Si Yun
It's ok
You are so good
Wherever you are, you will shine
I heard that Sun Yang went to America this time
Lao Li will take you along
If market there going well, probably not coming back in 2-3 years
Are you going?
May be...
I wish you
You too
This kid
This feeling is really good
From childhood to growing up, thing that I envy other children the most is
they can be in parents' embrace, always be a child.
Finally, now I can do this
No need to be afraid that the electricity will shock you guys
You are not our little batteries anymore
Dad
Really ugly
However, the electricity is not that strong
Not shocking anyone to die
And also
Make you shock until you get a boyfriend too
Mai Si Chong, he didn't shock by me electric
He really like me
My daughter is wonderful
Like you guys
Oh yeah
Even now you will not have electricity
But still have to be careful
Still have to keep checking regularly
I know
Two beautiful women, eat strawberries
What are you doing?
I just watched a movie with my parents, and you?
I just finished playing a game with Ding Yi
You know he so sucks
This sucks, will also bring Li Dai Xi to play as well
I'm in trouble
I can confirm
Ding Yi said that Li Dai Xi is the same
Then he lied
What are you staring at?
I didn't feel before
Now I have looked at you. You are beautiful
So
So you mean that before I was ugly
No
I...
Didn't go to observe much of the feminine appearance
Just feel like
i'll go to sleep
Please don't
I haven't told you any other plans yet
What plan? say it
Tomorrow I will pick you up
Let's go camping
Ok
Then hurry to sleep. I still have to book a ticket
Then see you tomorrow
Fighting
See you tomorrow, good night
Bye bye
Oh no! The website page has crashed, please reload it
So many people, how can I buy a ticket?
Let's try one more time
Weiwei, breakfast
Weiwei
Weiwei, you...
Lao Mei
Doctor
What's happen?
Is she ok?
Weiwei
Last time because you said you wanted to remove electricity from you
Do you still use other methods?
Weiwei, you have to tell me the truth
Otherwise I couldn't help you
Say it
I took the medicine that you gave me
Whole box
You!
Are you crazy? To eat the whole box
You said you were anxious to remove this electricity
Why exactly
Dr.Jiang
Is there any other way to treat this?
Yes
You have to help us
Her heart rate looks normal now
But before
Her heartbeat will determine the electrical release
With wristband
She will be sure that  she is safe or not
But now
From the results of this examination
Electricity is more unstable
Like this
Weiwei
I will give you medicine first. To stabilize the body
Within 24 hours of receiving the drug
Your emotional state of mind will stabilize
Will not easily release electricity again
But
Because the drug is a powerful antidepressant
After eating
Will be very sleepy
In addition
I advise you guys
Find a place that is less crowded
Stay for half a year
Maybe the situation might change