San, what are you doing?
-Type!
-Let me go!
I said let go.
I'm gonna kill him!
Type, calm down.
This is a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
I saw it with my own eyes.
You think I'm stupid?
What did you see?
I saw you two kissing.
-The fuck are you laughing at?
-I'm laughing at you.
I thought you were Tharn's roommate.
You said it yourself.
So, why are you interrupting us?
San…
that's enough.
Stop messing around.
I'm not messing around.
I call it like I see it.
I respect you.
But if you're trying to mislead him…
I won't forgive you.
I haven't done anything.
He told me there was nothing
between you and him.
So I have the right.
You have no right!
Please leave.
Thank you for bringing my car here.
Let me go, Tharn.
Calm down, you misunderstood.
Let me go.
He's mine!
Tharn is mine.
You hear me?
Tharn belongs to me.
I belong to you.
The fuck are you laughing at?
Tharn…
won't you invite me to come up?
I brought your car here.
Or do you want other people to witness…
a gay couple's argument?
I hate your senior!
Type…
San kissed me…
because…
he brought my car here for me.
Because he brought your car here?
He was kidding.
I swear to God,
I only have eyes for you…
and no one else.
I'd better not catch you cheating on me.
Type…
So you can admit it.
What the hell do you mean?
You can admit you're Tharn's boyfriend.
I thought you were a coward.
I'm not a coward.
But you are selfish.
Thorn said you had a problem before.
Me?
What problem?
You were moping
when you went home that time.
So I wanted to see
who had made Mr. Thara mope.
After I saw him,
I knew he was a troublemaker.
I'm a troublemaker?
You're the type
who won't admit you're dating Tharn.
You let Tharn handle problems for you.
You think you're always right.
That's a troublemaker.
And why do I have to go around
saying I'm dating a man?
I don't want you to do that.
But I want you to care about his feelings.
Because he's straightforward.
He always speaks his mind.
Thorn said Tharn couldn't say
a thing this time.
Because his partner
wanted to keep it a secret.
In the end, Tharn will always
go out of his way for you.
San…
Type's not that kind of man.
Are you trying to pick a fight with me?
I'm okay with the way things are now.
Are you sure?
You'll always have to change
yourself for him.
It won't work out.
It won't last if you're the only giver
in this relationship.
Actually, I didn't want to get involved.
But Thorn said you're serious about him.
So I wanted to teach him a lesson.
I was afraid you'd be
the only one getting hurt.
Tharn's your baby or what?
No.
He's my first love.
He was the one I loved the most.
The one I wanted to take care of the most.
But I never got the chance.
Tharn, seriously, what do you see in him?
Leave the way you came!
Type.
No need to chase me away.
I'm an outsider, that's all I can say.
Tharn's suffered enough heartbreak.
Don't make him experience it again.
You sure are worried about him.
It's fun to see a big baby get agitated.
-Type.
-Let me go.
-That's enough.
-Why are you stopping me?
I guess you're happy now, Tharn.
I hate your senior.
I understand.
I hate it
that he won't just leave you alone.
I know.
I hate seeing you with him.
I hate it that he acts
as if he knows everything about you.
I hate how it felt
when I saw you two kissing.
I hate that you're his first love.
And most importantly,
I hate this feeling of jealousy.
Okay.
I admit it.
I'm jealous.
And I'm…
sorry.
Sorry about what?
I'm sorry I've never been
a good boyfriend.
I'll try coming to terms with the fact…
that I'm dating a man.
Actually,
you don't have to push yourself…
because…
I can wait for the day you're ready.
Your senior's right.
I'm self-centered.
But this self-centered man
never wants to break up with you.
I guess this means…
I…
have to thank San, right?
Don't mention his name again.
Most importantly,
even if he has a thing for you,
you should remember…
that you are mine!
Where are you going?
Downstairs, to get what I dropped.
I almost threw a Suki sauce bottle
at your senior's head.
But I was in too much of a shock.
If my groceries are gone,
you have to pay for them.
Why did you drag me here?
You don't have anything to do anyway.
I was playing games, you know?
Come on, drinks on me. Let's go.
Come on.
-Khong, hello.
-Tharn, you've arrived.
You brought a friend. Sit down.
Make yourself comfortable.
-Jeed.
-Yes?
-Come here and take care of them.
-Okay.
Here.
-Hello, Jeed.
-Hello.
Make yourself comfortable.
I'll be right back.
Just go, Khong.
So…
How come you came here together?
We can't come here together?
Last time, I got drunk here
because you broke my heart.
But this time,
you look much better.
Do you have good news?
We're just friends.
Friends…
who are more than just friends.
I'm blushing.
Oh, my God!
Why do you look so surprised, Tharn?
Why are you surprised?
I just want to let people know
you're mine.
-I can't take it. I'm blushing.
-What are you talking about?
You scared me to death! There's good news.
You're pregnant?
No! Sit down right now.
-You're absolutely clueless.
-So, what's the good news?
It's about them.
By the way, the restroom is pretty empty.
You can get busy in there.
Too blunt.
-We can discuss business in my office.
-Okay.
I've come to talk to Khong
about coming back to perform here again.
So, I wanted you to be here with me.
I guess he needs support.
Yes. I never get any.
-Let's talk, shall we?
-Okay, I'll be right back.
Don't worry about him.
-Don't do anything to him.
-Okay.
-What would you like to drink?
-Anything's fine.
Tharn, you finished?
This is Ten and Kae.
Hello, Tharn.
How…
do you know me?
They're your fans.
They saw me with you,
so they came to say hi.
Hello.
Tharn, do you remember me?
If I say I don't, will you get mad at me?
I can't get mad at such a handsome face.
I've often bought you drinks.
Thank you very much.
Can I buy you a drink tonight, Type?
Maybe next time.
I got turned down.
I'm not turning you down.
Why do you think I'm making an excuse
to see you again?
I'm not easy,
but I'm not hard to get either.
This is my number…
Is talking all you want to do?
Type…
What?
Don't get on my nerves.
What did you whisper to her?
Nothing.
Type…
Don't be crazy. I was just playing around.
It didn't look
like you were playing around.
It's your turn to get jealous.
We're even.
I guess I'm pretty charming too.
Charming, huh?
Come with me.
What the hell?
Tharn…
this isn't funny anymore.
But I'm really enjoying it, Type.
If you do it here, I'll kill you.
Go on.
I want to try dying…
while on top of you.
Tharn!
You want to practice
your flirting skills that much?
Then practice with me!
Don't mess with me.
Did you enjoy provoking me?
Did you enjoy making me jealous?
And did you enjoy making me
want to yank that woman away from you?
I sure did.
I enjoyed it…
because I knew tonight
was gonna be a blast.
Let me tell you something.
No matter how many fangirls you have…
if you cheat on me…
I'll cheat on you back
worse than you can imagine.
Don't think I'll go soft on you
just because I tell people we're dating.
I, Thiwat, am more evil than you think.
By the way,
looks like someone
won't be having a blast tonight.
I'LL BE BACK LATE TODAY.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
KHONG'S BAR. WITH BANDMATES.
WILL BE A LONG TALK.
OK.
DON'T WAIT UP.
WHEN WILL YOU BE BACK?
YOU'LL WAIT?
DICK.
NOT SURE.
WHATEVER.
POSSESSIVE?
WANNA DIE?
LOL.
What are you doing?
Why don't you go practice?
You've been addicted to your phone lately.
Is it the girlfriend
they've been talking about?
What's she like?
Is she prettier than Puifai?
I guess, if they had long hair.
So how are things with your friends?
I haven't talked to them
since they gave me the cold shoulder.
Anyway,
you need something?
Can you tutor me?
Please?
I can't believe someone
who rarely shows up to class like you…
can be so smart.
LET'S GO ON A DATE AFTER THE EXAM.
Wait a minute, Type.
I didn't know you could have
that lovestruck look.
What are you talking about?
Are you drunk?
Anyway, will you help me?
Your girlfriend will love you heaps.
Love me heaps?
Are you a love potion or something?
I'll pray for your girlfriend to love you
heaps and bunches.
Okay, I'll help you,
but you don't have to pray for me.
Because, right now, that person
is already falling head over heels for me.
Damn, Type.
You're so full of yourself.
I'm glad you came with me.
What's this place?
Answer me now.
What do you think this place is?
Your house!
Why did you bring me here?
You already know.
So, why are you asking?
What a jerk!
Come on.
I'm stopping by to switch cars.
And my brother wants to meet you.
Don't worry, Thorn's the only one home.
You can relax.
How can I relax?
This is your house.
I don't want to be here.
Why are you two standing out here?
Hi, Thorn.
Do I look intimidating?
You didn't make it inside,
so I came to get you.
-Hello.
You're Type, right?
I've seen your photos.
You look better in person.
You've seen me in photos?
He's following you on Instagram.
I love to stalk people.
Especially when it comes
to my brother's life.
Seems like Type had no clue
you were bringing him here.
But I can assure you
our parents aren't home.
Come on.
Tharn!
I missed you so much.
I forgot to tell you Thanya's home.
Don't you have a piano lesson today?
I let it slip to her
that you were bringing a friend home,
so she wanted to see you.
Because I missed you.
I missed you too, Thanya.
Hello.
Why didn't you tell me
you were coming home?
I'm just stopping by to switch cars,
so I didn't tell you. Sorry.
Thorn said you were bringing
your special friend,
so I called Mom and Dad,
and they hurried back.
Did I do good?
Guess whose favorite food this is?
Just in time. Let's have dinner.
Let's eat.
Type, come sit next to me.
Tharn, go sit at your place.
Come on, don't be afraid.
Eat up, everyone.
Okay, can I eat now?
Of course, go on.
Have you known each other long?
Not long.
We met last semester.
You lived on campus together.
Yes.
And you moved off campus together.
Actually, I'd wanted to live off campus,
but my dad wouldn't allow it.
Until…
Tharn…
offered to split the rent.
So my dad gave me the green light.
Does this mean your house
is far from the university?
My parents live in Surat Thani.
To be precise, his dad owns a resort
on Ko Phangan.
Don't you have any relatives here at all?
Actually, my aunt lives here.
I'd lived with her
since I was in junior high school.
But when I entered university,
I asked my dad if I could live in a dorm.
Have you had any problems living together?
Does Tharn ever make you uncomfortable?
Not at all.
Tharn doesn't make me
uncomfortable at all.
Relax, I just want to chat with you.
Okay.
Honey, speaking of Phangan,
we should plan a family trip
to Phangan, don't you think?
Sounds good.
We can stay at his family's resort.
That's right, Dad. Let's go now.
It's nothing.
But didn't you use up all
your annual holiday leave, Dad?
We should go another year.
But we haven't been to a beach
in Thailand for years.
I think I can manage it.
Let's hold off for a while longer.
You just went on a trip with your friends.
And you said you've been too busy
and you don't have time to rest.
I think we should let Tharn
explore the place first.
And we can go there together later.
Because I don't want to get hurt again.
Will you stay overnight, Tharn?
That's right,
you two should sleep here tonight,
so you don't have to drive back.
You should stay. I'll head back by myself.
You can spend the night
and leave together tomorrow, okay?
It's okay, I don't want to impose.
You're not imposing at all.
Thorn used to bring San here to play games
and stay overnight all the time.
San?
San, Thorn's friend. Do you know him?
Yes.
I know him.
So you're going to stay overnight, right?
You too, Type. Please.
Then, I hope you don't mind if I stay.
Not at all.
Eat this.
Eat up.
My mom's cooking is the best.
Give it a try.
Please don't be angry with me.
Do I look like I'm angry?
Then, what are you feeling?
Read my lips.
I'm fucking angry.
Is that clear?
I'm…
sorry.
Still angry.
I didn't know…
my parents had found out about us.
But they don't mind.
Let's make up.
Don't stress yourself out.
Don't worry.
Don't think too much.
So what if I do?
If you overthink…
I'll overthink even more.
If you're stressed…
I'll be even more stressed.
And if you're worried…
I'll be even more worried.
Trust me, Type.
I…
won't let you feel bad alone.
I'm your boyfriend.
You think I'll forgive you?
Do you?
Tharn…
Tharn, stop. I'm ticklish.
If you don't stop,
I'll hold out on sex for a week.
Okay.
So…
we can do it now, right?
Perv.
Don't touch my face.
I'm happy…
you're sleeping over.
But your parents are scary.
My parents…
seem to like you.
Otherwise, they wouldn't have
let you sleep over.
So that means they like San too.
He used to spend the night
here every week.
He invited himself here.
But…
my parents really like you.
So…
you can relax.
I hate you.
But I love you.
I love you.
Type…
Normally, people give morning kisses.
Dream on.
You said you wanted it.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Tharn gets to play in such a big place?
Why are you so excited?
I thought he played in a small bar,
not a big one like this.
I really respect him
after he showed me his drumming skills.
His hands are swift.
Isn't it cool?
How long has he been playing here?
I didn't tell you?
You never told me about anything at all.
I had to find out by myself…
that you two are together.
He's been playing here
since he was in high school.
His old band broke up
because he fought with a bandmate.
He's just formed a new band
during semester break.
So the bar owner held an audition
to see their skills.
As you know, his band is playing
in the evening time slot.
It's not peak hours.
But Tharn said it's good enough
for a new band.
You sure know a lot about your boyfriend.
-You asshole.
-I'm serious.
-How many members does his band have?
-Four.
-Lead singer?
-His friend, Lhong.
See? You can be a good boyfriend.
How is this relevant?
That's good.
Being attentive is better
than being hot-headed.
Usually, when I babble this much,
you give me such an earful
that I can't find my way back home.
-Want me to do that?
-No.
Type!
You're here to show support
for your boyfriend?
No.
My friend here asked me if I knew
a good bar with great atmosphere.
Your place came to mind.
You're so sweet.
Let me find you the best table.
How about a table in front of the stage?
You can have a clear view of Tharn.
-Okay.
-Follow me.
Make yourself comfortable.
Wait.
I didn't know you had a thing
for older women.
Not to mention,
she teased both you and Tharn.
Normally, you wouldn't let that slide.
It's because she's older.
And Tharn works here.
What does that have to do with Tharn?
Use your brain, Techno.
If I upset Jeed,
Tharn will get into trouble.
You've really changed, Type!
-Go!
-What?
Hey.
Type.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
It wasn't my idea. It's his.
-Hi, Techno.
-Hi.
Why are you sitting here?
Let me rest my legs a bit.
I'll take to the stage in a minute.
Please?
Wanna drink?
Not yet. I'll wait until the gig's over.
No need to give him a drink.
He'll get plenty when he gets on stage.
Are you…
jealous?
Jealous, my ass.
I knew it.
You can't speak nicely.
Are you saying I have a dirty mouth?
I'm not saying anything.
But you know me so well.
You two are so…
lovey-dovey.
The hell you talking about?
I mean…
you're talking to each other…
as if you're the only two people
in the world.
You're wrong, Techno.
My world doesn't revolve
around just me and him.
But the most important person…
is him.
-I'm gonna be sick.
-Me too.
-What's going on here?
-Hey.
Wait, let me introduce myself first.
My name's Lhong.
I'm his friend and I study music.
-Okay, hello.
-Hello.
-I'm Techno.
-Techno.
-Sports science major.
That's Type.
Sports science major too.
Type?
I know you.
You're famous.
What do you mean?
Everyone on campus knows you
because your photo was posted online.
I'm sorry, I said too much.
Sorry.
You said way too much, Lhong.
I'm sorry.
Let's get on stage.
I've finished tuning up.
Tae's already waiting.
Are they your friends?
Hello, I'm Song.
I'm the guitarist.
Tharn and Lhong are my idols.
I really admire them.
Song, I think you should've
just introduced yourself.
I'm Techno.
That's my friend, Type.
Hello, Techno, Type.
Let's go, Tharn, Lhong. I'm super excited.
-Sure.
-Let's go.
-Come on, hurry up.
-All right.
Hurry up!
Type, I have to go now.
Do your best.
What a good supporter.
What?
By the way, are you okay?
Please give us a round of applause.
Here's our next song.
Please sing along if you know the lyrics.
I know you are not keen on me.
You are far from interested in me
But I am not the type to give up
I am such a saint and you know it
But it seems like I am not
The one you want
I am ready to do whatever it takes
I will do everything I can
To make you mine
I will not let you walk awaywith anyone
I will not let anyone stay by your side
No matter how long it takes
I will give my all to make you mine
I will not let anyone else love you
Because you are the only one
I want to hold
My heart is yearning
My heart is calling out
I need to let you know
I will not let you walk awaywith anyone
I will not let anyone stay by your side
No matter how long it takes
I will give my all to make you mine
I will not let you walk awaywith anyone
I will not let anyone stay by your side
No matter how long it takes
I will give my all to make you mine
I will not let anyone else love you
Thank you.
Here, put the blanket on him.
Our team is going to kill me
if he catches a cold.
-Okay, wifey.
-Watch it.
You'll be next.
Who's wifey?
Tharn is Type's wifey.
Tharn…
I'm curious.
About what?
The face you made
when you were playing drums…
What about it?
It was so damn sexy.
When I was playing drums?
To me…
music is like sex.
It gives me climactic pleasure.
And now…
I know…
what my most cherished instrument is.
Drums.
No.
It's you.
My most cherished instrument.
Type!
Type…
-You want to do it now?
-Be still.
Type, be gentle. It hurts!
Shut up and be still.
Techno.
Get up and eat your congee.
Tharn bought it for you.
I can't.
Feels like my head's gonna explode.
Come on, get up.
Here.
What's up, Lhong?
Hold it properly. Don't spill it.
Type?
-What?
-It's just…
Last night…
I…
-heard--
-Techno!
If you keep talking…
I'll kill you!
If you tell anyone about last night…
Dude! I slept like a baby last night.
Very soundly and comfortably.
-Good.
-Great.
Type…
Lhong will stop by this evening.
Can I tell him…
we're together?
That's your personal business.
None of my business.
I'll go eat my congee over there.
Hot!
Please help me just this once.
Yes.
When the professor takes the roll call,
answer it for me.
All right, I'll treat you
to lunch for a week.
Thank you.
Tar, when did you get here?
I've been standing here forever.
Really?
How come you can pick me up today?
You see…
I'm free.
Don't you have class?
I did.
But it ended early.
So I rushed here to pick you up.
You hungry? Do you want to eat anything?
I just want to go home.
Really?
Let's go home, then.
Let's go.
Type…
if I tell Lhong that we're together…
will you be okay with it?
-'Cause if you're not okay--
-Stop being selfless.
I feel like the bad guy.
Haven't you heard?
We always fall for the bad guys.
Whether it's a good guy or bad guy…
I don't want either one.
I'm only okay with you.
I love you, Type.
I might too.
You really…
Hi, Lhong.
Handsome boy is here!
Water.
Thanks.
Lhong…
I have something to tell you.
What's wrong?
You look serious.
You see…
Type and I…
We're together.
Are you okay?
Don't.
I'll clean up later.
What's wrong with you?
Why didn't I know about this before?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
I forgot I have to meet my family.
I have to go.
But you just got here.
It's really important.
Gotta go now.
Here, you can have them.
What's up with him?
No idea.
Take this.
I'm going to clean up.
Be careful. They're sharp.
Tharn, why can't I get
a girlfriend at all?
Nobody's interested in me.
I want a girlfriend. What should I do?
-Don't be silly, Song.
-Come on, Tharn.
-Let's go home.
-Okay.
I'm sorry.
-Tar?
-Tharn?
Tharn, wait!
I… I've been missing you.
I have to go, Tar.
Let's go, Song.
You're back?
Go back to sleep.
Take a shower, quickly…
and hurry back to be my pillow.
Tharn has never dated anyone
more than two months.
Until he met…
Tar.
-Who?
-I never wanted to break up with you!
Tar wants me back.
Why didn't you tell me…
that kid's your ex-boyfriend?
Does he taste as good…
as when you were together?