Type, wake up.
You've been lying on my arm
the whole night.
My arm is numb.
Type.
Don't squeeze my shoulder. It hurts.
What's with the shocked face?
You got into my bed last night.
You… me… on a bed…
and you're naked.
Last night, you and I--
I don't believe it!
Tharn, you bastard!
Asshole! Son of a bitch!
What's happening? Are you okay?
Do you want me to tell them
last night you and I--
No!
Type.
You can be surprisingly cowardly.
Are you…
going to cry?
I'm not!
How did I end up in your bed?
You got in it yourself.
Liar!
Are you implying I dragged you to my bed?
It's because I was drunk.
Why would I drag you to my bed
if you were sleeping in yours?
I could have done it in your bed.
Except you already did!
How your body feels…
is my answer.
Shit.
My butt hurts.
But I fell off the bed.
Nothing happened to me.
Tharn! You tricked me!
I'll get you back for this.
Just mosquito bites.
Not a goddamn hickey or anything!
Tharn, I'm gonna kill you!
When we're seniors,
don't forget to vote for me.
-Vote to be what?
-Team captain.
Techno!
Type! He's my friend.
Please, calm down! I'm begging you!
Stop! Calm down.
How can I be frickin' calm?
This is because of you, mother trucker!
You ditched me last night.
Do you realize what happened to me?
Don't tell me you two already…
Wait! Stop! Stop right now!
I had nothing to do with this.
You climbed into his bed!
What's wrong with you, Techno?
I'm leaving.
Can't you help me?
I climbed into his bed?
Yeah, you climbed into his bed.
I tried to drag you off,
but you wouldn't budge.
It's not my fault, I'm telling you.
Besides, the dorm was about to close.
My mom would've killed me
if I had slept over.
Stop right there!
This whole thing is your fault.
You got yourself drunk
when you knew who you were with.
My head!
Which means I went through hell
this morning because you left me.
I didn't leave you.
-So, did you two do it?
-No!
How did you get out of it unscathed?
Believe it or not, I did.
-Tharn is true to his word.
-What the hell do you mean?
Take it easy and listen to me, okay?
Last night, I asked him
not to do anything to you.
He said he wouldn't do drunk people.
That's why I said he was true to his word.
That asshole!
Why are you still mad?
He said that because he's confident
that anyone who jumps
into his bed is willing.
If something really had
happened last night,
it would mean I'd done it willingly,
and that's impossible.
Just forget about it, man.
It's in the past.
Actually, I have good news for you.
What is it? Nothing's ever been
good ever since I met Tharn.
Come on, this one is for real.
I've found someone
to switch rooms with you.
Who?
Hey, Champ! Over here. Come here.
What's up, Techno?
This is the guy I told you about.
He's the only one who's agreed
to switch rooms with you.
Yeah, I want to switch rooms too.
Not that my roommate is bad,
but he studies medicine.
He's up reading all night. I can't sleep.
That's why I want to switch rooms.
I'll let you discuss
and go to the Dorm Office to…
I changed my mind.
Thanks for agreeing
to switch rooms with me,
but I have some unfinished business
with my roommate.
Sorry for wasting your time.
It's all right. Come talk to me
if you change your mind again.
See you.
-Where are you going?
-To the locker room to change.
Okay.
What the hell is wrong with you again?
I tried to help.
If I move out, I'll lose the war.
He's the one who must leave, not me!
But, Type, your grudge…
will put your ass virginity on the line.
BUILDING THREE
How is Techno doing?
Techno? He's fine.
He's been practicing hard lately.
He wants to be team captain.
That's awesome.
Wait a sec, let me tie my shoelaces.
I'm sorry.
-What the hell?
-What's up with him?
-Should've watched where he was going.
-Yeah.
-Someone's here to pick him up again?
-Who are you talking about?
That student from the French program
who bumped into you.
He always has someone to pick him up.
But he took time off school last year.
Do you know why?
Forget him. I don't care.
I only care about Techno.
You prick.
What else do you care about
aside from my brother's butt?
Send me his pictures,
and I'll give you anything you want.
You really know me well.
In that case,
I'll go to my room first, Tum.
Okay.
Hello, Mom.
I can take care of Tar.
You don't need to worry.
Let me see.
Hurry up and taste it.
I want to know if it's delicious.
Looks as good as always,
but I'm not sure if it tastes good yet.
How is it?
Is it bad?
But I followed the recipe
exactly like last time.
Did I make too much sauce?
I'm just kidding.
Why are you spacing out, Tharn?
It's nothing.
I'm just…
thinking about what to eat.
Just eat whatever you want.
And stop looking so stressed.
Or…
does one of your exes want to make up?
No.
I'm stressed out…
about forming a new band.
Come on, we have plenty of time
to find new members.
We only need to find
a bassist and a guitarist.
That reminds me.
I found this clip…
being shared on Facebook.
Do you remember Song?
-Song?
-Yeah.
Song, who calls you his "idol."
Yeah, that's him.
I think his guitar skills are pretty good.
I'll let him audition for our band.
What do you think?
I'm okay with it. I think he's good.
-Then, I'll leave it to you.
-I'm on it.
I'll tell you the date
as soon as possible.
-I'm going to buy lunch.
-Okay.
DON'T TOUCH MY STUFF!
"Don't touch my stuff!"
Think of it as payback
for what you did this morning.
Just a bunch of cheap snacks.
In case you're hungry,
lick the bed, roomie.
I ATE THEM. SO WHAT?
What the hell did you do?
What did I do? I didn't do anything.
If it wasn't you, then which jerk did it?
Damn it! I don't know!
Stop making so much noise, God damn it!
WATCH BEFORE IT'S DELETED.
WHAT DID YOU JUST SEND?
DO YOU STILL SEE ME AS A WOMAN?
THERE ARE SO MANY
INSPIRING CLIPS OUT THERE.
INSTEAD, YOU SENT PORN.
MY MOM'S SITTING RIGHT NEXT TO ME.
IF SHE SAW ME WATCHING PORN,
I'D BE KILLED.
MORE. GIVE ME MORE.
BE RIGHT BACK.
I'M GONNA CHECK IT OUT. THANKS, DUDE.
This is good stuff.
The hell are you smiling at?
What are you looking at! Get out!
And why is that?
It's you who should know
this is a shared room.
And I thought you were disgusted by me.
Or do you…
-have feelings for me.
-The hell I do!
I hate you so much I don't even want
to breathe the same air as you.
Why did I have to be put
in the same room as you?
Did your dad not love you as a kid?
Is that why you go after men?
-Don't insult my dad!
-What are you doing?
I've had enough
of your shitty attitude, Type!
Let me go!
Kick me, I dare you. Kick me.
-I said let go.
-Why should I do as you say?
Let me go.
Where's the arrogant bastard
who insulted my dad?
Let me go!
Please, let me go.
Don't hurt me.
Please.
I'm sorry.
Please, let me go.
I just want to help you relax.
Calm down.
Don't.
Let me go.
Are you okay?
Get off me!
What the hell is wrong with you, Type?
I hate you.
It's okay, Type.
What's up?
I thought you didn't want to eat.
Good thing I haven't gone home yet.
Sorry.
I forgot I didn't have
any food in my room.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I ordered for you.
Do you want to eat anything in particular?
No, I'll eat what you ordered.
I hate you.
What's the matter, Tharn?
I'm sorry, Lhong.
-I have to go.
-What?
What about your dinner?
Excuse me, I want to cancel…
the order.
Too late for that.
I'll finish all of it.
Just two dishes.
No!
Don't do it!
Type!
What are you doing here, kiddo?
You like football?
Yes.
I know a football field
with lots of balls.
Do you want to play there?
Yes.
Don't do it!
Type!
Don't!
Daddy! Mommy! Help me!
Let me have fun with you, kiddo.
What's the matter, Type?
Let me go.
Let go! Let me go!
Type, what's wrong?
Help me.
-Type, wake up.
-Help me.
Wake up.
-Wake up, Type. Wake up.
-Help me.
Help me…
Tharn.
-Wake up, Type!
-Help me, Tharn.
Wake up!
Wake up.
It's okay, Type.
I'm here.
I'm here with you.
It's okay.
Leave me alone!
What the hell was that for?
I helped wake you up!
I didn't ask you to do it.
That's true, you didn't.
But I'm kind enough…
to help a grown man
who's still afraid of his nightmares.
I'm not afraid of nightmares.
You don't know anything. So, back off!
Then, what are you afraid of?
I'm not afraid of anything!
I'm never afraid of anything.
Do you expect me to believe that when
you're crying and trembling like that?
Stop being so cocky!
I can be as cocky as I want.
I'll tell you this.
Even if I cried myself to death,
I wouldn't ask for your help.
Remember that.
I'm sorry…
for meddling in your life.
I didn't ask for your help.
Type.
Wake up. It's almost 8:00.
Get up, already.
I'm waking you up…
not because I have a thing for you,
but because I pity you.
-Wake up, it's almost 8:00.
-Shut up!
Leave me alone.
Suit yourself.
Sleep all you want.
What the hell?
My head is killing me.
Techno.
Type, where are you?
I'm already on campus.
Let's have some breakfast.
I don't want to.
You sound weird. Did you just wake up?
Get up now. The class is about to start.
Don't tell me you're going to skip.
I have a headache.
You're sick?Should I go check on you?
Don't, I'll be fine.
I'm hanging up.
Damn.
Shit, what should I do?
Tharn. Come this way.
What's wrong? Feeling cranky?
What do you want? I'm in a hurry to class.
I wanted to ask if Type is seriously ill.
You didn't know he's sick?
And how do you know that?
I called him this morning
to invite him for breakfast,
but he said he had a headache.
And his voice was really hoarse.
I called him again just now,
but he didn't pick up.
That's why I asked you
if he's seriously sick.
Sorry, you have class, right?
It's okay. Just go.
I'll go check on him myself.
I have to hurry back to class too.
The professor is super strict.
See you.
What?
You…
can go back to class.
I'll check on him.
Didn't you say you have to hurry to class?
Just go. This rice soup
is for him, right? Give it to me.
So, I'll go check on him,
and you go to class. See you.
Tharn! That's my rice soup. It's mine.
Type, take some medicine.
Take some medicine.
Get up.
Type.
I'm going to try to bring your fever down.
Dad, don't go. Dad!
Don't leave me.
I'm not going to leave you.
Just trying to lower your fever.
Don't go.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm sitting right beside you.
Stupid me, I forgot to ask
for Tharn's number.
Tharn, where are you going? How's Type?
Still sleeping.
He's been sleeping since morning.
I'll go buy medicine and gel patches.
It's okay. I already bought them.
I asked Champ to let me in.
You go with Type's roommate.
Take care of him.
I'll go find something to eat.
See you, Tharn.
Bye.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
I'll go with Tharn.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Nothing.
It's just that you have my respect.
You guys fight every day,
but you're still helping him
with his fever.
We live in the same room.
I can't let him die in there.
That's why I said you're super-duper nice.
Let's say you were the one who's sick.
I bet he'd leave you to rot.
-Techno.
-What?
Can you do me a favor?
What is it?
Don't tell Type I'm the one
who took care of him.
Why not?
Come on. Pretty please.
Okay, if that's what you want.
You two are equally weird.
Just a sec.
Give me your number.
In case I want to ask you
how Type's doing.
Okay. Let's go.
Why are you being nice to me?
What exactly do you want?
What a nice smell.
Is it a sin to steal food from the sick?
You're awake? How are you?
Feeling better now?
Let me check.
I skipped practice to take care of you.
Is this your rice soup?
Yeah, I bought it for you this morning,
but you were sleeping,
so I didn't wake you up.
I already reheated it, though.
I'm about to eat it myself if you don't.
-So, it's you.
-I'm what?
Nothing.
Get up and eat, so you can take the meds.
I'm not hungry.
Don't be like this. You have to eat.
Come on, the meds will hurt your stomach
if you don't eat anything.
Come on, get up.
At least take a few bites.
You're so stubborn.
Where is he?
He?
You mean Tharn?
I don't know.
Why do you ask?
Never mind.
I'm full.
Only three bites?
The meds.
Are you okay?
So, you've been taking care…
Tharn, you're back?
Where have you been? Type's up.
I went out to get worksheets.
Type, what were you saying?
Nothing.
Who's calling?
Shit!
-Type, the senior's calling me.
-What?
-I'm screwed.
-Just pick up.
I know that.
I'm screwed big time.
I'll take the call outside.
Hello.
Yes.
Who took care of me?
You don't want it to be me, right?
That's right.
Then, you're lucky.
Because I'm too busy
to nurse a big baby like you.
So, it was Techno.
Your friend took care of you.
Good thing you got better.
Go take a shower if you're awake.
I don't want to be near a germ spreader…
who's also dirty.
My fever's still high.
I'm not blushing or anything.
-So close.
-I'll play with one hand.
Where the hell is Technic?
Hello, Type.
-Hello.
Game over. You lost.
Where have you been since morning?
You took my motorbike again, didn't you?
-You're lucky I didn't call the cops.
-Are you crazy, Techno?
I went to see Kla. He got me snacks
from Japan. Don't you want some?
-Really? Give it to me.
-Yeah.
I almost forgot.
Don't throw!
-What's this?
-My dad bought them for you.
What's this?
Salted eggs.
I talked to my dad
on the phone the other day.
When he found out I was sick,
he sent this as a thank you gift
for taking care of his beloved son.
-Is that so?
-Yeah.
Why are you giving it to me?
Why not give it to Tharn?
Tharn? Why him? It'd be a waste.
Don't you know the one
taking care of you was Tharn?
What did you say?
-It wasn't you?
-No.
I didn't do it.
Tharn was the one who took care of you.
He gave you food and water, meds,
helped reduce your fever, and…
changed your clothes too, I guess.
Type.
-What?
-Listen to me.
Tharn, your so-called enemy,
is a really great guy.
Type.
He skipped classes to take care of you.
By the way, how come you didn't realize
the one who helped you get better
was the one you hated the most?
He said you took care of me.
Definitely not me.
As I recall, I checked on you
the first day you got sick.
Bastard!
You're my friend.
Why didn't you take care of me?
Yes, I'm your friend.
But if I take care of you now,
you'll end up in a hospital.
Tharn is the right guy for the job.
Damn, it hurts.
I'm going.
-Where?
-Back to my dorm.
I thought you didn't want to go back.
-Piss off!
-What the hell?
What was that for?
Salted eggs and taros.
I'll be totally stuffed.
Type, what are you doing?
Why aren't you going in?
What's wrong?
Fighting with your roommate again?
Who told you?
Techno.
Why? Is he a total prick
despite his good looks?
No.
He's too good.
So good…
that I feel guilty for hating him.
And why do you hate him…
if he's that good?
I'm still confused why you wanted
to switch rooms with me.
What's with him?
Tharn.
Last night, did you do something to me?
Where are my boxers?
Give them back!
Let me shower with you.