So…
What are you gonna do next?
For someone like me,
it has to be an eye for an eye.
What are you doing?
Hello?
Hello, my name is Type.
I'm Tharn's boyfriend.
I have something to--
Son of a bitch!
That coward hung up on me.
Don't tell me you called…
Tharn's ex-boyfriend.
He acted as if I was a bad guy
who tried to kill him.
Techno.
What?
You said that kid went to
the same school as Technic, right?
Don't tell me you're gonna…
I'm gonna find him.
Type, isn't there any other way?
No.
I'm gonna deal with him.
Relax.
Nic's home!
Man, that was fast.
What have you got?
Don't rush me. You gave me only one night.
There's quite a few 11th graders
in my school.
So you have nothing?
I do have something.
But what do you have in exchange, Techno?
I…
Are these photos of all the 11th graders?
Yes.
You made a bargain with me,
but you gave in to Type so easily.
Flexibility is key.
You need to know who can
or can't be bargained with.
-For Type…
-What?
I give in.
So you're saying I'm stupid.
You know?
I found him.
Let me see.
This is him.
He's the French program student.
I've met him many times.
He's well known because of his good looks.
If you're done, I'm going to school now.
Hold on.
Do me one more favor.
Is that him?
No, he's taller than that.
Type.
Isn't this bullying?
What? When did I ever bully him?
Yeah, right.
But there's three of us.
We are ganging up on him.
And you could kill people with that look.
Speaking of which,
I have something to say.
What?
Your brother's good looking.
So?
-So, why are you fugly?
-Asshole.
Don't you want me to relax?
Just keep stressing out.
Type, that's Tar.
Bring him here.
Hurry up.
Easy, man.
Type!
I thought my brother was here.
You're Tar, right?
-Yes.
-I'm Type.
What's the rush?
Don't you wanna talk to Type?
Or do you only wanna talk to Tharn?
Aren't you gonna say anything?
I'll make you break up with Tharn.
What did you say?
Calm down, Type.
You are good-looking,
but how could you be so foul-mouthed?
How can you steal someone's boyfriend?
You're going to break up anyway.
-You shitty brat!
-Calm down, Type.
-Please.
-Take it easy.
This is a café.
There are other people here.
They'll think you're bullying him.
And you too.
You broke up with Tharn a long time ago.
So why are you interfering
with their love?
No matter what you say,
you two are going to break up.
No matter what,
I'm going to be the cause of your breakup.
Took you long enough to return.
Had a tryst with your ex-boyfriend again?
I had band practice today.
If you don't believe me,
ask Lhong.
There's no need.
I believe you.
Because I just met
your ex-boyfriend today.
Are you stunned?
I only met with your Tar.
Tar's not mine.
But you're his.
Do you really have no idea?
What do you mean?
There's nothing to interpret.
He told me…
you belonged to him.
And no matter what,
he's gonna take you away from me.
Type…
-you know that I--
-I'm not finished.
Don't interrupt me.
That kid…
He said that you still loved him.
And that he loved you so freaking much.
So much so that he's willing to be outed
as a boyfriend stealer.
Because he doesn't want to lose you.
He said all this time…
he's never forgotten you.
He's been dying to return to you.
He was even crying
when he said that to me.
Poor him.
Type.
-I still love you--
-Shut up!
I never said you could speak.
You know what?
Your old flame…
is so full of shit!
He was crying and sobbing.
Saying he wanted you back.
Does he see himself as a novel heroine
and think I'll give back his ex
just because he begs and cries?
I won't lose anything easily.
A single punch to his face…
is not satisfying enough.
You punched Tar?
Why?
You're worried about him?
Are you that worried about him?
Are you blind?
He's also a man.
A single punch…
won't kill him.
Please calm down, Type.
I'm worried about you.
I don't want you to get into trouble.
You're full of shit too!
Admit you're worried about him.
And, yeah.
This is how I am…
hot-tempered…
vulgar…
impulsive.
Just a scumbag who bullies kids.
But no one puts themselves in my shoes.
No one understands me at all!
I understand you, Type.
But you need to listen.
I want to explain about last night.
Let me go.
-I love you.
-Let me go.
I love you, Type.
I said let go!
I don't wanna listen.
It's over.
I told that kid…
you're not his!
You're mine!
And don't meet him again.
Promise me.
I promise.
I won't see Tar again.
Look me in the eyes and promise.
I promise.
I won't be with anyone but you.
Believe me, Type.
Please.
Remember your promise.
Where are you going?
Somewhere without you.
Damn it.
Type.
Slow down.
You'll get drunk early.
Don't stop me.
I'm acting like this
because of your shitty friend.
Come on.
Trust him when he says
there's nothing going on.
You want me to believe someone
who lied to me?
He probably didn't want to upset you.
You know how caring he is.
Maybe he thought you'd overthink
if you knew about it.
Besides,
he only met with Tar.
He didn't sleep with him.
First Techno,
and now you.
Am I so bad
that nobody takes my side at all?
I didn't mean it that way.
What do we do now?
If what you said is true,
then this is all Tar's fault.
You just realized that?
Well…
you have to understand.
Your personality's
the exact opposite of his.
Anybody would think you're the bad guy.
I mean, look at you.
You punched an 11th grader.
You're lucky no teachers were around
and no one recorded it,
or you'd be screwed.
Calm down.
The more you play his game,
the more you lose.
This is how I am.
I'm always the bad guy, anyway.
He said he could accept the way I am.
And now he wants me to change.
As Tharn's best friend…
I know he can accept you the way you are.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have
given you his all.
But you need to keep your cool.
Because Tar is cunning.
I didn't realize…
an innocent-looking boy…
could be so evil.
He also told me he wanted his Tharn back.
Have I been fooled all this time?
Tum even said his brother was
a goody two shoes.
Both you and Tharn have been fooled.
No matter how evil Tar is…
or how much he cries and begs…
if Tharn doesn't reciprocate…
it's nothing more than an unrequited love.
If he does,
I'll break up with him.
Don't worry.
He'll never do something like that to you.
He really loves you.
I hope you're right.
Take your man back.
Why is he with you?
You two are fighting.
So I had to deal with him.
Type.
Why is he wasted?
-Type.
-I already told you.
Because you two are fighting.
Can't you just talk nicely?
Thanks so much for bringing him back.
-Type.
-You're welcome.
Handsome Lhong is glad to be of service.
Be nice to each other, okay?
I'm leaving.
Lhong.
So…
did Type…
tell you anything?
Type, what are you doing?
Boyfriend.
You're mine, Tharn.
You should take care of him first.
Didn't know this tough guy…
could be so cute when he's drunk.
I'm yours, Type.
Thanks so much…
for bringing him back.
Let's go.
No problem.
I'm leaving.
I…
have always been yours, Type.
Don't be stubborn.
I'm trying to make you comfortable.
You're awful, you know?
You always drive me crazy…
whenever you want.
When I saw Lhong hugging you…
I was very jealous.
I don't mind
that you went out for a drink.
But why did you go with another man?
Even though Lhong's my friend,
I'm still possessive of you.
And Tar…
Don't worry.
Because that kid…
doesn't mean anything to me anymore.
You're the only one for me.
What are you rambling about?
You woke me up.
Sorry.
So…
how do you feel?
I'm sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
For…
losing my temper.
You serious?
Talking with Lhong made me realize…
that I never listened to you.
I always get mad at you.
I don't know why, but I'm frustrated.
I feel awful.
I don't know how to explain my feelings.
Stop apologizing.
I'm the one who should apologize.
I won't see Tar again.
Please forgive me.
Tharn…
hug me.
You…
are drunk.
I'm not drunk.
I guess what people say is true.
Drunk people never admit they're drunk.
Jerk.
So…
You forgive me, right?
No.
Not until you hug me.
You're such a tease.
Forgive me.
Your friend already defended you.
You have a good friend.
Lhong…
is the best friend I've ever had.
If there's a next time,
I'm gonna kill you.
I promise.
You've made a promise.
You've promised.
Tharn!
What's wrong, Lhong?
Why are you yelling?
Read this.
What's this?
I wondered the same thing at first.
Last week, I uploaded the clips
of our band practicing
and playing at Khong's bar on YouTube.
And a scout actually contacted us.
But doesn't it look fishy to you?
If we don't try, we'll never know.
Let's give it a try, then.
We'll talk to them.
Then I'll tell Tae and Song, okay?
I don't think you should.
We'd better discuss this ourselves.
I don't want to get their hopes up.
We should be happy…
and disappointed together.
So, who's going to do the talk? You or me?
I'll do it.
-Send me the contact details.
-Okay.
If I make an appointment with them,
let's go together.
Sure.
I'LL BE BACK LATE TODAY
I HAVE SOCCER PRACTICE.
WILL BE BACK LATE TOO.
WANNA EAT ANYTHING? I'LL BUY IT FOR YOU.
NO, I'LL EAT TECHNO.
"EATING WITH TECHNO" AND
"EATING TECHNO" ARE DIFFERENT.
Hello.
Where are you?
I got a flat tire.
Just when I'm in a hurry too.
I don't know how to change a tire,
so I called a mechanic.
But I don't know when they'll arrive.
-Do you want me to be there?
-No, it's okay.
It's almost time
for the meeting with the record label.
Just buy me some time.
I'll be there as soon as I'm done here.
Okay.
Just hurry.
Let me go!
Tum is not here!
So let me go!
I said let go!
Let me go!
Tum is not here!
I said let go!
What the hell are you doing!
-Stay out of this.
-Stay back!
I paid for this kid. He's mine.
Tharn, I didn't sell my body.
What's going on here?
Should I alert the staff?
Damn! I wasted my money for nothing!
Is he okay?
He's fine.
It's just a misunderstanding. I'm sorry.
Okay.
Tar, are you okay?
I'm not a prostitute.
I'm really not.
Get up.
COME AND SEE FOR YOURSELF.
Is this how you want to play?
Type.
Why are you here?
At a hotel, no less.
Did Tharn tell you to come?
Tharn told me to come too.
Let's find him.
Are you all right now?
I'm feeling better.
Then…
I'll call Tum.
Do you hate me that much?
What are you doing?
You…
didn't get punched?
Why did you trick me?
I was worried sick, you know?
At least,
you still worry about me.
Tar! Stop!
Tar, let me go.
No.
I won't.
I'll never let you go again.
I said let me go.
No.
I won't let you go.
Tar!
If you don't stop…
you won't even be a brother to me.
No.
I won't let go.
I won't.
Tar.
I have an appointment,
so let me go.
They won't come.
What do you mean?
You…
tricked me?
Tharn, listen to me.
I didn't want to trick you.
But I had no choice.
You had a choice.
And you chose to trick me.
I said let go.
No!
Tharn, listen to me.
It's the only way I could
be with you again.
I didn't want to trick you.
Just this once.
Give me just this once.
Tar!
You can't do this.
Just this once and I'll leave
you alone for good.
Tar.
Tar!
Stop stooping so low!
I have no choice.
I haven't had it for a long time.
Now I'm just a loose brat…
who can sleep with anybody.
I'm despicable.
But I love you.
I love you.
I really love you.
Tar.
I have a boyfriend.
Break up.
You'll eventually break up with him.
You have no choice.
Just like me.
You brat!
Let's take it outside…
It's not what you think.
I can't believe it.
You're mistaken.
There's nothing between me and Tar.
You win.
Happy?
I was a fool…
to think Tharn would never screw around.
to think men like Tharn could change.
And I should've realized that…
in the end…
you'd screw him.
Let's break up, Tharn.
No, Type.
I won't break up with you.
Please don't say this. I won't break up.
I won't put up with this anymore.
How do you think I feel
when I have to get possessive
and jealous all the time?
And I don't want to play
your ex-boyfriend's game anymore.
I've had enough.
Calm down.
Type.
It's obviously that brat's plan.
Don't take it out on Tharn.
What do you mean?
What plan?
Stop being so easily manipulated.
Type!
He's still furious.
Let's wait until both of you calm down.
Calm down?
You're telling me to calm down?
After Type's just broken up with me?
What do you know?
Tell me everything.
All I know is…
when I arrived…
Type took the elevator to come see you.
He told me…
Tar texted him…
saying you still loved him.
He told Type to come here
if he didn't believe it.
He'd prove it.
Tar…
I don't ever wanna see your face again.
-Tharn.
-Tharn!
What are you doing?
Moving out, of course.
So I won't stand in your way
when you bring new boyfriends here.
I won't break up with you, Type.
I'll never do it.
But I will.
Type!
I didn't sleep with Tar.
Please believe me.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
But you know, don't you?
Tar was the one who texted you.
So, how could you believe him?
I know it's a set-up.
Then, why--
But I won't take it anymore.
This time, it's a set-up.
But which one of your exes
will come crying to you next time?
First, San was messing with my head.
Now your old flame keeps bothering me.
So who's it gonna be next time?
Do you want me to lose my goddamn mind?
But I haven't done anything.
That's why I'm telling you.
I can't take it anymore.
I don't wanna be a joke anymore.
Look at me.
I'm a man.
Do you think I wanna be like this?
To constantly get jealous?
To keep telling everyone you're mine?
I'm fed up.
Each day…
I hate myself more and more.
And if we have to break up some day…
isn't it better to do it now?
Before we get in deeper.
Before I lose myself
more than I already have.
Please, let me go.
Type…
I love you.
Please, give me another chance.
Please, give me one more chance.
I promise.
I won't hurt you anymore.
I won't make you cry.
So, please, don't leave me.
Don't break up with me.
Don't do this, Tharn.
Don't make me give up everything.
Type!
I'll eat spicy food.
I'll eat raw food.
I won't be picky anymore.
I'll get up early to wake you up
every morning.
I'll learn how to cook…
for you.
But please don't leave me.
Don't break up with me, Type.
Everything I do…
I do it for you, Tharn.
Type?
What happened?
Why are you carrying a bag?
I broke up with him.
Do you expect me to stay?
I think you should calm down.
You're angry right now.
If you think this through…
you might be able to forgive him.
I don't think so.
Whether it's now…
or later…
I have to break up with him anyway.
Maybe it's for the best…
to break up with him now.
Before I'm not able to let him go.
How's Tharn doing?
I don't know.
Take care of him for me.
Are you sure?
Yes.
If this is your decision…
then I'll take care of Tharn.
They're all a bunch of idiots.
I did as I was told.
Give those clips back to me.
Sure.
I'll send you the original files.
Thank you for your hard work.
Tharn will never be into you.
What are you talking about?
I know who you are.
I've stayed silent for a year.
But I know it's you…
Lhong.
No matter how hard you try…
Tharn will never look at you.
And you think you have a better chance?
You think Tharn will take back someone
who made him break up
with his dear boyfriend?
Besides,
that someone…
also slept with three men
at the same time.
You sent them to rape me.
Go to hell, you bastard!
I won't go to hell that easily.
Unlike you, who can cry yourself
to death all you want,
and Tharn will never take you back.
Remember that!
Tum.
Tharn.
I'm sorry.
Tar.
Tar, what's happening?
Are you okay?
What's happening? Tar?
Tar, open the door.
Tar.
Come out and tell me what's wrong.
Why don't you ever tell me anything?
Can't I help you at all?
I'm sorry.
I'm the only one who never abandons him.
I'm the only one who never betrays him.