My life as a university freshman
begins here.
And everything is better than expected,
because even though my dearest dad
forced me to live on campus,
at least I still have
my friends, my peers…
and even a roommate…
who's perfectly handsome
and so goddamn nice.
I bet he and I can help each other
get laid within the first year.
And did I mention…
I…
hated gay people…
until…
Type!
What the hell? You're so noisy.
Did you know?
Know what?
Your roommate…
is gay!
What did you say?
Type.
When did you get back?
Have you eaten yet? I have some snacks.
Tharn, I have something to ask you.
What is it?
And why do you look so serious?
Are you gay?
Well?
Yes.
Then, I have to be honest.
I hate gay people.
-So, what do you want me to do?
-One of us has to move out.
Are you disgusted just because I'm gay?
Yeah, that's right.
And how does me being gay…
have anything to do with you?
It doesn't,
but I won't live with a gay person.
Then, move out.
Because I'm not the one with a problem.
You are.
Tharn, I'll say it one more time.
I hate gay people
with every fiber of my being.
If I had known you were gay,
I wouldn't have come near you.
You filthy perv!
That's none of my business.
Because I'll never move out.
Even if I have to live
with a narrow-minded jerk like you.
You must leave!
I don't know what kind of assholes
you've been around before…
but even if you can get rid of me,
you won't be able to live in this society
if you still judge people
with that ridiculous logic.
Remember that!
What are you doing?
Congratulations.
You have to live with this gay man…
for a year.
Fine.
I want to switch rooms.
No can do.
All the rooms are jam-packed this year.
Do you realize how lucky you are
to even get a room?
The upperclassmen moved off campus
so that the freshmen could live here.
I'll do anything.
Isn't there anyone who wants
to switch rooms, Auntie?
Everyone switches rooms by themselves.
They don't come here to complain.
But this is the Dormitory Office, Auntie.
If there really is a problem,
I can arrange the change.
I have a problem with my roommate.
What is it? It has to be really serious
or I can't help.
My roommate is…
Never mind, Auntie.
I really can't live with him.
Call me "Auntie" one more time,
and I won't help.
Sorry, sis.
You can't switch rooms without a reason,
and I don't accept petty reasons,
like not helping with cleaning.
It's your responsibility to handle things
with your roommate.
What should I do?
Find someone to switch rooms with you
and come here.
Sis will do the rest.
Okay, Auntie.
You brat!
Hi, Techno, are you free this evening?
Free or not, you have no choice,
you have to help me.
Type, do you really want to move out?
I already told you I do.
Type.
Honestly, who would want
to switch rooms with you?
Everyone must be close
to their roommates by now.
I don't know, but I'm gonna find one.
Why are you so stubborn?
-Hello, my friend wants to--
-I want to switch rooms with you.
I'd rather not.
He didn't even listen.
Techno.
Let's check other rooms.
Okay, let's go.
You wouldn't survive a night
if you switched to this room. Damn!
Let's check other rooms.
There are still more.
Can you switch rooms?
-With who?
-My friend here.
Not a chance.
Everyone's turned you down
because of that look on your face.
Wait a minute.
Calm down.
Over there.
The last room on this floor.
Besides…
it's right next to your room.
What are you gonna do?
Fine.
What's wrong with you?
What's up?
-Khlui, Type wants to--
-Wait a sec.
Seo Duang, quiet down.
Khlui, can you switch rooms with me?
What's going on?
Come on, please switch rooms with me.
Nah, my roommate is pretty decent.
Hey.
I guess.
Okay.
Khlui, is your roommate Korean?
I'm beginning to have my doubts.
Not sure if he's Korean
or just plain crazy.
Okay. I'd better go.
What the hell?
He gave me a murderous look
just because I said no?
Why?
Why did he come?
Stop speaking Korean. I don't understand.
You have to move out.
I won't stand living with you anymore.
Get up and talk to me.
Move out.
No way.
Type!
I won't live with gay people.
Is that clear, you piece of shit?
You have no right to kick me out.
I've done nothing to you.
Not yet, but maybe in the future.
I don't trust people like you.
I bet you screw anybody
who comes your way.
Do you hate me that much, Type?
Then, how about I screw you too!
No!
Still falling out of bed at your age?
What an idiot.
Who did you call an idiot? You…
See you tonight, roomie.
Who's your roomie?
I told you I'm moving out!
Last time, we talked
about Baroque and Classicism.
Today's topic is Romanticism.
Does anybody know
the characteristics of Romanticism?
Okay. Romanticism is the artistic movement
in which characteristics of each composer
-are vividly demonstrated…
-Which page are we on?
…in terms of imagination,
emotion, and musical expression,
which are free of constraints.
It focuses on emotional expression
in music rather than boundaries.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
But your face says otherwise.
Okay, I have a little problem.
Ran into your ex this morning?
No.
Then some guys must've fought over you.
I said no!
The professor will get angry.
Just take notes.
Someone asked you out,
but he turned out to be a muscle bear,
and he asked, "Can I bang you, Tharn?"
Am I right?
Are you having fun?
Stop teasing me.
It's rare to see you upset.
Just tell me what's wrong.
I can help.
It's nothing.
If you say so.
About our new band.
I'm interested in a guitarist.
He has awesome skills.
Tharn.
What were you saying?
I said I'm interested in a guitarist.
He has awesome skills.
Hey, I'm here.
Judging from the look on your face,
things didn't go well, huh?
No, he won't move out.
Honestly, Type,
why would he want to move out?
He's done nothing wrong.
Just because he's not into girls,
it doesn't mean he's a rapist-murderer.
And he never hassles you.
So why does he have to go?
Because he's gay.
Yes, he's gay.
But he hasn't made a move on you.
-Or has he?
-Quit bullshitting, Techno.
One more word, and I'll shut
your mouth with my foot.
Almost hit my face.
Just kidding.
So, what are you gonna do?
What type of roommate
is the most disgusting for you?
Don't tell me you're going to--
Hell yeah!
Man, you're so childish.
Okay, I'll help.
As your friend, I have no choice.
First of all, someone who disrespects--
Wait a sec.
-Ready.
-Someone who disrespects people's privacy.
That's a no-no.
For example,
you're dead tired from practice.
You return to your room, ready to sleep.
He comes in, switches on the lights,
brings his friends, and blasts some music.
-No manners.
-Correct.
Next, a slob.
For example, he finishes eating
and puts the dishes in the sink.
You have to do the dishes for him.
Think about it. Are you his slave?
More, give me more.
How about this?
Remember when we were in 10th grade?
I know what to do now.
And what is that?
You haven't answered me.
What's gotten into him?
Damn, I shouldn't have told him
Tharn was gay.
They were getting along just fine.
THREE WEEKS EARLIER
Hi, roommate. My name is Tharn.
Hi, I'm Type.
Is this my bed?
By the way, you can eat the snacks.
That's really nice of you.
Someone gave them to me.
I can't finish them all.
You must be pretty popular.
Who would be interested in me?
If nobody liked you,
there'd be hope left for me.
If you need any help, just tell me.
We'll be living together for a year,
after all.
Might take you up on that.
THREE WEEKS LATER
The war has begun.
MOVE OUT, GAY MAN!
What the hell is this?
I was going to leave you alone, Type.
But if you want to play a game…
then game on.
Type, you sure you want to use
this plan to get rid of Tharn?
It was your idea, Techno.
My idea, but you didn't have
to follow through with it.
Messing up his stuff? Really?
Yeah, and if he cleans up,
I'm going to mess it up again.
Let's see how long he lasts.
I bet he'd last a long time.
Wait!
Type! Calm down, man!
I give up!
Man, it was a joke.
Not funny.
I was just kidding.
Don't be so serious, man.
I WON'T MOVE OUT! BIGOTED JERK!
What the hell happened?
What the hell is this?
I've been looking for this.
So, that's where it went.
This is lube, you asshole!
Yeah.
No one said it was dishwashing liquid.
Damn you, Tharn!
It's almost empty.
But that's okay.
A filthy perv like me
still has plenty more.
This one is for you.
Think of it as a welcome gift.
I don't want it!
Gifts should be accepted.
What you do with it is up to you.
And this…
is a bonus.
I WON'T MOVE OUT! BIGOTED JERK!
-Don't mess with me.
-You started it.
Did your parents never teach you
not to touch others' belongings!
So you messed with my stuff as payback?
If you can do it, so can I.
I will make you move out.
You hate me that much?
Fine!
Wait a minute.
What?
-What are you thinking?
-What do you mean?
Are you sure about inviting
Team and Oam to party here?
I don't care.
Besides, they're already inside.
You want me to kick them out?
Heartless.
Why are you attacking me?
I'm warning you for your own good.
If Tharn finds out,
he'll be really pissed.
The angrier the better.
Damn, you're a total asshole.
Let's drink. Cheers!
Look at that smug face.
Type, I think your roommate's back.
You're back?
I have my friends over.
We'll be a little noisy.
Since your roommate's back,
we'd better leave. Let's go.
What's the rush? It's not even 8:00 yet.
My roommate won't mind.
Right?
I don't mind.
The more…
the merrier.
Let me join you.
-No--
-Sure, man.
Go ahead.
Team, mix some booze for Type's roommate.
Sure.
By the way,
I'm Oam.
Type's high school friend.
And my name is…
Team.
I'm…
Techno.
What about you?
I'm Tharn.
What are you doing on my bed?
Your bed?
Type.
You said it was your bed.
Damn, you tricked me.
Tharn, I'm sorry.
I thought it was his bed.
Don't be mad.
I'm not mad at you.
It's no big deal.
You're really nice, just like Type said.
Type complimented me?
-I didn't.
-Quit it, man. You just said it.
What did he say, Team?
He said you're nice,
and very generous.
No matter how much we mess up the room,
you won't mind.
I didn't know…
that you admired me this much.
I'm gonna buy more snacks.
Type.
I'm so thirsty.
I'll go help him carry it.
Hurry back.
I'm going crazy.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I'm stressed, man, very stressed.
Damn, I thought I was in the middle
of World War II.
It's driving me crazy.
Auntie?
The guys next door are so noisy.
They argue every day.
I don't know anything about that.
But will you stop calling me "Auntie"?
Come on, Auntie. I'm worried about them.
And I want to know
what they're fighting about.
Such a busybody.
I'm curious.
Hey, what are you doing here?
You want to go up together?
-Hello.
-Hi.
Seo, can you speak Thai?
I don't understand.
I asked what you were doing here.
Do you want to go back up together?
No, you go first.
I'm still talking to Auntie.
Auntie, my ass.
Okay.
-See you later, Auntie.
-You!
I love you!
I'm really curious, Auntie.
They're at it again.
What's going on?
You're such a busybody.
Type, we need to talk.
You're so immature.
Do you actually think…
that you can get rid of me
with your childish plan?
If my plan wasn't working,
you wouldn't be here, picking a fight.
Do you seriously think I'll give up
just because you have your friends over?
Looks that way to me.
I should've told them you're gay.
I'm dying to see their reactions.
Go ahead.
I'm dying to see their reactions…
when they find out you've been living
with a gay man all this time.
I'm not gay! I'm not like you,
and I'll never be like you!
But don't forget.
You're living with a gay man.
And…
Son of a bitch!
If you stay around me,
you'll get infected with gay virus.
If you do that one more time,
I'll beat you to death!
Didn't you say I screwed around?
Then, there's nothing wrong…
with screwing you too.
Damn you, Tharn!
Stop right now! What's going on?
Nothing, Auntie.
We're just saying hello…
as friends.
What are they fighting about?
Korean ghost!
Korean, my ass. I'm Thai.
You really scared me.
When did you get here?
Just now.
Damn you! They're gone!
I'm here to get you.
You didn't return to the room.
Come on, it's getting late.
Let's talk to Auntie tomorrow.
Okay.
This is awesome.
It's definitely your "type," Type.
No wonder you like fair-skinned chicks.
Superb.
Oh, my God!
Type.
Your roommate's back.
Should we ask for his permission?
What for?
I play clips, you just watch.
My roommate is a nice guy.
No matter what I do, he'll never move out.
Since when have you been a jerk?
Let me tell you something.
Empathy is key
when living with other people.
That's rich coming from the prick
who used someone else's bed.
On second thought,
this stuff is not that good.
Tharn, come watch with us.
-Let me see.
-Don't bother. He's not interested.
Who says I'm not interested?
-Because you're--
-I'm what?
-Play it already. Stop spacing out.
-All right.
Let me switch to full screen first.
Damn.
Type.
I really can't get it up with your stuff.
This is not great at all.
-Do you want to watch mine?
-No way!
But we're interested.
My skin crawls just thinking about it.
Why?
What do you mean by that?
Tharn.
Are you into some hardcore stuff?
Damn!
Looks can be deceiving.
Try it and you'll be hooked.
Let me play it for you.
Are you bi?
No, I don't like women.
So you trick people into thinking
you're straight with this video.
To be honest,
I don't care about the video.
All I care about
is the person watching it.
What the hell are you saying?
Don't try my patience again.
It's wearing thin.
-Screw you!
-You two!
Go drink if you have nothing to do.
You're so noisy.
We're getting to the best part.
Look, things are heating up.
Damn! Look at her huge boobs!
-This one is yours.
-Thanks a lot for this, man.
See you. Techno, hurry up and go home!
-Safe trip.
-Yeah.
Type, wake up.
Do you know whose bed you're sleeping on?
Come on, wake up.
I'm gonna sleep.
Type!
You know exactly where you are.
Damn it.
But you still got yourself drunk.
I wouldn't be surprised if you get raped.
Hey.
Type, come on, get up.
He told you, right?
Wake up. Come on.
You need to wake up right now. Type.
You know, don't you?
Know? Know what?
I don't know anything.
-About us partying here?
-About me being gay.
So, you know, then.
What else did he tell you?
He told me a little bit.
He's always hated gay people.
But I don't know why.
Ever since I met him…
he's always said he hated gay people.
When we were in high school,
some classmates even teased him
about being molested by gay people.
And do you know what happened?
He beat them to a pulp.
It was so funny.
But I'm not anti-gay or anything.
I have lots of gay friends.
Most are very feminine.
But… you…
I've never known one like you before.
Tharn.
I want to apologize on Type's behalf.
Okay?
He's not a bad guy.
Please, understand him.
Tharn.
Can you do me a favor?
What is it?
Can you move out of this room?
Please?
Please, do it for my sake.
All this stress is turning me gray.
Please.
I can't.
I've done nothing wrong.
Why do I have to go?
So you won't have to put up with him.
I don't know…
where your friend's gotten this attitude…
but if I move out…
it will mean I believe
my sexual orientation is wrong.
And I don't think I'm wrong.
So I'm not moving out.
Suit yourself.
If you want to put up with his silliness…
I never would have thought
a smart guy like him
could be silly enough
to play this mind game with you.
Get up.
Man, he's heavy.
Help me, so I can get him out of your bed.
Leave him be.
Why?
I'm going to teach him a lesson.
Don't tell me…
Don't worry.
I don't do drunk people.
You sure?
Just go home.
It's almost 11:00.
Shit! What am I gonna do?
Damn, the dorm security officer
is strict, too.
Okay, I'm leaving.
But…
you wouldn't really
do anything to him, right?
Just…
go easy on him.
He has class tomorrow.
Hickeys are hard to get rid of.
Why am I so attracted to you, Type?
You must really hate me.
You started this.
Do you realize…
you're just like…
a child.
But when you're awake…
you're nothing but a brat.
I want to see you…
when you wake up…
and find out you've been sleeping
next to me all night.
How crazy are you going to be?
Sweet dreams.
Roomie.
In case you're hungry, lick the bed.
Don't insult my dad!
Who took care of me?
You don't want it to be me, right?