Hey.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Then why did you startle?
Who are you texting?
Take a look.
I'm talking with Lhong
about an assignment.
Glad everything's fine then.
I won't cheat on you.
Paranoid, aren't you?
Let's find something to eat.
I have to finish the assignment.
Bring it with you.
You're the hubby.
You have to pamper me.
Well, hubby?
Will you come with me?
Whatever wifey wants to eat…
hubby will get it for him.
Very good.
They say your life gets better
if you pamper your wife.
Have I become someone
who's afraid of his wife?
Aren't you then?
Come on, have lunch with me.
I'll buy dinner for you later.
Thank you, wifey.
What's up?
You…
Tharn's friend.
You can't remember my name.
I am…
-your boyfriend's--
-Freaking Lhong!
Just Lhong is enough.
That's me.
The handsome lead singer of the band.
But I've heard you're not
as popular as the drummer.
Harsh.
That really hurts.
Don't be overdramatic.
I'm going to tell Tharn
you're picking on me.
Go on, and let's see whose side
he's gonna take.
Playing the boyfriend card?
I'll lose for sure.
How about…
you treat me to a meal in exchange for…
Tharn's information?
I just bought a new guitar.
I can't even buy cafeteria food
with money I have left.
Tharn's info?
I know everything.
He can confirm it.
Interested?
Deal.
Thank you.
I paid for your food.
Your turn.
Ask anything you want to know.
I know everything.
Especially about ex-boyfriends.
Why would I need to know about his exes?
He has quite a reputation
when it comes to dating.
He'd dated people from every class year.
But the flings didn't last long.
I guess he's cursed.
With what?
I've been going out with him just fine.
You're the one who broke the curse.
If you don't count San though.
You know him?
Apart from San…
all of Tharn's exes were assholes.
Tharn had his first boyfriend…
when he was in tenth grade.
He was a sophomore student
and extremely handsome too.
He was a violin major.
But Tharn…
caught him…
five-timing.
You heard it right.
Five-timing.
He even had a sugar daddy.
Tharn said…
he was lucky he didn't catch any STDs.
But at that time, he was totally crushed.
After that…
the two-month curse had begun.
What two-month curse?
Excuse me, I want to order a drink.
-What would you like?
-What do you want?
I'm good.
Then…
-I'll have Sprite.
-Okay.
Thank you.
You see…
Tharn never dated anyone
more than two months.
He either got cheated on…
or dumped…
with stupid-ass reasons.
Like, "you're too good, Tharn."
At one point, he began to sleep around.
He had sex with anyone who offered.
Until he met…
Tar.
Who?
My ex-bandmate's little brother.
He was cute, tiny, and all that stuff.
He had a crush on Tharn.
He said he fell in love the moment
he saw Tharn playing drums.
So he plucked up the courage
and confessed.
Seriously, it was like
reading a romance manga.
They even declared their love
in front of everyone at a bar.
And then they…
did it.
Isn't that skipping steps?
They really did it.
During that time,
Tharn was deeply in love.
He even wrote songs for Tar.
They were so much in love.
What happened next?
They…
broke up.
The end.
How did it end just like that?
They really broke up.
No. I mean, why did they break up?
The kid found a new guy?
Tharn got bored?
Or what?
It couldn't have just ended like that.
I really don't know.
Tharn told me they broke up.
Tum punched him,
saying he hurt his brother.
And Tar…
never saw him again.
He even wrote him love songs,
so why did they break up?
Come on.
In the end…
you and Tharn ended up together.
And if you want to know more,
go ask Tharn.
Most importantly…
don't rat me out.
I don't want him to blame me
for putting heavy stuff
in his darling boyfriend's head.
I'm gonna tell him
you sold him out over food.
But I know you won't do that to me.
Right?
You haven't touched your food.
Let me eat it.
The hell?
You sure eat a lot.
I don't get fat.
Tharn.
May I sit with you?
Tar, I have to go.
Wait, Tharn.
I need to talk to you.
But I have nothing to talk to you.
I have work too. Bye.
Tharn, wait!
We used to…
hold hands like this.
What do you want?
I want talk to you about something.
You must be really mad at me.
I'm not mad anymore.
It's been over a year, Tar.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sorry for what I did.
Actually, just say what you want to say.
I told you I have to go to work.
Well…
I don't know how to tell you…
or explain it to you.
But I have my reasons
for everything I did.
When you figure it out…
go tell Tum and have him tell me then.
I have to go.
I never wanted to break up with you!
Why are you saying this now?
Well, Tar?
It's okay.
I'm sorry, Tar.
I never wanted to break up with you.
So why did you do it?
I can't tell you.
But I really have my reasons.
Is it so hard to tell me?
Or did you break up with me
because I did something bad?
I really can't tell you.
But…
please forgive me, Tharn.
What if I say…
no?
Then I'll keep apologizing
until you forgive me.
Why are you doing this?
What do you want?
Let's get back together.
I love you.
I loved you then and I love you still.
Please give me a second chance.
-Tar, I…
-Don't reject me just yet.
Please give me one more chance
to make it up to you.
Tar, I have to go.
Tharn.
Freaking hot.
You're back?
I've been back for a while now.
Are you hungry?
I bought you dinner.
Yeah.
But let me take a shower first.
Tharn.
Is there a party or something?
Whose birthday is it?
My birthday is on April the second.
Tharn.
Don't hug me. It's hot.
I'm sorry.
The hell is wrong with you?
You're sorry for buying too much food.
Next time, just buy enough to eat.
I'm sorry, Type.
What's going on with you?
You keep saying sorry.
Did you do bad things behind my back?
I didn't.
I just feel that…
lately…
I've rarely had time for you.
You worry too much.
Don't sweat the small stuff.
I understand you're busy with the band.
And I'm also busy with the team.
If you say it's your fault
you haven't had time for me…
you're implying it's my fault too.
I didn't mean to imply that.
So…
are you going to eat?
Of course, you already bought them.
Let's eat just a few things
and put the rest in the fridge.
I love you, Type.
Don't say it too often.
It'll lose meaning.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Type.
Why are you so adorable?
Whatever, let me take a shower first.
Tar.
Stop doing this.
We won't get anything out of it.
I really messed up, Tharn.
I have something to tell you.
Okay.
I've found someone new.
And I love him very much.
What happened between us…
is over.
It was over last year.
Don't bring up the past again.
Do you understand me?
If you really love me…
don't ever do this again.
Break up.
What did you say?
You'll eventually break up with him.
Your love will never last.
Never.
Tar!
How could you say that?
Tar! Hello!
Tharn.
What were you yelling about?
Are you okay?
Who was on the phone?
Well…
I was arguing with Lhong.
What about you?
Why haven't you taken a shower?
We're out of soap.
I told you to keep the spares
in the bathroom cabinet.
Where do you keep them?
I'm sorry.
I'll get it for you.
Tar
Do you want to eat right after
I set up the table?
Tar.
Do you want to eat right after
I set up the table?
Tar.
-Tar.
-Yes?
I said, do you want to eat right after
I set up the table?
No, not now.
I'd better take a shower first.
Tar.
Tar!
Are you okay?
Tar! Tar!
Tar.
Tar, look at me. Tar.
Wait here.
Tar! What's wrong?
Tar, are you okay?
Look at me, Tar!
Tar!
Look at me!
Look at me! Tar!
Tar.
Tum.
I'm sorry.
I'm a bad person.
How are you bad?
How can you be bad?
Do you know?
In my entire life…
you're the most important person to me.
I really don't know
how to live without you.
Please don't do it again.
Don't be like this again.
I'm sorry.
Tar.
Tharn, I'm exhausted.
Okay.
I'll get you some food.
I'll put it here.
Tharn.
I'm thirsty.
My feet hurt from running all day.
I'm too lazy to get up.
I'll get you water.
I…
Your hands are too tired
to pick up the spoon.
Do you want me to feed you?
You're reading my mind.
And you…
are asking for more attention.
Dick, who's asking for your attention?
Then why do you want me to feed you?
You're so annoying.
I should just smack you.
Tharn.
I wanted to ask you something.
What is it?
We're using the same shampoo brand.
But why is your hair so soft?
Look at my hair, it's so coarse.
You play football under the sun.
I barely go outside,
so my hair is softer, I guess.
What's wrong with you?
Do you enjoy it?
And are you enjoying
rubbing your head on me?
I'm not only enjoying it, but I'm also…
on cloud nine.
So corny.
I admit it.
I'm happy too.
Don't die this time.
Tharn!
Come sit here.
Tum.
Anyone has a portable charger?
My battery is running out.
I have a request.
I have nothing to talk to you.
It's about your brother.
I'm not trying to start a fight.
But your brother called me the other day.
I don't believe you.
Shit!
Calm down. Both of you.
My brother will never
get involved with you.
Is this…
his new phone number?
Why do you keep in touch with Tar?
I don't.
-Tar called me.
-I don't believe you.
My brother will never get involved
with a scumbag like you.
Take it easy, will you?
We're in a classroom.
Tum.
I'm begging you.
Let's talk outside.
Okay.
Want me to come with you?
Wait here.
I don't believe Tar contacted you.
Believe what you want.
But I need to talk to him.
No way!
I don't know…
why you hate me so much.
But I swear.
I never hurt your brother.
And one more thing, Tum.
Tar wants me back.
I don't believe you.
You don't have the slightest idea, Tharn…
what Tar's been through all this time.
He wouldn't eat…
wouldn't sleep…
and wouldn't go to school.
We had to take him to a psychiatrist.
But Tar never said anything.
And do you know…
how much pain…
I've had to endure…
to see Tar getting hurt
by someone like you?
Don't tell me…
-You think of him more…
-That's none of your business!
And bear this in mind!
No matter how much you beg me…
I'll never let you see Tar ever again!
When you feel like drawing again…
can you draw me a picture?
Okay.
I'll do it.
I have to take Song's call.
Type.
I'm going to Jeed's bar.
But you're not playing today.
Well…
A junior asked me to join him.
And if you're not hungry yet…
can we have dinner around 10:00?
Are you crazy? I'd be starving by then.
Who said you could kiss me?
Please wait for me.
I hope you don't mind the kiss this time.
Then…
I'm leaving.
Be a good boy
and don't eat dinner without me.
Bye.
Do you think I'll be waiting idly
like an idiot?
Dream on.
Here you go, three drinks for two people.
Don't get too drunk
and have a safe trip home.
-Tharn? Hello.
-Hello, Jeed.
What are you doing here?
You're not playing today.
I'm here to meet someone.
Where's the bright-eyed boy?
He's not with you?
No.
By the way, I saw Tum and…
Tar. They're here.
I don't want you to fight with them.
I know you two broke up.
We're not going to fight.
Tum's asked me to come.
-Okay, that's a relief. So, no fighting?
-No.
-Then I'll go take care of the customers.
-Sure.
Tar.
Tharn.
Don't sit next to my brother.
And don't sit next to me.
Tum.
Don't be like this.
Tar.
Yes?
You know why I wanted to see you, right?
Why did you say I would break up
with my boyfriend?
What are you thinking?
Even though we used to be together…
I don't like what you said.
I came to see you today…
not because I wanted to.
But I want to know why you said
what you said.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
This is the last time I'll see you.
If you have something to say…
say it now.
I can't tell you.
Tharn.
Please believe me just this once.
What do you expect me to believe?
Believe that I love you.
I really love you.
But I don't love you anymore.
I know that.
I just want to say I love you.
I really love you, Tharn.
Who is he, Jeed?
Type, I think you should calm down.
It may not be what it looks like.
Tell you what.
He's Tharn's ex-bandmate's brother.
Maybe he's asking for advice or something.
There's nothing to worry about.
I'm leaving.
Don't tell him I was here.
I'll talk to him when he gets back.
Take it easy, okay?
Hello, Lhong.
Tell me everything
about Tharn's ex-boyfriend.
Stop crying, okay?
This time…
is the last time I'll see you.
-But--
-If you really love me…
respect my wishes.
I don't want any problems
with my boyfriend.
Okay.
I wish you two the best of luck.
Don't end up like we did.
I have to go.
Good luck, Tar.
You finally came back.
Are you okay?
Why were you sitting in the dark?
Where have you been?
I went to Jeed's bar.
Who did you meet?
Song.
I'll let you say it one more time.
Who did you meet?
I met Tar.
He is…
my ex-bandmate's brother.
And why don't you also tell me…
that the kid…
is your ex-boyfriend.
You must be shocked I know about him.
Because I'm not a moron!
You think I didn't know…
you were lying?
you were acting suspiciously?
So how was it?
Did he taste as good…
as when you were together?
Was it satisfying?
You hadn't seen him for a year.
Type!
What?
What do you want to say?
What did I say wrong?
That kid was crying for your attention.
Or are you gonna tell me…
Tharn who screws around…
couldn't get it up?
It's not what you think.
There's nothing going on.
Do you expect me to believe
someone who's been lying to me?
Cat got your tongue?
Argue with me.
Answer me.
I'm sorry.
But I didn't sleep with him.
I believe you.
You couldn't have slept with him.
Because you couldn't cum
in such a short time.
But do you still have feelings for him?
Answer me!
Do you still have feelings for him?
Just deny it…
and I'll believe everything you say.
Answer me!
I love you with all my heart, Type.
Do you expect me to believe someone
who can't answer a simple question?
But I didn't do anything.
I swear.
I'll never meet Tar again.
I don't want to hear that brat's name
in this room.
Type.
Let go of me.
-Where are you going?
-None of your goddamn business!
Techno.
What are you doing?
-You don't know gold facial mask?
-This is not the time for that.
Facial care is important.
Focus on Type first.
What's the matter with him?
You know.
It's a grown-up thing.
You don't need to know.
Harsh.
The thing is…
we'll let him stay for the night.
Got it?
Okay, got it.
Type.
Did you have a fight with Tharn?
I'll let him sleep in my room.
I brought you some water.
Type.
I don't want to get involved
in a lovers' quarrel.
But…
I have something to tell you.
The other day…
I skipped the practice.
And I saw Tharn at a department store.
I don't know…
if it's related.
But did you leave the apartment…
because of that high school boy
with pale skin?
What did you say?
I had to do some shopping that day.
And I saw Tharn with that kid.
I thought he was a junior
from Tharn's school.
But on a closer look.
That kid wore the same school uniform
as Technic.
Techno!
What?
Did you just say that kid
went to the same school as Technic?
Don't tell me you're gonna…
I'm gonna find him.
Shit.
Type, isn't there any other way?
No.
I'm gonna deal with him.