Tharn?
What's wrong? What happened?
Tharn.
Tharn, hold on.
What's the matter?
What happened?
I'm hurting.
I got dumped again.
It's okay.
What did I do wrong?
Why did Type leave me?
It's okay, Tharn.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I love him so much, Thorn.
Why did he have to leave me?
I know, Tharn. I know.
It's okay.
I love him.
It's okay, Tharn.
I want to be with him.
Why did he leave me, Thorn?
It's okay, Tharn.
Tharn.
Type.
I miss you, Type.
They're all messages from you
cursing me out.
Come back and curse at me.
I'll let you do anything.
You can insult me all you want.
But please come back to me.
Tharn, you idiot!
Tharn.
Thorn.
It's okay, Tharn.
It's okay.
If you want to cry,
just cry.
I'll be right here with you.
It's okay, Tharn.
I believe you can get over it.
It's okay.
It's been awhile.
Yes.
The last time I came here,
I was in 11th grade.
By the way,
where is everyone?
Dad's still at the office.
And mom took Princess to her piano class.
You still call Thanya "Princess"?
Why?
I won't stop calling her that.
It's kind of cute.
That's true.
Your family's always lovely.
Thanks.
You're here to see Tharn, right?
Yes.
So…
how's Tharn doing?
Wait here for a moment.
I'll go get him.
Okay. Thank you.
I'm so jealous.
What's there to be jealous of?
Your family is so loving.
It's always been like this.
So loving that it makes me…
jealous.
Lhong…
listen to me.
Tharn's friends are like my brothers.
If you like it here,
you can come visit often.
Then… I'll come visit more often.
Sure.
So… Tharn…
He's sleeping.
He's been through a lot,
so he must be tired.
I guess he doesn't want to see even me.
Don't be mad at him.
He's been through a lot.
I know.
I never get mad at him.
I'm sorry on his behalf.
And thank you so much
for always being there for him.
Have you eaten yet?
Do you want anything?
It's okay.
I don't want to impose.
When Tharn wakes up…
please tell him to call me.
Okay.
I'm leaving, then.
Goodbye.
Good luck.
I've always been there for him.
But he doesn't want me.
You're spacing out.
Here.
I bought it for you.
Thanks.
So…
what are you gonna do?
Just what I told you.
Really, Type,
I don't get you sometimes.
Why are you letting yourself suffer?
I'm not suffering.
Judging from the dark circles
under your eyes…
you must have had a good night's sleep
after your fairy godmother
sang you a lullaby.
Type!
Here you are. I've been looking for you.
What do you want?
Seriously, did you get into a fight again?
No. Why?
There's someone over there
asking for a first-year named Type.
So I rushed here to tell you.
Who could it be?
I don't know. I didn't ask for his name.
But he's handsome.
The girls kept staring at him.
I'll be right back.
Be right back.
What's wrong with him?
Honestly, Champ. I don't know.
I'm confused.
-Whose drink is this? Can I have it?
-Sure, go ahead.
So? Wanna find something to eat?
Sure, let's go.
Let's go.
Where is he?
Type.
Thorn.
Can I talk to you?
Let me cut to the chase.
Why did you break up with Tharn?
I said…
why did you break up with Tharn?
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to get involved.
I just…
My brother's in bad shape.
How is Tharn?
If you still love him,
why did you break up with him?
It's over.
For Tharn, it's not.
I feel bad for him.
Do you know how he was when he got home?
He cried.
My brother, who I'd never seen cry,
was crying.
He kept asking what he did wrong.
"Why did Type break up with me?"
I don't understand.
That time you came to our house,
you were getting along just fine.
What happened?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to yell at you.
I just…
Before…
when Tharn was young…
he was very attached to me.
Inseparable.
We always stayed…
and played together.
Until…
Mom was pregnant with Princess.
Tharn probably knew…
that he was no longer
the youngest sibling.
He acted more mature.
Stopped following me around.
Stopped asking for my attention.
Everyone teased him…
that since he had a little sister…
he'd become a big brother.
He can sacrifice for her.
But he can't lose you.
Tharn never cried…
when he lost Dad, Mom, or me to Princess.
But he was crying his heart out
after he lost you.
Please, answer me.
What's so bad about my brother?
Why did you break up with him?
Tell me and I won't get involved anymore.
Is he in really bad shape?
The worst.
Everything I do…
I do it for him.
For him?
Can you promise…
that you won't tell him…
what I'm about to tell you?
What do you mean?
Promise me.
Okay, I promise.
Lhong, can't get through?
What the hell?
How many days has Tharn been absent?
Damn. So irresponsible.
Don't blame him, Tae!
Why?
Why can't I blame him?
You see he's been skipping practice.
Let me tell you this.
No matter how talented he is,
no one can stand a lazy ass like him.
Then, leave. Get out.
Come on, Lhong. Calm down. Don't fight.
Don't think I can't find someone
to replace you.
You know who's the best in this band.
Not me.
Not Song.
And certainly…
not you!
Tharn is the best!
Tharn completes our band.
If you want to quit,
I won't stop you.
Do you know how many people
want to play with him?
-Lhong.
-You dare say that to me?
Come on, that's enough. Please stop.
Tae, please stop.
Lhong, don't say that.
Let's call it a day.
Let's talk after you guys calm down.
Okay.
I'll stop for Song's sake.
Are you trying to get on my nerves?
-You want a piece of me? Come back!
-Tae, stop. Calm down.
Tae, that's enough.
Calm down. Take a deep breath.
Look at him.
You know he's worried about Tharn.
We haven't been able
to reach Tharn at all.
It's normal Lhong would get upset.
You're siding with them
because you idolize them, right?
Stop smiling.
What are you smiling at?
Your mood's lifted.
Let's practice.
So no one can look down on us again.
Come on.
Shit!
I thought you were a ghost!
What the hell are you doing here?
How many times
are you gonna watch that clip?
What the hell am I doing, Techno?
If it's the answer you gave me,
you're doing this for Tharn.
Of course.
This is for Tharn.
Even if he hates me…
after this.
He's never hated you.
But he'll hate me after this.
Type.
Three times.
Three times what?
In my lifetime…
I'll break up with him only three times.
Type…
Go to sleep.
You have to help me tomorrow.
I don't want to help you.
But you and I are friends.
Too late to stop being your friend now.
Thanks so much.
When it's my turn…
don't forget to help me.
This is not the time to be emotional.
It's late.
Let's go to sleep.
I'm sleepy.
Turn off the light.
I know.
Damn it!
It's okay.
Tharn can't be like this for long.
Give him time, Lhong.
Lhong.
Type.
What's up?
Haven't seen you in days.
How are you?
I'm fine.
How about you?
I think…
you should reconsider the breakup.
You really think so?
What do you mean?
If I apologize,
will Tharn really forgive me?
I already told you…
to think carefully about breaking up.
It's too late to change your mind now.
At first…
Tharn couldn't get over it.
But he's gotten so much better now.
He told me…
he's gotten over you.
And if you wanted to go back now…
I'd better not say it.
Just tell me.
Because nothing can make me hurt
any more than I already am.
He told me…
even if you apologized,
he wouldn't want to see you.
He said that?
I heard it with my own ears.
What if I don't believe you?
It's okay if you don't believe me.
But my friend's not a fool.
You hurt him like hell.
You think he'll forgive you so easily?
You even fell for Tar's plan.
I don't think
Tharn will want to get hurt again.
I'm sorry, but I have to tell the truth.
I'm saying this because…
I mean well for both of you.
Bullshit!
What's up with you?
You're worse than I thought.
What the hell, Type?
You're upset with Tharn,
and now you're taking it out on me?
You're so full of shit.
I was such a dumbass
to believe your shit this whole time.
This is too much!
Too much?
What about hiring people
to gang-rape a tenth grader?
Wasn't that too much?
What are you talking about?
-I don't know anything about that.
-Stop bullshitting.
Tar told me everything…
about how evil you are.
No matter what,
I'm going to be the cause of your breakup.
What do you mean?
Answer me!
I'm being forced.
What do you mean you're being forced?
Type!
You believe him?
Be quiet, Techno!
I can't tell you.
If you don't tell me,
then it means you did it
because you hate Tharn.
I don't hate Tharn.
I love him.
-Shut up if you don't know anything.
-Then tell me what I don't know!
In the end,
I can't escape the fact
that I was gang-raped.
You really believe the boy
who made you break up with Tharn?
You're stupider than I thought.
I'm not stupid.
Tar showed me the clip.
Enough.
So…
Tar is Tharn's ex-bandmate's brother?
I'll recap one more time.
Tar is Tharn's ex-bandmate's brother.
When he first met Tharn…
he fell in love.
He asked Tharn out and Tharn said yes.
But on their goddamn anniversary
or something,
Tharn told him to meet at a hotel.
He drank some booze a waiter gave him,
thinking it was from Tharn.
Eventually…
he woke up on a bed
with the three men who'd just raped him.
And you believe him?
He ran away to throw up.
I bet he's faking it.
No.
I don't think he's faking it.
I know it.
You know?
It looks consensual, right?
That's why I couldn't tell Tharn.
He's going to hate me for sure.
When I woke up…
with those men…
Disgusting.
Revolting.
Stinking.
Filthy!
Say no more.
I'm begging you.
Don't break up with Tharn.
Don't let his plan succeed.
Who are you talking about?
That person has Tharn's trust…
more than me…
more than you.
He's always been by Tharn's side.
But I never noticed.
Don't tell me…
Lhong.
He's the mastermind.
He'll destroy you like he did me.
But he'll never get to hurt me.
And he's gonna regret…
messing with the wrong guy.
All the bastards' faces
are shown in the clip.
And I'm lucky enough…
to have a friend who knows all of them.
I just gave them money,
and they told me who paid them to do it.
What does that have to do with me?
They told you I paid them?
No.
But I'll show Tharn the clip.
-Techno.
-What?
Are Tharn and Type really together?
This is not the time to ask.
I'll tell you everything.
But right now, hold the phone still.
Type told us to film everything.
Tharn will never believe you!
Even if he doesn't believe me,
he'll learn the truth about Tar.
Do you think a good guy like him
will just sit around
if he knows his ex was framed?
Even if he doesn't forgive me,
he'll return to Tar.
And you…
will be tossed aside once again.
Try to come up with a good excuse.
You'll never succeed!
You hear me?
You'll never beat me!
Techno!
Shit! What do we do? Should I go help him?
No, we have to keep filming
until Lhong confesses everything.
-Take it. I'll go help him.
-No, Champ! You can't go!
You must keep filming.
Wait a little more. Calm down, please.
You hear me?
You'll never beat me!
Do you hear me? He's mine!
I've been by Tharn's side for four years!
Four years of worthlessness?
Shut up!
Shut your mouth!
Shut your mouth.
Tharn will never love you.
Remember that!
Shut up! You don't know anything!
I'm not like those sons of bitches.
They believed whatever I said…
and quickly lost faith in Tharn.
But not me.
I believe in Tharn.
I'm the only one who loves him.
No one but me is perfect for him.
But you have no right to hurt Tar.
No right, you say?
Tar said Tharn loved him the most.
But you saw…
that he begged those men
to do it all night.
You're a piece of shit.
Tharn will never love you.
Then, you'd better die.
If it hadn't been for you,
Tharn wouldn't have ended up like this.
He wouldn't have changed.
Because of you!
This is all your fault!
-You're a sore loser!
-I'm not a loser!
I'm the winner.
You…
lost.
-Then, die!
-Lhong, stop!
Tharn!
Lhong!
Die!
Type…
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
How did you get here?
Later.
I'm glad you're okay.
Tharn…
Techno…
look after Type for me.
Take it easy, okay?
Tharn…
don't look at me like that.
I'm Lhong, your best friend.
Tharn…
don't look at me like that.
What the hell have you done?
I haven't done anything.
How could you do this to me, Lhong?
Tharn…
I haven't done anything.
He was provoking me.
I was angry for you.
Believe me.
Please believe me, Tharn.
Believe you?
You want me to believe the person
who hurts everyone around me?
Tharn…
you believe other people more than me?
I've always been by your side.
Everything…
I've done everything for you.
For me?
This?
You did this for me?
Because no one's good enough for you!
That's none of your business!
No one truly loves you.
No one is perfect for you.
I want you to find a good man,
so I tested them.
But no one is good enough for you.
They're all evil.
You said…
you did what?
What did you do to them?
I only said you cheated on them…
and they turned on you so quickly.
Unlike me.
No matter how much you lie to me,
I still believe you.
I'll always be by your side, Tharn.
It should be me.
It has to be me.
It has to be me, Tharn.
I know…
I know that…
I'm important to you.
You can break up with them.
But you can't break up with me.
You're fine without a boyfriend.
But you can't live
without your friend by your side.
I know…
I know you love me too.
You're important to me, Lhong.
But not in the way you think.
That's not true.
Not true.
I trusted you.
But you hurt Tar.
You hurt everyone.
Tar?
Tar didn't really love you, Tharn.
I can prove it.
He can have sex with any man.
You have to see…
how much he enjoyed it.
I felt disgusted every time…
I saw you with him.
Tar didn't love you.
He's fine with any man.
I have a clip.
I have a clip, Tharn.
I can send it to you.
Tar's slutty…
It's my fault.
I hurt that boy.
If I had left him alone…
he wouldn't have gone through this.
Stop blaming yourself.
The one who must take responsibility
is him…
not you.
Don't touch him.
Get away from my friends!
Tharn…
I'm going to drop out.
What the hell are you saying?
You can't drop out.
Didn't you say you love music the most?
You can't quit.
You can't.
I'm the cause of all this.
Because I'm friends with Lhong.
Because I was Tar's boyfriend.
Everything happened because of me.
I must take responsibility.
Will you stop being heroic?
The one who must take responsibility
is him, not you.
Do you really want to break up with me?
No, Type.
Don't break up with me.
Don't break up with me, Type.
You hear that?
How many times are you gonna hurt him,
so you can be satisfied?
You took away his loved ones.
Now you're taking away
what he loves the most?
No, Tharn.
You can't drop out.
You can't quit music.
You can't quit drumming!
Didn't you tell me
you love music the most?
Leave him alone!
Tharn…
Look at me.
Look at me!
I'm Lhong, your best friend.
-Don't ignore me.
-I said leave him alone!
Tharn…
I love you, Tharn.
I love you, Tharn. I love you.
But I don't love you.
Type…
Let's get out of here.
Come on.
Come on. Please.
I think that's enough.
Let's go.
Don't drop out!
I'll drop out instead.
Since I can't be by your side…
nothing matters anymore.
I'll go.
I can't take music away from you.
I really can't take music away from you.
Tharn!
Tharn, I love you!
Tharn, I love you.
I love you.
Tharn…
Surprise! I came back from Germany.
Lhong?
What happened?
Why are you crying?
Why did I have to be born?
What's wrong with you?
If nobody cares about me or loves me,
then why did I have to be born?
What are you talking about?
What's wrong with you?
Dad and Mom never loved me.
Big brother and you never cared about me.
If they don't see me as their son…
and you don't appreciate me
as your little brother…
then why don't you just let me die?
Why would you let me live?
I'm hurting.
I'm suffering.
Has anyone ever noticed?
Even now,
Tharn doesn't appreciate me anymore.
So, what's the point of living?
I don't want to live anymore.
You should let me die.
Because I have nothing left.
You said you had nothing left,
but you still have me.
I know you hate me too.
No, I never hated you.
You're lying.
I don't believe you.
Whether you believe me or not,
I'm still your sister.
My being away doesn't mean
I don't love you.
If I hadn't loved you, I wouldn't have
let you cry on my expensive clothes.
I'm sorry.
Big brother and I didn't know
you suffered so much.
I love you.
Big sis…
I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
-Big sis…
I'm sorry.
Be gentle.
Just a bit more.
Be gentle. It hurts.
Almost done.
I was certain when I went out
for a drink with Lhong.
I pretended to be drunk.
When I told him you were mine…
the look on his face convinced me…
that he was behind all this.
I'm sorry.
You…
won't say that word to me again, right?
Not ever again.
I've said it enough.
You're not the only one who was sad.
I…
almost went mad with grief…
when I broke up with you.
I'm hurting too.
I'm sorry…
for being so self-centered.
I just wanted…
to open your eyes.
Techno said…
I didn't have to do it.
That there was no need
to play Lhong's game.
But I couldn't let him fool you anymore.
And I…
didn't want to wait for the day
he'd tear us apart.
So you…
broke up with me first.
I'm sorry.
You hurt me.
You drove me crazy.
I'm sorry.
My family was very worried.
What do you want?
I got down on my knees and begged you,
but you still left me.
I stopped going to class for a week.
I stopped playing at Khong's bar too.
Sorry.
If Thorn hadn't told me…
I would've been clueless until now.
Damn, Thorn.
He promised.
You must pay for what you did.
What do you want me to do?
Should I get down on my knees
and apologize?
You must get back together with me.
And stay with me forever.
Let's be together.
Let's be together
for the rest of our lives.
When I said I didn't want to
get in deeper…
it wasn't because I wanted
to break up with you…
but I was afraid my love for you
would stop me from keeping to the plan.
What did you say?
Why do you ask?
Because you said…
you loved me.
I never said I loved you?
You never did.
Then, that was my way of saying it.
Come on, Type. Don't cheat.
Say it again.
Please.
Listen carefully.
I won't repeat it.
I love you…
you asshole, Tharn.
Crybaby.
Why are you crying?
Come here.
Be gentle!
Then, stay still.
You're hurting me.
You usually like the pain.
Now you're complaining?
How many punches did you take?
No idea.
I lost count after the third punch.
Didn't know a skinny guy like him
could throw some heavy punches.
You can hit me.
Playing the hero again?
Why don't you hit Lhong for me instead?
If you do that, I'll call you a hero.
You can't.
Because he's still your friend.
It's not that I can't do it.
But I just…
I just don't want to see him again.
I don't want to know what else
he did behind my back…
or who else he hurt.
Forget it.
Lhong…
wasn't like this before.
He was quiet
and didn't like being around people.
I was the one who approached him.
I was jealous of him
because his family gave him freedom.
He could do anything
and study whatever he wanted.
But now…
I've realized
there was nothing to be jealous of.
Nobody paid attention to him at all.
Lhong told me…
he wasn't lonely…
because I was his friend.
I should've known…
how he was feeling.
I've already made it up to you.
Now it's your turn.
How?
With this.
More?
Don't ask.
It's your ex.
Tar?
Techno told Tar everything.
So he wanted to say sorry…
for making us fight.
And…
he's gonna study in France.
Is that so?
Why?
Feeling regretful?
No.
Don't start a fight.
I'm not starting a fight.
He also said…
he told me everything
because he planned to study abroad.
Good thing it's over.
What's wrong?
Tell Tar something for me.
Tell him…
I'm sorry for everything.
I'm not that jealous, you know?
I knew a hero like you
would say something like that.
So, will you tell him yourself,
or you want me to do it?
Tell him for me.
Let's go. I'm hungry.
I'M NOT STRONG ENOUGH IN THIS LIFE,
SO LET'S COMPETE IN OUR NEXT LIVES.
Dream on.
Whether it's this life or the next,
you'll never beat me.
Why are you talking to yourself?
You're so annoying, Tharn.
What do you mean? Let me see.
No.
Let me see.
I'll show you in the next life.
What do you mean "next life"?
Type!
Come in.
What are you doing?
Drawing.
Why are you still up?
You have an early flight tomorrow morning.
I'll go to bed soon.
Now that you're here,
I have a present for you.
-What is it?
-It's here.
What's that?
-It's…
this.
As promised.
I made you look handsome.
You made yourself look too handsome.
You should go to bed.
When you're there,
take good care of yourself, okay?
You can't go to bed late anymore.
Okay.
And…
eat regularly and don't skip meals.
Because if you get sick,
who will take care of you?
The weather there
is a lot colder than here.
You have to keep yourself warm, okay?
Cover yourself with a thick blanket
when you go to bed.
Okay.
Tum.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
Why are you apologizing to me?
Well…
I'm sorry…
I never told you anything.
Don't worry.
Actually, I just want you to know
that whatever happens,
I'll always be there for you.
That's enough for me.
No need to apologize.
Thank you.
Tum.
I am who I am today…
because of you.
You're the most important person
in my life.
And you're the one I love…
the most in the world.
Cheers!
Damn.
We came here today to watch
you, you, and you.
But you've disbanded?
That's right. I chose to come here
instead of watching a live comeback show.
Come on, bro.
So…
Did Lhong really drop out?
Do we really have to find a new singer?
Who's going to replace him?
I don't know.
No serious topics today.
We're here to drink.
You'll find a new singer. Right, Champ?
The hell did you say? I don't understand.
What?
Seriously, Champ.
When will you stop eating?
Damn it, you eat like a pig.
Techno, stop complaining. I'm hungry.
Look at your skinny bones and my muscles.
My body needs more food.
Leave my skinny bones alone.
So, aren't you gonna play a song at least?
Don't waste my trip.
-Come on.
-Give me time, Khlui.
What are you going to do? Need my help?
It's okay, Song.
Tonight…
let me handle it.
What's he gonna do?
How would I know?
I'm sitting here with you.
You prick.
Woke up this morning
To a world that seemed different
The alarm clock woke me up
Like it usually does
You are peacefully sleeping
Not knowing what was in my mind
I'm letting you dwell on your sweet dreams
Thinking of the time we stared
Into each other's eyes
Without uttering a word
The way you looked at me
Was the proof of our love
With all the good times we've shared
Do you feel the same way I do?
Should I keep it to myself?
Or should I tell you?
I want you to be my last love
And the one who will be
With me every step of the way
I will never ever hurt you
Do you hear me, my love?
Please don't let go of my hand
No matter what happens
Please believe in me
No matter how tough things get
We will make it through together
Because I know our meeting
Was not a coincidence or a dream
And today I have come to a decision
From now on, I want you to be
I want you to be my last love
And the one who will be
With me every step of the way
I will never ever hurt you…
Tharn…
Do you hear me, my love?
I'm sorry.
If the world falls apart,please remember…
My love for you will never change
You can rest assured
The two of us will walk side by side
As long as you love me
As long as you hold my hand
Please don't let go of my hand
So romantic.
What?
-What?
-So happy.
The flowers make me happy.
-Nice smile.
-That's for sure.
-What did you think?
-Cheesy.
But I know you liked it.
That's too much.
Let's drink.
Cheers!
You've turned red. Just kidding.
Wait for a bit.
Are you sleepy?
No.
Then…
are you hungry?
In the end,
I actually did fall in love with you.
And you'll keep loving me.
Corny.
So…
are you hungry?
No.
I ate too much to be hungry.
I mean…
are you hungry for me?
You're always trying to have sex with me.
I'm trying to show you my love.
Shut up.
-Let's go home.
-Sure, let's go.
One more thing.
Don't let go of my hand again.
Hold on tight.
THREE YEARS LATER.
WHERE ARE YOU? CLASS OVER YET?
ALREADY LEFT. HEADING TO THE FIELD NOW.
You're leaving?
So, why are you here
if you're not playing soccer?
I forgot my stuff in the locker.
Perfect timing. Let's have dinner.
Good offer at a buffet place,
four people for the price of three.
I'll eat for two.
Champ.
What the hell? Are you crazy?
Wanna come?
Sorry, my driver's almost here.
I'll be your driver…
if you ride with me.
So you have a date with your hubby.
This is why Can was whining.
What do you mean?
Can said you drove
a four-million-baht Audi…
but couldn't afford to buy him
a 40-baht meal.
You wallet costs 15,000 baht,
but you couldn't afford to buy
a five-baht grilled pork.
You paid 2,000 baht per person
for an international buffet.
-But…
-But Tharn paid for it.
No shame at all.
And I don't mind paying at all.
We'd better go.
See you.
Good luck.
You assholes!
Treat me too, damn it!
Am I your friend or what?
Come on, I'll eat you.
What? Eat me?
-I mean, I'll eat with you.
-Okay.
Man, it's so cold.
I've got chills down my spine.
Pete.
Tin, you're here to pick Can up?
And you?
I'm heading home, Tin.
Tharn, Type, hello.
What's up? Here to pick Can up?
He went to take a dump. We just met him.
Might have to wait long.
I'll wait at the soccer field.
Ever since he kissed you that day,
you've been more straightforward.
Because he's mine.
I have to go. See you on Monday.
Okay, Tin.
Tharn, Type,
well…
I have something to ask you two.
So…
are you two together?
Why are you embarrassed
when you're the one asking?
Remember what I told you?
You always get what you hate.
Before now…
Type and I…
used to fight a lot.
I'm sure you already knew that.
We'd better go.
Okay.
Bye.
Those kids are funny
every time we see them.
Hilarious. Especially their boyfriends.
But Pete's is not as funny as Can's.
Aren't you gonna ask
about what I said to him?
Ask?
Ask what?
Forget it.
If you don't ask, I won't tell you.
Then, I'll ask.
You used to say you hated me.
How about now?
I hate you more than ever.
You sure about that?
Yeah.
Keep saying you hate me.
Because I know…
that you…
love me.
I hate you.
That means you love me.
I hate you so much.
It means you love me so much.
I hate you more than anyone in the world.
That means…
you love me more than anyone in the world.
It's as you said.
I love you.
I love you too.