[English subtitles are available]
[One and Only]
[Episode 9]
I promise.
I'll still give you
the title of Prince of Fengyang.
I'm already a monk.
Xiao Yan,
although you've got tonsured,
you still attach to the world.
When you avenge,
come tell me
whether you want this title or not.
I...
Just follow the edict
of His Majesty.
Don't disobey it.
Yes, Your Majesty.
That's right.
When will you set off, uncle?
Tomorrow.
When will we meet next time?
We'd better not meet again in this life.
Have I done something wrong
and offended you, uncle?
My return to the Central State
always means something serious has happened here.
so I'd rather
not see you again in this life.
I'll look out to the Central State while I'm in the Central State
harboring the hope that you'll be a wise emperor.
I envy you
having these able men around.
I want someone of them.
Who?
I'd like to invite Advisor Xie
to help me in the Central State
like how he taught the late emperor.
Are you thinking about Your Majesty's words, Master?
Advisor Xie to me,
is like a teacher, a father.
I won't feel at ease
if I let him stay in the capital.
You are back, Advisor Xie.
Your Highness, I am here to say farewell to you .
You want to stay?
Yes.
His Majesty didn't force you to stay.
You can still think about it.
I know
Your Highness is concerned about me.
Back then,
I was asked by the late emperor
to follow Your Highness out of the Palace.
How time flies.
We have already spent over ten years
fighting on the battlefield together.
Now that Your Highness can totally
manage on your own.
Whether I am there or not
won't make a difference.
Your Highness.
Whenever and wherever,
you will always be my right-hand man,
part of my body.
You should never get hurt,
nor severed with me.
I can now die without regret
after hearing what you said, Your Highness.
His Majesty is still quite young
and there is no one he could ask for help.
That's why I
decide to stay and assist him.
Just like I assisted you before.
Okay.
Since you have made your decision,
I am gonna have to let you go.
Advisor Xie,
remember this,
the Western State
is always waiting for you to come back.
Okay.
I also want to ask Your Highness a favor.
On that day,
please bury me in the Western State.
[Chonghua Palace]
Your Highness.
When is your wedding with the princess?
In three years?
The last words of my father says
I don't have to get restrained by the three-year mourning period for his death.
The sooner, the better.
And so is the Empress Dowager's opinion.
When did the Empress Dowager want this to happen?
Before I go back to Qinghe County.
She wants the princess
to accompany me back to Qinghe County
and observe mourning rituals for my father.
Even if we ignore the mourning period,
how are we going to hold the wedding ceremony?
According to the Empress Dowager' edict,
there won't be any wedding ceremony
as the marriage is complete
once Shiyi is sent to the residence.
You...
I will be going back within two years.
Look how worried Shiyi gets.
She's so worried about that His Highness won't let her go back.
I was thinking about the time
to see if I can pick you up in person.
By then,
I should be in the Six-garrison.
The state affairs are more important,
I can go back on my own.
The state and family affairs are equally important.
Even if I couldn't make it to see her off,
General Cui Shou will accompany her on the way back.
Please don't worry, Your Highness.
[Taiji Palace]
Father,
I conducted a divination practice for you.
And the symbol is ominous.
Involved in the battle for the supreme power,
I wonder whose symbol could be auspicious.
Don't tell anyone anything about the divination result.
Not even His Highness.
What are you doing here, General Feng?
Greetings, Prince of Fengyang.
How kind, General Feng.
We are so special to each other.
Both of our names contain the character Feng, meaning phoenix.
I am nowhere as good as you.
General Feng is a heroine.
The character Feng in my name
doesn't live up to its worth.
Someone's really got a good destiny.
Born to be a prince.
And wherever he is, he's still a prince.
Someone's really got a good destiny.
Born to be
the disciple of the junior Prince of Nanchen.
And wherever she is,
she's a member of the Nanchen Royal Mansion.
That makes sense.
Especially for you.
You're always trying to join the Royal Army.
But I am one of them from the very beginning.
So,
I should envy you, General Feng.
Master doesn't want to be disturbed.
Feng Qiao.
Is Master in there?
He is.
Go in there.
Master is waiting for Shiyi.
After he leaves tomorrow,
it will take a long time
before she can see him again.
I suggest you come
on another day.
Thank you for letting me know.
Shiyi.
How do you know it's me, Master?
Feng Qiao is guarding outside,
she won't let anyone else in.
You are leaving tomorrow.
Yes.
This is the longest time I have been away from here
since I became your disciple.
Yeah.
My mother has fixed the date,
but I haven't been home for a long time.
If there is any delay,
I am afraid that I can only go back to the Western State
after a long time.
It's okay.
After all that I said,
how could you reply with only a few words.
You just need to remember
the Nanchen Royal Mansion will always be there,
your senior brothers and sisters and I
will always be there.
To us, you are only
going somewhere else for a while and will soon return.
Let me take you to a place.
Okay.
[Shiqian Palace]
I want to take Shiyi out of the Palace,
do you want to come along?
I don't see it's proper.
Nobody knows that
you are back in the Central State,
I am afraid we'll expose ourselves
if you bring us with you.
General Feng's got a point.
And it's natural to be sentimental
as we are about to leave here.
So I also want to have a good look at the Palace
of the Central State.
Sorry I can't go with Your Highness.
[Shiqian Palace]
Let's go.
[Baima Temple]
Master.
I forgot we are outside of the Palace.
Did you use to come here when you were a kid?
Before leaving the Central State,
I did.
Then I'll take a good look at this place.
Why is he filling it with water?
The well-respected monks of Baima Temple
has a custom over the years.
Every time when it's the end of the year.
They would ask their disciples
to check the water in there.
If there was a sheet of ice,
they must change the water immediately
in case the pigeons won't get the water.
That's very considerate.
Pigeons are intelligent,
they love to stay in the temple during the winter.
By the way,
Have you burnt incense here, Master?
Nope.
I am a general.
I have been through blood wars and seen numerous bones of the dead.
I should be the last one to disturb the tranquility of Buddha.
But you protect a lot more people.
Don't worry.
From now on,
I will burn the incense for you,
and for my senior brothers and sisters.
Let's go.
Let's burn the incense
that you failed to burn when you were young.
Come back.
Do you know how to get there?
Is he a regional prince who just arrived in the capital?
A regional prince?
how can you tell he's a regional prince?
Look at his bearing,
he must be one of the nobility.
If there is such a man in the Central State,
we would've known.
How can we have never seen him?
The prince is waiting outside,
the princess
must be burning incense inside.
[Grand Hall]
I have finished burning the incense
that you couldn't burn before 13.
Next time we are here,
we can make up the rest.
We couldn't burn too much at once,
that way we are like slacking off.
Sounds good.
It's still daylight,
where are we going next?
[Grand Hall]
Are we going back?
[Residence of the Grand Mentor]
Why are we here?
It's getting late.
I need to take you back.
Are you leaving?
I still get time to sit for a while.
For how long?
If your mother doesn't mind,
I can stay for dinner.
Then let's go.
Your Ladyship, you are back.
I am taking one of my friends
for a quick meal.
Let's go.
Go.
Yes, My Lady.
Your Highness.
The reason why I am here today
is that I, as a junior,
want to burn a stick of incense in front of the memorial tablet of Grand Mentor Cui.
Please.
[Father Cui Guang Honorable Memorial Tablet]
I wonder if Cui Wenji would love to
give me a tour around the Residence of Cui.
I don't know Your Highness very well, I am afraid...
Aunty.
Go ahead.
If so,
I will give Your Highness a tour,
please.
Shiyi.
My uncle mentioned about you.
What did he say?
He said,
he did let you down.
And if he ever knew that he would let you down one day,
he should never go to Qinghe County to see you.
Exactly.
If he didn't want to marry me,
he shouldn't come to see me.
He came to see me, yet he didn't marry me.
How am I supposed to face the Cui family?
For outsiders,
they would think that I was some kind of monster
that made people break off an engagement
with some contact.
He said,
not being able to marry you
is the only regret in his life.
My uncle was, in fact,
forced to break off the engagement.
The late emperor feared that the connection through marriage between the Cui family
and the Nanchen Royal Mansion
would make the Western State an overpowering state.
That's why
there was a secret edict from the Palace，
forcing my uncle to break off the engagement.
I am not here
to ask you forgive my uncle.
I only wish
you could work it out
and feel better.
Your Highness, please help yourself.
The liquor
is unique to Qinghe County.
Have a taste, Master.
Is it good?
Not bad.
This is called sandfish sashimi.
It's shredded skin of sandfish,
which is also unique to Qinghe County.
You won't see sandfish if you don't live near the sea.
Try it.
How's it?
Not too bad.
I'll see you off at the city gate tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
I have to go now.
Being a criminal when you entered the city,
yet being the Prince of Fengyang when you leave.
No wonder people would come out to see you.
What they don't know, however,
is that their beloved junior Prince of Nanchen
is now at the back of the convoy.
If there is anything you don't know
in the Palace or on the court,
consult Advisor Xie.
Don't say anything wrong
that would implicate him.
I will make sure Advisor Xie is in one piece
by being next to him all the time and protect him.
I have trained you personally,
don't let me down.
Keep that in mind.
I won't, General Hong.
Your Highness,
take care.
Advisor Xie,
Go.
see you.
Let's go.
Where are you from?
Why don't you give way
when you see the Prince of Taiyuan come?
We are from the Western State.
Master,
this man is called Jin Rong,
he is a Qihu people,
and got the credits for counter-insurgency during the late emperor's reign.
One of his daughters
now is a concubine in the Palace.
So sorry.
General,
why would you give way to them?
Did you see
the man in white just now?
He should be
the junior Prince of Nanchen.
[Mingguang Palace]
Your Highness.
General Jin.
Please take a seat.
I saw a man
at the city gate
who looks like the junior Prince of Nanchen.
That's him.
Liu Yuan handed all the troops
to a man
named Qin Yan,
have you heard of that?
Yes, I have.
Some nobody
comes from nowhere
should delude His Majesty
to hand the strong army of the Central State
to him.
He is from the Nanchen Royal Mansion.
Xie Chong, the military advisor from Nanchen Royal Mansion
was also left in the Palace
to assist His Majesty in the future.
We have killed Zhao Teng and Liu Yuan.
Now comes the Xie Chong and Qin Yan.
The son-in-law of mine,
is really simple-minded
and is always influenced by other people.
Your Highness.
Is my daughter in the Palace
having a good time?
She is not favored by His Majesty.
Nevertheless,
with the friendship between you and me,
I will take care of her for you.
I appreciate it, Your Highness.
I
am counting on you in the future, General.
No problem.
From now on, the Taiyuan Army
will be at your disposal, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Dad finally remembers to see me.
Come on,
let me have a look.
Looks like someone's really mad at her dad.
I don't want this either.
I am only doing this
for my useless son-in-law
to suppress the rebellion everywhere, isn't it?
You help him suppress the rebellion,
while he already left your daughter uncared-for.
The Prince of Guangling is here.
Don't talk nonsense.
Shiyi...
Miss Cui is in the Residence of Cui,
does Your Highness want to see her?
There is no engagement
and no point of seeing her anymore.
On the day when Xinghua gets married,
I will take her to the Residence of Cui on behalf of His Majesty.
and I will see her for sure.
Feng,
Mother's afraid that you may get cold feet
and she lets me accompany you all the way.
Does your brother look like
that kind of man?
Men from the Nanchen Royal Mansion
will never get cold feet.
Let's go.
[Residence of the Grand Mentor]
Your Highness.
Wenjun.
The Empress Dowager and His Majesty got caught in their business and couldn't get out of the Palace,
so, as the emperor's brother,
I will send the princess here instead.
Here's His Majesty's verbal instruction,
since Grand Mentor Cui just passed away,
we don't have to hold a grand wedding ceremony.
Everything must be kept simple.
I accept.
Xinghua?
Xinghua.
This is no joke.
Get down now.
It is hard for girls to leave their family when they get married,
and the princess is no exception.
Hope you won't mind.
Understandable.
Please.
What are you burning in the middle of night?
Some confidential military documents.
Military intelligence?
Why are you crying?
[Confidential]
I never knew I would marry you.
I have fallen in love with someone else.
Do you have someone you love, General Cui?
I'll be honest with you.
Yes.
Tonight,
are you going to take me as her?
You are not her.
You and me tonight,
are not who we really are.
But rather, the princess and general of BeiChen.
General,
please go to bed.
You have watched the moon for up to two hours.
I miss Xiaoyu.
Your Highness.
It's pretty late at night,
why is Your Highness not back yet?
Still mad?
Nope.
On the day I learned the engagement was canceled,
in desperation,
I embarrassed you in front of everyone.
I owe you an apology.
What is done is done.
Your Highness doesn't have to put it in mind.
If Your Highness is fine,
I take my leave now.
Shiyi.
If I get a fief,
and stop being obsessed with position of the crown prince
and stay away from the Central State,
will you go with me?
No.
You still want to be the crown princess,
and the empress in the future?
Never.
It has nothing to do with being the crown princess or not.
I have never wanted to enter the Palace.
If you have the chance to choose again,
why don't you
choose someone you want?
How do you know
you are not the one I want?
And how do you know
that I don't want to marry you?
Please behave yourself, Your Highness.
When the engagement was made,
I was not born and couldn't make the decision.
What's in the past
is the agreement of our fathers,
not mine,
and definitely not my intention.
From today on,
Your Highness, please forget me.
A prince who has no power,
and an imperial concubine who is not favored.
In this Palace,
we are somewhat alike.
What
do you want from me?
The title of the empress.
The fact that His Majesty and I being each other's brother
doesn't give me the power to decide
which concubine he wants to favor.
What if you were the emperor?
My father can help you get the throne.
While you,
need to repay me with the throne of empress.
[Residence of Cui]
My Lady,
every branch of the family is here.
They said they wanted to offer their condolence.
Keep the body in the room
and send the princess back to rest.
Yes, My Lady.
[Residence of Cui]
Please go inside and have a rest, Your Highness.
Only Shiyi follow me inside.
Wenjun.
Wenjun is here.
Sit down and let's talk.
Wenjun,
sorry to hear the sudden death of the clan chief.
We made it here
as soon as we learned the news.
Why don't you send someone
to send a letter here first?
So that I can arrange people to receive you.
We are afraid that you worried too much.
Wenjun.
So far, in your generation,
only you and Wenji were left.
Do you
have any plan for the future?
From now on,
I will be in charge of
both internal and external affairs of Wushui House.
Here is the bride-price list.
Please have a look.
Who is this bride-price for?
To you, from me.
Wushui House can't sustain without having a chief, not even a day.
This is bride-price list
that I asked someone to prepare overnight.
I thought
it was prepared for the younger generation.
I never knew it was for me.
Shiyi.
Yes, Mother.
Return it to your uncle.
Yes.
If it were for the younger generation.
Two of the three sons left by my brother
remain unmarried.
I can help arrange.
If it were for me,
there is no need.
We are only doing this for your good.
I appreciate it.
As the clan chief is gone,
if there was no marriage connection between Wushui
and the rest of us,
once anything goes wrong,
we are left without proper reasons
to offer a hand.
We have the same ancestry,
if you want to help,
you will do it no matter what.
If you don't want to help anymore,
I won't say a thing.
We are here for your good,
why do you have to turn us down?
What you may not know
is that before my brother passed away,
he recommended his eldest and second son to the Imperial Palace
and he let his third son marry Princess Xinghua.
My youngest daughter, Shiyi,
who was a disciple of the junior Prince of Nanchen.
Be it the Liu Royal family,
Empress Dowager Qi ,
or the Zhousheng family in the Western State,
we will be family to each other someday.
If you're
so insistent,
then I won't push it.
What kind of bride-price is this?
They are literally here
to rob my family property.
The person who wanted to marry me today,
is called Cui Zheng.
His branch was once the most thriving
among our six branches.
But they offended the emperor later
and in despair,
they had to flee to the south of the river.
That was also the darkest time
for us, the Cui family.
Later.
Your uncle became an official on the imperial court.
And our family
gradually regained its past glory.
And those who fled to the south
have gradually returned.
My uncle is the one who made it possible for them to come home,
yet they want to steal the position of clan chief
after he died.
Glad that he is gone
so he won't be sad about this.
You finally opened your mouth
to talk to me.
My master said,
the Gao family
was always trying to get a chance to destroy our family.
If Mother didn't do that,
not only you and me,
the whole family is going to suffer.
I can't help recalling that night over and over again,
and I regretted.
[Residence of Cui]
If only
I could go with him
on that night.
It is really heartbreaking
to see him leave alone.
You did that for me.