Hey.
Where'd you go?
I'm here.
Um, guys.
So...
the barn is full
of walkers.
You cannot tell me
you're all right with this.
No, I'm not, but we're guests here.
This isn't our land.
- God, this is our lives!
- Lower your voice.
We can't just sweep
this under the rug.
It ain't right. Not remotely.
We've either
got to go in there,
we've got to make things right
or we've just got to go.
Now we have been talking about
Fort Benning for a long time.
- We can't go.
- Why, Rick? Why?
Because my daughter
is still out there.
Okay.
Okay, I think it's time
that we all start to just
consider the other possibility.
Shane, we're not leaving
Sophia behind.
I'm close
to finding this girl.
I just found her damn
doll two days ago.
You found her doll, Daryl.
That's what you did. You found a doll.
You don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
I'm just saying
what needs to be said.
You get a good lead,
it's in the first 48 hours.
Shane, stop.
Let me tell you something else, man.
If she was alive out there
and saw you coming
all methed out with your buck knife
and geek ears around your neck,
she would run in the other direction.
- Shut your mouth!
- Wait!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
What are you doing?
Don't come at me, man!
- Calm down!
- Shane!
- Back off!
- Keep your hands off me.
Now just let me talk to Hershel.
Let me figure it out.
- What are you gonna figure out?!
- Enough!
If we're gonna stay,
if we're gonna clear this barn,
I have to talk him into it.
This is his land.
Hershel sees those things
in there as people--
sick people--
his wife, his stepson.
- You knew?
- Yesterday I talked to Hershel.
And you waited the night?
I thought we could survive
one more night.
We did.
I was waiting till this
morning to say something.
- But Glenn wanted to be the one.
- The man is crazy, Rick,
if Hershel thinks those
things are alive or no.
Maggie.
Hey, Maggie,
just talk to me.
Hey.
Maggie.
Give me your hat.
You said talk to you,
I'm talking to you. Give me your hat.
Why would you waste
an egg like that?
I think it was rotten.
Does Shane think
Sophia's dead?
Shane's just scared.
- Of the walkers in the barn?
- Yeah.
Mom,
I'm not leaving
until we find Sophia.
And I don't want to go
even after that.
Well, we're not
leaving, Carl.
Now finish those problems.
I just think she--
she's gonna like it here.
This place,
it could be a home.
- You can't.
- I'm fine.
Hershel said
you need to heal.
Yeah, I don't care.
Well, I do.
Rick's going out later
to follow the trail.
Yeah, well, I ain't gonna
sit around and do nothing.
No, you're gonna go out there
and get yourself hurt even worse.
We don't know if we're
gonna find her, Daryl.
We don't.
I don't.
What?
Can't lose you, too.
- Are you all right?
- Just leave me be.
Stupid bitch.
Andrea's looking for you.
Thank you, Glenn.
Any chance you got
an extra hat?
Nope.
Thanks.
Going off with Rick
to look for Sophia.
I thought he was
talking with Hershel.
He is.
We're gonna go after.
I'm headed to the barn
in the meantime.
Shane wants a watch duty
down there.
Does Rick?
Why wouldn't he?
Are you only
getting yours?
I don't know what's going
on with you and him.
- Him?
- Shane.
- Dale.
- It's not my business.
All that matters to me
is that you--
you may not
really know him.
We don't need
to do this.
- You and I are finally--
- It's important.
I get it.
You don't like him.
- It isn't that.
- Then what is it?
Is that how you want to be?
Like him?
He's not a victim.
You don't know him.
Dale, I need you to stop.
You spend so much time
watching me,
looking out for me.
You want to beat me up
anytime I show any concern.
Go ahead.
I'm done.
I'm not beating
you up, Dale.
I'm okay, really.
Things are...
different.
You got your gun.
Okay.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
You mind running
and getting me some water?
I just--
I need a second.
You'll keep watch?
Dale?
Yeah, sure.
Come on in.
A little light reading
for lunch?
Been working
so hard lately
I get my studying
where I can.
You know we can help
you out with your work.
It's my field to tend.
We found the barn.
Leave it be.
Well, I'd like
to talk about it,
but either way-- your barn,
your farm, your say.
I don't want to talk about the barn.
I don't want to debate.
Not a debate,
a discussion.
I need you and your group
gone by the end of the week.
I talked to Dale.
You and I have
our differences
with the way we look
at the walkers.
Those people,
they may be dead,
they may be alive.
But my people, us,
we are alive right now,
right here,
right in front of you.
You send us out there
and that could change.
I've given you safe harbor.
My conscience is clear.
This farm--
this farm is special.
You've been shielded from what's
been going on out there.
Dale said you saw everything
happen on the news.
Well, it's been--
it's been a long time
since the cameras
stopped rolling.
The first time
I saw a walker
it was just half a body
snapping at me from the ground.
My inclination
wasn't to kill it.
But what the world is
out there isn't what you saw on TV.
It is much much worse
and it changes you.
Either into one of them
or something a lot less
than the person you were.
Please do not--
do not send us out there again.
My wife's pregnant.
That's either a gift here
or a death sentence
out there.
If we were to stay
we could help you
with the work,
with securing this place.
We can survive together.
Rick, I'm telling you we can't.
- You think about what you're doing.
- I've thought about it.
- Think about it.
Think about it again.
We can't go out there.
What's it gonna be, man?
Which way does
this thing go?
I don't know yet.
Well, what did he say?
- We're negotiating.
- You're nego--
Clock's ticking, Rick.
No, it isn't, Shane.
That barn--
the barn is secure.
We didn't even know
about it till this morning.
We didn't.
Well, we know about it now.
Right? We know there's over
a dozen walkers in there.
We know that it's about
a stone's throw
from our camp, Rick--
where we sleep.
So look, if we're not gonna go in there
and clear it out then we just got to go.
We're not gonna clear it
out and we're not gonna go.
We at least
need our guns.
We can't have them,
not here.
Why do you want to stay here
when it's not safe?
We can make it safe.
- How we gonna do that?
- We will, okay?
- How we gonna make it safe?
- No, man, it's not okay.
- Shane, Lori's pregnant.
We need to stay.
We need our guns.
No, I can work this out.
- You good?
- Yeah.
Lori's having a baby, man.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Hi, honey.
Carl doesn't need
any more of my help.
So that's it?
Rick was trying
to make his case.
It'll be hard.
They'll have to be careful.
But he was being dramatic.
They're a strong group.
They've done well on their own.
They're just gonna have to go
out and find their own farm.
There's plenty of them
now to chose from.
There aren't.
Every one of them nearby
is burned out
or full of walkers.
Walkers?
So we just keep these
people here forever?
How are they
my responsibility?
"A new command I give to you:
love one another
as I have loved you."
That's what you
told me, right?
I was mad about Mom.
Mad about you
marrying Annette.
I was 14 years old
and I was awful,
to you more
than anybody.
All I wanted to do
was smoke and shoplift.
"Love one another."
That's what you told me.
Maggie.
That was different.
No.
You're different.
I am.
But we're not.
I love you.
That's part of this.
Is this about you
and the Asian boy?
- Do you want me to--
- No.
His name is Glenn.
He saved my life yesterday
when one of the people
you think is sick
tried to kill me.
How's that for dramatic?
Things aren't what
you think they are.
They aren't.
Don't do this.
Okay? It's not about
me and Glenn.
It's not about
me and you.
It's about you.
It's about who you are,
who you're gonna be.
Hershel!
It happened again.
...also shows she could
be moving this way south.
If Sophia kept
in that direction,
she might have gotten out
of the forest and into the farmland.
So we take 74
up to Ivy Road,
then push down south on foot through
the forest till we hit Christopher,
go east a couple of miles
and then double back.
- Rick.
- Hershel.
We just have our guns out because
we're gonna go look for Sophia.
Before you do that, I could use
your help with something.
Count me in.
Thank you,
but I just need Rick.
I'll be down at the barn
keeping watch until you're ready.
- I thought he was dead.
- Shane, I don't--
Then when he came back,
right then, right there,
you see I wished he was.
Not-- not because you
wouldn't be mine,
but because I knew that sooner
or later he would be dead.
See Rick,
he ain't built
for this world,
not for what it is now.
You're wrong.
Lori, how many times
has he saved your life?
I want to know how many times.
Because by my count,
I've saved your life on four different
occasions. And that's Carl's, too.
So I just want to ask you, how many
times has Rick saved your life?
That night at the camp. That night
at the camp after the fish fry.
No, no, no.
See, no.
That was me, too.
You see, Rick,
he showed up late
because he went on
a suicide mission over nothing.
Yeah, he joined in,
but, see, we wouldn't
have been in that situation
if he hadn't left
because he felt
that he needed to leave
to save a drug dealer.
And so we lost Amy
and we lost Jim.
We lost--
Rick told me.
Told you what?
And I know the reason
why you didn't
is because
you know it's mine.
- It's Rick's.
- Okay.
You know, we carried on
quite a bit
before Rick got back, Lori.
It's mine. You know it is.
You're wrong.
I'm sorry.
Shane, I'm sorry.
But even if it's yours,
it's not gonna be yours.
It's never gonna be yours and there's
nothing you can do to change that.
I don't need to.
Hey, Shane.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
You okay?
Yeah.
I know you think
that Sophia's dead
and that we should stop
looking for her.
- But that's bullshit.
- Hey, man, watch your mouth.
We're gonna stay here
until we find her.
You think that's
what we should do?
It's what I know
we should do.
Then we stay.
That means we got to do
whatever we got to do
to make that happen.
- Hmm?
- Like help out with chores?
Mmm.
Like help out
with the chores.
Carl.
Come here for a minute.
Why don't you go
see what your mom wants?
Hmm?
Go on.
Hey, Carl.
Don't let me hear
you talk like that again.
S'up?
Son of a bitch.
You see where he went?
- Who?
- Don't even try to shit me, okay?
- What?
- Dale, Glenn.
Did you see
where Dale went?
Yeah, he asked me to run
and get him some water.
He said he'd cover
me on watch.
And he was gone
when you got back, huh?
Yeah.
- You think he's okay?
- Oh, he's fine.
Why'd he bail then?
So you wouldn't tell me
which way he went.
I don't get it.
No, man, you don't.
The silt on the bottom
is like glue.
You just sink in.
That's Lou Bush.
You knew him?
Lou as in Louise.
She has a farm
up the road.
Sweet corn mostly.
Worked at Hatlin's Bar
on weekends.
The man, I don't know him,
but the coveralls,
I've been
to where he worked.
How many
have you killed?
Too many to count.
Can you stop?
There are people out there
who haven't been
in their right minds,
people who I believe
can be restored.
You're not talking
about the walkers, are you?
It doesn't matter if you see them
as human beings anymore.
But if you and your people
are going to stay here,
that's how you're gonna
have to treat them.
My farm, my barn, my say.
- You see it?
- See what?
I'll find her.
Hell, I'm sorry about
what happened this morning.
You wanted
to look for her.
Why?
This whole time
I've just wanted to ask you.
'Cause I think
she's still out there.
Truth is,
what else I got to do?
We'll find her.
We will.
I see it.
Otis said if you get them halfway
out they'll do the rest of the work.
How many times
did he do this?
If one wandered onto the property,
Otis would get them into the barn.
Now we have to.
What happens when
the barn gets full?
- Jeez!
- Get the pole!
Jimmy. Jimmy.
You got it.
Easy. Easy, Rick.
Lead him.
Jimmy will spot for us.
Lead him
lead him, Rick.
- You're the carrot, not the stick.
- What?
You heard me,
just lead him.
He'll come to you.
You told me
he handled them easily.
This is easy?
It's easier
than some things.
All right, it's through this way.
Maggie.
Hey.
Maggie, just stop
for a second.
You talked about it.
You told Dale, fine.
I asked you.
I told you.
I just asked you
for one thing. One thing.
I couldn't do it.
My dad's gonna kick you guys
out now. He told me.
No, Rick's gonna work
something out with your dad.
- Okay? I had to tell them.
- You did not.
No, I did.
I wanted to.
You see, I forgot.
Okay? I forgot or I stopped
thinking about it
or maybe I didn't want
to think about it.
I let them lower me into
that well like it was fun,
like I was playing "Portal."
- It's a video game.
- Of course it's a video game.
And then the pharmacy happened
yesterday and I realized something.
I forgot that
they're dangerous.
I don't care if they're sick
people or dead people,
they're dangerous.
And then I realized
something else.
That I don't want you
in danger ever.
So I hate to blow
your dad's big secret,
but I'm sick of secrets.
Secrets get you killed.
And I'd rather have you
pissed off at me and alive
than liking me and dead.
So that's why I told them.
Hey, walker bait.
Don't call me that.
Okay, Glenn.
Man, this is a good hiding place.
We ain't been in
the swamps much, huh?
Imagine if you applied
your tracking skills
to finding Sophia.
How about
you just give me
that bag, huh?
I'm not gonna do that.
Yeah, you are, Dale.
Unless, well,
you do have that rifle
over your shoulder.
You gonna shoot me
like you did Otis?
Tell another story?
No, man.
Hell, when you
really look at it
in the cold light of day,
you're pretty much
dead already.
Just give me the guns.
Do it now.
You think this
is gonna keep us safe?
Mm-hmm.
I know it is.
Rick is trying
to get Hershel--
Dale, shut up. Just shut up
and give me the guns.
Am I gonna
have to shoot you?
Do I have to kill you?
Is that what it's gonna take?
Eh.
Yeah.
That's what it's gonna take.
This is where
you belong, Shane.
How's that, Dale?
This world,
what it is now,
this is where
you belong.
And I may not have what
it takes to last for long,
but that's okay.
'Cause at least I can say
when the world goes to shit
I didn't let it
take me down with it.
Fair enough.
You look like you should be in line
for the Early Bird Special.
Go get your cap.
I'll wash it for you, okay?
- Do you know what's going on?
- Where is everyone?
- You haven't seen Rick?
- He went off with Hershel.
We were supposed to leave
a couple hours ago.
Yeah, you were.
What the hell?
Rick told us
he was going out.
Damn it. Isn't anybody taking
this seriously?
We got us a damn trail.
Oh, here we go.
- What's all this?
- You with me, man?
- Yeah.
- Time to grow up.
- You already got yours?
- Yeah. Where's Dale?
- He's on his way.
- Thought we couldn't carry.
We can and we have to.
Look, it was one thing sitting
around here picking daisies
when we thought this place
was supposed to be safe.
But now we know it ain't.
How about you, man?
You gonna protect yours?
That's it.
Can you shoot?
Can you stop? You do this,
you hand out these guns,
my dad will make you
leave tonight.
- We have to stay, Shane.
- What is this?
We ain't going
anywhere, okay?
Now look, Hershel,
he's just gotta understand.
Okay? He--
well, he's gonna have to.
Now we need to find Sophia.
Am I right?
Huh? Now I want
you to take this.
You take it, Carl, and you
keep your mother safe.
You do whatever it takes.
You know how.
Go on,
take the gun and do it.
Rick said no guns.
This is not your call.
This is not
your decision to make.
Oh, shit.
This way. Come on.
What is that?
- What is that?
- Shane!
To me. Over this way.
What the hell
are you doing?
- Shane, just back off.
- Why do your people have guns?
Are you kidding me?
You see?
You see what
they're holding onto?
- I see who I'm holding onto.
- No, man, you don't.
Shane, just let us do this
and then we can talk.
What you want
to talk about, Rick?
These things ain't sick.
They're not people.
They're dead. Ain't got to feel
nothing for them
'cause all they do,
they kill!
These things right here,
they're the things
that killed Amy.
They killed Otis.
They're gonna kill all of us.
Shane, shut up!
Hey, Hershel, man,
let me ask you something.
Could a living
breathing person,
could they walk away
from this?
No!
- Stop it!
- That's three rounds in the chest.
Could someone who's alive,
could they just take that?!
Why is it still coming?
That's its heart,
its lungs.
Why is it still coming?
- Shane, enough.
- Yeah, you're right, man.
That is enough.
Enough risking our lives
for a little girl who's gone!
Enough living next to a barn
full of things that
are trying to kill us.
Enough.
Rick, it ain't like it was before!
Now if y'all want to live,
if you want to survive,
you got to fight for it!
I'm talking about
fighting right here, right now.
Take the snare pole.
Hershel, take the snare pole.
Hershel, listen to me,
man, please.
Take it now.
Hershel!
Take it!
No, Shane.
Do not do this, brother. Wait!
- Don't do it!
- Rick!
Please!
Come on.
This is not the way!
Please!
Get behind me.
Come on.
- Maggie.
- Okay.
Stay back!
Stop!
Oh, God.
Sophia? Sophia!
Oh, Sophia.
Sophia.
Don't watch.