Don't look. Don't look.
Shh, shh.
Wait, wait.
Ma.
Come on!
Pull her away!
We've been out. We've been combing
these woods looking for her
and she was
in there all along?
- You knew.
- Leave us alone.
- Hey, Shane, just stop, man.
- Get your hands off me.
You knew
and you kept it from us.
- I didn't know.
- That's bullshit.
- I think y'all knew.
- We didn't know!
- Why was she there?!
- Your--
Otis put those people
in the barn.
Maybe he found her and put her
in there before he was killed.
You expect me
to believe that?
- I look like an idiot?
- Shane, hey, hey, hey.
- I don't care what you believe!
- Everybody just calm down.
- Get him off my land!
- Please. No.
- Let me tell you something.
- Hey. Don't touch him!
Haven't you done enough?
I mean it-- off my land.
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
Daryl almost died
looking for her, Rick.
Any one of us could have.
I'm gonna tell you right now--
that son of a bitch,
he knew.
He didn't know.
He's not like that.
- He opened his home to us.
- Put us all in danger.
He kept a barn full of walkers.
So you just start
an insurrection,
hand out guns
and massacre his family?
- His family's dead, Rick.
- Well, he doesn't believe that.
He thinks you just
murdered them in cold blood.
No, man, I don't care
what he thinks.
I was handling it, brother.
I was handling it and you just--
You had us out in those woods
looking for a little girl
that every single one
of us knew was dead!
That's what you did.
Rick, you're just
as delusional as that guy.
You were handling it, huh?
I have to ask you--
did you know
she was in the barn?
You know, maybe in some
weird way this is for the best.
At least we know
and now we can move on.
- Move on?
- Yeah, it's just like...
it meant so much to everyone--
finding her, you know?
- And then--
- So now you'll just move on?
If we can.
I mean, we've lost others.
This is-- this is Sophia.
The whole group--
this one was different.
So what happens now?
We bury her...
with your stepmom
and your stepbrother.
And then?
I don't know.
- I thought I'd find her.
- We all did.
I mean me.
That I'd be the one.
Like maybe she was
hiding somewhere
in a cave or a tree.
She'd be safe
and I'd find her
and bring her back.
He did the right thing...
shooting her like that.
I would've done it, too.
Dale?
Yeah?
Could you take Carl
up to the house?
I want you to rest.
Okay.
Hey, you dropped that.
You want us
to start burying?
We need a service.
Carol would want that.
Yeah, we all want that.
Let's-- let's dig
a grave for Sophia,
and Annette and Shawn...
over by those trees.
And we'll need a truck
to move the bodies.
- I'll get the keys.
- No, no.
I got the truck.
And the others?
That's a lot of digging.
We bury the ones we love
and and burn the rest.
Let's get to work.
What did Hershel say?
He wants us off the farm.
Or Shane at least.
That's not a surprise.
We're lucky
someone wasn't killed.
And all that gunfire--
more walkers
could've heard it.
Baby, what is it?
She was there all the time.
And you did
everything you could.
Yeah, I know.
I always do, don't I?
Went after her,
protected her,
killed those walkers,
but she still got bit.
And Carl still got shot.
People counting on me
and I had 'em chasing
- a ghost in a forest.
- Hey.
Do you got something
to say, Dale?
Well, go ahead, man.
Mr. Moral Authority, huh?
You the--
the voice of reason.
Let me ask you something, man.
What do you do?
What do you do to keep
this camp safe, huh?
What do you do?
What, you fix up an RV?
You babysit some guns?
Man, you pointed one
at my chest, right?
But you just-- you couldn't pull
that trigger, could you?
If I was such a danger,
if I was such a threat,
what did you do
to stop me, huh?
I smashed that barn open.
I saved Carl.
That's me. That ain't you.
That ain't Rick. That's me.
Tell you what, Dale--
next time I need
a radiator hose...
I'll give you a call, man.
That's it.
They're ready.
Come on.
Why?
'Cause that's your little girl.
That's not my little girl.
That's some other thing.
My Sophia was alone
in the woods.
All this time, I thought--
She didn't cry
herself to sleep.
She didn't go hungry.
She didn't try
to find her way back.
Sophia died
a long time ago.
- A few more trips.
- We got lucky.
If that barn had any more,
we could've been overrun.
Good thing Shane did
what he did when he did.
You can't tell me
this was right.
It wasn't.
It'll cost us with Hershel.
He's grieving.
He'll come around,
see we had no choice.
Look, I shot, too.
This wasn't all Shane.
Look, I got no qualms about it.
Walkers in my backyard?
Mm-mmm.
I'm not saying
that we shouldn't have
taken care of the problem,
but creating a panic to--
There's no point arguing
about it. It's done.
There's nothing
we can do about it.
Better get moving.
Hey! Hey!
All right!
So if your group leaves,
you wouldn't stay?
I-- I hadn't really
thought about it.
I mean, I--
I didn't know that--
do-- do you think
this is really the time
to discuss this, I mean?
Well, I'm not really feeling like
there's a lot of time for anything.
No, no, there-- there is.
There is.
I'd want--
Oh, my God.
Sweetie, can you hear me?
- What's wrong with her?
- She might be in shock.
- Where's Hershel?
- We can't find him anywhere.
Hey, kiddo.
- Your stepmother's things?
- He was so sure she'd recover.
They'd just pick up
where they left off.
Looks like he found
an old friend.
That belonged to my grandfather,
gave it to Dad when he died.
I didn't take Hershel
for a drinker.
No, he gave it up
on the day I was born.
He didn't even
allow liquor in the house.
- What's the bar in town?
- Hatlin's.
He practically lived there
in his drinking days.
Betting that's where
I'll find him.
Yeah, I've seen the place.
I'll take you.
- All right, I'll get the truck.
- Okay.
- No.
- It's an easy run.
- Like the pharmacy?
- Hey, Maggie?
I'll bring him back.
Maggie, that was different.
Rick?
You want to have a conversation
about this before you leave?
So you're seriously
gonna go after this guy
with everything
that's going on, huh?
He's right.
This is not the time
to head off, not today.
- You don't always have to--
- I'm not arguing.
It's the least I can do
for Hershel after we--
What?
After we what?
Carl said he would've
shot Sophia himself.
That's your son.
He's getting cold.
He's growing up
in a world with--
he's growing up in a world where
he needs a father like you--
around, alive,
not running off, solving everybody
else's problems.
It's not just his problem
I'm trying to solve.
We need Hershel
for the baby.
I'm going after him.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Hey.
Carol?
Carol.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, are you all right?
- Keep away.
- Come here.
I want you to know
that I'm real sorry for your girl.
Thank you.
When I opened that barn
I had no idea.
If I did...
Everybody thinks
that I'm a...
I was just trying
to keep everybody safe.
I had no idea
she was in there.
This place is going to hell.
Yeah, I'm trying hard
to prevent that.
You won't be able to.
No, there are people
in this group
who think that what
Shane did was justified.
I know you two
can't stand each other,
but he did something
that needed to be done.
He's dangerous.
Yeah, he's a hothead.
No, Lori,
he's dangerous.
I think he killed Otis.
Otis was killed
by walkers.
He knew how
to handle walkers.
Otis was the one who was
putting them in the barn.
You need to be really clear
with me right now.
- What are you saying?
- I believe that--
that Shane sacrificed Otis.
I can't prove it,
but I-I-I--
I think that he--
I think that he shot him
and left him for bait,
so that he could get away.
Shane may be a hothead,
but he's not a murderer.
And why would he kill somebody
who's trying to help?
I don't know.
Maybe he was pinned down.
He said-- he said it.
He all but threw it in my face.
I'm telling you--
I knew guys like him,
and sooner or later...
he's gonna kill
somebody else.
Maggie said she loves me.
Mm-hmm.
She doesn't mean it.
I mean, she can't.
I mean, why...
She's upset or confused.
She's probably feeling, like--
I think she's smart enough
to know what she's feeling.
No. No.
You know, she wants
to be in love,
so she needs something
to, like, hold onto.
Glenn, it's pretty obvious
to everyone Maggie loves you,
and not just because you're one
of the last men standing.
So what's the problem?
I didn't say it back.
Huh.
I've never had a woman
say that to me before
except my mom, of course,
and my sisters.
But with Maggie,
it's different.
I mean, we barely
know each other.
What does she really
know about me? Nothing.
We're practically strangers.
But I didn't know
what to do with it.
I just stood there like a jerk.
Hey. Hey, this is
a good thing.
Something we don't get
enough of these days.
Enjoy it.
And when we get back,
return the favor.
It's not like
she's going anywhere.
Rick?
I know about Lori,
her being pregnant.
- I got her those pills.
- I figured.
Hey, I'm sorry
I kept it from you.
Don't be. You did what
you thought was right.
It just so happens it wasn't.
Her heart's racing.
She's burning up.
We need Hershel.
He'll know what to do.
- Would you look in on Carl for me?
- Of course.
Moving to the suburbs?
Listen, Beth's in some kind
of catatonic shock.
- We need Hershel.
- Yeah. So what?
So I need you to run
into town real quick
and bring him
and Rick back.
Daryl?
Your bitch went
window-shopping.
You want him?
Fetch him yourself.
I got better things to do.
What's the matter with you?
Why would you be so selfish?
Selfish?
Listen to me, Olive Oyl.
I was out there looking
for that little girl every single day.
I took a bullet
and an arrow in the process.
Don't you tell me about
me getting my hands dirty!
You want those two idiots?
Have a nice ride.
I'm done looking for people.
Hershel.
Who's with you?
Glenn.
Maggie send him?
He volunteered.
He's good like that.
- How many have you had?
- Not enough.
Let's finish this up
back at home.
Beth collapsed,
is in some sort of state.
Must be in shock.
I think you are, too.
Maggie's with her?
Yeah, but Beth needs you.
What could I do?
She needs her mother.
Or rather to mourn...
like she should've
done weeks ago.
I robbed her of that.
I see that now.
You thought
there was a cure.
Can't blame yourself
for holding out for hope.
Hope?
When I first saw you
running across my field
with your boy
in your arms,
I had little hope
he would survive.
But he did.
He did.
Even though
we lost Otis.
Your man Shane
made it back
and we saved your boy.
That was the miracle
that proved to me miracles do exist.
Only it was a sham,
a bait and switch.
I was a fool, Rick.
And you people saw that.
My daughters deserve
better than that.
So what do we do?
Just wait for him to pass out?
Just go.
Just go!
I promised Maggie
I'd bring you home safe.
Like you promised that little girl?
So what's your plan?
Finish that bottle?
Drink yourself to death
and leave your girls alone?
Stop telling me how to care
for my family, my farm.
You people are like a plague!
I do the Christian thing,
give you shelter,
and you destroy it all!
The world was already
in bad shape when we met.
And you take
no responsibility!
You're supposed
to be their leader!
Well, I'm here now, aren't I?
Yes.
Yes, you are.
Come on.
Your girls need you now
more than ever.
I didn't want
to believe you.
You told me
there was no cure,
that these people
were dead, not sick.
I chose not
to believe that.
But when Shane
shot Lou in the chest
and she just kept coming,
that's when I knew
what an ass I'd been,
that Annette had
been dead long ago
and I was feeding
her rotten corpse!
That's when I knew
there was no hope.
And when that little girl
came out of the barn,
the look on your face--
I knew you knew it, too.
Right?
There is no hope.
And you know it now,
like I do.
Don't you?
There is no hope
for any of us.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Man, how many times
we gonna have to do this?
Look, I'm done.
I'm not doing this anymore,
cleaning up after you.
You know what the truth is?
Nothing has changed.
Death is death.
It's always been there,
whether it's from
a heart attack, cancer,
or a walker.
What's the difference?
You didn't think it was hopeless
before, did you?
Now there are people
back at home trying to hang on.
They need us, even if it's just
to give them a reason to go on,
even if we don't
believe it ourselves.
You know what?
This isn't about
what we believe anymore.
It's about them.
Son of a bitch.
They're alive.
I'm Dave.
That scrawny-looking
douche bag there is Tony.
- Eat me, Dave.
- Hey, maybe someday I will.
We met on I-95
coming out of Philly.
Damn shit-show that was.
I'm Glenn. It's nice
to meet some new people.
Rick Grimes.
- How about you, pal? Have one?
- I just quit.
You've got a unique sense
of timing, my friend.
His name's Hershel.
He lost people today, a lot of them.
I'm truly sorry
to hear that.
To better days
and new friends.
And to our dead--
may they be
in a better place.
Ah. Ah.
Not bad, huh?
I got it off a cop.
- I'm a cop.
- This one was already dead.
You fellas are a long way
from Philadelphia.
It feels like we're
a long way from anywhere.
What drove you south?
Well, I can tell you
it wasn't the weather.
I must've dropped 30 pounds
in sweat alone down here.
- I wish.
- No, first it was DC.
I heard there might be
some kind of refugee camp,
but the roads were so jammed,
we never even got close.
We decided to get
off the highways, into the sticks,
keep hauling ass.
Every group we came across had a new
rumor about a way out of this thing.
One guy told us there was
a Coast Guard center in the Gulf,
sending ferries
to the islands.
The latest was
a rail yard in Montgomery
running trains to the middle
of the country--
- Kansas, Nebraska.
- Nebraska?
Low population,
lots of guns.
Kinda makes sense.
You ever been to Nebraska, kid?
The reason they call 'em
flyover states.
How about you guys?
Fort Benning, eventually.
I hate to piss in your cornflakes,
officer, but...
we ran across a grunt
who was stationed at Benning.
He said the place
was overrun by lamebrains.
Wait, Fort Benning is gone?
Are you for real?
Sadly, I am.
Ugly truth is there is
no way out of this mess.
Just keep going
from one pipe dream to the next,
praying one
of these mindless freaks
doesn't grab ahold
of you when you sleep.
If you sleep.
Yeah, it doesn't look like you guys
are hanging your hats here.
You holed up
somewhere else?
Not really.
Those your cars out front?
Yeah. Why?
We're living in ours.
Those look
kinda empty, clean.
- Where's all your gear?
- We're with a larger group.
Out scouting,
thought we could use a drink.
A drink?
Hershel, I thought you quit.
Well, we're thinking
of setting up around here.
- Is it safe?
- It can be.
Although I have killed
a couple of walkers around here.
Walkers?
That what you call them?
- Yeah.
- That's good.
I like that. I like that better
than lamebrains.
More succinct.
- Okay, Tony went to college.
- Two years.
So what-- so what,
you guys set up
on the outskirts
or something?
- That new development?
- Trailer park or something?
A farm?
You on a farm?
Is it safe?
It's gotta be.
- You got food, water?
- You got cooze?
Ain't had a piece
of ass in weeks.
Listen, pardon my friend.
City kids--
they got no tact.
No disrespect.
- So listen, Glenn--
- We've said enough.
Well, hang on a second.
This farm, it sounds pretty sweet.
- Don't it sound sweet, Tony?
- Yeah, real sweet.
How about a little
southern hospitality?
We got some buddies back at camp,
been having a real hard time.
I don't see why you can't make
room for a few more.
We could pool our resources,
our manpower.
Look, I'm sorry.
That's not an option.
Doesn't sound
like it'd be a problem.
I'm sorry. We can't.
We can't take in any more.
You guys are
something else.
I thought-- I thought
we were friends.
We got people
we gotta look out for, too.
We don't know
anything about you.
No, that's true.
You don't know
anything about us.
You don't know what we've had
to go through out there.
The things we've had to do.
I bet you've had to do some
of those same things yourself.
Am I right?
'Cause ain't nobody's hands clean
in what's left of this world.
We're all the same.
So come on, let's--
let's take a nice friendly
hayride to this farm
and we'll get
to know each other.
That's not gonna happen.
- Rick--
- This is bullshit.
- Calm down.
- Don't tell me to calm down.
- Don't ever tell me to calm down.
- Whoa.
I'll shoot you three assholes in
the head and take your damn farm!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. Relax.
Take it easy.
Nobody's killing anybody.
Nobody's shooting anybody.
Right, Rick?
Look.
We're just friends
having a drink. That's all.
Now where's
the good stuff, huh?
Good stuff, good stuff,
good stuff. Let's see.
Hey, look at that.
That'll work.
You gotta understand--
we can't stay out there.
You know what it's like.
Yeah, I do.
But the farm is
too crowded as is.
I'm sorry.
You'll have to keep looking.
Keep looking.
Where do you suggest
we do that?
I don't know.
I hear Nebraska's nice.
Nebraska.
This guy.