Are we gonna go soon?
I don't know, baby.
I sure hope so.
- I'm hungry.
- I know, Carl. We all are.
Why don't I get
him something to eat?
Ed's into all this
survival stuff.
We've got enough MREs
to feed a small army.
- I'd sure appreciate it.
- No trouble.
What in the hell
did you tell her that for?
We don't even know
these damn people.
That boy is hungry.
We can spare one box.
It's called
operational security.
How long do you think
this stuff is gonna last
if you keep running your damn
mouth off to everybody we meet?
I'm sorry.
I wasn't thinking.
Are you getting anything?
- There's nothing.
- Big surprise there.
No, I mean there's nothing.
Emergency Broadcast
System stopped,
and that recording about
the refugee center.
It's all gone.
I'm gonna go up the road,
see what I can see.
I'll come with you.
Ed must have forgot
to pack those MREs.
- I found these in my purse.
- It's all right.
Listen, do you mind keeping
an eye on Carl for a minute?
No.
Shane and I are gonna go
scout up ahead a little bit
and see if we can find someone
that knows what's going on.
- I want to come with you.
- Huh-uh.
Huh-uh.
Hey, we'll be back before you know it.
Okay, little man, huh?
Why would they stop
broadcasting about the refugee center?
- I don't know.
- Think they're turning people away?
They're gonna have a riot
on their hands if they try.
- Your dad's nice.
- Shane's not my dad.
My dad's dead.
- What do we do?
- Come here.
We're gonna do what Rick
would have wanted us to do,
get you and Carl
out of here.
That's not lightning.
You stay with me now.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
They're dropping napalm
in the streets.
Shane.
Come here.
Morning.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
I can't believe I slept in.
You must have needed it.
Feeling all right?
Next time wake me, all right?
Especially on laundry day.
I can manage.
I had an idea
I wanted to run by you.
What's that?
That big kitchen of theirs
got me thinking.
I wouldn't mind cooking
in a real kitchen again.
Maybe we all pitch in
and cook dinner for Hershel
and his family tonight.
Kind of looking for things
to keep my mind occupied.
After everything
they've done for us,
seems like the least
we could do.
You mind extending
the invitation?
Would just feel more
right coming from you.
How so?
You're Rick's wife.
It sort of makes you
our unofficial First Lady.
Morning, guys.
Let's get going.
We've got a lot
of ground to cover.
All right, everyone's getting
new search grids today.
If she made it as far as
the farmhouse Daryl found,
she might have gone further
east than we've been so far.
I'd like to help.
I know the area
pretty well and stuff.
Hershel's okay with this?
Yeah, yeah.
He said I should ask you.
All right then.
Thanks.
Nothing about what Daryl found
screams Sophia to me.
Anyone could have been
holed up in that farmhouse.
Anybody includes her, right?
Whoever slept in that cupboard
was no bigger than yay-high.
- It's a good lead.
- Maybe we'll pick up her trail again.
No maybe about it.
I'm gonna borrow a horse,
head up to this ridge right here, take
a bird's-eye view of the whole grid.
- If she's up there, I'll spot her.
- Good idea.
Maybe you'll see your
chupacabra up there, too.
- Chupacabra?
- You never heard this?
Our first night in camp, Daryl tells
us that the whole thing reminds him
of a time when he went squirrel
hunting and he saw a chupacabra.
What are you braying at, jackass?
So you believe in
a blood-sucking dog?
Do you believe dead people
walking around?
Hey, hey.
Ever fire one before?
Well, if I'm going out,
I want one.
Yeah, and people
in hell want Slurpees.
Why don't you come
train tomorrow?
If you're serious,
I'm a certified instructor.
For now he can
come with us.
He's yours to babysit then.
All right, Andrea, T-Dog,
I want you guys...
Nice guitar.
Dale found it
on the highway.
You know, we still
have 11 condoms.
Yeah, you see 11 condoms,
I see 11 minutes of my life
I'm never getting back.
It wasn't that bad,
was it?
Look, I don't even know
if I like you.
But you're thinking about it.
You should.
You remember the name of that
waitress at the Dairy Queen
when we were in high school?
I know you, Shane, well enough
to know that there is only one
sure-fire way of engaging
you in a conversation,
and that is to start asking you
about girls you did in high school.
I don't want to, but I'll willing
to do it if that's what it takes.
Maryanne.
I told you about her?
In excruciating detail.
Excruciating, my ass.
You used to live for those
details back in the day.
Yeah, I was impressionable.
And I may have been living
vicariously through you.
Why wouldn't you,
with my impressive list
of accomplishments?
I was an artist
in his prime.
- A protégé.
- You mean prodigy.
Maybe.
Is prodigy what you call
a young high school stud
that bangs 30-year-olds
on the regular?
What 30-year-old were you
banging in high school?
- The PE Teacher.
- Mr. Daniel?
Mrs. Kelly.
The girls volleyball coach?
- Wasn't she married?
- C'mon.
You know what
I just remembered?
Why I never ask you
about this stuff.
Why don't we talk about your
high school love life then, huh?
Well, that's
a short conversation.
- It may even already be over.
- That right?
There was Holly, right?
Nope, that was me, too.
Then there was Sheila.
That's the one you lied to me about.
I never lied about Sheila.
I just got mixed up about
what the bases meant.
Just so you know, a home run,
that usually means a sexual act.
- That's intercourse.
- Yeah, I realize that now.
I think what you did was more like
a ground rule double or something.
I'm aware
of the judge's ruling.
Shouldn't be talking
about this stuff.
That life, it's gone
and everyone in it.
Sheila.
Maryanne.
Mrs. Kelly.
It's like we're old folk.
All the people
in our stories are all dead.
- We can't just forget them.
- The hell we can't.
It's hard enough accepting
what's happened
without digging
up the past.
I'll tell you what it is.
It's nostalgia.
It's like a drug.
Keeps you from seeing
things the way they are.
That's a danger.
You got people depending on you.
You think
I don't know that?
I don't know.
What are we doing?
You got every able body
at your disposal
out scourging these woods for a little
girl we both know is likely dead.
You think we should
abandon the search?
It's not my call, is it?
I'm asking.
Survival, Rick.
It means making hard decisions.
But you've got this knack.
You spread us thinner and thinner.
I'm trying
to save lives here
and you're out saving
cats from trees.
Is that what you think
Sophia is, a cat in a tree?
Don't do that, man.
Don't twist my words.
How many times we get called up
to look for a missing child, man?
You got 72 hours.
72 hours, and after that
you're looking for a body.
And that was before.
I mean you honestly think
we're just gonna find Sophia alive?
Are you that sure we won't?
- We being completely honest?
- I'm counting on you to be.
It's math, man.
Alive or not, Sophia,
she only matters
to the degree in which she don't
drag the rest of us down.
I thought you wanted honest.
If we'd just moved on, man,
we'd be halfway to Fort Benning
right now and Carl
wouldn't have gotten shot.
You said so yourself.
But we're out here, we're risking lives.
Your own son almost died.
Otis, he paid that bill.
What the hell are we
still doing this for?
I had her in my hand, Shane.
She looked in my eyes
and trusted me.
I failed her.
If I hadn't,
she wouldn't be out here.
I think she's still alive
and I'm not--
I'm not gonna write her off.
It's blue.
It's Andrea and T-Dog.
Looks like we wandered
into their grid.
Whoa.
Sophia!
Whoa. Easy, easy.
Come on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Son of a bitch.
Mind your own
business, Glenn.
You're pregnant.
You can't tell
anybody, okay?
You haven't told him yet?
Something wrong?
I just had
a long talk with Shane.
He wants to call off
the search.
What do you think?
What if it was Carl?
Would you want us
to keep looking?
If it was Carl, yes I'd want
to know one way or another.
Shane says my good intentions
are making us weaker,
that I can't make the hard decisions
for the good of the group.
They're all hard decisions.
But maybe I'm holding on
to a way of thinking
that doesn't make
sense anymore.
He says it's math,
basic survival--
how much fuel, how much food,
how much ammo.
Not much room in that
equation for being soft.
It's pretty simple when you start
thinking of life like that.
Hey.
None of us were prepared
to be living life this way.
You are making the best
decisions you can
with the information you have.
I don't see soft in that.
Mr. Grimes.
My dad wants to talk to you.
Oh, come on.
You've done half.
Stop being such a pussy.
Come on.
One of my horses
is missing.
Did one of
your people take it?
I was given the impression
you knew about that.
I did not.
I'll have a word with Daryl.
And Jimmy?
You took him out today.
Did he also give you
the impression of my consent?
No, he said it outright.
I took the boy at his word.
Jimmy is 17.
He's not my kin,
but I am responsible for him.
These things need
to be cleared with me.
Sounds like we need to work
on our communication.
What do you suggest?
Keep it simple.
I'll control my people,
you control yours.
Why don't you pull
that arrow out, dummy?
You could bind
your wound better.
Merle.
What's going on here?
You taking a siesta
or something?
A shitty day, bro.
Like me to get
your pillow?
- Maybe rub your feet?
- Screw you.
Huh-uh. You're the one screwed
from the looks of it.
All them years I spent
trying to make a man of you,
this is what I get?
Look at you.
Lying in the dirt
like a used rubber.
You're gonna die
out here, little brother.
- And for what?
- A girl.
They lost a little girl.
So you got a thing
for little girls now?
Shut up.
'Cause I noticed you ain't out
looking for old Merle no more.
Tried like hell
to find you, bro.
Like hell you did.
You split, man.
Lit out first chance
you got.
You lit out.
All you had to do was wait.
We went back for you.
Rick and I,
we did right by you.
This the same Rick that cuffed me
to the rooftop in the first place?
Forced me to cut off
my own hand?
This him we're talking
about here?
You his bitch now?
I ain't nobody's bitch.
You're a joke
is what you are,
playing errand boy
to a bunch of
pansy-asses, niggers,
and democrats.
You're nothing
but a freak to them.
Redneck trash.
That's all you are.
They're laughing at you
behind your back.
You know that,
don't you?
I got a little news
for you, son.
One of these days, they're gonna
scrape you off their heels
like you was dogshit.
Hey.
They ain't your kin,
your blood.
Hell, you had any damn nuts
in that sack of yours,
you'd got back there and shoot
your pal Rick in the face for me.
Now you listen to me.
Ain't nobody ever gonna care about
you except me, little brother.
Ain't nobody ever will.
Come on,
get up on your feet
before I have to
kick your teeth in.
Let's go.
Come on.
Son of a bitch was right.
Please, don't feed the birds.
What's the matter, Darylina?
That all you got in you?
Throw away that purse
and climb.
I liked it better
when you was missing.
Come on, don't be like that.
- I'm on your side.
- Yeah? Since when?
Hell, since the day
you were born, baby brother.
Somebody had to look after
your worthless ass.
You never took care of me.
You talk a big game,
but you was never there.
Hell, you ain't here now.
Some things never change.
Well, I'll tell you what--
I'm as real
as your chupacabra.
I know what I saw.
And I'm sure them shrooms you ate
had nothing to do with it, right?
You'd best shut the hell up.
Or what?
You're gonna come up here
and shut my mouth for me?
Well, come on
and do it then,
if you think
you're man enough.
Hey, kick off them damn
high heels and climb, son.
You know what?
If I were you, I'd take a pause
for the cause, brother.
'Cause I just don't think
you're gonna make it to the top.
Come on.
Come on, little brother.
Grab your friend
Rick's hand.
Yeah, you'd better run.
It's nice to be cooking
in a real kitchen again.
Oh, yeah? I never thought
I'd be so happy to see a potato peeler.
I'm just glad we're not roasting
squirrels over a fire in the woods.
Thank you, Patricia, so much
for letting us into your house.
What's this?
Lori and Carol are cooking
dinner for us all tonight.
That's the first
I've heard of it.
Well, I didn't think
it was that big a deal.
They want to thank us
for helping them.
We need to be setting clear
boundaries with these people.
They're getting
a little too comfortable.
It's just dinner.
What's going on with you
and the Asian boy?
Glenn.
He's a friend.
I'd rather he wasn't.
Bad enough I have to chase
Beth and Jimmy around.
Well, you don't have
to chase me around.
- I'm not 16.
- I know you're not.
That's why I'm counting on
you to be the mature one.
You know how I feel.
Please don't make things
harder than they need to be.
I'm a little old for us to be having
this conversation.
Don't get close to them.
They're not going
to be around forever.
What's with
the Annie Oakley routine?
I don't want to wash
clothes anymore, Dale.
I want to help
keep the camp safe.
Is that all right with you?
Sorry.
Just returning your book.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
If I had known
the world was ending,
I'd have brought
better books.
Dale, you think
Andrea's on her period?
I'm only asking 'cause
it's like all the women
are acting really weird.
And I read somewhere
that when women
spend a lot of time together,
their cycles line up
and they all get super crazy
hormonal at the same time.
I'm gonna advise you
to keep that theory
to yourself.
- Yeah.
- Who else is acting weird?
- Maggie.
- Ah, Maggie.
She started off
being mean to me.
Then she wanted
to have sex with me.
And now she's being
mean to me again.
And I don't even want to know
what's going on with Lori.
What's going on with Lori?
Nothing.
I don't know.
All right, let's take
this back a step.
How do you know that Maggie
wanted to have sex with you?
Oh, son, you didn't.
Did it ever occur to you how
her father might feel about this?
She's 22.
And he is our host.
He doesn't know.
Well, see that it
stays that way.
Jesus, Glenn,
what were you thinking?
I was thinking
that I might
be dead tomorrow.
Thanks for the book.
You're right, it sucks.
Walker. Walker!
Just the one?
I bet I can
nail it from here.
No, no, Andrea.
Put the gun down.
You'd best let
us handle this.
Shane, hold up.
Hershel wants to deal with walkers.
What for, man?
We got it covered.
Damn it.
- Andrea, don't.
- Back off, Dale.
Is that Daryl?
That's the third time you've
pointed that thing at my head.
You gonna pull
the trigger or what?
No!
No! Stop!
Rick!
What on earth's
going on out here?
- Oh, God.
- Come on.
- I was kidding.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God,
is he dead?
Unconscious.
You just grazed him.
But look at him.
What the hell happened?
He's wearing ears.
Let's keep that
to ourselves.
Guys, isn't this Sophia's?
I found it washed up
on the creek bed right there.
She must have dropped it
crossing there somewhere.
Cuts the grid
almost in half.
- Yeah, you're welcome.
- How's he looking?
I had no idea we'd be going through
the antibiotics so quickly.
Any idea what
happened to my horse?
Yeah, the one who almost killed me?
If it's smart, it left the country.
We call that one Nelly,
as in nervous Nelly.
I could have told you she'd throw
you if you'd bothered to ask.
It's a wonder you people
have survived this long.
He'll be all right.
I hate to say it, but I'm with
Hershel on this one.
Can't keep going out there,
not after this.
You'd quit now?
Daryl just risked his life
to bring back the first
hard evidence we've had.
That is one way
to look at it.
The way I see it, Daryl almost
died today for a doll.
Yeah, I know
how you see it.
I'm not out to be a hard case.
Just being realistic.
He's just got to start
making the tough calls.
You know I'm right.
I may not agree with
all of his choices,
but I respect him.
I know yours and mine
and your way isn't harder.
It's the easiest thing in the world
to cut our losses and to not help.
You keep telling yourself
you're making the tough calls.
You're really just trying--
The only thing I care about now
in this world is you and Carl.
So I apologize
if I appear to be insensitive
to the needs of others,
but you see
I'll do whatever it takes
to keep the two of you safe.
Even abandoning
a lost child?
Really?
My son and I are not
your problem anymore,
or your excuse.
- How's he doing?
- He'll be fine.
What about you?
I shot Daryl.
Don't be too hard
on yourself.
We've all wanted
to shoot Daryl.
Baby, what do I do?
Dinner's ready.
You coming?
Mm-hmm.
- You need anything?
- Huh-uh, I'll be right there.
Does anybody know
how to play guitar?
Dale found a cool one.
Somebody's got to know
how to play.
Otis did.
Yes, and he was
very good, too.
How are you feeling?
As good as I look.
I brought you some dinner.
You must be starving.
Watch out,
I got stitches.
You need to know something.
You did more for
my little girl today
than her own daddy
ever did in his whole life.
I didn't do anything Rick
or Shane wouldn't have done.
I know.
You're every bit
as good as them.
Every bit.
You weren't supposed
to see this.