Holy shit.
You all right?
Yeah.
Hershel?
Let's head back.
Car. Car.
Get down.
- Dave? Tony?
- He said over here?
Yeah. I'm telling you,
man, I heard shots.
I saw roamers two streets over.
- Might be more around here.
- It's hot.
- We gotta get out of here.
- Dave! Tony!
Shut up, you idiot!
You wanna attract 'em?
Just stick close.
We're gonna find 'em.
Dude, he said to stay close.
Tony.
Shit!
No!
They should've
been back by now.
Yeah. They just got
holed up somewhere.
We'll head out
first thing tomorrow.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Carl, I want you to keep
your head up, okay?
Your old man,
he's the toughest son of a--
No cussing
in the house.
Sorry.
- Lori, dinner.
- She's not in there.
Where is she?
Carl, when's the last time
you saw your mom?
This afternoon.
She was worried about Rick,
asked me
to look in on Carl.
- She went after them?
- She didn't say that.
Nobody panic.
Gonna be around here somewhere.
- Why won't they leave?
- Would you?
We can't sit here any longer.
Let's head out the back
and make a run to the car.
- What happened?
- Roamers, I nailed 'em.
They disappeared,
but their car's still there.
I cleared those buildings.
You guys get this one?
- No.
- Me neither.
We're looking for Dave and Tony
and no one checks the damn bar?
- What?
- Someone pushed that shut.
There's someone in there.
Yo, is someone in there?
Yo, if someone's in there,
we don't want no trouble.
We're just looking
for our friends.
- What do we do?
- Bum rush the door?
No, we don't know how
many are there. Just relax.
We don't want any trouble.
We're just looking
for our friends.
If something happened,
tell us.
This place is
crawling with corpses.
If you can help us not get killed,
I'd appreciate it.
Dude, you're bugging.
I'm telling you nobody's in there.
Someone grab the door.
If they're in there,
they might know where
Dave and Tony are.
They drew on us!
Dave and Tony in there?
They alive?
- No.
- They killed Dave and Tony.
- Come on, man, let's go.
- No, I'm not leaving,
I'm not telling Jane.
I'm not gonna go back and tell them
that Dave and Tony got shot
by some assholes in a bar.
Your friends drew on us!
They gave us no choice!
I'm sure we've
all lost enough people,
done things we wish
we didn't have to,
but it's like that now.
You know that!
So let's just chalk
this up to what it was--
wrong place,
wrong--
Get out of here! Go!
We can't find Lori.
And the others
aren't back yet either.
That dumb bitch must've
gone off looking for 'em.
- What?
- Yeah, she asked me to go.
I told her I was done
being an errand boy.
And you didn't say anything?
Don't do this.
Please.
I've already lost my girl.
That wasn't
my problem neither.
- She's not at the barn.
- I checked the yards.
- Well, where is she?
- She asked Daryl to go into town.
Must've gone herself.
Hey.
Carl.
- Did you know about this?
- No.
Look, just--
did she take a gun?
I don't know.
I wouldn't let her
go out there alone.
Hey!
We all know this is not
gonna end well!
There's nothing in it
for any of us!
You guys just--
just back off,
no one else gets hurt!
Shit!
Glenn! Glenn!
I-- I'm all right.
I'm all right.
Lori.
I'll hold 'em here.
You cover Glenn.
See if he can make it
to your car.
Tell him-- tell him
to pull up back.
We'll run for it,
get the hell out of here.
You want me
to cover Glenn?
You missed
all that gun training.
It could've come
in handy now.
No, I can shoot.
I just don't like to.
Sorry. Sorry.
Rick wants you
to try for the car.
Try?
You'll try and succeed.
I'll cover you.
That's a great plan.
- What happened?
- He fired.
He must have hit Glenn.
He's behind the dumpster.
Doesn't look like
he's moving.
Help!
You hit?
Are you hit?
No. No.
It's all right.
The car's right there.
- Okay.
- We're almost home.
- You good?
- I'm good.
Let's go.
Get back.
Let's get out of here!
Roamers all over the place!
Hurry up!
- We gotta get out of here!
- What about Sean?
They shot him. We gotta go.
Roamers are everywhere.
- We're leaving?
- Jump!
Hurry up,
jump already.
Dude didn't make it.
Help me!
I've gotta go.
- I'm sorry!
- No, no, don't leave!
Help me! No! No!
- Help! Help!
- Get Hershel.
Help! Help me!
Hershel!
No!
Hershel. Hershel.
The gunfire must've
attracted the walkers.
- Where's Rick?
- He ran across.
Well, hell,
we can't go without him.
Rick!
- We have to go now.
- No!
- Shh!
- I'm sorry, son. We have to go.
- No, no, don't leave me, please.
- We have to go.
- We can't.
- He was just shooting at us!
- He's a kid.
- Please help me.
This place is
crawling with walkers!
- We can't leave him!
- The fence went clean through.
There's no way we can get
the leg off in one piece.
Shut up!
Shut up
or I will shoot you!
That may be the answer.
We're not gonna get
that leg off
without tearing
the muscle to shreds.
He certainly can't run.
He may bleed out.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
Sh-sh-- shut up.
- Shut up.
- Maybe we should put him down.
I don't wanna see any more killing,
but this is cruel.
Can't we just take the leg off?
- That hatchet still in the car?
- No, no, don't-- don't--
don't cut
my leg off, please.
- Please, not my leg.
- Will this cut through the bone?
I'll have to sever the ligaments
below the kneecap,
cut above the tibia.
He's going to lose his lower leg.
- No, no, no.
- When we get clear of here,
we're gonna have to find some tinder,
cauterize the wound
- so he doesn't bleed out.
- All right, no choice. Hurry up.
Oh, God! Oh, God!
- No!
- Hand me that stick.
Here.
Guys, walkers.
- Shut up!
- Oh, my God!
Hurry up!
Shut up!
Oh, God.
They're everywhere.
Hershel, how we doing
over there?
I need more hands!
Easy, son, easy.
No, don't!
Don't cut my leg off, please.
Come on, we gotta go!
I'm almost out of ammo!
We don't have much time!
Come on, we've gotta go!
I can't hold 'em off!
Hershel, do it now!
- Come on, Hershel!
- There is no time!
Hershel, come on!
Please, don't leave me!
Please! No!
No, don't leave me!
Please! Please, don't leave me!
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
You're not fine.
I saw the wreck.
Let me look at you. Oh.
What happened?
Looked down at the map
and hit a walker.
Next time stay put,
you won't need a map.
Come on,
I've gotta get you back.
No, we got to find Rick.
He's back.
They're all back.
They're all safe
and sound.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Oh, thank God.
- What are you doing?
- God.
Keeping an eye on you.
Ain't you a peach?
I'm not gonna
let you pull away.
You've earned your place.
If you spent half
your time minding
your daughter's business
instead of sticking your nose
in everybody else's,
she'd still be alive!
Go ahead.
Go ahead and what?
Man, just go!
I don't want you here!
You're a real piece
of work, lady.
What, are you gonna make this about
my daddy or some crap like that?
Pfft!
Man, you don't know jack.
You're afraid.
You're afraid
'cause you're all alone.
You got no husband,
no daughter.
You don't know what
to do with yourself.
You ain't my problem!
Sophia wasn't mine!
All you had to do was
keep an eye on her!
Yeah.
Oh, my God, are you all right?
What happened?
- I was in an accident. I'm fine.
- She was attacked.
I'm fine, I really am.
Where's Rick?
They're not back?
Where are they?
Look, I had to
get you back here.
- You asshole.
- Lori.
- He's my husband.
- Lori, I will go after him.
I will find him. Hey!
Now, look, first things first--
I gotta--
I gotta look after you.
I gotta make sure
the baby's all right, okay?
You're having a baby?
Why didn't you tell me?
Come on.
Let's make sure you're all right.
Thank you.
Hey.
I am so sorry
that I left
without telling you.
It's okay.
I wasn't scared.
When's Dad getting back?
Let's hope soon.
I wanna be there when
you tell him about the baby.
Oh, he already knows.
We were just trying
to find the right time to tell you.
Is it a boy or a girl?
Well, we won't know that
until it's born.
- Will I be able to feel it?
- Not for a while.
You must have a lot
of questions, huh?
We never had the talk.
I guess we forgot.
Don't look at me.
That's your father's job.
If the baby's a girl,
can we name her Sophia?
Hey, dude.
Hey, I'm sorry, bud.
Okay?
- I thought you knew.
- Big brother Carl.
- Pretty cool, huh?
- I say that's very cool.
You-- you mind if I talk
to your mom a sec? Hmm?
How about a little later,
after she's had some rest?
Lori, I had to get
you back here.
You wouldn't
have come otherwise.
How about you--
how about you just
hear me out, please?
It's okay.
Will you give me a minute?
Thanks, bud.
Okay, Lori, it was a lie.
It was one little white lie.
But I think that--
I think you oughta be
thinking about
how lucky we are
that the baby's safe.
You just can't
stop lying, can you?
My husband is back
safe and sound.
- My husband is dead in some hospital.
- Oh, when are you gonna--
when are you gonna stop
throwing that in my face, huh?
I thought that he was--
the point here, Lor,
is that you cannot keep
running off like that.
What were you thinking about?
I was thinking we needed
Rick here to keep us safe.
Rick?
I keep you safe.
Like you did with Otis?
What happened that night?
You haven't been
the same since.
You wanna know
what happened with Otis?
What happened with Otis happened
because I love you.
I love you and I love Carl.
That's right.
I told Rick.
What?
You told--
you told him what?
Did you tell him that you thought
you were a widow?
That you were grieving and that
the world was coming to an end?
That-- that you
needed comforting?
Did you tell him
it was a mistake?
Mm-hmm.
You know, Lori,
that ain't true.
What we had...
it was real.
- It was not.
- It was a long time coming.
- It was real, Lori.
- It was not.
It was you and it was me
and Carl, and it was real.
It was right.
Don't say it wasn't.
It wasn't.
Just think about
what you felt,
just for a second.
What you fe-- what you felt.
Everything falling apart
all around us,
but it--
it was the one good thing.
And you know it's true.
How is she?
Dehydrated.
I'll set up an IV.
Best I can do
without Hershel.
Hey.
Can I get you anything?
Nah, I just wish
my dad was here.
She'll be okay.
You just need
to be strong for her.
I was just
reminding her about--
- Never mind.
- No, no.
I'd love to hear.
My dad would die
if he heard this.
My first summer
back from college,
I drove home,
dumped my stuff off,
went straight out
to the stable for a ride.
My family comes back
from church
and Beth grabs my things and starts
unpacking my stuff upstairs.
- That's sweet.
- Yeah, until this one here
starts rifling
through my backpack.
She finds this little
plastic container
with these pink and green
candies inside.
She didn't even know
I was on the pill.
She was so freaked out
by the idea of me and boys and sex
that she runs outside and chucks
them in the duck pond.
And I ride up,
I see this, I'm screaming.
She's crying
and Shawn runs outside,
thinks one of us
is drowning.
Soon as he figures out
what's going on,
the jerk busts out
laughing so loud
that my horse rears up
and gets mud all over the three of us.
My dad comes out, "What the heck
is going on out here?!"
And she turns around,
bats her eyelids and says,
"We're just swimming, Daddy."
In her Sunday dress,
all covered in snot and mud.
Rick and Glenn will get
your dad back.
Glenn's a good guy.
Yeah. He is.
Are you sure
you wanna risk it?
- You might not make it back.
- I'll be fine.
And with Shane at the helm,
I wouldn't be too sure.
He's lost people before.
And he's had my back.
What are you insinuating?
He doesn't want Rick back,
or Hershel.
With them gone,
he's got everything he wants
and no one
to tell him otherwise.
Shane has done more
to keep this group alive
than anybody,
including Rick.
You can't possibly
believe that.
I do.
Guys.
Dad!
You're okay.
Patricia, prepare the shed
for surgery.
- Are you hurt?
- No, but what happened to you?
- I was in a car accident.
- Accident? How?
I went looking for you.
Snuck out on her own.
I brought her back.
- Are you crazy? You could've--
- Who the hell is that?
That's Randall.
We couldn't just
leave him behind.
He would've bled out,
if he lived that long.
It's gotten bad in town.
What do we do with him?
I repaired his calf muscle
as best I can,
but he'll probably
have nerve damage.
Won't be on his feet
for at least a week.
When he is,
we give him a canteen,
take him out to the main road,
send him on his way.
Isn't that the same
as leaving him for the walkers?
He'll have
a fighting chance.
Just gonna let him go?
He knows where we are.
He was blindfolded
the whole way here.
- He's not a threat.
- Not a threat.
How many of them were there?
You killed three of their men,
you took one of them hostage,
but they just ain't
gonna come looking for him?
They left him for dead.
No one is looking.
We should still post a guard.
He's out cold right now,
will be for hours.
I'm gonna go get him
some flowers and candy.
Look at this, folks--
we back in Fantasyland.
You know, we haven't even dealt
with what you did at my barn yet.
Let me make this perfectly clear,
once and for all--
this is my farm.
Now I wanted you gone.
Rick talked me out of it,
but that doesn't mean I have to like it.
So do us both a favor--
keep your mouth shut.
Look, we're not gonna do
anything about it today.
Let's just cool off.
Can I talk to you?
What's going on
with you?
Your dad saved
my life today.
And Rick saved us both.
And I--
I froze.
Well, you were
being shot at.
No, that...
- You don't have anything to prove.
- All I've done,
then this-- okay.
It's because
of what you said.
That I love you?
Yeah.
A bullet hit
the wall behind me
and I-- I thought of you--
losing me, hurting.
And I couldn't take it,
so I hid
to stay alive.
- Glenn.
- No, no, no.
No, you don't get it.
Rick, your dad--
they were counting on me
and I--
I only thought of myself.
Has she eaten?
I'll give her a sedative--
stop her body from
working too hard.
You were drinking.
That was the least
of my worries.
You left and I didn't know
what to do!
- Want me to take watch?
- Yeah.
Relieve T in a few hours.
I'm gonna take the graveyard.
And then what?
We just send him
on his merry way?
According to Rick and Hershel.
If he finds his people
and leads them here,
we'll have a war
on our hands.
You know, you're preaching
to the choir, girl.
You ever consider
a lighter touch?
Abandoning
the search for Sophia,
taking out the walkers in the barn,
lying to Lori today--
those were
all the right calls.
It's your presentation that leaves
something to be desired.
Dale send you?
I see you pushing
everyone away.
For what?
They need you.
Huh. I'll always be
the odd man out--
- the same as you.
- I've made my peace.
Have you?
The way I see it,
you and me, we--
we're treated the same way.
Everyone's always trying to take
the gun out of your hand.
These folks--
they want to play house.
They wanna pretend
that Rick and Hershel--
they know what they're doing.
Let me tell you something--
- they bound to get us all killed.
- Then we have to stop that.
They don't listen. They're gonna
give this kid a care package.
They're gonna send him on his way.
And you're right.
That's gonna bring on a war
or something worse,
and we're just gonna--
we're gonna sit here and wait for it.
But you and me...
we're the only ones
who see it coming.
I should've left with you
when I had the chance.
Oh, man.
Come here.
Thank you.
Need your help.
Come here.
We're like a couple of old people.
We need to talk
about Shane.
What's he done now?
He thinks the baby's his.
No matter what, it's yours.
He'll accept that.
You're gonna have to make him.
He won't listen to me.
He's delusional
and he's dangerous.
When I went looking for you,
he came after me.
- Well, of course he did.
- And he lied to me
to get me back here,
said you were already back.
What?
You saw what he did
at the barn.
He's threatened Dale
and Hershel.
He's scaring people.
He's scaring me.
And I think he killed Otis.
I think he left him behind
and I think--
I think he did it
not just to save Carl,
- but because he loves me...
- But you don't know that.
...and he thinks that we're
supposed to be together
no matter what.
Those gunmen left
that kid behind today.
I killed two people
myself because of you,
and Carl, and the baby.
It was gonna be me
and not them no matter what.
You killed the living
to protect what's yours?
That's right.
Shane thinks I'm his.
He thinks the baby's his.
And he says
you can't protect us,
that you're gonna
get us killed.
He's dangerous, Rick,
and he won't stop.