I thought we were
going further.
We are.
18 miles out.
So why are we stopping?
I wanted to talk.
Been waiting a week
till we were gonna do this.
- I just want to talk.
- We don't need to.
We do.
No, man, we don't.
We're doing this.
I get it.
He was passed out when
y'all brought him back,
doesn't know
where the farm is.
That isn't what I need
to talk to you about.
I heard
what really happened
at the school.
Was it to survive?
Yeah.
One of us wasn't
gonna make it out.
It had to be him.
One shot to the leg,
Carl lives.
Reality is...
he had no business
being here.
Or there.
Whatever.
You don't think
I would've done it?
No, man, I know
you wouldn't have.
You don't think I can keep
Lori or Carl safe?
I didn't say that.
Or my baby?
Is it gonna
have to be me, too?
Rick, you can't just be the good
guy and expect to live.
Okay? Not anymore.
I'm not
the good guy anymore.
To save Carl's life,
I would've done anything.
Anything.
Now Lori says
you're dangerous,
but you're not
gonna be dangerous.
Not to us, not to me,
not anymore.
How about
you look at me?
You and Lori--
I get what happened.
When I figured it out--
and I figured it out pretty quickly--
I wanted
to break your jaw,
let you choke
on your teeth.
But I didn't.
That wasn't weakness.
It took everything.
That is my wife.
That is my son.
That is my unborn child.
I will stay alive
to keep them alive.
You don't love her.
You think you do,
but you don't.
Now the only way
you and me keep on...
is that you accept everything
I just said right here, right now,
and we move forward
with that understanding.
When it started
it was just--
it was a couple
of weird stories on the news.
Then it was so quick.
Everything--
it just happened.
Two weeks later
I'm in the hospital
and there were soldiers shooting
people in the halls.
They were shooting people,
man, not walkers.
Then the walkers
came through.
You know,
I tried to get you out.
I tried, but we weren't
gonna make it.
Man, there was no way
and I knew it.
But I couldn't live with it.
I couldn't live, knowing--
But I had to.
I didn't keep Lori
and Carl alive, man.
They kept me alive.
I want you to know that
I didn't look at her before that.
Brother, if I could
take it all back, I would.
I wanna check the ropes.
It's all good.
Rick say anything to you about Glenn
when they got back from town?
Just that it had
gotten pretty bad.
He's not the same.
Says he froze.
Blames me.
Says I got inside his head.
He came back--
that's what matters.
Men have to do certain things--
you know that--
and they're either gonna
blame the little woman
as the reason they do 'em
or the reason they don't.
I'll tell you something--
what happens out there
happens out there.
And we--
we're just trying to keep it together
till they get back.
- Things were good. Maybe I--
- Glenn's a big boy.
He makes his own choices.
I mean, do you--
do you have anything
to apologize for?
Tell him to man up
and pull himself together.
Just don't say, "Man up."
It never goes well.
Let me just
get this to Beth.
You go on. I got it.
We've gotta start
using our knives more.
If there's one walker,
we use our knives.
We keep things quiet.
We save ammunition.
Yeah.
We need dry goods
ahead of the winter--
warm clothes, fuel.
Maybe we get a break.
You gotta think
the cold affects them.
If it doesn't kill 'em,
it's gotta slow 'em down.
The second week
of January last year,
we got all that
snow and ice.
My cousin got stuck
on 85 for 24 hours.
Sitting in his car
with a birthday cake
for his girlfriend
at Georgia Tech.
He just sat
and ate birthday cake
and listened to the "Lord
of the Rings" book on tape.
We get lucky, we get the same
winter as last year.
By December,
it's a different world.
Safer.
Maybe we find some snowmobiles
to make runs.
Yeah, sounds good.
Knock, knock.
How about this--
you, uh--
you eat up all your food,
we'll get you up and out of here
and go take a walk.
What do you say?
It'll do good
to be outside.
You're pregnant?
How could you do that?
Uh, I don't really
have a choice.
You think it'll make
a difference?
Of course it will.
You eat something.
It's more than 18.
Yeah, I'm looking
for a place.
A place for what?
Give him a fair shake.
A shot.
There.
This'll do.
We'll leave the boy here,
scavenge some supplies.
Psst.
Over there.
Wait.
Like I said.
Gun's quick, easy,
but other ways to do this.
One more. Your turn.
Hey, Rick.
I don't see any bites.
Gotta be scratches then--
this one's hand,
other one's cheek.
They had walkers here--
burned bodies down the hill.
I guess it gotta
be scratches then, huh?
Haven't eaten a thing, huh?
You're gonna--
Hey.
I know how hard it is.
I tried for days to reach my mom
and get her on the phone.
I can only assume--
It's just so pointless.
Oh.
You have Maggie
and your father
and Patricia and Jimmy.
And you've gotta
stay strong for them.
I wish I could promise you
it would be all right in the end.
I can't,
but we can make now
all right.
And we have to.
Thank you.
I'll be right back.
We'll go take that walk.
Beth?
You give it to me,
sweetheart.
You don't
wanna do this.
Andrea, have you seen
Maggie or Hershel?
I haven't seen Hershel, but I saw
Maggie and Glenn walk by
- maybe 20 minutes ago.
- Could you find her for me?
- I've gotta get back to the house.
- Of course.
What the hell is this?
Oh, come on,
don't be stupid.
I owe you guys.
I can help protect
what you've got.
Why would you save my life just
to kill me by leaving me here?
One guy-- one guy
can't make it alone.
That's why I was
with those dudes-- I was alone.
Don't be stupid!
I'm not like them!
I'm just some guy.
I used to watch football
and screw around on the internet.
I lived with my mom!
I lost her
like you lost people.
I went to school with Maggie,
for God's sake!
I went to church.
I rode the bench
on varsity baseball.
- You went to school with Maggie?
- Did you go to school with Maggie?
- Answer the question!
I-- it--
she didn't know me.
Didn't even know
I existed.
I mean, I knew her.
I knew who her dad was.
There is no way
I would ever do anything
- to hurt her or her family.
- Jesus.
Or you.
Or your people.
I'm not like the guys
I was with!
He knows where the farm is, Rick.
Where we are.
He knows.
Say he finds his way
back to his people...
Shane, no!
Not now.
Just not now.
Well, when, Rick? When?
When I've had a chance
to think about it.
- Don't let him kill me. Please, don't.
- Shut up!
We're going back.
It's a man's life.
I need a night
to think it through.
You're gonna bring
this piece of garbage--
this piece
of garbage who--
he shot at you, Rick.
He ran with men
who tried to kill you.
You gonna bring him back
to where Lori sleeps?
- To where Carl sleeps?
- He'll be locked up in the barn.
- Unless you bust it open.
- Oh, don't start that shit.
- I'm taking the night.
- Man, you take that--
you think on it, Rick.
Keep struggling with it.
It ain't hard, man. The right choice
is the one that keeps us alive.
It's always the same with you.
It's like the first moment--
it's whenever you're put to the test.
Stop acting like you know the way
ahead, like you know the rules.
There are no rules, man.
We're lost.
No, no, no, man.
I know exactly where I am.
- You don't know shit anymore.
- I don't think you can do it, Rick.
- It's my call, man.
- I don't think you can keep them safe.
Ah!
Damn!
Oh, God!
No!
Get off me, man.
You're not doing this!
You don't get to make
these calls anymore.
I won't let you.
Are you crazy?
What if Dad finds out?
What's he gonna do?
Kill me for committing suicide?
Stop being such a brat.
He'd die.
So would I.
This isn't
just about you.
We all lost Mom.
May lose each other,
and I couldn't stand that.
So you give up?
Come on, bitch.
Let's see what you got. Come on.
Where's Hershel?
Maggie doesn't want him
to find out yet.
It's a family affair.
We'll let them work it out.
That's working it out?
When Beth stops fighting,
that's when it's time to worry.
You are being so selfish!
This could've
been handled better.
How so?
You shouldn't have
taken the knife away.
- Excuse me?
- You were wrong.
Like Dale taking my gun.
That wasn't your decision.
She has to choose
to live on her own.
She has to find
her own reasons.
Want me to tie
a noose for her?
If she's serious,
she'll figure out a way.
Doesn't mean
I can't stop her
or let her know
that I care.
That has nothing
to do with it, Lori.
She only has so many choices
in front of her,
and she believes
the best one is suicide.
- That's not an option.
- Of course it is.
She doesn't need to be yelled at
or treated like a child.
She needs
a loaded gun, right?
You'll understand if
I don't send you in there.
I came through it.
And became such a productive
member of the group.
- Let Maggie handle this her way.
- I contribute.
I help keep
this place safe.
The men can handle this on their own.
They don't need your help.
I'm sorry.
What would you have me do?
Oh, there's plenty
of work to go around.
Are you serious?
Everything falls apart, you're in
my face over skipping laundry?
Puts a burden
on the rest of us,
on me and Carol
and Patricia and Maggie.
Cooking and cleaning
and caring for Beth.
And you--
you don't care about
anyone but yourself.
You sit up on that RV,
working on your
tan with a shotgun in your lap.
No, I am on watch
against walkers.
That is what matters, not fresh
mint leaves in the lemonade.
And we are
providing stability.
We are trying to create
a life worth living.
Are you kidding me?
Look, I went after Rick.
I took down two walkers.
After crashing Maggie's car.
Ever apologize for that?
Crashing her--
- You're insane.
- No, you are.
And you're the one
that's self-centered,
the way you take it
all for granted.
My husband is out there
for the hundredth time.
My son was shot.
Don't you dare tell me
that I take this for granted.
You don't get it,
do you?
Your husband came back
from the dead, your son, too.
And now you've
got a baby on the way.
The rest of us have
piled up our losses--
me, Carol, Beth-- but you just
keep on keeping on.
We have all suffered.
Playing house,
acting like the queen bee,
laying down rules
for everybody but yourself.
You know what?
Go ahead.
Go in there and tell
that little girl
that everything's gonna
be okay, just like it is for you.
She'll get a husband,
a son, baby,
boyfriend.
She just has to look
on the bright side.
Mom would be ashamed
to learn she raised
such a coward.
- What about Dad, Beth?
- He's clueless.
- He had us waiting for a cure.
- He knows he was wrong.
When has Dad ever
admitted he was wrong?
He's just telling Rick's group
what they want to hear.
And Jimmy?
We went out for three months
and now I'm married to him?
And me?
You could do that to me?
I can't take
another funeral.
You can't avoid it.
What are we waiting for?
- We should both do it.
- What?
At the same time.
Help each other.
- No.
- It's hard to do it.
- No one wants to, but...
- No.
- we could do it so it's easy.
- Stop talking like that.
Our choice,
and then it would be over.
Or we'll be forced to do it when
the farm and this house is overrun.
- No one can protect us.
- That's not true.
Who, Glenn?
I heard what happened.
Rick will save his family,
the others, too.
We're alone.
You, me, Patricia,
with only Dad and Jimmy
against a whole world of those things.
I don't wanna be gutted.
I wanna go...
in this bed tonight...
with you beside me.
Please.
Okay.
You want some of that?
Oh, shit.
Hey.
You can't sit on top of her.
- I can't leave her by herself.
- You're gonna have to.
You're exhausted.
Go get some air.
I'll sit with her.
Go ahead.
Wash up,
get something to eat.
- I got it.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
Aren't you gonna
say something?
Is this what you want?
The pain doesn't go away.
You just make room for it.
- Stop!
- Holy shit.
Where the hell do you think
you're going?
What did you
expect me to do?
Please,
just let me go, man.
That's what
you came here for.
- I'm not gonna tell anyone anything.
- Shut up.
You wanna stay here?
Help the guy that just tried
to bash your head in?
There's 10 roamers there.
You think you can
take that on?
They don't see us.
We can get out of here.
Fine. Fine!
But let me have a gun.
I'll help you.
I'll show you.
Let's go.
- What?
- He did this.
- We're going.
- Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Rick. Rick.
Come back, man.
Beth?
Beth? Beth?
- Maggie?
- She's in there. I heard glass.
Beth, you all right?
Don't do this, Beth.
Don't do this.
Open up, please.
God, I left her
with Andrea.
- Where's the key?
- I don't know.
Beth, honey,
please open the door.
I'm not mad.
I'm not mad, Beth.
Maggie.
Hang on.
I'm sorry.
Okay. It's okay.
Stay there.
All right.
Come on, that's it.
Yeah, you like that?
Shane!
Go for the back door!
Come on!
Come on, get in!
Go, man, go!
Come on!
Whoo! Yeah!
Hell yeah!
You see that?
You see what we did?
Just keep driving.
- Where were you?
- I heard. Is she all right?
She would be if you had stayed
with her. Where were you?
- How bad is she?
- It wasn't deep.
She wants to live.
She made her decision.
- She tried to kill herself.
- No, she didn't.
My father is stitching
her wrist right now.
She'll live.
Stay away from her.
From both of us.
Don't you dare step foot
inside this house again.
I'm not gonna say
she was right,
but Beth has
made her choice.
She want to live
and now she knows it.
And sometimes you have to
cross the line.
If you want to kill me,
you're gonna have to do
better than a wrench.
Probably gonna
have to kill that boy.
But I am gonna
think about it a night.
It can't be that easy,
killing someone,
killing anyone.
You know that.
That is my wife.
That is my son.
That is my child.
If you're gonna be with us,
you gotta follow my lead,
you gotta trust me.
It's time
for you to come back.