♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
I can teach you a cultivating method
that might help you become a soul master.
Ten Thousand Year Ginseng?
You're brave to be making trouble
for my Purple Pearl Pirates!
Let go of Wu.
The strongest is the leader, Purple Pearl.
She is a level 68 soul emperor,
and has about 40 ships.
Teacher, don't kill her!
We were attacked by the Chill Poison.
Even my Phoenix Flames couldn't melt it.
Leader Pearl rescued us after.
If I win,
Wu stays with the pirates.
You want to catch me
without using soul skills?
Fine, I'll take that bet.
[Episode 167]
Time is almost up,
we're going to win for sure.
Wait!
We can do whatever we want with you!
Excuse me, excuse me.
Teacher, you're finally back.
San, where is Purple Pearl?
He didn't capture our leader, so he lost!
Young man, don't be too arrogant.
The entire ocean is ours.
Do you think you are that powerful?
Go!
Let me out!
It's our leader!
Tang San, you bastard!
You conniving villain!
Let me out if you dare!
Let me out! Let me out!
What are you looking at?
The tiny person in there
is Leader Purple Pearl?
This is the second skill
of my Vast Sea and Universe Shield,
Universal Freezing Protection.
It can shrink whatever is trapped in it.
You lost.
So what if I lost? I admit it!
You are my boss from now on.
Boss...
Everyone, go back and rest.
Boss.
Our island is full of natural produce.
You can ask for whatever you want.
San.
Your disciple is pretty good.
I was able to survive this time
all thanks to him.
After you guys recover,
we will continue towards Haishen Island.
You are going to Haishen Island?
Yes.
Actually, I came from Haishen Island.
Ji Xiang,
you said earlier
that you came from Haishen Island?
Yes.
In order to stay on the island,
you have to pass
the God of the Ocean's test.
I was born without soul power
and wouldn't have passed,
so my parents sent me here
under the care of Leader Purple Pearl.
Teacher,
you shouldn't go.
Haishen Island is a sacred place where
ocean soul masters worship the God of the Ocean.
Lots of foreign ocean soul masters
have died during the test.
Much less land soul masters.
Even if you pass,
you have to stay and serve the God of the Ocean
for the rest of your life.
God of the Ocean?
(God of the Ocean.)
The God of the Ocean rules the entire ocean.
Ocean soul masters can control the immense
power of the sea with his blessing.
In the hearts of all ocean soul masters,
the God of the Ocean is their single and only faith.
There are really
gods
in this world?
Yes! The God of the Ocean really exists.
Many ocean soul masters have seen
the presence of the God of the Ocean before.
Does he test
by showing his presence?
No.
The God of the Ocean gives prophecies
to the Head Flamen to conduct his tests.
So the test
still comes from a person.
It's hard to describe.
Only those who go through it
understand.
This...
The Head Flamen is the messenger
for the God of the Ocean,
and leads the strongest ocean soul masters
with his power.
(The Head Flamen...)
(It must be Bo Sai Xi,
the Grand Ocean Master uncle mentioned.)
She can control the power
of the ocean for her own use.
Unless you're at level 100,
you won't be able to defeat her.
(Even the level 99 Grand Soul Land Master,)
(Tang Chen, lost to her.)
(How likely is it)
(that we win against her?)
(But...)
Ji Xiang,
I understand your intentions.
But for us,
passing the God of the Ocean's test
is our challenge.
How we leave Haishen Island
with our powers
is also a challenge.
I believe that the God of the Ocean does exist.
When someone's power is more
than anyone else's,
they can be called a god.
This God of the Ocean is likely
an ocean soul master that broke the limit,
who can control all power in the world
and is more powerful than anyone...
As a soul master,
this is also our goal.
Yes.
That's right, boss!
Let me take you.
The Purple Pearl is truly great,
much faster than the Sea Devil.
Of course, this is my ship.
But I can only take you here.
Any closer, and I will upset
the God of the Ocean.
I have to think about my brothers too.
I understand.
Boss.
There are many strong ocean soul beasts
near the island,
and several hundred Devil White Sharks.
You will definitely be attacked
if you approach by ship.
What are you going to do?
Devil White Sharks?
[Soul Land]
Devil White Sharks are the fiercest
ocean soul beast.
Even if only a millennium old,
they can fight against decade millennium
ocean soul beasts.
The king of the Devil White Sharks
used to be the God of the Ocean's own mount,
a century millennium Protection Beast.
Even though the Protection Beast is not as big
as the Magic Whale King of the Deep Sea,
it's much faster.
No one can escape
its attack.
Then how will we get there?
Devil White Sharks sometimes go out
to hunt together.
But no one knows its habits.
We don't know if they happen
to be out hunting today.
We can't only rely on luck.
But we can try this.
Boss, if you really run into
Devil White Sharks,
never hurt any of them,
or else you will be attacked
by all of them.
Okay.
We're almost there.
We should get going.
Leader Purple Pearl.
You don't need to take our bet seriously.
Thank you for your hospitality
these past few days.
I have already passed Tang's Clan's
secret skills to Ji Xiang.
Please continue taking care of him.
Don't worry!
Teacher...
Become a real soul master.
Boss! I accept that I lost!
Since I accepted you as my boss,
you will be my boss forever!
You have to come back alive!
Ji Xiang,
they will come back alive,
right?
Yes.
Retract the anchor, set sail!
What is this?
Oh, no,
there are decade millennium
ocean soul beasts up ahead!
Even though the Dragon Boat
is surprisingly quick,
it can't stand up to a decade millennium
ocean soul beast.
We have to use the Vast Sea
and Universe Shield's invisibility
to try and avoid a fight.
Vast Sea and Universe Shield, First Skill,
Vast Sea Protection!
Shush.
Who knew that the Shield
also protects against water?
There's no way for the Dragon Boat
to keep moving forward.
Look.
Let's walk along the ocean floor.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 167 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1550 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2525]
[Total scene: 61631]
[Total CGI: 28345]
[Total plan of action scene: 12678]
[Total scene model: nearly 573]
[Total character model: nearly 1044]
[Total props model: 13401]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
That's the scent of
a Grand Soul Land Master.
You won't be able to pass
the God of the Ocean's test
for land soul masters.
Devil White Sharks.
I've never heard of Shrek School.
At least make up something convincing
if you're going to lie.
Why do you reject everyone that comes?
Only those who come before
the Seahorse Totem can take the test.
If you act rash while young,
you'll pay with your own life.
Haishen Island's Protector
of the Seven Sacred Totems.
Based on your current skills,
you will die for sure.
You're not welcome on Haishen Island.
Hurry and leave.