[-The dance battle...
-Begins now!]
[Planet Dance Battle in which the team's
pride is at stake begins!]
[Who will become the dancing queen
to represent Girls Planet?]
[The girls are getting ready
for the first mission.]
It goes over 50 seconds...
I can take another part.
[The girls are losing their smiles.]
This is not fair to other people.
[I felt so hopeless.]
You didn't look like one team.
You all think you're the best.
So you all have problems.
[Rehearsal on the shooting day]
You're not in sync at all.
Did you slack off?
Aren't you guys too complacent?
[The Connect mission begins
when everyone is nervous.]
[Let the Connect Mission begin!]
♫ You have both options ♫
They're so cute.
[The "How You Like That" match continues.]
Four of them are in the TOP9.
[Masters have high expectations
for the team with 4 Planet TOP9s.]
She made a mistake.
They were much better at the rehearsal.
The winning team is...
[What will be the result
of their performance?]
-Are you okay?
-Don't cry.
[Interim result
of the first global voting]
[Let us reveal the current cell ranking
determined by the number of votes]
[they received from Planet Guardians.]
[Interim result of the cell voting]
[33rd, 20,354 points:
Ryu Si On, Chang Ching, Terasaki Hina]
[32nd, 22,029 points:
Kim Yu Bin, Lin Shu Yun, Nakamura Kyara]
[31st, 24,374 points:
Han Da Na, Lin Chen Han, Kitajima Yuna]
[30th, 25,599 points:
Cho Ha Eun, Ho Sze Ching, Kanno Miyu]
[29th, 27,886 points:
Lee Yun Ji, Gu Yi Zhou, Murakami Yume]
[28th, 27,914 points:
Kim Ye Eun, Liu Shi Qi, Ikema Ruan]
[27th, 28,721 points:
Choi Hye Rin, Liu Yu Han, Aratake Rinka]
[26th, 30,194 points:
Lee Sun Woo, Poon Wing Chi, Hiyajo Nagomi]
[25th, 34,587 points:
Lee Ra Yeon, Cui Wen Mei Xiu, Oki Fuka]
[24th, 40,667 points:
Lee Yeon Gyung, Xia Yan, Inaba Vivienne]
[23rd, 40,982 points:
Suh Ji Min, Wang Qiu Ru, Ito Miyu]
[22nd, 52,096 points:
Kim Hye Rim, Ma Yu Ling, Okuma Sumomo]
[21st, 54,526 points:
Sim Seung Eun, Chien Tzu Ling, Ando Rinka]
[20th, 62,168 points:
Joung Min, Liang Qiao, Hayashi Fuko]
[19th, 100,410 points:
Kim Bo Ra, Zhang Luo Fei, Hayase Hana]
[18th, 100,515 points:
Yoon Ji A, Zhou Xin Yu, Shima Moka]
[17th, 110,687 points:
Kim Se In, Wen Zhe, Okazaki Momoko]
[16th, 117,496 points:
Guinn Myah, Yang Zi Ge, Kamimoto Kotone]
[15th, 122,428 points:
You Da Yeon, Xu Ruo Wei, Kamikura Rei]
[14th, 148,979 points:
Lee Hye Won, Liang Jiao, Nagai Manami]
[13rd, 156,595 points:
Huh Ji Won, Chia Yi, Yamauchi Moana]
[12th, 156,942 points:
An Jeong Min, Wang Ya Le, Fujimoto Ayaka]
[11th, 183,342 points: Lee Chae Yun,
Leung Cheuk Ying, Kishida Ririka]
[10th, 209,637 points:
Choi Ye Young, Chen Hsin Wei, Kubo Reina]
[9th, 223,105 points:
Kim Da Yeon, Wu Tammy, Sakurai Miu]
[8th, 286,390 points:
Kim Su Yeon, Fu Ya Ning, Nonaka Shana]
[7th, 351,067 points:
Kim Chae Hyun, Li Yiman, Kuwahara Ayana]
[6th, 502,682 points:
Kim Do Ah, Xu Zi Yin, Arai Risako]
[5th, 534,755 points: Huening Bahiyyih,
Hsu Nien Tzu, Sakamoto Shihona]
[4th, 843,274 points: Kang Ye Seo,
Huang Xing Qiao, Sakamoto Mashiro]
[3rd, 1,065,592 points:
Jeong Ji Yoon, Su Rui Qi, Ezaki Hikaru]
[2nd, 1,176,035 points: Seo Young Eun,
Shen Xiao Ting, Kawaguchi Yurina]
[1st place, 1,328,882 points:
Choi Yu Jin, Cai Bing, May]
[Planet Guardians,]
[The first global voting ends
August 28 10 a.m. KST.]
[the first global voting on Girls Planet
will come to a close in a week.]
[Whose dream will you protect?]
[Girls Planet 999]
[Ep.03 CONNECT:
You're drawn to my universe as well]
[It was filmed according to
the COVID-19 safety measurements.]
[This was filmed before
the social distancing level 4.]
[People in the same cell
will wear clothes of the same color.]
Thank you.
[The cell that will be voted together
in the first mission]
This is only for the people in TOP9.
[Special outfits provided only
for Planet TOP9]
This is pretty.
[Envious]
That's cool.
[On the other hand,]
["Pretty U" team doesn't have
Planet TOP9.]
[What's that?]
-Right?
-TOP9.
-Is that it?
Right. It's the sparkly top
that only TOP9 can wear.
Only allowed for TO9...
Liu Yu Han. TOP9 gets to wear
different clothes.
Right, I saw that too.
TOP9's top must be a different color.
[Let me see.]
[It's the color that represents
Girls Planet. Purple.]
[When everyone's gathered,]
[they stand out.]
[You can tell they are TOP9 members]
at once.
It's a little... You know what I mean.
They're on a different level.
I was so jealous of them.
It's sparkly purple and yellow.
This feels good.
[The other studio in the meantime]
["How You Like That" by BLACKPINK]
That purple looks so cool.
[My gosh.]
My gosh.
That's so cool.
[Impressed]
So cool.
[What caught Team 2's eyes?]
TOP9 looks cool.
[Team 1 in purple]
The bib for TOP9.
[Team 1 changes into clothes
provided only for Planet TOP9.]
It's a different color.
It's cool.
Three TOP9 members?
Four.
Four?
[There are 4 Planet TOP9 in Team 1!]
Four people.
Like half of TOP9 is on that team.
I couldn't even become a candidate,
but there were four of them on that team.
It made me anxious and intimidated.
They're like the Avengers.
Since there are many TOP9 members...
[Some of them have already debuted...]
[The prettiest girls are on that team
as well.]
[I thought they must be competing
against each other.]
[Only one can do the killer verse!]
[Only one person gets to have
the killer verse.]
Killer verse?
-Only one person for the killer verse.
-Oh, killer verse.
I want the killer verse.
[I want it.]
[Getting the killer verse means
you get the most attention.]
[I really wanted to get the part,
of course.]
[Team 1 checks the killer verse
of "How You Like That".]
-Wow.
-They're so cool.
[Everyone is immersed in the part.]
[The one at the center
stood out the most.]
Should I cut my hair short?
[The killer verse makes them want
to have short hair.]
My gosh.
Should I dye my hair like that?
[I can't lose.]
[The thought of competing
put me under a lot of pressure.]
[They weren't easy opponents.]
They're taking turns and performing.
[Let me see.]
No!
Shouldn't we do the same
to get more screen time?
[Choi Yu Jin, her 7th year since debut]
We must do it to be on TV.
Yes, we must.
[Laughing]
Of course I'm confident.
This song suits me. I can do it.
Who will go first?
Let me try...
No, not me.
I'll do it later.
Some girls are already in TOP9.
[In K Group]
Since I'm ranked 33rd,
they might think I'm not as good.
I'll go first then.
[Choi Yu Jin confidently comes forward.]
All right.
[Gulping]
♫ Now one, two, three ♫
[The first candidate for the killer verse,
P7 Choi Yu Jin]
♫ How you like that? ♫
[Staring]
[Watching carefully]
[I thought I could do better.]
[Second candidate, P6 Seo Young Eun]
♫ How you like that? ♫
[Impressed]
[I could see her determination]
[and fierceness. It was impressive.]
♫ Boom, boom, boom ♫
["What should I do?" I was so worried.]
[The third candidate for the killer verse,
P8 Cai Bing]
♫ Now one, two, three ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
[Nervous]
♫ Now one, two, three ♫
[The fourth candidate
for the killer verse, P3 Shen Xiao Ting]
♫ How you like that? ♫
[She's a good dancer,
and she's pretty and tall.]
[She's so cool.]
She's cool.
[Dry mouth]
Yeon Gyung.
This is so nerve-wracking.
This is like an audition.
[The last candidate for the killer verse,
K33 Lee Yeon Gyung]
♫ Laugh all you want,
this serves you right ♫
♫ Now one, two, three ♫
[Completely changing]
[They're doing their best
for the killer verse.]
♫ How you like that? ♫
Shall we pick in turns?
Okay.
I really want it.
I...
-I pick Shen Xiao Ting.
-Thank you.
[1 vote for Shen Xiao Ting]
-Shen Xiao Ting.
-Thank you.
[2 votes for Shen Xiao Ting]
-Shen Xiao Ting.
-Thank you.
[P3 Shen Xiao Ting will do the killer
verse, receiving 3 votes in total.]
Thank you.
[It was obvious to everyone]
[that Shen Xiao Ting had what it takes
to be at the center.]
I'm pretty too.
I'm...
Have you thought about
which position you'd like to take?
I...
I thought I could rap.
I'm confident about rapping.
Who wants to rap?
Me too.
[There are 5 people
who want to do the rap part!]
♫ Your girl need it all
and that's a hundred ♫
[C10 Xia Yan tries
to become the main rapper.]
♫ I want hundred out of hundred ♫
♫ What's up? I'm right back ♫
[She even tries the next part
while she's at it.]
♫ Cock back the hammer ♫
[Impressed]
That was so cool.
Xia Yan's style is too charismatic.
It's too charismatic.
[The next main rapper candidate,
P8 Cai Bing]
♫ Look at you, now look at me ♫
-♫ Look at you, now look at me ♫
[-She's pretty good.]
♫ Look at you, now look at me ♫
[Lee Yeon Gyung tries to be the main
rapper after trying the killer verse.]
♫ How you like that? ♫
-Okay.
-Who wants to vote for Xia Yan?
[Who will vote for Xia Yan
as the main rapper?]
Xia Yan.
[2 votes for Xia Yan]
How about for Cai Bing?
[3 votes for Cai Bing]
For Yeon Gyung?
-Yeon Gyung.
-Two votes for Yeon Gyung.
[One vote for Lee Yeon Gyung]
Shall we decide? Main rapper? Rapper one?
[Cai Bing becomes the main rapper
with three votes.]
-Thank you.
I think I can sing too.
[Trying for the second time]
[I wanted to rap, but I couldn't]
so I changed my mind quickly
and decided to sing.
♫ Light up the sky in this darkness ♫
[Seo Young Eun tries vocal part 1.]
[Young Eun's really good at singing]
[I knew why she was in the TOP9.]
♫ I'll look at your eyes
I'll kiss you goodbye ♫
[Lee Yeon Gyung tries the vocal part.]
[Lee Yeon Gyung's voice cracks.]
♫ Laugh... ♫
[The crucial mistake gives her
a mental breakdown.]
Keep it together.
[Get a grip.]
Young Eun can be vocal one.
Thank you.
[Seo Young Eun will sing
the vocal part 1.]
Thank you.
[Seo Young Eun: vocal 1,
Cai Bing: main rapper]
[Shen Xiao Ting: killer verse,
Choi Yu Jin: leader]
[Planet TOP9 took all the parts.]
[How about "How You Like That" Team 2?]
Shall we start?
Who wants to be the leader?
[A leader?]
[They look at one person like meerkats.]
[That's you.]
Should I try leading?
[I am the leader.]
-Yes.
[Please lead us.]
We were thinking about you.
I became the leader.
[The leader is Sim Seung Eun anyways.]
Leader.
[Leader]
-Leader.
The leader has been decided already.
[Decided at once]
Super fast.
That's how we should practice.
[You know?]
Everyday happy.
- Yes.
- Totally.
[Sounds good.]
And personally,
our team
doesn't have anyone who's in the TOP9.
-Don't get discouraged.
-Totally.
We'll stick together through this.
Let's do this!
-Let's do this!
[We don't have anyone in the TOP9]
[so it does feel like
we're at a disadvantage.]
But we have great teamwork
and great atmosphere,
so I'm pretty confident.
-How you like that!
[Go, "How You Like That" Team 2!]
["Fiesta" Team 1 is dividing the parts.]
Shall we decide who'll be the main vocal?
Anyone want the position?
[Looking around]
The song "Fiesta" is a very high key song
so I thought it would be a chance for me
[The main vocalist plays an integral role
in "Fiesta".]
[to show how good of a singer I am.]
[The main vocalist's high pitch is very
important in "Fiesta".]
Anyone want the position?
-Me.
[Kubo Reina and Lee Sun Woo apply
for the main vocal part.]
♫ On and on, on and on
Gogobebe ♫
[The two are impressive vocalists.]
♫ Wherever I am ♫
♫ I'm cool, wow ♫
[Who will become the main vocalist?]
♫ The real me that I always ♫
[The first main vocalist candidate
is Kubo Reina.]
♫ Imagined myself to be is closer ♫
[Nervous]
[They get nervous as she reaches
the high pitch part.]
♫ Oh yeah ♫
Wow.
[She's good.]
-She's good.
-She's really good.
[Lee Sun Woo's counterattack]
It's your turn now.
You can do this!
[She's from my cell.]
[Nervous]
Don't be too nervous.
♫ The real me that I always ♫
♫ Imagined myself to be is closer ♫
[Will she be able to pull off
the high pitch part?]
♫ Oh yeah ♫
[Even the girls far away respond
to her powerful high pitch.]
[This is "Fiesta".]
Bam!
["Fiesta" Team 2 watched everything.]
Thank you.
♫ Oh yeah ♫
["Fiesta" Team 2 is silent.]
Did our team have a main vocal?
That's what popped into my mind.
I think the main vocal
is really important.
Can someone sing high notes?
Someone who can sing high notes?
[Turning away]
[The team members lacked confidence]
[so those who were left became a team.]
Please call out a name.
[Three cells that weren't selected
became "Fiesta" Team 2.]
[We kept getting dispirited
without meaning to.]
[Ito Miyu tries for the main vocal part.]
Anyone else?
Anyone else? You two?
[Wang Qiu Ru also tries
for the main vocal part.]
Thank goodness.
[Ito Miyu and Wang Qiu Ru both try
for the main vocal part.]
[I knew they'd do well.]
I think it'll be best
if everyone takes a turn.
♫ The real me that I always ♫
[Ito Miyu tries
for the main vocal part first.]
♫ Imagined myself to be is closer ♫
[Listening carefully]
[Expectant]
♫ Oh yeah ♫
[Will she be able to overcome
the pressure of Team 1?]
[You can do it.]
♫ Imagined myself to be is closer ♫
[Close to me]
♫ Oh yeah ♫
[Is that wrong?]
[Nervous]
♫ Oh yeah ♫
[Wang Qiu Ru tries
for the main vocal part.]
♫ To be is closer ♫
[Team 2 is desperate for the high pitch.]
♫ Oh yeah ♫
[Singing]
I lost my voice.
[When they actually gave a try...]
A main vocal's singing should be powerful
to draw the attention of the judges.
I didn't know what to do
and I was worried we wouldn't do well.
How should we arrange the song
[In agony]
so that our performance of
"YES or YES" can be the best?
First of all, your cheekbones
should be smiling constantly.
Constantly like this.
[Agreed]
[Smiling happily]
[A cute and fresh look is important
for "YES or YES".]
I think the energy is important.
Right.
From what I can remember,
this song has a lot of ad-libs.
-Really?
-There's a lot of singing parts.
-Live?
-Live.
["YES or YES" Team 1 is mainly led
by Kim Hye Rim and Huh Ji Won.]
And we have to harmonize.
I think it should be powerful.
If the harmony isn't perfect,
-it's better not to do it at all.
-Right.
[That's true.]
-We'll just take it out.
-Take it out.
[Becoming one]
Hye Rim and Ji Won took the lead.
Hye Rim and Ji Won
talked a lot about the song.
I barely talked and just nodded along
while listening.
[How about "YES or YES" Team 2?]
-What about this?
-Like this?
- There are too many.
- Too many.
There are this many?
I know.
[The killer verse stands out
from the start of the song.]
You know the first member
who'll do the killer verse...
I think they should grab
the attention of the audience.
I think Do Ah should do it.
I think Do Ah will be able to
grab the attention of the audience.
I feel like she has a lot of energy.
Do Ah.
[Kim Do Ah will take the killer verse
followed by the team's opinion.]
Yes!
We will win!
♫ Yes or yes ♫
[Team 2 will win. "YES or YES".]
[Harmonious]
I'm in charge of the killer verse.
So I want to sing part eight.
It's the shortest.
[Kim Do Ah picks the vocal 8 part
which is the least part.]
So everyone will get a chance.
It's pretty long.
[Respect her consideration.]
Respect.
Shall we decide on the part?
We have to find
the best combo for our team.
I think
this part should be sung very brightly.
["YES or YES" Team 2 shares various
opinions for an ideal part distribution.]
I think this part is sung like...
For this part, we should be cute.
We divided all our parts.
[The parts are divided
through enough conversation.]
-Yes.
-Yes!
No one was discouraged and everyone
said their opinions.
[Everyone expressed their opinions.]
If members already
start to have complaints
we won't be able to practice together.
I wanted to listen to
other people's opinions.
["YES or YES" Team 1 starts
dividing the parts.]
-Now...
-We need to divide our parts.
I want part one.
Can I try out for part one?
[Huh Ji Won got the killer verse,
but she also wants part 1.]
Nice.
I want part two.
-Vocal two...
-Can I try out for that too?
Sure. Go ahead.
[Indecisive]
-Can I try out for part three too?
-Yes.
No one wants to do part eight, right?
[The smallest part]
I think Li Yiman would be
perfect for part eight.
[C Group]
[Me?]
I think I like that.
[Huh Ji Won suggests part 8 to Chia Yi.]
Chia Yi can also...
[Well... Well...]
For vocal part three,
[Kim Hye Rim recommends Huh Ji Won
for the vocal 3 part.]
Ji Won was the best.
[Sighing]
I like part three.
[Huh Ji Won also tries
for an additional part.]
Ji Won is in charge of the killer verse,
so I thought it would be better
to give the other members a chance.
Okay,
Ji Won can take vocal part three.
[I wasn't sure if I should say it.]
I thought if I didn't say it,
the members would find it strange.
I'm really sorry, but...
I'm really sorry, but
if you look at the back,
it says how long each part is.
But if you do the killer verse
and take vocal part three
that'll be more than 50 seconds.
-So I was thinking you could...
-I can take another part.
If it's okay with you...
[Kim Chae Hyun carefully suggests an idea
on behalf of other teammates.]
I think we should divide the part
so everyone can get a chance to shine.
Yes, okay.
That's good.
I was relieved.
I was thankful,
because she said
she was okay with another part.
But I did feel a little uncomfortable.
♫ Yes or yes ♫
[We had no problem communicating]
[I felt like the other members]
-♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
[-had something they wanted to say.]
["The Fifth Season" by OH MY GIRL]
Shall we decide on our leader?
-Okay.
[Yes!]
Shall we point to someone
who we think is leader material?
-One, two, three.
-Three.
[Everyone votes for Kim Bo Ra.]
[Shy]
Thank you.
[Bowing]
[Decided swiftly]
-That was fast.
-Really fast.
The members trusted me
and elected me as their leader
so I was determined to be a good leader.
You look like a leader.
I do?
[Kim Bo Ra is fit as leader.]
I feel reassured.
Oh my gosh. Thank you.
[We all picked Bo Ra to be our leader]
because she has a lot of experience
and is good at many things.
I'll do my best. Let's do it!
["The Fifth Season" Team 1 is
energetic with the leader, Kim Bo Ra.]
-Let's do it!
[How about "The Fifth Season" Team 2?]
[Awkward]
Shall we decide on the leader?
-Yes.
-Let's do that.
Who wants to be the leader?
[Avoiding the gaze]
[Avoiding the gaze as well]
No one wanted to be the leader.
[For our team to win,
someone needs to guide us.]
And I kind of knew I'd be it.
[Giving her a look]
No?
[Pondering]
[Ra Yeon, please be our leader.]
[She sensed the looks she got.]
I want to be the leader.
-Really?
What do I do?
I pretended like I wanted
to be the leader.
I didn't want the other girls
to feel pressured.
-Then...
-Thank you.
Ta-da.
This mission will determine
whether they'll stay here or go,
[Through the Connect Mission...]
[so it put a lot on my shoulders.]
The moment I decided to be the leader.
["The Fifth Season" Team 2 watches
the video of the song.]
The notes are so high.
This part's so high.
Who wants to be the main vocalist?
[Silent]
[Gaze aversion]
[Silent as well]
No one?
[Someone, please answer me.]
No.
Me. I recommend her.
[Raising her hand]
[Oh...]
[Embarrassed]
[Thinking]
Then...
During the Demo Stage,
[I went off-tune.]
♫ I fall into you ♫
[Ra Yeon sang the high notes in falsetto.]
[That made me lose my confidence.]
[So I was worried if I'd be able
to pull off the high notes.]
[Who will be the main vocalist?]
Then...
I'll be the main vocalist.
["The Fifth Season" Team 2's
main vocalist, Lee Ra Yeon]
-Thank you.
Who wants to become the main vocalist?
[Who's the main vocalist
of "The Fifth Season" Team 1?]
No one?
-No one?
-Me.
[Bo Ra applies for the position.]
["The Fifth Season" Team 1's
main vocalist, Kim Bo Ra]
Wow.
It's Bo Ra.
[I'll be going up against Bo Ra.]
[Worried]
And she's so good.
♫ Do you want me, baby? ♫
[Bo Ra was highly praised
for her steady singing skills.]
You were the first one that made me
put both my earphones in.
Bo Ra is an incredible singer,
[and she debuted before me.]
[Bo Ra made debut in January, 2019,
and Ra Yeon in May, 2020]
[We'll be competing head-on.]
So I'm worried.
[Sighing]
But I'll do my best as much as I can.
[Bo Ra from Team 1
versus Ra Yeon from Team 2]
♫ La la la la
You wash over me ♫
[The head-on match
for the pride of main vocalists]
[While expectations for
the vocalist battle increase,]
[there's another team that already started
a war of high notes.]
♫ So they can see us ♫
[Impressed]
[I'm honestly worried about the team
that will perform "The Eve" by EXO.]
["The Eve" Team looks like they'll win.]
[Admiring their high pitches]
Listening to them sing
gives you goosebumps.
[When I watched "The Eve" Team
practice next to us,]
I couldn't breathe.
[Sighing]
I think we're going to lose.
I think "The Eve" Team will win.
[Changing her attitude]
But we'll show them
that we're enjoying this
and how refreshing and sporty we can be.
We'll capture your hearts with our charm.
["Pretty U"]
♫ I have a lot to say,
but I can't get it together ♫
["Pretty U" by SEVENTEEN,
the best at performances]
[and the global idol band
that knows no limits]
♫ Help me, SOS ♫
♫ One, two, three, four ♫
[Make some noise!]
I love it!
I love SEVENTEEN.
[We've got this!]
We can do this.
Energy!
We need to decide who will perform
the killer verse.
[The highlight of "Pretty U" has
a refreshing vibe]
[and cute, little dance moves.]
Does anyone want to do it?
[Raising their hands]
Me!
[Then me too.]
[They all raise their hands.]
Me too.
I really wanted to perform
the killer verse.
I always wanted to do the killer verse.
[Hence, the selection contest
for the killer verse began.]
[Kamimoto Kotone showed off
her adorable moves.]
[She's so cute.]
She's cute.
[They keep showing their charms
to earn the killer verse.]
♫ You're pretty ♫
[Here goes Myah's cuteness.]
[Adorable]
[That was so cute.]
The youngest!
Baby.
[Looking]
[Yun Ji, the leader,
also appeals to them.]
♫ Pretty words to you ♫
♫ You're pretty ♫
[Sweet]
[Yun Ji received
the most active reaction.]
[Reading their countenances]
[How will the last candidate,
Ikema Ruan, perform the part?]
Start now.
[Enthusiastic]
♫ I want to give ♫
[How do I look?]
[Doing her best to show all her charms]
[I asked, how do I look?]
She's so cute.
Because everyone said I looked cute,
I realized I could look cute after all.
[Who will take the killer verse
in Team "Pretty U"?]
The one who'll take the killer verse is...
Who is it?
It is...
It's Yun Ji.
[They choose Yun Ji
who received the most reactions.]
Good luck.
[Sad]
[Yun Ji takes the killer verse.]
I'll do my best.
You can do it.
[How are things going at Team "Mic Drop"?]
-You can do it.
-Thank you.
[They were all good.]
They looked like they were having fun.
[My teammates]
weren't exactly in a good mood.
[What's the song for the team
with a different atmosphere?]
[The song topped the Billboard Hot 100
for 7 weeks in a row.]
["Mic Drop" by BTS, the world-class band
which has become a genre itself]
Wait a minute.
This is hard.
[Shaking her head]
[It looked so complicated.]
So I thought about giving up.
[I knew that it'd be hard.]
[Everyone got intimidated
and lost confidence.]
No one looked happy.
We were happy at first...
[Things were congenial
when choosing the song.]
Let's have fun.
Let's go.
[They were happy this morning,
thinking of performing "Mic Drop".]
-"MIC Drop"?
Okay.
[They're now depressed as the song is
much tougher than expected.]
-It's hard.
-It is.
[We needed to practice,
but we were so lost.]
[Frustrated]
I don't know what to do.
[Team "Mic Drop" starts practicing
led by Han Da Na.]
Start now.
♫ Did you see my bag? ♫
[Bumping]
Move faster please.
[Team "Mic Drop" continues to practice.]
Let's move on.
Start now.
♫ How you think about that? ♫
[They try to get in sync,
but they keep falling apart.]
♫ Haters already got sick of us ♫
We're not in sync.
Right.
[We're not doing it quite right.]
[I wasn't sure if we could do it.]
[I wonder if we'll be able to survive.]
I'm not confident at all. I'm scared.
[How about Team "The Eve"?]
Pick a leader.
[Raising her hand]
[Yes, that'll be me.]
Because I'm older than most of you.
[There's a pause
after she mentions her age.]
I'm 25 years old.
[You're 25. We approve.]
All right.
Can I be the leader?
-Yes, you can.
-Sounds good.
You're the best!
[The oldest member becomes the leader.]
Then...
I also wanted to be the leader.
[I wanted to raise my hand, too.]
[But since she's older than me...]
Also...
Pick a leader.
[That made me hesitant for a second.]
[Girls, do you believe in me?]
Who wants the killer verse?
[They spend time listening to the song
to divide the parts.]
[The beginning of the song]
[and the center during the chorus]
[The killer verse is the key part
of "The Eve".]
[Fu Ya Ning asks for volunteers first
as it's an important part.]
Raise your hand if you want it.
All of you?
[Most of the teammates applied for it.]
[I really want it.]
I think the whole vibe
of the song suits me really well.
So I decided to go for the killer verse.
It will decide the color of our team.
I want it so badly!
[The first candidate of the killer verse,
Nonaka Shana]
♫ We must breakthrough ♫
[The second candidate of the killer verse,
Jeong Ji Yoon]
[The third candidate of the killer verse,
Ezaki Hikaru]
♫ We must breakthrough ♫
♫ So they can see us ♫
[Gazing]
♫ We must breakthrough ♫
[The fourth candidate of the killer verse,
Su Rui Qi]
She's good.
♫ So they can see us ♫
[Fatal]
She's so cool.
[The killer verse.]
It was the main reason
why I chose "The Eve".
♫ So they can see us ♫
[She's been practicing the killer verse
before distributing the parts.]
[I thought it had to go to the person]
who could interpret this song the best.
[How will You Da Yeon do
after practicing so hard?]
♫ We must breakthrough ♫
♫ So they can see us ♫
[Winking]
I'll take the part no matter what!
[Who will be chosen by the majority?]
-In 2, 3...
Ji Yoon got 2, Shana got 2,
Hikaru got 2, and Rui Qi got 3 votes.
[A total of 9 votes]
Ji Yoon got 2, Shana got 2,
[Da Yeon gets 0 votes.]
Hikaru got 2, and Rui Qi got 3 votes.
So it's Rui Qi.
[Su Rui Qi is picked
for the killer verse.]
-Congratulations.
[Forcing herself to smile]
Thank you.
[Having great teammates is relieving,]
[but they can also be your rivals.]
[So I'm worried a lot.]
How should we split the parts?
[They officially start dividing
the parts.]
The parts...
[Contemplating]
About the parts...
Can we apply for only one part each?
Or can we apply as much as we want?
One part for each person.
One part.
Just say the part you want first.
-If they overlap, then you compete.
-Okay. That's good.
That would be much faster.
The part that you want the most.
[I like it!]
Good.
Who wants to do vocal one?
[Raising hand]
Me too.
[Fu Ya Ning and You Da Yeon competes
for vocal part 1.]
[Kim Su Yeon as well.]
[Kim Su Yeon tries first.]
♫ You must shout out loud ♫
[Leader Fu Ya Ning
also competes for vocal 1.]
♫ So that it spreads far away ♫
-Cool.
-It's really cool.
[Kamikura Rei is having a crush.]
[You Da Yeon is
going for vocal part 1 too.]
♫ You must shout out loud ♫
♫ So that it spreads far away ♫
[Shifty eyes]
-Should we put it to a vote?
-Okay.
[This time again,
the majority vote will decide the part.]
In 1, 2, 3.
[Who will take the vocal part 1?]
Five votes.
Yes! Thank you.
[Fu Ya Ning who won five votes wins.]
[Feeling bitter]
-Thanks.
-Congratulations.
[It was bad.]
[I suddenly had a mental breakdown.]
[You Da Yeon couldn't win
the part she wanted.]
Let's decide on part seven.
Part 2. Part 3.
[All parts except for
vocal 7 and 8 are fixed.]
Part 4. Part 5.
Six. Lead vocal.
Da Yeon, you first.
I don't think I can do it.
[You Da Yeon failed to win all the parts
that she wanted.]
[She cries unexpectedly.]
What's wrong?
[Although it didn't go perfectly
as I planned,]
there was an alternative.
But it didn't work out either.
[Then all my determination]
somewhat seemed meaningless.
I couldn't take what I wanted,
but I didn't get to show
what I could do either.
Let me show you first.
If it's still not good enough,
I'll take part 7 or 8.
This is not fair for the others
because everyone had only one chance.
Everyone got to choose once.
One chance per person.
[Opportunities
were given to everyone evenly.]
Okay.
[We placed first for the morning mission,
so we were able to make a choice.]
We should...
[You Da Yeon made her team by winning
the wake-up mission.]
Nonaka Shana.
[Had I known we could be rivals,]
[I wouldn't have picked
the current members.]
Nothing worked as I wanted.
I didn't feel like
I could survive here.
[It was so depressing.]
[99 girls started practicing in full-scale
for the first mission.]
[After the practice]
-Yes?
-Come in.
-Is Miyu here?
-I'm here.
Let's do well tomorrow, okay?
I'll do the best I can too.
-Kyara.
-Yes?
Great job today.
Really?
Let's work hard together
-Together...
-tomorrow as well.
-Okay. Let's do it.
-We can do it.
-Okay?
-Okay.
[Ito Miyu]
[My voice is hoarse which gives burden
to the members.]
[I feel pressured and anxious.]
[Not only do I want to improve my skills.
but also myself in Girls Planet!]
[Girls are practicing over and over,]
[even though they're back to their dorms.]
-We can do it.
[Ando Rinka]
[I can't believe I can sing and dance
on the big stage I've dreamed of.]
[I want to be in an enjoyable stage
so that I don't have any regrets!]
It was my dream to perform on stage.
Me too. I want to do a good job.
Let's get the benefit
and go to "M Countdown."
After "The Fifth Season" is over,
our season will be over too.
Gosh.
No, it won't.
Our season will bloom.
Bloom? Yes.
[It's a very important performance
for me and my team.]
[I feel so anxious.]
[It makes me feel more responsible]
[that I could drop out with my teammates.]
[I don't want to cause any harm
to my teammates.]
[I want to survive with them
all together.]
[I know I can put my life on the line.]
[I'm so desperate.]
Let's do it tomorrow.
-We can do it.
Gosh, you're wet.
Sorry.
Let's make it
-our season.
-Our season.
-Let's go.
[“A dream you dream alone is
just a dream."]
["A dream you dream together is reality,”
by John Lennon.]
[Connect Mission]
[Girls Planet 999]
[The day of the first mission
has finally started.]
[Girls are entering the stage of fate.]
[Filming was in compliance with
COVID-19 guidelines.]
[All staff and cast went through
COVID-19 PCR tests.]
[A stage that could be the first
and last for 99 girls.]
[Who will win on this stage?]
[Masters are entering to assess
the girls' performance.]
Hi.
[They're greeting brightly,
but with nervous expressions.]
-Hello.
[Sunmi is so sweet.]
Have you practiced a lot?
-Yes.
-You must be nervous.
[Smiling like their sister.]
Still, you've got to do it.
[Sad]
Don't be nervous. Good luck, everyone.
-Thank you.
[Girls cheer up thanks to
the Masters' support.]
[Surprised]
[Planet Master to host
the mission is here.]
[His appearance relieves the tension.]
Dear 99 girls.
Finally today,
the 1st mission of Girls Planet 999,
Connect Mission's performances
will unfold.
[Connect Mission]
[Heart is pounding.]
I'm nervous again.
The 99 girls become one together
through K-pop on this Connect Mission.
Contestants from three cells are
to perform together as a team.
For 8 teams among a total of 11 teams,
[each team will compete with another team
that chose the same song.]
[For the teams that chose a song
of EXO, BTS, or SEVENTEEN,]
[the three teams
will compete against each other.]
And the winner of each match
[Masters will decide the winner.]
will be decided by the masters.
For this mission,
I'll be seeing how much effort
you have put into your performance.
I'll focus only on skills again.
And I'll look forward to seeing
high quality performances.
The winning teams
from the one-on-one matches
will have their votes counted twice more
for 24 hours
before the global voting ends.
The winning team from the three-team match
will have their votes
counted three times more.
[I thought I shouldn't miss this chance.
That I should win.]
There's one more special benefit.
[Special Benefit of the Connect Mission]
[Among the five winning teams,]
[the master will choose the best team.]
[One team selected by the Master's choice]
[And this team will have the glory
of performing on "M Countdown."]
[A chance to perform in "M Countdown"]
It's crazy.
[To get three times the amount of votes]
and perform on the dream stage.
I want to seize this chance
no matter what.
Based on the votes
of the Planet Guardians worldwide,
16 cells among 33 cells
will be eliminated.
In short, a total of 48 girls
[48 girls will be eliminated.]
will have to leave the show after today.
[This is the first mission,
but this could also be the last mission.]
[Kim Da Yeon,
I'm number one in K Group, but...]
I feel so strongly that
I'm the only one not showing anything.
[I have to work hard to get this benefit.]
[I thought
I should show everything I could.]
[Who's going to win the benefit
on the stage today?]
Before we get started
with the performances,
Master Baek and Master Jang,
I hear there was a special mission
to decide the mission order.
[Yeo Jin Goo, getting curious]
[Baek Gu Young, surprised]
It was incredible.
[He's funny.]
Planet Guardians, let's watch it together.
[Baby MC Gu Young]
[Planet Guardians, let's watch together.]
[What's the special event
for the battle stage?]
[Seven days before the mission]
[What's the screaming about?]
What?
-Is it right?
-100 percent sure.
[I'm 100 percent sure!]
[What is it?]
[A circular stage
that made the girls terrified.]
There's a stage.
I've seen this before.
Maybe we have to perform here.
Could it be about changing mission songs?
-A battle?
[Huh Ji Won is a good detective.]
There must be a reason
why we're seated in teams.
It's probably that.
[The seats are divided into teams
per mission songs.]
[Amid all kinds of speculation,]
[familiar music is heard
and their hearts react.]
[I can't stay still to the Signal song!]
[Suddenly, they are dancing perfectly.]
[Feeling awesome]
[Feeling excited]
[The stage is full
but they can dance while sitting.]
[In the zone]
[What's going on?]
Awesome!
[Perfect ending]
[The real ending is only when
the connection is successful.]
What a surprising entrance.
[This is too good.]
Hello.
[Greeting after dancing]
-Hello.
You guys are practicing for
the Connect Mission, right?
-Yes!
[Everyone answers together.]
I'm looking forward to it.
[I'm watching. I will look forward to it.]
Why do you think Joo Hee and I
are here today?
For a dance battle?
What?
Why didn't anyone say anything?
[Because everyone wants to avoid it...]
That's right.
Today's the day of Planet Dance Battle.
[Yes!]
[Today is
the first "Planet Dance Battle".]
But it's no fun without a prize, right?
So we're going to give
the winners something.
-You guys are curious, right?
-Yes!
The winners will get
[What will be the benefit
of the dance battle?]
to decide which group will go first
for the performance!
If I'm being really honest,
whether we go first or last
didn't really matter.
We just have to win, right?
[This is a survival program!]
Who goes first is really important.
We have to avoid the last spot.
No.
[Determined]
We have to avoid the last spot.
No.
Whether we go first or last
[You said you didn't care
whether you go first or last.]
didn't really matter.
We have to avoid the last spot.
No.
[Okay, I get it.]
We have to win this.
We have to win.
Please select three members
from each group
[1. Each team will choose
their best three dancers.]
[who are good at dancing.]
[A random music will be played]
[2. These dancers will do
freestyle dancing to random music.]
[and you have to do
a freestyle dance to it.]
Once the battle is over,
[the winners will be decided
by the masters.]
[3. After the dance battle, the dance
masters will decide which team wins.]
You know, the talent and appeal
to attract the audience
[Charm]
is important, right?
For girls who never participated in
a dance battle
Master Baek Gu Young will...
-Show us!
How can I do a dance battle alone?
[He's provoking her.]
[They're looking forward to it.]
Okay. Give us the music.
[This is unbelievable!]
[Shouting]
[The entire group fainted.]
She liked slid down.
I got dizzy.
[Dizzy]
[Protect Myah, roger that.]
[They're saving it in their corneas.]
[Driving insane.]
[The next to attack.]
[Dance Master Baek Gu Young
goes into action.]
When he did this, I was so...
[She's speechless.]
[Jang Joo Hee, are you watching?
This is what dancing should be like.]
[Even Gu Young's ending is perfect.]
So is this what they call dance?
[Kim Bo Ra, A person who opened
her eyes to dancing, Main vocal]
[The girls will start
the dance battle now.]
The first team to participate in
the dance battle is...
[The first battle team is
Team "How You Like That".]
"How You Like That" Team.
Please come up on stage.
[They're making a ruckus
from their entrance.]
[Pow?]
Bam!
-Okay.
[They saw it from somewhere.
It's necessary to get a head start.]
[It's hard to understand the meaning
of the gestures of each team leader.]
Now please pick three members.
[Who are the best three dancers
of each team for "How You Like That"?]
[Team 1: Seo Young Eun, Xia Yan, Cai Bing]
[Team 2: Kim Da Yeon, Sim Seung Eun,
Chien Tzu Ling]
Do you think you guys will win?
Definitely.
[Hooray!]
You guys all know we're going to win.
[Is this "Show Me the Money"
or Girls Planet 999?]
Let's get this battle started!
[The dance battle for
the stage decision benefit will start.]
Yes!
I thought we were a little better.
Bring it on!
[The random music starts.]
[Who will run to the stage first?]
It's her?
[It's me!]
[Xia Yan of Team 1 starts
attacking first.]
[Shouting]
She was pretty good.
[She knows how to enjoy the stage.]
[Kim Da Yeon appears on the stage.]
[When she came up on stage,
I was flustered.]
I thought she was good at dancing.
[It's steaming hot with excitement.
Who will perform next?]
[C Group play-off
Cai Bing versus Chien Tzu Ling]
[Chein Tzu Ling preoccupies
the floor first.]
[Shouting]
[Me too!]
[She covers her mouth.]
[She was crawling across the floor.]
Maybe it's because she's older.
[They are a year apart in age.]
Oh, I'm sorry.
[The second match ended.
All of the last dancers start dancing.]
[K Group play-off
Seo Young Eun versus Sim Seung Eun]
[Oh my, goodness!]
[Her dancing is too intense to watch
on a Friday night at 8:20 p.m.]
[You're the best!]
[The competitive dance battle ended.
Which team is the winner?]
The winners are Team 2!
["How You Like That" Team 2]
[They will choose who will go first
for the mission stage.]
[This battle is
"Fiesta" Team 1 versus "Fiesta" Team 2.]
I can't look.
Let's start.
[I'm nervous.]
[Is she the Reina who was
nervous just now?]
Let's do this!
They crushed the stage.
Look at her energy!
Good job!
The winners are
"Fiesta" Team 1!
["Fiesta" Team 1 won.]
[They will choose who will go last
for the mission stage.]
[This battle is "YES or YES" Team 1
versus "YES or YES" Team 2.]
[Bring it on.]
She's good.
[Dancing]
[Calm down.]
Music cue.
[When the music starts,
they start dancing.]
[Team 1 Kim Chae Hyun versus
Team 2 Wen Zhe]
I felt like she was immersed in
her own dance.
Next.
[Who is the second dancer?]
[I should show them]
what I could do if it means winning.
[She gets a head start.]
[Win!]
The winners are Team 2!
["YES or YES" Team 2]
[They will choose who will go last
for the mission stage.]
Team EBS.
[This battle is "The Eve" versus
"Mic Drop" versus "Pretty U".]
I'm scared.
Their team is scary.
[They're shaking from Su Yeon's
neck stretch.]
Look at them.
[The battle starts.
Have fun if you can't avoid it!]
[Shouting]
It was shocking.
[Surprised]
[She even went down the stage.]
The Eve is the best!
[She's having difficulty in breathing.]
"The Eve" is the best!
[Thank you for lending me the mic.]
Thank you.
[She's polite.]
She's amazing!
She did splits and it was amazing.
[She did a turn and it was amazing.]
She crawling all over the floor
and it was amazing.
[The match isn't over yet.]
[The "Mic Drop" team is using
a shoe instead of a mic.]
The winners are "The Eve" Team!
["The Eve" Team won.]
[They will perform at the end
for the mission stage.]
Good job!
In second place, "MIC Drop" Team!
["Mic Drop" Team is in second.]
[They will perform first
for the mission stage.]
When she pretended to get that call,
I thought I dialed her.
[That stole Gu Young's heart.]
It was great.
[The real match will be held
at the Connect Mission.]
The real winners will be chosen
at Connect Mission, right?
I'll be looking forward to
great performances.
[The first planet dance battle ended.]
-Great job, guys. Thank you.
-Thank you!
Thank you.
Well, you guys had a fun time.
If we get another chance for
a dance battle
[He's jealous.]
I'd like to see it in person.
-Please call me.
-Please come.
[Jin Goo is welcome any time.]
I'm excited.
Now, we will start
the first mission of Girls Planet.
The Connect Mission begins now.
[Connect Mission]
[They will start the first mission
to gain the benefit.]
[I was very nervous,
but we practiced enough.]
[I can do it.]
I will announce the first battle team
for the Connect Mission, the mission
where the story of amazing girls starts.
[Nervous]
"YES or YES" by Twice.
["YES or YES" by TWICE]
"YES or YES" Team. Very interesting.
I hope they do a good job.
Cute.
[Team 1 versus Team 2]
They look refreshing.
["YES or YES" Team 1 introduction]
One, two, three.
-We didn't know what to pick
-So we got a bit of everything.
-Singing,
-dance,
-talent,
-and energy!
-Are you ready to win?
-Yes!
We are, "Can't Help But Look"!
[Everyone is pleased by
their bright and energetic introduction.]
Yes!
That was very cute.
I like that.
"YES or YES" Team 2.
Please introduce yourselves.
["YES or YES" Team 2 continues
to introduce their team.]
We're here to charge
your happy energy. We are...
♫ Bar ♫
We are "Energy Bars"! Yum-yum!
[Both teams' introductions are
as cheerful as their song.]
That's cute.
Cute.
Can't Help But Look team,
how did you practice
so we couldn't help but look at you?
First, we prepared a surprise.
[I see.]
You may look forward to it.
[Anticipating]
You've prepared a surprise.
I'm curious.
[Laughing]
Good.
This is pretty addicting.
[Envious]
You're good.
Let's hear a word of determination
from the two teams.
I believe that
we will do a good job for sure
as long as we perform
like when we practiced.
We'll do our best.
Energy Bars?
[What?]
I'll enjoy it.
[Masters excited
by the unexpected provocation.]
[What a surprise.]
You're good.
[Tilting her head]
Team 2.
Oh, gosh.
Against this,
[What's Team 2's resolution]
[after Team 1's provocation?]
-say a word of determination.
-Gosh.
Their eyes have changed.
We've practiced hard too,
so with our happy energy,
we will defeat Team 1.
[Kishida Ririka's witty resolution]
Nice.
Masters, it's time for you
to ask questions.
-Ji Won.
-Yes.
Do Ah is in charge of the killer verse
for Team 2,
and she received better comments
during the interim evaluation.
How have you practiced since then?
Well...
[Interim Evaluation]
[Interim evaluation, "YES or YES" Team 1]
Team 1.
Who led the practice?
Ji Won took charge of directions
in the choreography,
Chae Hyun led the choreography.
and I led the diction and singing.
[K Group led Team 1.]
So those from K Group led the team.
Right.
Let us watch it.
-Okay.
[Team 1's "YES or YES" begins
with Ji Won's killer verse.]
♫ Hey, boy ♫
♫ Look ♫
♫ I'm going to make this simple for you ♫
♫ Yes or yes ♫
[Team 1 is struggling
while performing "YES or YES".]
♫ Choose one already, yes or yes ♫
♫ Your eyes make me selfish ♫
[As the performance goes on,]
[the masters look grimmer.]
♫ One more, yes or yes ♫
[What do the masters think of it?]
I'm confused about what I've just watched.
If some people weren't good enough,
you needed to encourage them
to practice more.
This is an exciting and cheerful song.
But it felt like you were doing homework.
Ji Won didn't stand out
when she did the killer verse.
It's the beginning of the song.
This song is all about the energy.
[We weren't used to performing the song.]
So we just couldn't be energetic.
[I kept thinking]
[that we needed to practice more.]
[Closing her mouth tightly]
Team 2, you're up.
[Next up is an interim evaluation
for "YES or YES" Team 2.]
-Okay.
[Team 2 does a chant before they begin.]
Let's do the battle cry.
Right, something like that is needed.
Two, three.
-Let's enjoy, yes or yes!
♫ Hey, boy, look ♫
[Team 2's performance
begins with Kim Do Ah's killer verse.]
♫ I'm going to make this simple for you ♫
[Watching]
♫ You've got two choices ♫
♫ Come on and tell me yes ♫
♫ You just have to make a choice ♫
♫ You don't even have to think ♫
♫ It's simple, Y-E-S, hey ♫
[The masters look different
from Team 1's performance.]
[They finish the song with smiles.]
In general, Team 2 was more energetic
than Team 1.
You guys made it yours
and grabbed attention.
The energy felt different from the start.
How would you give the bright energy
to the performance?
First off,
we've got to practice enough
to be able to do it
even with our eyes closed.
I thought we needed to be more in sync.
[Practice begins properly
after the interim evaluation.]
One, two, three, four.
Slowly from the start.
Let's do it slowly from the start.
Dance big. Again.
Let's go again.
[Team 1's practice progresses quickly]
Again.
[as Kim Hye Rim and Huh Ji Won
from K Group lead the session.]
Again.
Let's do this part once again.
One more time.
Let's do it one more time.
[I felt like we were doing
only as we were told.]
[I don't want to fake the bright energy.]
[I want to enjoy performing on the stage.]
Our personality itself
isn't assertive.
A lot of those from J Group are timid.
[Okuma Sumomo tears up in the end.]
I'm confused.
I feel like I'm only causing harm.
No, you aren't.
You aren't causing harm.
It's always my mistake
that stops us in the middle.
Don't blame yourself.
It's tough because we don't have
much time to practice alone.
I bet everyone wants
to practice properly now.
I guess.
[Chae Hyun came after
hearing J Group's conversation.]
It's okay.
I feel a little frustrated.
Was it a little too fast
when we practiced together?
A bit.
Fast?
I'm sorry.
[She's sorry for not being able
to consider J Group's feelings.]
Sorry it was too fast.
They kept being led.
We felt sorry about it too.
Maybe that's why they lost confidence.
Hey.
I think we need time to talk.
Okay.
We may work hard
on details and dance moves,
but if we aren't close,
we can't make a good performance.
We'll try harder to be closer
with each other.
[A bond?]
Closer?
-Like this.
-One.
[It means we're one!]
Thank you.
Being able to talk with the teammates
made me feel a little better.
["YES or YES" Team 1's bond
became stronger after the talk.]
Close.
Sumomo reminds me of my past.
[When I first came to Korea,
I had language problems.]
[I didn't understand
what people were talking.]
There are non-Korean members in my group.
[Cherry Bullet]
[They probably felt similar]
[when they first came to Korea.]
[She reminded me of them.]
[And I was sorry
that I couldn't be more caring.]
[I wanted to get closer with her.]
[I want to make a good performance
with pleasure.]
We're doing great.
-We just need to do as we practiced.
-Okay.
-I trust you.
-I love you.
-I love you too.
Quite a lot of them lacked confidence.
Right.
I wonder how much they improved.
-Go for it.
-You can do it.
-Good luck.
[Everyone is cheering for
the first Connect mission performance!]
-You can do it.
-Let's go.
[Deep breathing]
Good luck.
Ji Won has to start it off well.
Gosh.
[Nervous]
[What would Team 1's "YES or YES"
look like?]
♫ Hey, guardians, look ♫
♫ I'm going to make this simple for you ♫
♫ You've got two choices ♫
["YES or YES" by TWICE]
♫ Hey, guardians, look ♫
♫ I'm going to make this simple for you ♫
♫ You've got two choices, yes or yes ♫
[Surprised]
Let's go!
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
♫ Choose one already, yes or yes ♫
♫ Was I this selfish? ♫
♫ I've never wanted ♫
-Aren't they good?
-Yes.
I like their energy.
♫ Everyone gets surprised ♫
♫ By my shamelessness ♫
♫ Come on and tell me yes ♫
♫ My scenario has become
bolder than I thought ♫
♫ This plan is perfect and satisfying ♫
-♫ Satisfying ♫
-♫ I don't care ♫
♫ Whatever people say ♫
♫ You better tell me yes ♫
♫ My mind is set, yes ♫
♫ Now it's your turn to answer ♫
♫ I'll give you options
to make it easier ♫
♫ You just have to make a choice ♫
-♫ You don't even have to think ♫
-She's cute!
♫ I don't know what you'll choose,
so I got you two choices ♫
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
♫ I don't know how you feel,
so I got you two choices ♫
-Hye Rim's good!
-♫ Choose one already, yes or yes ♫
-♫ I don't want a no ♫
-♫ It's me or us ♫
♫ I respect your choice ♫
♫ But don't say no ♫
♫ Only one option,
and it's up to you ♫
♫ It's all up to you ♫
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
-That's it!
-♫ Your eyes make me selfish ♫
♫ They meet my curiosity for you ♫
-♫ It burns up ♫
-♫ Up ♫
-♫ It's burning ♫
-♫ Burning ♫
♫ My heart, burn, burn, burn ♫
♫ You better hurry up ♫
♫ Let me make this easy for you ♫
♫ Whatever you choose
will end up with me ♫
♫ It may be a little flustering,
it may be unreasonable ♫
♫ But you will never regret it ♫
♫ It's simple, Y-E-S, hey ♫
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
♫ Choose one already, yes or yes ♫
♫ One more, yes or yes or yes ♫
♫ Choose however you'd like ♫
♫ I don't know what you'll choose,
so I got you two choices ♫
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
♫ I don't know how you feel,
so I got you two choices ♫
-♫ I got you two choices ♫
-She's good!
♫ Yes or yes ♫
♫ I don't want a no ♫
♫ It's me or us ♫
♫ I respect your choice ♫
♫ But don't say no ♫
♫ Only one option,
and it's up to you ♫
-♫ It's all up to you ♫
-♫ Up to you ♫
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
[Cell:
Ma Yu Ling, Kim Hye Rim, Okuma Sumomo]
Li Yiman, Kim Chae Hyun, Kuwahara Ayana]
[Cell:
Chia Yi, Huh Ji Won, Yamauchi Moana]
They're so cute!
[You can watch the full performance
on YouTube and Naver TV after the show.]
They're so pretty!
[Exclaiming]
-They did well!
-Yes!
It makes me feel happy.
It made me feel so good.
-Yes.
-They did so great.
I wonder how the masters saw it.
As soon as it finished, I said, "Yes!"
It made me feel so good.
Singing, focus, and choreography.
They even made eye contact
with each other when they moved around.
[Watching that made me feel good.]
[They stood together
to present the performance.]
We could see your teamwork through it.
I received so much energy from it.
I'm worried about Energy Bars.
Good luck.
Energy Bars?
Did she say she's worried about us?
Energy up!
[It's okay.]
[I think they did well.]
I feel a little bit pressured.
[We really have to do our best.]
They changed
-since the interim evaluation.
-Completely.
Like your team name says...
-They're good.
-I want to keep watching you.
-Thank you.
You did great!
[It was the best.]
Thank you.
[Behind the stage after the performance,]
Careful.
Be careful.
[they burst into tears
they've been holding back.]
Good job.
You did so well.
-Good job.
-I love you.
[Team 1 congratulates
and consoles each other.]
-I really love you.
-You all did a good job.
It was so fun.
[We performed well
thanks to our practices.]
[It made me so proud.]
Team 2 must be nervous now.
Because Team 1 did so well.
Team 2 must have heard
how we evaluated them.
-Yes.
I think it'll drive Do Ah even more.
-She'll give it her all.
-Definitely.
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
We're a team of talented girls
and we can push it up to 200 percent.
[I believe we have a good chance
of winning.]
Let's all pour everything out today.
-Okay.
-We can do it.
Let's enjoy it! "YES or YES"!
They don't look nervous at all.
They're always confident.
Full of confidence.
I hope Se In doesn't make any mistakes.
She made several mistakes
during the interim evaluation.
[Worried]
[Connect mission interim evaluation]
Let's see what Team 2 has prepared.
-Okay.
[How did "YES or YES" Team 2's
interim evaluation go?]
♫ I respect your choice ♫
♫ But don't say no ♫
♫ Only one option,
and it's up to you ♫
[The main vocalist Kim Se In keeps
making mistakes.]
Se In...
Se In keeps getting her lyrics
or moves wrong.
You can't do both
at the same time, right?
I should've gone in front of Ririka,
but I couldn't, so I made a mistake.
Did you sing in a style
that fits this song?
Zi Yin said I sound like
I'm singing a children's song.
-Like what?
-Like a children's song.
Like a children's song?
She asked me to sing
in a more mature style.
Se In, stop making excuses.
-Okay.
-Don't blame others.
You made the mistake. Don't blame others.
It's not because someone did
or said something.
I want you to get a grip
and do it properly.
[Who are you the most concerned about?]
Se In.
Se In couldn't concentrate at all today.
Me.
[Embarrassed]
I'm really forgetful.
I have a question. I'll ask on the side.
[It's a secret.]
When are we getting our snacks?
Se In
only does things her way.
[Maybe it's because she's young.]
[She can never concentrate.]
[Her head is in the clouds.]
[She always gets the same things wrong.]
[She's always zoned out during practice.]
[She would just stand there.]
[She blanks out all the time.]
I don't know what to do about this.
I'm still thinking.
[As a leader]
Should I scold her?
[Kim Se In's sleeping
when everyone else is practicing.]
Se In, don't fall asleep.
[She advises Se In.]
[As Se In keeps making
a choreographic mistake,]
Stay focused! I'm going to scold you.
[she even scolds her.]
I tend to memorize the moves fast,
but I couldn't put everything
into my head.
[Kim Se In needs snacks.]
I feel overloaded.
It's mealtime soon.
Let's go eat, guys.
[She goes for the food
faster than anyone.]
We did better. It's fine.
No.
What is this?
[The masters graded the teams
after the interim evaluation.]
[The best and the worst cells
are announced.]
[Connect mission
interim evaluation record]
"YES or YES".
[Though they practiced together,
it's a bitter sweet moment.]
We did it!
[Kim Do Ah, Xu Zi Yin, Arai Risako,
"YES or YES" Best Cell.]
That's incredible.
What does that mean? Tell me.
What does that mean?
The nine of us, the nine from that team.
And these cells did the best.
The cells that did the worst...
[Kim Se In, Wen Zhe, and Okazaki Momoko
are in the worst cell.]
The cells that did the worst...
Oh, is that it?
But guys, if we look at it positively,
the top-ranking cell is in our team.
That cell can lead us. We have a leader.
[Wen Zhe's shocked
to be in the worst cell.]
Eating is the most important.
[I'm so worried.]
Do you people want to get eliminated?
Do you want to go home?
I don't want to go home.
Se In, I told you yesterday.
You have to smile as the main vocalist.
You didn't do that just now.
The thing is, we don't focus enough!
Are we going to be like this on stage?
We must beat them no matter what.
Please give it your best. I mean it.
Please do your best.
[She advises the teammates
who don't practice enough.]
[The three of us are a team.]
[Kim Se In, Wen Zhe, Okazaki Momoko]
Se In needs to stop fooling around,
and I'll really work hard.
We need to move up.
We can't get eliminated.
We can't.
[How will "YES or YES" Team 2 do?]
In 3, 2...
["YES or YES" by TWICE]
♫ Hey, boy, look ♫
♫ I'm going to make this simple for you ♫
♫ You've got two choices ♫
♫ Yes or yes ♫
♫ Energy up ♫
[Energy up!]
They're cute.
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
♫ Choose one already, yes or yes ♫
♫ Was I this selfish? ♫
♫ I've never wanted something
this badly before ♫
♫ Before ♫
- ♫ Everyone gets surprised ♫
- ♫ Surprised ♫
♫ By my shamelessness ♫
-She's good.
-♫ Come on and tell me yes ♫
♫ My scenario has become
bolder than I thought ♫
♫ This plan is perfect and satisfying ♫
-♫ Satisfying ♫
-♫ I don't care ♫
♫ Whatever people say ♫
♫ You better tell me yes ♫
♫ My mind is set, yes ♫
♫ Now it's your turn to answer ♫
♫ If it's hard, I'll give you choices ♫
♫ So you don't even have to think ♫
♫ I don't know what you'll choose,
so I got you two choices ♫
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
♫ I don't know what you'll choose,
so I got you two choices ♫
♫ Choose one already, yes or yes ♫
-♫ Don't say no ♫
-♫ Me or us ♫
-♫ I'll respect your choice ♫
-♫ I won't accept no ♫
♫ There's only one choice,
and you can choose as you want ♫
♫ It's all up to you ♫
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
♫ Your eyes make me selfish ♫
♫ They meet my curiosity for you ♫
-♫ It burns up ♫
-♫ Up ♫
-♫ It's burning ♫
-♫ Burning ♫
♫ My heart, burn, burn, burn ♫
♫ You better hurry up ♫
♫ Let me make this easy for you ♫
♫ Whatever you choose
will end up with me ♫
♫ It may be a little flustering,
it may be unreasonable ♫
♫ But you will never regret it ♫
♫ It's simple, Y-E-S, hey ♫
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
♫ Choose one already, yes or yes ♫
♫ One more, yes or yes or yes ♫
♫ Choose however you'd like ♫
♫ I don't know what you'll choose,
so I got you two choices ♫
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
♫ I don't know what you'll choose,
so I got you two choices ♫
♫ Choose one already, yes or yes ♫
-♫ Don't say no ♫
-♫ Me or us ♫
-♫ I'll respect your choice ♫
-♫ I won't accept no ♫
♫ There's only one choice,
and you can choose as you want ♫
-♫ It's all up to you ♫
♫ Choose one already, yes or yes ♫
Nice.
[Cell: Wen Zhe, Kim Se In, Okazaki Momoko]
[Cell: Leung Cheuk Ying,
Lee Chae Yun, Kishida Ririka]
[Cell: Xu Zi Yin, Kim Do Ah, Arai Risako]
So cute.
[You can watch the full performance
on YouTube and Naver TV after the show.]
-Didn't they do a good job?
-Yes, they did.
-How cool.
-It's so hard.
Wen Zhe did a good job too.
She improved so much.
It's hard.
[How will the master evaluate
"YES or YES" Team 2?]
Masters, how did you like
"YES or YES" Team 2's performance?
They did well.
-Thank you.
This is bad. What do I do?
I want to give a hand to Ririka.
With such a clear voice,
she performed stably
from the start to the end.
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
[Kishida Ririka easily pulled off
her first vocalist part.]
♫ Choose one already ♫
Good job, Ririka.
-Thank you.
-Good job.
How cute.
-Don't cry.
-Okay.
[Teary]
So cute.
It was great,
but one thing bothered me. Se In.
You were always a bit too fast.
You were fast throughout.
That bothered me a little.
Wen Zhe.
[Nervous]
I think you showed an example
of how one can improve so much.
I want to thank you for that.
Good job.
Thank you.
To be honest, I had this much hope.
I thought we had a chance
because that was one
of our best performances.
It makes me happy to see them do well.
They did well.
-It feels good, doesn't it?
-Yes.
It's hard.
It's time for the masters to decide.
Masters, please discuss
and pick the winning team.
It's hard.
[The masters discuss the performance
of "YES or YES".]
-Team 2 did really well.
-Right.
-Leung Cheuk Ying sounded so stable too.
Not to mention Xu Zi Yin.
Do Ah's eyes were no joke.
♫ Yes or yes ♫
She can't keep her talent hidden.
But Team 1's lead vocalist did better.
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
[The two main vocalists, Hye Rim and Se In
showed different charms.]
♫ Choose between the two, yes or yes ♫
As the lead vocalist,
Se In didn't look like
-she knew what she was doing.
-Right.
She couldn't fulfill the role.
But she still sang well.
You're right, she did quite well.
For me, Team 1 performed
so stably in general
that I didn't feel nervous at all.
I really can't choose.
I made up my mind.
[After the discussion, they judge
by themselves and cast secret votes.]
We totaled up
the votes for the winning team.
Good work.
Both teams did well.
They're crying already.
Oh, gosh.
Both teams received good comments
from the masters.
so they must be even more nervous.
Now,
I will announce the winning team
who will take the benefit.
Between the two "YES or YES" teams,
the winning team chosen
by the masters is...
[I can't guess who'll win.]
[Please...]
[I really want to win.]
The winning team is...
[The masters also get nervous
as they don't know about the result.]
[Which team will take the benefit
of double ballots?]
Team 1.
["YES or YES" Team 1 wins.]
[Team 1 wins in the Connect mission.]
Gosh.
They're crying.
They're cute.
Team 2 did a good job too.
Let's hear how Team 1 feels.
How do you feel?
Well... First of all, I want to tell
my dear team that they did so well.
I also want to thank the masters
for liking our performance.
Good work.
We'll do our best. Thank you!
Unfortunately, Team 2 ended up losing
despite the good reviews.
How do you feel?
Our team went through so much
and did well.
We did our best
and put up a great performance.
I also want
to thank Team 1.
We practiced together
and cheered each other on.
We spent good times.
Thank you.
Good job.
Both teams did great.
Good work.
What a shame. Really.
[Sad]
[It wasn't just about winning.]
[We were moved]
[to have accomplished it.]
Gosh.
[I'm a little disappointed.]
[Actually, it was
an important opportunity.]
Honestly, I was desperate to win.
[If we had practiced without sleeping,]
[the result may have been different.]
I'm sorry.
Here's the next Connect Mission match.
"How You Like That"
by BLACKPINK.
["How You LIke That" by BLACKPINK,
Team 1 versus Team 2]
"How You Like That" is
an intense hip hop song
about never giving up and flying high.
I can't wait to see how they do.
"How You Like That" teams, please come up.
-Go.
-Let's go.
[Dignified]
Both teams were good during the rehearsal.
These two will be the hardest to decide.
-I can't pick one.
-Right.
Team 1 of "How You Like That."
Please introduce yourselves.
Two, three.
♫ Look at you, now look at me, huh? ♫
-Huh?
They're so cute.
We're here to capture the hearts of
Plant Guardians.
-We're Plan Girls!
So cute.
[Very busy]
They must've come up with an arrangement.
What did they prepare?
-Hello, we're...
[Confused]
-Wait.
-Poor Rinka. Look at her legs.
We're hidden gems.
-Hidden Cards!
What is this?
Look at Rinka's legs.
[Joo Hee's worried of Ando Rinka's legs.]
Oh, dear.
Masters, please ask your questions.
Okay. Ji A.
-For the Planet Demo Stage,
-Yes.
you and Young Eun were a team
but now you're rivals.
[Now an enemy]
Is there anything you think
you're better at than her?
[Speechless at the sudden attack]
-Be honest.
-Yes?
Who's the better dancer?
I...
I think it's me.
Do you agree, Ji A?
[Curious and nervous]
I'm also confident I can show neat moves.
[Shy]
[It means she won't lose.]
[They showed cute chemistry
at Planet Search.]
[But now they met as a rival.]
I'm better than Young Eun
[That's not good.]
at rapping.
At rapping.
[She's stepping out.]
♫ Look at you, now look at me ♫
[Getting the drop]
[Being shy again]
Team 1's members are more competent
if you look at them individually.
There are more TOP9 members too.
But the teamwork...
Team 2 had great teamwork.
Seung Eun really kept the team together.
One, two, three.
[Leader Sim Seung Eun is leading
the team to practice "How You Like That."]
Boom. Ha-how you like. Wave.
Like this. Look straight.
[She's making it easy to understand with
customized and kind explanation.]
Straight. Diagonal.
[Seung Eun taught us the moves,]
one by one.
[She made it easy for us,
so we were able to learn very quickly.]
We got the best leader.
♫ Looking into your eyes ♫
[Team 1 is looking at Team 2.]
Rather than having someone lead us...
We have 4 TOP9 members,
[and all of them are great dancers.]
[So we memorized the moves individually]
then came together to practice.
That's how we did it.
Yeon Gyung here. Who stands here?
[After individual practice, leader
Choi Yu Jin leads for group practice.]
-Xia Yan.
-Where's May?
-She comes in later.
Okay.
May can do her thing by herself.
Who's the vocalist 2?
[Who's vocal two?]
-You.
-Oh, it's me.
[Oh! I forgot!]
What do we do?
[The practice seemed smooth.]
[Yu Jin's leading but she's having]
[a hard time since she's never done it.]
[So I helped her with
the detailed choreography.]
[Xiao Ting in my cell]
[helped lead the dance.]
[And... Wow.]
It feels like I'm freeloading.
I think I am.
I definitely am.
Thank you.
Team 2, did you practice a lot?
[D-day mid-check, starting with
Team 2, "How You Like That"]
-Yes.
You said it yourselves
that you practiced a lot, right?
Show us.
[Suddenly changing]
♫ I proudly fell to the ground ♫
♫ Looking into your eyes,
I kiss you goodbye ♫
[Team 2 is constantly surprising
the Masters.]
♫ What's up, I'm right back ♫
♫ Cock back the trigger ♫
♫ Don't like me? ♫
♫ Then tell me how you like that ♫
I got chills.
♫ Look at you, now look at me ♫
-♫ Shine like the stars ♫
-So good.
[What are they?]
The teamwork was great.
[Speechless]
They really are hidden cards.
[Joo Hee gives a great compliment.]
They're good.
Team 1 should be on your toes.
Ji A was so...
She was...
She transformed when the music started.
[Changing to a predator's gaze in beat]
You know who surprised me?
Zhou Xin Yu. I was surprised.
Thank you.
I've never seen you like that before.
So she can be fierce.
And Da Yeon...
She showed us why she got first place.
Thank you.
We kept you out of TOP9 on purpose.
Okay.
You'd get there regardless.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
You were hurt by it.
[Kim Da Yeon,
the first place in K Group, tears up.]
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
[K Group members start to cry too.]
Everyone's crying.
Don't cry.
Why?
No, it's okay.
Actually...
At the Demo Stage,
K Group's first place was the only one
who didn't get in TOP9.
The TOP9 members selected by Masters.
Xiao Ting from C Group.
[During the Planet TOP9 selection,]
[the first of C Group, Shen Xiao Ting
and J Group, Ezaki Hikaru were called.]
and Ezaki Hikaru from J Group.
[The first of K Group was never called.]
I felt so much pressure from it
so what you said touched me.
You're the one who shows the most stable
singing skills and dancing skills
in this team.
- You did great.
- Thank you.
[That was a load off.]
That refueled my confidence.
I'll do my best.
[Mid-check for Team 1 is coming next
for "How You Like That"]
They're like the Avengers.
There are four purples.
-That means half of TOP9 is in this team.
-Right.
I can't wait.
[How would Team 1 Avengers
perform "How You Like That"?]
♫ Plan Girls in your area ♫
♫ Smiling while I kiss you goodbye ♫
♫ One, two, three ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
[Shen Xiao Ting made a timing mistake.]
♫ Your girl need it all and ♫
[Team 1's main rapper, Cai Bing.]
♫ Don't go, you can't help it ♫
[They didn't look ready.]
[Master Sunmi can't bring it up easily.]
[Team Avengers with high expectations
made a lot of mistakes.]
I'm not sure if this is really
what four members of TOP9
can put together.
[Things suddenly got solemnized
by harsh criticism.]
Shen Xiao Ting.
It was the killer part.
♫ How you like that? ♫
[Shen Xiao Ting's hook was
lacking energy.]
It's all or nothing. You need to look like
you're really going to kill this part.
It had to be like this.
But it didn't feel like that.
Cai Bing.
Why did you become the main rapper?
♫ Your girl need it all and ♫
[Cai Bing made mistakes
in both beat and lyrics.]
You are ahead of the beat all the time.
You were off the beat every time.
Yesterday was my first day of practice.
But Xia Yan was so on point.
[Rapper 1 part]
♫ What's up, I'm right back ♫
[Xia Yan, on the other hand,
performed her part well.]
♫ Cock back the trigger ♫
If you go down as the main rapper,
you'll take the team with you.
[Before the day of the performance,]
I never once heard her rap.
[Everyone voted for me
to be the main rapper.]
I feel I've let everyone down.
I felt so awful.
[Cai Bing's cell is
selected as lowest rank.]
[Cai Bing]
[I felt so guilty to my cell group mates.]
[Late at night, before heading home,]
[Cai Bing approaches the staff.]
Can I stay and practice?
It's okay.
-Why?
-Why are you crying?
Because of me...
[Cai Bing is sorry as she thinks
she burdened everyone.]
♫ Your girl need it all
and that's a hundred ♫
[Cai Bing is practicing
the main rapper part repeatedly.]
♫ Hundred out of hundred ♫
[She continues to practice
until late night.]
♫ Hundred out of hundred,
I want my share ♫
[If I don't give it my all,
I'll let my team down.]
[Boom, boom. One.]
[After more practice,
it's the next day's practice again.]
Stop.
[Cai Bing dances together with her
team after her individual practice.]
♫ How you like that? ♫
[Cai Bing's moves look
more organized in perfect beat.]
Okay.
It feels great that we're in sync now.
Right.
Cai Bing is touched
that you complimented her.
You did great.
Thank you.
[Thank you.]
Don't cry.
Our main rapper.
You really are.
[I'm confident now.]
[Rehearsal starts now. Stand by.]
[Connect Mission Rehearsal]
Which one's better? Team 1 or 2?
I think Team 2 is.
Because Cai Bing was too ahead
of her beat.
Maybe she's fixed it.
♫ Your girl need it all
and that's a hundred ♫
♫ Hundred out of hundred,
I want my share ♫
She's good.
♫ I feel bad, but I can't help it ♫
Plan Girls!
["How You Like That" Team 1,
the rehearsal is going smooth.]
They've improved so much
since the interim evaluation.
I don't have anything to comment on.
Good work, girls.
[We might actually win.]
♫ I proudly fell to the ground ♫
["How You Like That" Team 2 starts
their rehearsal.]
♫ Your girl need it all
and that's a hundred ♫
They're good too.
[The rehearsal goes on smoothly.]
Great.
[Both teams did so well.]
[I can't choose.]
They're good.
[My team and I came here]
to show 100 percent of our abilities.
We will not lose.
We worked hard,
so we'll put on a great show.
We can do it.
This is going to be tough to choose.
[He's expecting a neck and neck match.]
Really?
It'll really depend on
who does better live.
-Is it up to their condition?
-Yes.
[It now depends...]
This is hard.
I'll be looking for which of them
really makes the song their own.
[What will "How You Like That" Team 2's
performance be like?]
["How You Like That" by BLACKPINK]
Look at her eyes.
♫ Hidden Cards in your area ♫
♫ I proudly fell to the ground ♫
Goodness.
♫ Through the ground deep under ♫
-Oh, dear.
-♫ To hold ♫
♫ On to your clothes ♫
♫ I reach above to you ♫
♫ I'm back in this darkness,
light up the sky ♫
♫ Looking into your eyes,
I kiss you goodbye ♫
♫ Laugh all you want,
it serves me right ♫
♫ Now, one, two, three ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
[Cheering]
Good.
♫ You're going to like that ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
♫ How you like that ♫
♫ Now look at you, now look at me ♫
-♫ Look at you, now look at me ♫
-So cool.
♫ Now look at you, now look at me ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
♫ Your girl need it all
and that's a hundred ♫
-Great!
-Ji A!
Ji A!
♫ Hundred out of hundred,
I want my share ♫
♫ Karma come and get some ♫
♫ You feel bad, but you can't help it ♫
♫ What's up, I'm right back ♫
♫ Cock back the hammer ♫
♫ Plain Jane get hijacked ♫
♫ Don't like me?
Then tell me how you like that? ♫
-Da Yeon.
-♫ In this darkness ♫
♫ Shine like the stars ♫
♫ Smiling while I kiss you goodbye ♫
[Why is she so fast?]
That was way too fast.
♫ Laugh all you want,
it serves me right ♫
♫ Now, one, two, three ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
♫ You're going to like that ♫
Oh, no.
♫ How you like that? ♫
♫ Now look at you, now look at me ♫
♫ I fell to the ground without my wings ♫
♫ I was trapped in the darkness ♫
-Oh, dear.
-♫ You should've finished me then ♫
♫ Look up in the sky,
it's a bird, it's a plane ♫
We have to give our all here. This part.
[We also have to do
this choreography fiercely.]
♫ Bring out your boss ♫
♫ Hidden Cards ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
♫ You're going to like that ♫
[Team 2's performance captivated
everyone's ears and eyes.]
-Ji A was awesome.
-She really was.
[She agrees.]
[Cell: Zhou Xin Yu, Yoon Ji A, Shima Moka]
[Cell: Wu Tammy, Kim Da Yeon, Sakurai Miu]
[Cell: Chien Tzu Ling, Ando Rinka,
Sim Seung Eun]
[You can watch the full performance
on YouTube and Naver TV after the show.]
Gosh. What was that?
[The masters don't look happy.]
-Why aren't they like before?
-It's different, right?
I think they did better at the rehearsal.
I'm very disappointed with the vocalists.
Why did she make a mistake?
[She really feels bad.]
What a shame.
Will you tell us how it was, Masters?
[What will the masters say
about the performance?]
You're all too ahead of the beat.
During the interim evaluation,
I told you to listen to the instruments.
There's the bass sound
in "How You Like That"
[During the interim evaluation
of the Connect Mission]
which sounds like a drum.
Practice your moves to it.
It'll be easier that way.
When you lost the beat in the beginning,
the rest also fell apart.
♫ I proudly fell to the ground ♫
[Sim Seung Eun started fast
from the first note.]
♫ I'm back in this darkness,
light up the sky ♫
[The beat also became faster
when Zhou Xin Yu started next.]
That was way too fast.
It was disappointing.
Oh, no.
Did you get your moves wrong?
Or did you bump into each other,
Zhou Xin Yu and Da Yeon?
No, we didn't bump into each other.
♫ How you like that? ♫
[Zhou Xin Yu even made
a choreography mistake.]
Why did she make a mistake?
Zhou Xin Yu got too nervous.
She could've done better.
And Yoon Ji A.
You're so cool.
Thank you.
You were so cool. Great job.
[Team 2 failed to perform
beyond expectations.]
-You did well. But I'm just disappointed.
-Right.
Because I know you could've done better.
Maybe because you got nervous...
But that also counts as your abilities.
[It's also skills not to make mistakes.]
And this was the worst you did so far.
["How You Like That" Team 2 performance.]
[I didn't know what to think.]
[I was so upset
and couldn't stop blaming myself.]
["How You Like That" Team 2's
performance ended with regret.]
I really liked Team 2. That's too bad.
Me too.
I have high hopes for Team 1
[She's looking forward to Team 1
who will appear next.]
-because some of them already debuted.
-That's right.
-Four from TOP9 are on that team.
-Right.
[There are 4 Planet TOP9s
and debuted girls in Team 1.]
They have to do a good job.
We can do this.
Let's just show them
what we've been doing.
-Take it easy.
-Relax.
-Let's go have some fun.
-Let's enjoy it.
[Team 1 is heading to the stage
amid growing tension.]
Will they survive or be eliminated?
Team 1 of "How You Like That"
will start now.
["How You Like That" by BLACKPINK]
♫ Plan Girls in your area ♫
Oh, no. She made a mistake.
-♫ I proudly fell to the ground ♫
-That's it.
♫ Through the ground deep under ♫
♫ To hold on to your clothes ♫
♫ I reach above to you ♫
♫ I'm back in this darkness,
light up the sky ♫
♫ Looking into your eyes,
I kiss you goodbye ♫
♫ Laugh all you want,
it serves me right ♫
♫ Now, one, two, three ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
♫ You're going to like that ♫
That's right.
♫ How you like that ♫
♫ Now look at you, now look at me ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
♫ Your girl need it all
and that's a hundred ♫
♫ Hundred out of hundred,
I want my share ♫
♫ You feel bad, but you can't help it ♫
♫ What's up, I'm right back,
cock back the hammer ♫
♫ Plain Jane get hijacked,
don't like me?♫
♫ Cock back the hammer ♫
♫ Plain Jane get hijacked ♫
♫ Don't like me?
Then tell me how you like that? ♫
♫ In this darkness,
shine like the stars ♫
♫ Smiling while I kiss you goodbye ♫
♫ Laugh all you want,
it serves me right ♫
♫ Now, one, two, three ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
Why won't she run over?
♫ You're going to like that ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
♫ How you like that ♫
♫ Now look at you, now look at me ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
-♫ Now look at you, now look at me ♫
-Go, Yeon Gyung.
♫ How you like that? ♫
♫ I fell to the ground without my wings ♫
♫ I was trapped in the darkness ♫
♫ You should've finished me then ♫
♫ Look up in the sky ♫
-♫ It's a bird, it's a plane ♫
-Go, girls.
♫ Bring out your boss ♫
♫ Plan Girls ♫
♫ How you like that? ♫
♫ You're going to like that ♫
[Team 1's performance made people
exclaim until the end.]
[Cell:
Xia Yan, Lee Yeon Gyung, Inaba Vivienne]
[Cell: Cai Bing, Choi Yu Jin, May]
[Cell: Shen Xiao Ting, Seo Young Eun,
Kawaguchi Yurina]
[You can watch the full version
on YouTube and NAVER TV after the show.]
Gosh...
Now, "How You Like That"...
They could've done better.
Too bad.
[It's a pity.]
Team 1's "How You Like That" is also over.
Thank you very much.
Vivienne and Yurina.
[Inaba Vivienne, Kawaguchi Yurina]
Participants with smaller parts
really pulled through in their roles.
That made the performance even fuller.
My only disappointment
is that you did much better
at the rehearsal.
[Team 1 as well]
Shen Xiao Ting.
I told you that you need energy
to attention for the killer verse, right?
[Team 1's performance]
♫ Now, one, two, three ♫
[Interim evaluation]
[Shen Xiao Ting doesn't have enough energy
for the killer verse.]
♫ How you like that? ♫
It's the killer verse.
[The most important]
It's all or nothing. You need to look like
you're really going to kill this part.
It had to be like this.
But it didn't feel like that.
In fact, Cai Bing's charisma
she showed before you was overwhelming.
But
she did make a mistake.
[Cai Bing made a mistake as she
missed a beat as soon as it started.]
♫ Plan Girls in your area ♫
A mistake means
you didn't practice enough
and focus enough.
After Cai Bing made a mistake,
everybody broke down.
And you made it so obvious.
You lost focus.
Once the flow is lost in a performance,
it's really hard to get your viewers
focus back.
It is.
[Team 1 tried their best but made
mistakes in the actual performance.]
Oh, no.
[I'm so mad at myself
for making a mistake]
[I would normally never make.]
It's okay.
I'm so disappointed. Seriously.
[I made a huge mistake.]
[I feel so guilty.]
Masters, have you decided?
I can't. What do I do?
Please choose which team will win.
[It's time for the masters
to choose the winning team!]
Oh, this is crazy.
[As the masters know
the participants' efforts,]
[they're thinking more carefully.]
I sent mine.
The results are in.
I thought so hard about this.
[Team 1 and Team 2 get back
on stage to hear the result.]
Both teams worked hard.
Which team will win the benefit
[There's a huge benefit which their
survival depends on in the mission.]
that will decide their survival?
Here are the winners the Masters chose.
[Plan Girls versus Hidden Card,
which team did the masters choose?]
"How You Like That" by BLACKPINK.
Two teams performed to this song.
The winning team is...
[Team 1 versus Team 2,
which one will win?]
[I have no idea.]
[I was so sorry to my team.]
[I had the killer verse,]
[and I messed it up,
so I felt really bad.]
[I hoped they'd see how desperate we are.]
The winning team is...
[Which is the winning team?]
[Team 1 Plan Girls
versus Team 2 Hidden Card]
Team 1.
["How You Like That" Team 1 wins.]
Really?
[Win for "How You Like That" Team 1]
Congratulations, Team 1.
Don't cry.
I'm not crying.
They keep making me tear up.
[Team 1 sheds tears out of relief
after the announcement.]
Don't cry.
Please tell us how you feel.
If it weren't for these girls...
It would've been so hard. I'm sorry.
We could've done better,
but we definitely showed
some improvements.
Thank you.
-You did a great job, Yu Jin.
-Don't cry.
Yu Jin must've gone through a lot.
And...
Unfortunately...
You lost, sadly,
but you did your best
for your performance.
Let us hear how Team 2 feels.
We lost, but I believe Planet Guardians
will now see that we're hidden gems.
And we will work hard
to show what we're really capable of.
[From now on]
We all did a great job.
Don't cry. We did well.
Thank you.
She's a great leader.
Both teams, please leave the stage.
Thank you.
["How You Like That" teams
showed their best performance regardless.]
They could've done better.
You all worked hard.
We can do it, Hidden Cards.
-We can do it.
I made a mistake today,
but I will never make another mistake
and show you great performance.
Of course.
[You worked hard, Plan Girls.]
Our killer verse girl.
For this team battle,
the winners
get 3 times the votes in 24 hours.
Three times?
[Oh.]
Here are the three teams competing for
[Team "Mic Drop", "Pretty U", and
"The Eve" will get 3 times more votes.]
the benefit of three times the votes.
Mic, Mic Drop! Let's go!
[Refreshing and cute]
[Howling]
The first idol group
with four million album sales!
The idol group that went
beyond borders to take over the world.
"The Eve" by EXO.
They're known for a reason.
I doubt they'll make a mistake.
Right.
Their one downfall may be
that there didn't make any improvements
-since their last lesson.
-They're the same?
So I told them this at the rehearsal.
[Team "The Eve"'s rehearsal]
♫ Faint light spreads
and drives away the darkness ♫
[The masters are watching
their rehearsal carefully.]
[Frowning]
♫ The new morning ♫
[Their moves are not in sync.]
The part I made you practice at the end.
You're still not in sync.
You had three days.
Did you not practice at all?
Everyone has high hopes for your team.
You seem overly confident.
[Each of us is]
[talented individually.]
[But we're not really a team.]
[We didn't practice]
[as a group enough,]
[I was worried whether the Masters
would feel everyone's energy.]
[What will Team "The Eve" show after
the heavily criticized rehearsal?]
["The Eve" by EXO]
♫ Look at it closely ♫
♫ What's the situation? ♫
♫ Over your flustered eyes ♫
♫ The wall breaks down ♫
[Planet Guardians.]
[The first global voting]
[The first global voting begins now.]
[You can vote at UNIVERSE app, the
official platform of Girls Planet 999.]
[As Planet Guardians,
who can protect the girls' dreams,]
[you can vote once a day]
[You can vote at UNIVERSE app, the
official platform of Girls Planet 999.]
[on the official app.]
[It includes]
[1st, cell voting determines
their survival and elimination.]
[the cell votes that determines
who stays and who get eliminated]
[and individual votes that determines
who will be included in TOP9.]
[2nd, individual voting decides
TOP9 candidates.]
[First, access the voting screen]
[Vote]
[and select three cells you support]
[to vote for your cells.]
[Next Page]
[Then select three girls from each group]
[to select nine in total
for individual votes.]
[Press the final submission button]
[to complete your vote.]
[Voting complete]
[The results reflect 50 percent
from Korean votes]
[and 50 percent from global votes
outside of Korea.]
[The number of votes
will be converted to points.]
[Planet Guardians!]
[It's time for you to choose.]
[Whose dreams will you protect?]
[The 1st global voting
for Girls Planet 999]
[will close at 10 a.m. on August 28.]
[Connect Mission performances will
be revealed tomorrow]
[on YouTube and Naver TV
and vote on Universe app.]
[Vote on Universe app,
Girls Planet 999's official platform.]
I liked it better
during the interim evaluation.
Yes.
[Why is that?]
[What is the next performance
in this tense atmosphere?]
-♫ Too heavy, my hands aren't enough ♫
-Oh, gosh.
What are they doing?
♫ Did you see my bag? ♫
Let's stop.
Stop.
This is bad.
That was a mess.
Don't cry. It's not time to shed tears.
Wang Ya Le.
Do you hate being here?
If you'd do it like this, just go home.
[I want a twist.]
I got overwhelmed.
It was the best.
[What is the result of Team "E.B.S"?]
The winning team is...
That was so unexpected.
["The Eve" by EXO, "Mic Drop" by BTS,
"Pretty U" by SEVENTEEN]
[Girls who protect the earth]
[It's the snack bar.]
It's a cafeteria.
-My gosh.
-This.
[Getting everything they want]
Put them in a plastic bag, please.
-Girls, wait.
[Surprised]
Why don't you use an eco-friendly bag
instead of a plastic bag?
[The girls protect the planet camp
by using a tote bag.]
-Bye.
[The girls protect the earth.]
Always protect the Earth.