Unforgettable Love
EP20
Qiaoyan,
You've met that girl.
You just forgot her.
But I hope
you'll never think of her.
I hope you will always
regard her as a person appeared in your dream.
Let's go.
Yiyue,
I've asked for leave for Xiaobao.
Today, Xiaobao and I
will go and cheer for you.
Cheer for me?
How did you forget?
I made an appointment with our aunt.
You're going to play golf today
Right, play golf.
Let's get changed first
Yiyue
Are you not feeling well?
If so, we can do it another day
No, I'm fine.
Sure?
Let's go and get changed.
Good shot, aunt.
Yiyue, I heard from Qiaoyan that
you've been practicing lately.
Come on, swing!
Come on!
Remember the action tips.
Trust yourself.
Mr. He, the car to pick up Xiaobao has arrived.
OK.
Aunt, I'll see Xiaobao off.
Come on.
Come here.
Let's go!
They really love you.
You must love them, too.
Am I right?
Aunt.
Don't worry.
I'll do what you want.
Leave him.
I love him.
I wish him well, too.
How's it going?
Is she satisfied?
It seems that the result is not satisfactory.
Never say die,
practice more.
You can do it.
What's wrong？
Qiaoyan
Let's break up.
Are you joking with me again?
I'm afraid it will stun Xiaobao.
So,
Please.
Slowly
make it clear to Xiaobao.
I'm leaving now.
You afraid it will stun Xiaobao.
Aren't you afraid to stun me?
Did aunt say something again?
Have your dinner.
Dad.
How about giving mom a seat?
Today is the anniversary of her death.
Your mother was a vegetarian.
Look at this.
Oh, I forgot.
You have filial piety.
Remember to go home every year today.
Of course, I'm very sensible.
Before your mother passed away,
I had a fight with her.
Now think about it.
What for?
There's no estrangement for a family that can't
be tided over.
If I haven't sulk with her,
call her back,
and make her a meal,
under the same roof,
she would get over it.
As a girl,
I'm more useful
than ten boys like you.
I don't have 100 thousand RMB.
You won't even get 10 RMB.
How can a family like this?
Son, when you're not busy,
You'd better move back home.
Dad,
Your Lake Villa.
Could you give it to me?
What?
You're tired of the house you live now?
No, it's useful for me.
Look what I brought you.
You scared me!
Why are you crying?
You, in the middle of the night
don't company with your Mr. He.
What are you doing here?
I'm here
holding you a pajama party.
Wait me a minute.
I'll go back to my room first
and change my pajamas.
Last time somebody
took all your clothes
away.
You're right.
Good sisters share their pajamas.
I'll put on your pajamas
No!
No, I have to.
Also,
You mask,
Give me one, too.
What happened to you?
Stop pretending.
When you hum,
I'll know what you
want to do.
So,
what you can see
in my eyes?
Smudged eyeliner.
Lovelorn.
You broke up with He Qiaoyan?
Really?
You're going to drive me nuts, aren't you
Why did you suddenly break up？
Two days ago, you two
were close as same
as the conjoined baby,
weren't you?
Don't ask.
Even you ask,
I won't tell you.
You cheated on him.
No.
With you stupid brain,
no way.
He Qiaoyan cheated on you?
Ruowei.
For modern man and woman,
falling in love and breaking up
are normal things.
Does it have to be so vulgar
and dramatic?
I and He Qiaoyan,
we are out of step with each other.
It was a very peaceful
and delight break up.
Is it OK?
Come on, Miss.
Just Relax.
How about a bunch of meat?
I'm sleepy, Yue'er.
Let me lie down for a while.
Who is it in the early morning?
Coming!
Good morning.
Don't come to me again.
Let me in,
or you come home with me.
You are own choice.
I've already said what I would say.
Xiaobao
Drunk again.
Were you drunk?
It's none of your business.
Every time you got drunk
are very funny.
Of course.
She's a famous
performing artist after drinking.
See me a passer-by, please continue,
Let's go.
You arranged it.
Praise each other every day.
Hold me.
You arrange this, too
Before going out every day,
we all need to give each other a loving hug.
I need to wash.
Please leave.
What's going on?
After breaking up, he came
and brought you breakfast.
How could I know what's going on?
I see, you two,
in a couple of days,
are too boring,
so looking for trouble.
Don't go out.
Why can't I go out?
What can I say to him?
Should I say, we broke up,
but we can be brother?
Do you think he came here today
to be your brother?
I'm really out of your business
I have to go to work.
Don't go out.
Tell me,
Mr. He,
what does he like about you?
I
Isn't that charming?
Glamorous.
Fashionable clothes and charming taste.
Especially these two dark circles
It's almost on the ground.
It's the finishing touch.
I am leaving.
I don't have dark circles.
Mr. He,
I am going to work.
OK.
Qin Yiyue, are you crazy?
What are you doing?
But it looks pretty good.
We can have breakfast now.
We agreed to have breakfast
What do you want on earth?
Bring my girlfriend Breakfast.
We've broken up.
That's what you thought.
I didn't agree.
Does this
still need your consent?
Article 9 of the Love Contract
clearly defines,
either party
is not allowed to break up unilaterally.
So,
So how you can agree?
Have breakfast.
If I finish this, you will agree.
Ok.
Take it easy.
Eating too fast is not good for digestion.
Finish breakfast before the sand glass finished.
It can't be early or late
That's the last piece.
Xiaobao Xiaobao
Don't do that.
Spit it out, spit it out.
You are very good at teaching.
Is it enough?
If it's not enough, I'll make you another breakfast.
You!
Take Xiaobao to school.
I will take the bus.
Go by myself.
Xiaobao is still there.
Say hello to him.
I walk with you to work.
You go by yourself
You see that, too
My car took Xiaobao to school.
Take a taxi.
I can't.
I'll do it for you.
I never take a taxi.
Online car-hailing is the same.
Stand here by yourself.
Not bad.
What do you want on earth?
Take you to work. What else can I do?
The bike is a little small
But there's no problem for two.
Mr. He, my bike is not suitable for you.
You'd better take your luxury car.
Who said that? No problem.
Move out.
-Get out of the way. -I said I could.
Come on, I'll take you.
Hey,
I'll go first.
If you want to send me, Mr. He.
Take your time.
How much is your motorbike. I'll buy it.
Are you insane?
How much is your bike, Madam.
I'll take it.
Twenty thousand.
Good.
I'll transfer it to you.
Transfer.
I want your hat, too.
Buy one and get one free!
Thank you!
Qin Yiyue.
Yiyue, wait for me.
Yiyue!
If my behavior
could make you happy.
I can keep them all the time.
Don't flatter yourself.
Let me go.
Just one minute.
Qin Yiyue, please listen to me.
I won't let you go.
I won't agree to break up with you.
In recent days,
You can live in Yang Ruowei's house.
It's like taking a vacation for yourself
But for breakfast and dinner,
you have to take with me.
I have to pick you up to and from work.
And the most important thing,
weekly appointment is
as usual.
Why should I listen to you?
You'd better listen to me.
Otherwise it's going to get really troublesome.
Are you threatening me?
All right, go to work.
Don't think too much.
I
You what?
Mr. He, I come to meet you.
OK.
Go ahead.
Wait for me to pick you up after work.
Just in time.
I think we should
conduct
an experiment of completely automatic electric vehicle.
-Good morning, Mr, He. -Good morning, Mr, He.
Let's go straight ahead.
It's been investigated
Manager Liu in charge of publicity,
manager Meng in charge of the channel,
and
Hans in charge of docking in Germany,
all have been in touch with Miss Lin recently.
It can be judged
their sudden
leaving from Heshi Group and the project
was influenced by Miss Lin.
What's the situation in Germany?
Kubo 5, Germany
has known that
we had an accident.
They said to suspend cooperation with us,
and think about it again.
They have time to think about it.
But we can't wait.
Is there any good news
for me?
President Jia said he would continue to support you,
as long as you keep your promise
launching the Bracelet Project in German market.
But there is one pre-condition,
that's if it's not a super shopping center like
Kubo 5.
It has to be
top three shopping centers in Europe.
What's more. It must be in accordance with the contract,
launching in a month.
Very good.
His words are encouraging.
German Mazer company
has received
our samples.
Recently,
their director, Mr. Jung,
will come to China.
I'll talk to him directly.
But I heard
Mr. Jung of Mazer company
is known for its preciseness.
So this time I think
our efficiency must be very high.
The good news is that
Mr. Jung and I are alumni.
In college,
our relationship is not bad.
But everybody,
there're only two days.
By any means,
Before I meet Mr. Jung
at the meeting,
you guys have to get
ready in advance.
Thank you very much.
Heshi Group
was picked on by Miss Lin.
Do we need to do something?
Don't care about that.
Put all our attention into
the bracelet project.
For this project,
I had given a pledge
to the board.
There must be no mistakes.
Yes, sir.
Assistant Manager Wen,
for the file you want,
I've already delivered it.
I'm going back to the company now.
You don't have to go back to the company
Why?
I'll send you a location.
and come over here.
Come in.
You're going to have a villa party.
But there's no one here.
It's too lonely, isn't it?
This is my dad's house.
But it's also mine.
How do you like it?
So much for a bet?
A villa for me?
But thanks.
I still like
my little rental house.
This place
is too big for me.
It's frightening to live alone.
You're not living alone.
Get in.
Ruowei,
I haven't seen you for so long.
It looks like you're doing well
No wonder you didn't agree to get married
back hometown.
It turned out to be in a big city
with a better boyfriend.
You see, Mr. Wen can arrange everything
Why don't you let him
look for a job for your brother?
You see in big cities,
there are so many enterprises.
To be a manager
or something.
It's very simple, isn't it?
Your brother will be back in a moment
Knowing these,
he'll be happy.
Where there's family,
there's home.
You're out on your own,
with no ability to
get them over here.
There's no way for you to
go back and take care of them.
Once and for all,
I took them all.
I found a big house.
Later, when you are busy with work,
your mother can take care of you.
What's wrong?
Yang Ruowei!
What's wrong with you?
Wen Gu, what's your problem?
Are you too idle?
Why did you get them here?
I know.
I know you are not getting along well
with your family.
But I think it's family after all.
Meet and live together.
With life goes on,
there will be a reunion.
More about that,
you're out on your own,
helpless and friendless.
If you could be with your family,
there will be no
difficulties that cannot be overcome.
You can also live a more easy life.
I know you and your mother are estranged.
I've seen your brother make trouble for you.
-But... -You know nothing!
I've worked so hard all these years.
Just to get rid of that
broken home.
But,
you got me back.
For sure,
There were no relatives around me these years.
I admit that I envy Qin Yiyue very much.
When she was hurt and wronged,
She takes a taxi,
in one hour,
she can back to her parents.
I can't.
I have no way back.
But I don't need kinship,
nor family.
I have myself, and it's enough.
But you can't be such stiff with your family
all the time.
Why it had to be like this?
You grew up loaded.
You don't understand that
every family has a skeleton in the cupboard.
But don't be self-righteous
and get involved in other's lives!
Come here and disgust me for no reason.
Disgust you?
Yes.
I admit.
For this matter,
It was thoughtless of me to do such a thing.
But I'm not
that idle to
specially find out the address of your hometown,
and send somebody to pick up your mother here.
And then I went out of my way to ask my dad
for this big house,
preparing everything
and waiting to surprise you.
Fine.
In the future, you
and your family mess.
You handle it by yourself.
I will be far away from you.
I won't disgust you,
and you don't bother me either.
Yang Ruowei!
If Xiao'an didn't tell me,
I would not have known you are sick.
Director,
Did you
forget to rest?
So those old problems
are troubling you again.
I have good news for you.
The project
that was suspended before
got an eye by
a research institute in Germany.
They said they would cooperate with us to
restart the project.
So you've been doing research day and night
for this project.
It's you who should be blamed.
You suddenly resigned,
leaving the project.
Up to now,
I don't have a person helping me.
Your little patient,
I heard he's cured.
Can you
come back and help me?
Don't you want to stay at
the consulting room of Ning Fang all the time.
I respect Ning Fang and
his original intention of running that consulting room.
But you're not like him.
You always want to
do this project well.
And you always want to
make some achievements
in psychological research on children.
Qin Yiyue,
I know you scarcely bear to leave him.
But when you love someone,
you hope he can be happy.
So you have to make up your mind,
and you can't go back.
Understand, Qin Yiyue.
Ning Fang
Why are you here at night?
I also want to ask you.
Why are you here?
Hello,
it's me.
Lucheng City?
Tomorrow?
I'll call you later.
Okay?
Thank you.
What's going on? Do you have to go on a business trip?
There's a hotel in Lucheng looking for me
They want me to help the hotel staff
for psychological examination.
What happened?
Don't want to go home?
Are you hiding from He Qiaoyan？
How can I avoid He Qiaoyan?
I've heard something from Ruowei.
Don't want to talk to me?
If you don't want to talk, I'm leaving.
Ning Fang, let me ask you a question.
Have you ever been in such a situation?
When you see a person,
you just feel nervous,
and want to do something for him.
But you can't do anything.
It seems that leaving him
is the right choice.
Yes, I had.
But most of my time
is happy.
What you said is still a minority.
I did everything with thinking of her.
Sometimes,
even if I know where she is,
and what is she doing,
I'll be in a better mood.
How about now?
After listening to me,
do you feel better？
I never have a bad time.
All right, it's too late.
Let me take you home.
Let's go.
OK, I'll take it myself.
Yiyue, where have you been?
Mr. He has been waiting for you all night.
I didn't ask him to wait.
Cake on the table,
Xiaobao bought it for you.
Go to bed early.
We're leaving now.
Mr. He, safe drive.
Yiyue, I'm leaving, too.
Have an early rest.
Ning Fang.
Let me go to Lucheng City for you tomorrow.
OK, go for a distraction.
I'll arrange for Xiao'an to go with you.
This way, please.
In addition to the catering department
and sales department,
employees in the other five departments
all need to take part in this psychological examination.
I looked at the list.
In total,
there are 223 persons.
Am I right?
Yes.
Dr. Qin.
How long do you think it will take.
So I can make
an adjustment of work arrangement.
The number of people in each of your departments
is almost the same.
Each department
will take one and half hours.
Then we follow the order
on the list.
By the way,
Let the employees in lobby department
come to the conference room.
OK, Doctor Qin.
Then I'll call
them to the conference room.
This way, please.
Do they live near here?
I think so.
Today,
we've revenged for Brother Jay.
and taught Zhang a lesson.
Only Yang Ruoqiang is left.
Early this morning,
he took his mother and run away.
Only half a million, can't imagine he was like that.
Come to think of it.
His sister.
What's her name, Yang...
Yang Ruowei.
Ruowei
Yes.
You don't know.
Beauty.
Working in a big company,
She's boss's secretary.
Good figure.
If she is encountered by us tonight...
You see,
we've known each other for such a long time.
Don't be so stiff.
Cheers.
Cheers!
Position has been sent.
I've given you the steps.
Come or not, your choice.
Come and have a drink.
drink
Be happy.
Come on.
Come on in, why are you standing here?
The contract is about to be signed.
It
just wait for your final assist.
Let's go.
Why?
From now on, the two of us
are just leader and member.
The bet or something,
I quit.
I'm tired.
We were in
leader-member relationship all the time.
What did you think it is?
I'm stupid.
No.
I'm not stupid.
You suck.
Bye.
Eight in the morning,
Xiaobao and I will be in your door way.
Don't forget get up and open the door.