[English subtitles are available]
[Director Yoo Seon Dong]
[Writer Kim Sae Bom]
[Lee Dong Wook]
[Wi Ha Jun]
[Han Ji Eun]
[Cha Hak Yeon]
[Bad, Evil, Crazy]
[Bad and Crazy]
[All characters, places, groups, events,
and organizations are fictional.]
[Forensic Psychiatry Institute of Munyang]
[I don't want to take it.]
[Ministry of Justice]
You have to.
You must!
I said I didn't want to. I'm not crazy!
Run, Su Yeol!
Let go! Let me go!
I told you to run fast.
Come on! Quick!
Hurry, quick! Run!
Shove him out of the way!
Hey, hurry!
Hey, are you all right? Ryu Su Yeol.
Ryu Su Yeol!
Su Yeol.
I'm bored.
Do you want to play rock-paper-scissors?
The winner gets to punch the loser
in the face.
What do you say?
I suddenly had this thought.
What thought?
Out of all our moments together,
when was the most messed up moment?
When was it? When? Tell me.
The fire.
Darn it!
It's hot.
It was burning hot.
Jumping out the window.
And getting beaten up all the time.
My gosh, yes.
I beat you up every chance I had.
Why are you reminiscing
about our memories?
Whenever I think about those moments,
I feel like I can do anything.
[Ministry of Justice]
Your life is like
that blank piece of paper in front of you.
Your life can change
depending on what you decide
to draw on it.
Now, get started.
What are you doing?
Why you...
What are you drawing?
Life is
like a map.
A map?
Then what does the "X" mean?
It's a spot
where no one can see me.
It's a security camera blind spot.
[Doctor Hong Seok Gyeong]
-What are you doing here?
-Why?
Do you not recognize me
now that my eyes look alert for a change?
[Doctor Hong Seok Gyeong]
You meticulously recorded every detail.
You've been busted.
What can you do? I did this for a living
in the outside world.
Dr. Hong, I always wondered
why you were so popular among the inmates.
You've been making a killing
selling pain meds.
But these are
all narcotics.
What do you want?
You'll have to
get me out of here.
Transfer me
to the nearest university hospital.
And you'll escape once you're there?
[Dr. Hong: Get rid of him.]
Su Yeol, you're in trouble.
These guys are going to kill you.
Maybe just tell them
that you want to go back, okay?
I've trained really hard
for the past five months.
I've been waiting for this moment.
Get this straitjacket off me.
You guys must know!
No, we don't!
[Final Episode]
Try calling him then, you fool!
He escaped. He doesn't have a phone.
Why doesn't he have...
Right, he doesn't have one
because he's a fugitive.
Darn it, this lunatic!
There is nowhere to hide
in this small country.
I can't believe he escaped.
Does he want to rot in prison
for the rest of his life?
Hey, it's the Commissioner.
Hello, sir.
My apologies.
We'll put out an APB on him at once.
I'll take care of it right away.
Yes, of course.
Darn it.
Gosh, Su Yeol must have
really lost his mind.
What do we do now?
Where could he be now?
Give me that.
Here, let me. Come on.
Oh, boy.
It's actually not that cold, right?
Darn it. He's not there.
I contacted every person
he could reach out to but can't find him.
He didn't contact us or his family.
Where could Su Yeol be?
Jeez, this is nuts.
He wasn't caught on
any of the security cameras.
Gosh, that idiot.
What on earth is he trying to do?
Hey, Jae Seon. You know...
Remember that psychiatrist
Su Yeol used to see?
You know, that quack.
-Yeom Geun Su?
-Yes, him.
He fled long ago.
That's right. That space is vacant now.
It's vacant?
-Let's go!
-Let's go! Come on!
-Inspector Lee, your jacket.
-Hey, hurry!
Yes, that's right.
[Grant me the strength
to get through this day.]
I was born between 5 and 7 a.m. Right.
That's correct.
Thanks to you, I got through another day.
And as you predicted,
I keep getting more new patients.
[It's all because
you've been praying with all your heart.]
Just lie low until the next full moon
[Attorney Nam Eun Seok]
and focus on
getting rid of your bad karma.
[Yes, sure thing. Will do.]
[Attorney Nam Eun Seok]
Wait, it doesn't look like you've sent
your membership fee for this month yet.
[Oh, that.]
I sent you extra last month,
so you said it'd carry over.
What?
My son takes care of my accounting.
You know, he's an attorney.
He must've missed it
[because he's been swamped with work.]
Oh, I should mention this to you
just in case.
If you're having a hard time,
you can always come to Attorney Nam
for practical advice.
I'm his mom, so I can make sure
he gives you a nice discount.
Hold on a moment.
Gosh, my goodness.
Mr. Ryu... Wait, are you K right now?
No, Su Yeol.
I have no idea anymore.
I'm really sorry.
At the time, I wasn't in my right mind.
Thank goodness
I have a connection in the police.
That was why I could flee in advance.
If not, I would've ended up behind bars
with you.
Thanks to you, I was labeled a lunatic
and ended up in a psych ward.
Because I had no one to testify for me.
I knew that you weren't a lunatic but...
Well...
Anyway, you made a difficult decision.
You're still a beginner,
but being a fugitive...
You see, I've been doing this
for four to five months,
and it's really awful.
Why did you get out?
On the news earlier,
they said that cop escaped.
If he finds out that I got out of juvie,
will he come and find me again?
He must know that
I refused to provide a statement.
Did you have something
to tell the police though?
I told the police everything,
and it all proved to be true.
Don't worry too much.
That man, Ryu Su Yeol...
He'll soon return to where he belongs.
[Save Voice Memo]
[Voice Memos]
[So you're saying]
you want to figure out
Shin Ju Hyeok's psychological weakness.
As you know,
he has destroyed all solid evidence.
Let me think...
What would you be most scared of
when you're hiding behind a mask?
Having the mask removed?
Someone revealing the fact
that he is Jeong Yun Ho?
That's right!
As they say, the sparrow near a school
sings the primer.
A lunatic has finally learned
how to handle a psychopath.
So I should help that jerk
reclaim his real name first.
Psychopaths who are obsessively meticulous
often have psychological weaknesses
that are fatal.
Mess with them a few times,
and they just fall apart.
I think I can figure out a way.
Let's get through the day
without getting caught.
Hold on.
If Jeong Yun Ho is Shin Ju Hyeok...
Then who is Shin Ju Hyeok?
[-Move. Out of the way!
-Back off.]
-Out of the way.
-Move! Hey!
-How dare you push me?
-Hey! What the heck!
-Move!
-Hey, you little...
-You punk.
-Wait, stop.
Stop!
Everybody, shut up.
-Sir.
-Jeez.
You followed us, right?
Look at you
trying to ride on our coattails.
Hey, Lee Hui Gyeom.
Watch what you say.
Ride on your coattails?
What are you talking about?
We received a tip
-that Ryu Su Yeol was here.
-What?
-Goodness.
-Who sent in the tip?
Who would send in such a tip?
Jeez, my ears hurt.
I'm not an amateur.
Why would I tell you who sent in the tip?
What about you guys? Why are you here?
-Captain, over there!
-Get him!
Stop them! Block them!
-Hey, stop.
-Move!
[Heart Mender]
Stop, you jerk!
-Hey!
-Wait up!
Wait up!
Hey!
[Hangukgwan]
Go! Get him!
Stop right there, you punk!
Su Yeol! Get in the car!
-Get him!
-Hey!
Hey!
Darn it!
Gosh.
How have you been?
Hey, Hui Gyeom! Goodness.
Hey, are you all right? Jeez.
Do you not trust us at all?
How could you escape
without even telling us?
What were you thinking?
Have you really lost your mind?
My, that was fun and thrilling
for a change.
-All right, I'm sorry.
-What? You're sorry?
You totally fooled us for months.
And what? You're sorry?
-Come here.
-Hey.
-Get back here.
-Calm down, Hui Gyeom.
Hey, it's not important right now.
Su Yeol, I didn't know
you were such a good actor.
Become an actor.
Why did you become a cop with that face?
Actor, my foot. He's a con man.
-Come here!
-Hey, calm down!
Calm down, all of you!
We should hear him out first.
Yes, let's hear him out. Goodness.
All right. Let's hear what he has to say.
-Speak.
-Go ahead, sir.
I must prove that
Shin Ju Hyeok is Jeong Yun Ho.
But I realized
that there's something I missed...
What? What is it?
Jeez.
My alter ego, K. Say hi to everyone.
It's nice to meet you. I'm Oh Gyeong Tae.
-Hey, well...
-What are you doing?
Tell him we've met before.
I saved his life.
You two have met before.
He saved your life.
-Pardon?
-When there was a fire at your place,
K threw me in there to save you.
Shall I profess my feelings to Hui Gyeom?
Profess what?
Don't you know the situation we're in?
Hey, I'm good. I don't need to meet him.
What about me?
He has nothing to say to you.
Really?
Well, anyway... So?
What was the thing you missed in the past?
There was one more person.
Who?
Someone else knew that
Shin Ju Hyeok was Jeong Yun Ho.
Who is this person?
Are you Jeong Yun Ho?
-You're laughing?
-Pick up your phone.
Yun Ho is waiting.
[That man died,]
but he certainly knew Jeong Yun Ho's name,
which means he knew Shin Ju Hyeok
even when he was Jeong Yun Ho,
so I'm sure they go back a long way.
If we do some digging on him,
we may be able to prove
that Shin Ju Hyeok is indeed Jeong Yun Ho.
About that man...
Even the autopsy found nothing,
[except for the fact that his fingerprints
were intentionally damaged.]
Identifying him...
I know that it'll be hard.
[But I have to try]
[because this is]
[my last chance.]
Even back then,
he was confident that he could catch him
and even risked his life for it,
but he ended up behind bars himself
instead of catching him.
Right?
Yes, I admit that things went haywire.
But to fix it,
I need to find out some things
about that man who died with Andrei.
Help me.
Back then,
how did you people find that man?
-Hey!
-Darn it.
Stop right there, you punk!
You little rat.
-Just tell us his name.
-I don't know. I have no idea!
You little...
We don't exchange names
with everyone we do business with.
He was just a homeless man. A vagrant!
Don't give me that!
-Tell us everything you know.
-Darn it.
Gyeong Tae, it's always easier
to use both hands, right?
-It sure is.
-Right?
The clinic. The mental health clinic!
A mental health clinic?
When I met him for the first time
about ten years ago,
he came to buy drugs
wearing his patient uniform.
The uniform was quite unusual.
[Yang Jae Seon]
Yeom Geun Su? Are you sure?
Yeom Geun Su?
The fake psychiatrist who treated Su Yeol?
[Yes.]
You don't commonly see a patient uniform
with an angel symbol.
[I did a little digging.
The clinic shut down ten years ago,]
[and he was the director of the clinic.]
Shin Ju Hyeok is dead meat now.
Okay, all right.
Meet us at Heart Mender, okay?
[Mom, you're okay, right?]
Why do you keep calling me?
Buy groceries and hurry back home.
[Mom, wave your hand at the camera.]
[I can see you, so don't worry.
Wait just a little.]
[-I'll be home soon.]
-Okay.
Of course,
I still have all the patient charts.
[Grant me the strength
to get through this day.]
I kept them to use
when I opened a new clinic soon.
They're all on my computer.
You have everything from ten years ago?
[Come on.]
A mental illness relapse is very common.
And it's not like my patients magically
recovered when I closed my clinic,
[so I need all the records for reference.]
[Yeom Geun Su]
This is how you do business.
Yes. You're absolutely right.
Hey, I'm sending you a photo.
[He was your patient in the past.
Find out his name.]
I'll be there very soon.
Okay.
All right, let's see.
I used to have so many patients.
Those were the good days.
Let's see.
[Patient Counseling Log]
[Personal Information]
Is it him?
[Name: Shin Ju Hyeok]
He's already here? Hey, you.
Oh, you've never met me before.
I've seen you many times,
so I'm happy to meet you in person.
My gosh. That's...
When... When did you put that there?
I was curious
what kind of treatment
Ryu Su Yeol was getting.
Oh, this?
I installed it over six months ago.
I'll go in first.
[Hangukgwan]
Hey, Dr. Yeom!
What happened?
Hey, Dr. Yeom.
What happened? Wake up!
What? What did we do?
Aided and abetted a fugitive?
Unbelievable.
Hey, that jerk...
Has he completely lost his mind?
[He wants to use this
to get us in trouble.]
[I didn't want to put Su Yeol in danger,]
[so we came back to the office for now.]
[What about Yeom Geun Su?
Did you meet him?]
I'm on my way there now.
Hey, I'll call you back.
Hey, Dong Yeol.
[Hey, Hui Gyeom.]
[Can you reach Su Yeol right now?]
Darn it.
Hurry! He's dying! Please hurry!
-You need to leave at once.
-Why?
What, then? Are you going to wait
for the police and medics here?
Here. Take this and go.
Hurry! I'll take care of things here.
[Dong Yeol]
Hey.
Su Yeol!
What happened?
What's with all this mess? Where's Mom?
Mom? I managed to calm her down.
She was doing well,
taking her medications on time and all.
I listened to Hui Gyeom
and made sure she wouldn't watch the news.
I don't know how she heard the news,
but she kept saying she had to find you
and save you from danger.
Su Yeol.
Are you okay?
All right.
Mom.
My dear Su Yeol.
Mom, it's me. I'm here.
What did you do to Su Yeol?
Who are you?
What did you do to my son, Su Yeol?
I'm...
What's going on?
Stay away, Dong Yeol! Don't come in.
I can't let you get hurt.
You. You're not Su Yeol.
I know everything. I read the letter.
I read the whole thing.
"Letter"?
Mom, what letter?
You impersonated Su Yeol and hurt people.
You made people suffer.
Where is Su Yeol?
Where is my son? You scumbag!
Bring the real Su Yeol back.
My son, Su Yeol! I want my son back!
Su Yeol, Mom!
[Su Yeol! Mom!]
Mom, I am Su Yeol.
It's me. Your son, Su Yeol!
The boy who ran away to survive.
You put your trust in me, remember?
It's me. I am Su Yeol.
Your son, Su Yeol!
You told me to pull myself together
and protect myself.
You told me that, remember?
Su Yeol.
My dear Su Yeol.
My dear son.
Mom.
Su Yeol.
It's okay, Mom. Everything will be okay.
It's all my fault. My poor son.
I put you through so much, Su Yeol.
Mom, I'm okay.
I'm really okay.
You are Su Yeol, right?
You are my son, Su Yeol.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mom.
[No Caller ID]
Just a moment, Mom.
[Mr. Ryu Su Yeol.]
[Don't you think
that every choice you've made]
[is wrong?]
The more you try to do things,
the more people will get hurt.
Why are you doing this?
What do you want from me?
You just won't
accept the fact
that Jeong Yun Ho saved you.
You saved me?
You committed murder.
[You think you saved those kids?]
[You just used them]
to justify the murders you committed.
[I'd say,]
it's about time we met.
Why do you look so scared?
I told you.
This man, Ryu Su Yeol...
He will soon be sent back
to where he belongs.
Why did you want to see me today?
To tell you that you can stop now.
Sorry?
Recording our conversations.
You've been recording our conversations
in secret.
You can stop that now.
Why here?
Because this is where it all began.
The very beginning,
with that scumbag and me.
I'm the one he's after.
So I should fix this.
Trust is key.
Of course, I have to trust you.
No.
You, not me.
Trust yourself.
I do trust myself.
Who knew we'd meet again here?
In Jae Hui
and Jeong Yun Ho.
Finally, you're admitting it?
That you are Jeong Yun Ho.
Seriously, why are you doing this to me?
We lived as complete strangers
for 22 years.
Do you remember everything now?
I saved you, right here.
I'm sick and tired
of hearing your nonsense.
You see, back then...
Did we have another option?
Let's say I chose not to kill your father.
Then do you think you would've been able
to escape that misery?
Really?
Let's find out.
-What?
-Jae Hui.
You really have to accept it now.
Killing your father
was the only way to save you back then.
Just like now.
Help!
Help me! Help!
-Is that Jeong Hun?
-Help!
-What is he doing here?
-Help...
-Once again, it had to come to this.
-Help!
Help!
Snap out of it, Ryu Su Yeol.
Have you forgotten already?
Fire doesn't faze us.
Help...
Help. Help me...
Jeong Hun, I can get you out of here.
Help...
Let's go. I won't let you die like this.
It was because of K.
The reason you believed that
I wasn't the one who saved you,
and the only reason you rejected my help.
It was because of K!
Now, say it.
"Save me." Now, you want me to save you?
Really?
Back then and even now,
I am the only one who can save you.
Say it.
Beg me for help. Beg me to save you!
Even back then, I graciously saved you!
I saved you!
Accept it, darn it!
Get lost.
Get lost, you psycho.
That was fun, Jae Hui.
K...
K.
Jeong Hun...
Save Jeong Hun.
-Su Yeol.
-Please...
[Then what is the solution?]
Who will save her?
Who will end her misery?
[Put that down.]
The person who made you like this.
I promise I'll catch that person,
at all costs.
So please don't do this.
No!
Young Joo.
Help me. He is...
No, don't talk.
Help me.
-He is...
-No.
[I've been here the whole time.]
Right by your side.
[Back then, you were just a little boy
who ran away to survive.]
And I still
believe that.
So you should trust yourself too.
Trust is key.
You, not me.
I can do this.
Jeong Hun.
Jeong Hun, let's go.
We must get out of here.
Let's go.
Come on.
I'll be right back, okay?
Don't ruin the fun.
You must be sick of me now.
You're scared of me, aren't you?
I bet that's why you're doing this to me.
Because you can't control me.
Look at you all scared.
You see, this is proof right here.
The fact that you're scared now.
It proves that you know
you committed crimes.
In Jae Hui.
I'm Ryu Su Yeol.
Jeez, you talk too much.
Forget it.
It's time for you to get beaten up.
[I did]
[pretty well, didn't I?]
K.
Hey, where are you?
Where are you, K?
Jeez, it's you again.
Why did you follow me all the way here?
Goodness.
I thought you were gone for good,
but you were hiding here?
You should've been there
to see Shin Ju Hyeok get pummeled.
-It's time for me to leave.
-Leave?
Heroes are never afraid to say goodbye.
I can say goodbye
and just be cool with it.
"Goodbye"?
-Why?
-What is this, Su Yeol?
Are you getting teary-eyed?
Are you, seriously?
Oh, boy. This is why I was going to
just disappear quietly like the wind.
Fine. Since you managed to find me,
I shall give you a gift.
My real name.
Your real name? I thought your name was K.
My real name. My full name.
K,
I,
N,
-and...
-Don't tell me it's "G."
Bingo! That is my name.
King! Of the world.
Just leave.
I should leave.
Okay. I really am leaving now.
If you grab me or hit me in the back
of my head the moment I turn around...
Or if you give me a wedgie,
-you will pay the price--
-Just go.
You're a good guy.
King...
K!
Thanks.
I haven't heard that
in a while.
Are you all right?
Thank you.
Thank you
for saving me.
You should thank yourself.
Because I am you.
It was all you.
You saved yourself. It wasn't me.
K!
[I think he'll wake up soon.]
But
why is he smiling?
It looks like he's crying too.
He's up. He's awake.
-What?
-Su Yeol.
Are you okay?
Goodness.
What about Jeong Hun?
Jeong Hun is fine.
And his injuries are mostly minor.
What about Shin Ju Hyeok?
There's no Shin Ju Hyeok.
What?
He's Jeong Yun Ho now.
Dr. Yeom had a patient file on the man
who died with Andrei.
So we identified him.
That man was the real Shin Ju Hyeok.
Shin Ju Hyeok wasn't the first one
Jeong Yun Ho stole identity from.
People at the shelter
and psychiatric hospitals
were his victims.
Jeong Hun testified.
And you'll be able to clear your name now.
And Dr. Yeom is fine too.
Right. So you just have to get better now.
That's all we need.
Are you okay?
You were smiling and crying earlier.
It was quite a scene.
-Oh, that crazy jerk.
-Crazy jerk?
What?
He's really gone.
Crazy...
-K?
-No.
He's not K. He's King.
-What?
-That's his real name.
Do you know what that means?
"King" means a ruler of a country.
I know that too.
[Convening of Reinstatement Committee]
Tell them that
you never had a split personality.
He's gone anyway, right?
You were just doing a sting operation.
To catch that psychopath.
Do you understand?
[Convening of Reinstatement Committee]
[Superintendent Ryu.]
[Evaluator]
We're sincerely glad that
you were able to clear your name.
Thank you.
It was suspected that you had
a split personality which was the issue.
And this was the strategy
for your sting operation.
Is that true?
What is your name?
K.
-"Gay"?
-K!
As in, H, I, J, K!
[Evaluator]
Superintendent Ryu?
Yes.
[Ryu Su Yeol]
I'm sorry.
Recently,
he had undergone a checkup.
And a psychiatrist said
he was perfectly fine.
Superintendent Ryu. Isn't that true?
Yes. That's true.
Then he won't have a problem
coming back to the job.
And his performance is great too.
And not utilizing this resource
would be a loss for our agency too.
[Evaluator]
You are right.
By the way,
how did you come up with this idea?
A split personality?
It's not like a movie, you know?
I can say that Superintendent Ryu is
competent as well as clever.
[K.]
[Ryu Su Yeol]
[You didn't kill anyone.]
[You saved me.]
[All right.
Let me introduce myself again.]
I am Su Yeol's hero, no one else's.
I am Su Yeol's action star.
[I am]
Su Yeol's K.
All right. We'll finish the evaluation
for his reinstatement here.
Okay.
-Good work.
-He was real.
K's existence
was real.
And he was with me.
Superintendent Ryu.
What are you talking about?
He was definitely crazy.
But he was a good person too.
You said he was cleared by the doctor.
Right. He was.
He was real.
And I can't deny his existence.
K was definitely with me.
And I liked him.
[Evaluatee]
Thank you for everything.
[Evaluator]
No. Hold on a second.
-Superintendent Ryu.
-Hey, Ryu Su Yeol.
Hey.
Ryu Su Yeol!
[Yeol Yeol Pizza]
When I see this, it makes me think
we're really biologically related.
Why do you say that?
Ryu Dong Yeol.
You've gotten better
at stealing money from the pizzeria.
You almost fooled me.
Seriously. You're so good
at revealing corruption.
And a lot of people thought
that we were biologically related.
You and I resemble each other.
Goodness.
Mom, slap him some more.
-You come here.
-You have a week. Bring back the money.
We're missing 200,000 won.
-What?
-I was buying stuff for the pizzeria.
-Come here.
-Mom, no! Stop it.
Mom, I think he's seeing someone.
Ask him about that!
-Hey!
-No!
He put a receipt for jeans between
the receipts for jalapenos and tomatoes?
He's unbelievable.
We're closed for the day.
Hey.
I was meaning to call you.
Thank you. Your statement helped a lot.
[Part-time delivery job available]
I'm here for the part-time job.
What?
You know I'm good
at driving the motorcycle, right?
-Dong Yeol.
-What?
We have a new part-timer.
[Pizza of the Day]
-Really?
-Don't go easy on him.
When did you get here?
Hey, you must be hungry.
Come on in. Have some pizza.
Mom.
Hey. You were at our house before.
Yes. He'll work for us now.
Really? Are you sure you can do it?
Hey, do you enjoy
following me around wherever I go?
Not by following around a loser like me.
Don't you want to live
the life that you want?
How?
Do you want me to join you?
Well, you played a critical part
in the operation.
And even if K was there,
the psychiatrist cleared you now.
I'll be honest.
Cops don't just talk about it.
But a lot of them are suffering from PTSD.
People said cops shouldn't be fired
because of that.
This went viral on our agency's website.
This is the first time realizing
that a lot of cops were rooting for me.
Right. Same here.
You'll come back, right?
I'm not sure.
-What else?
-What?
It looks like there's something else.
I thought you came here
to talk about something serious.
That's why you probably
came here alone without the team.
Right.
Do you remember the day
when we arrested Kim Gye Sik?
You stopped by my house briefly
because of your wound
-on the forehead.
-Oh, that day.
I can't forget that day.
What? What about that day?
What?
I'm curious about the thing
that happened that day.
Who were you back then?
Were you yourself? Or were you K?
-What do you mean?
-What?
Who was it? You know, the thing...
The one who kissed me.
-Hey.
-I knew it.
-Let go of me, you jerk.
-I already warned you.
When it comes to justice and love,
-heroes go all out.
-Hey, let go of me.
You crazy jerk.
It's been a while. Say hi first.
Say hi?
How can I be happy
and say hello to you right now?
You. Tell me what happened
between you and Hui Gyeom that day.
Tell me everything!
Nothing happened.
We just watched "Amazing Saturday."
Let go of me!
I will never believe you, jerk!
Su Yeol.
-What?
-What's wrong? Are you okay?
Did K show up again?
No.
He doesn't show up anymore.
If he knew that we had kissed,
he would have done everything to kill me.
So what do you want to do, Hui Gyeom?
Me?
Well...
Are you going to stay with our team?
I see. The team...
What? "Our team"?
You're coming back?
Right. K is gone, anyway.
I should keep an eye on you now
and make sure you don't revert back
to your old days.
Like you said,
let's argue that you were fragile
due to your childhood trauma.
We can try that,
but you shouldn't get your hopes up.
All right, then.
[Keep it clean.]
[One year later]
Gosh.
This place has gotten bigger already.
Hey, don't pour me one. I'm on duty.
Why are you offering a drink to him?
He's on duty now.
-Come on. Read the room.
-Gosh.
Right. Superintendent Ryu.
I can't describe you
without complimenting how cool you are.
That's right.
And you're a zombie after money,
Superintendent Ju.
I'm a zombie who only cares about money.
I should have taken care of you.
I know it's long overdue.
I messed up again!
-All right. Here
-Gosh.
Take it.
Detective Kim,
you're really going to upset me.
I came out here to catch up
because it's been a while.
I didn't even know he was here.
-Isn't that right?
-Right.
Why do I keep messing up?
Why do you make so many mistakes?
I have way too many people
I ought to take care of.
Ta-da.
This is for you.
Just spend it on whatever you need.
And as for this,
put it in the bank.
Look how thick that is.
By the way, if I keep digging,
how far will I get?
I can't help but get curious.
What do you take me for? Gosh.
It's obvious that you're bribing me.
-Wait. What are you doing?
-Hey.
-Hold on.
-Pictures?
Don't touch it.
It will only make it worse.
All right. Evidence number one.
Let's talk about the rest at the agency.
Why?
All right, students.
You're listening, right?
Come on in.
Come on!
Darn it. That jerk, Ryu Su Yeol.
Stop them.
Gyeong Tae.
Get them on the count of three.
-Okay.
-Three!
Look.
You startled me.
Detective Kim, it's been a while.
Do your salute properly.
You have no respect for your seniors.
Then live properly.
You have no respect for others.
Wait.
Hey, let go of me. Su Yeol. Hear me out.
Getting arrested by me
sure feels awful, right?
You crazy jerk.
I'm with the Police Commissioner!
The moment you start this fight,
your career will be over!
The Police Commissioner?
Our Police Commissioner? Kim Pyeong Jung?
Now you get it?
Before he goes to the National Assembly,
he's collecting money from everyone!
How will you handle this mess?
You nutcase.
Where are you going, Su Yeol?
-Sir!
-Where are you going?
No. Don't do it! No!
Hey! Come on!
-No. What do we do? Mr. Kim!
-Su Yeol.
-No! stop it. Where are you going?
-Stop him.
-Don't do it!
-No!
Police Commissioner Kim!
-Don't do it, Su Yeol!
No!
[It's nice to meet you, Ryu Su Yeol.]
You crazy jerk! Hey!
[Who the heck are you?]
Who are you
and why are you doing this to me?
To punish those trash-like rotten punks.
The last of this era! The hero.
You're one crazy idiot, aren't you?
-Want one?
-You were going to come out anyway.
What? Take off what?
-Why? Why would you take that off?
-I'm boiling! I'm so hot right now!
Idiot! If you take that off
in this situation right now,
it'll look so weird.
Think about that, you twerp!
Let's go!
- Kungtari shabara
-Hey!
[-Isn't it obvious?
-I'm a superhero.]
[Bad and Crazy]
[Bad, Evil, Crazy]
[Thank you for watching Bad and Crazy.]