A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 25
Good morning, Ms. Zhou.
Good morning, Mr. Lu.
Why are you...
I'm going to the school library
for my graduation project.
I have to go.
Mr. Lu, I have a question.
Go ahead.
Did something happen
when I got home last night?
Last night, you were carried home
by two people.
You looked very happy.
You were jumping and dancing.
I gave you a towel to wipe your face.
You took it and jumped up and down.
I'm old. I don't get it.
Were you dancing a famous dance?
All right.
All right, Mr. Lu. I've got to go.
CHANGTAI WEST COUNTRYSIDE VILLA
Hello?
Meizuo.
I want to ask you.
Do you know what happened
to me last night?
He was the boyfriend I met
while traveling?
I really said that?
Yes.
You also said
that you and Terence
fell in love at first sight.
-You--
-Stop.
I said that?
And right in front of him?
That's so embarrassing.
Was I crazy?
Goodness...
What's the matter?
You're worried about this?
Actually, I think it's fine.
You said you regretted it anyway.
You left him the next day.
But Caina,
who exactly is that Terence guy
anyway?
I don't even know his name.
I met him while traveling in Yunan.
Since you're only her friend,
that means I can pursue her, right?
You didn't even ask his name.
Does that mean you're not interested
in him anymore?
Of course.
I was just playing around.
Why are you smiling like that?
But seriously,
did you two brought me home
together last night?
When I woke up this morning...
Look.
My face is bruised and it's swollen.
My whole body hurts.
What happened last night?
Well...
Let's drink.
I don't want to go home.
I'm not going home.
Listen, man.
I brought Caina here.
I should take her home.
Do you know where she lives?
She'll tell me.
How will she do that when she's so drunk?
I brought her here.
So?
Can you hold her properly?
-You let go first.
-It was you.
It was you.
Cut it out. Let's go.
Do you know where she lives?
No.
Then where are you taking her?
It's because
you didn't want to go home last night
and I couldn't hold you by myself--
Stop.
Don't say anything anymore.
Did I do any other stupid thing?
I promise.
I've already told you everything.
I knew it.
I shouldn't drink.
I still reeked of alcohol
when I woke up this morning.
My goodness.
You even have a Chanel perfume with you.
I prepared that for you, okay?
Then remind me next time
not to drink again.
Actually, I was really happy
with what happened yesterday.
Look.
Ms. Zhang, are you all right?
I'm fine. I just have a bad cold.
I don't want to make you sick too.
You don't look good.
Go and rest. I can manage here.
How can I do that?
You have your own tasks.
And you still have class today, right?
It's fine. My class is at 9:00 a.m.
I can still make it.
But you haven't had breakfast yet.
I'm on a diet.
Just go. Take care of your health.
Go.
Shancai.
You're so nice.
You're Si's girlfriend.
But you still insist
on doing these things.
Ms. Zhang, we're just the same.
We should help each other.
Go.
CHOOSE CONTACT: SHANCAI
IN A RELATIONSHIP WITH SHANCAI
POST
Look.
Class, let's begin.
I'm nearly done
with your thesis evaluations.
They don't look very good.
You've studied for one semester already.
Can someone summarize
what the core of this class is?
Professor.
The core of sales and marketing
is exchange, of course.
-Yes.
-It's exchange.
Daoming Si.
Very good.
Of course.
And Professor.
If you've carefully evaluated
all the thesis,
you'll realize that this class
has a lot of talent.
All right. Let's start class.
Let's begin.
It's so strange.
He hasn't interacted
with the professor much before.
Since when did he become so assertive?
For the first time...
The big bad wolf became a sheep.
Love is so powerful.
I'm so worried for Qinghe.
Seeing that professor's face,
I don't think there's much hope.
Yes, I agree.
It's entirely hopeless.
Chen Qinghe.
If you don't study hard,
you're wasting your own life.
But Shancai, you did so well earlier.
You handled it with ease. You were fine.
I was so nervous.
-No, I think--
-Dong Shancai.
You have such an incredible
boyfriend to help you.
Of course you'd be well-prepared.
What do you mean?
Look. Daoming Si and Dong Shancai
are in a relationship.
Why are you feigning innocence?
That's right.
We're in a relationship.
And it's going very well.
Thanks for your concern.
-I...
-You...
Let's go.
It's fine, Shancai. Don't mind them.
Shancai.
Are you really dating him?
I'm so furious.
Shancai.
Why am I so unlucky today?
Daoming Si.
What does your relationship status
post mean?
Which one?
The one that says we're in a relationship.
Is there a problem?
Isn't that a fact?
I guess so.
Since it's a fact, why do you mind?
It's not something
worth telling everyone about.
Why not?
I have a girlfriend.
I liked her for a long time.
Now she finally said yes.
The most important thing is
nobody can steal her from me.
And now I'm feeling happy every day.
I'm improving a lot.
Earlier, our professor
even complimented me.
The professor who had a 60 percent
chance of failing you?
How's that possible?
How's that impossible?
As long as I'm happy,
everything is possible.
-You're the stupid one.
-No, you're the stupid one.
I passed my exam earlier, okay?
That's all because of me.
Have you forgotten
who sacrificed sleeping at night
-and helped you study?
-Never mind. Let's just go.
Let's go.
Yes.
Thank you.
But didn't I also help you
with social anthropology
and sales and marketing?
I wanted to thank you for it.
But you came and blamed me
about posting our relationship status.
Sorry.
If apologies worked,
why would we need the police?
Then what do you want?
Go on a date with me.
Why are you laughing?
Do you want to come along?
Daoming Si.
Where do you want to go
after you graduate?
I thought you didn't care.
After I graduate,
I'll go back to London, I guess.
Back to London?
For a vacation?
Of course not.
I'll help with my family's business.
Then are you still coming back?
If I don't, would you be sad?
Of course.
Won't it be hard to see you then?
Why don't you
beg me?
Beg me and I'd consider staying
in Shanghai for you.
Really?
You'll stay if I beg you?
Will you beg me or not?
Will you die if you do that?
Of course I won't die.
But just stay if you want to stay.
Why do I need to beg you?
You silly girl.
Why are you so stupid?
You want me to say everything.
You're stupid.
What do you want me to stay?
You should say,
"Can you not go to London?
Can you go to graduate school
and wait for me to graduate?
Can you stay with me forever
after I graduate?"
Couldn't you say that?
Really?
You're going to graduate school here
so you can graduate with me?
Daoming Si.
What?
I'm so happy!
Seeing you smile so cheerfully,
I'm so happy too!
How silly.
Why are you here?
I'm waiting for you.
For me?
You're free, right?
I'm not.
I have a date with Meizuo.
A date?
Then why are you coming home?
I left earlier.
Then I realized I forgot something.
So I came back.
And I'm leaving now.
I'm not the police.
I'm not interrogating you.
Why give such a detailed explanation?
I...
I want to tell you something.
I'm in a hurry. Maybe next time.
Meizuo's waiting for me.
I'll drive you.
But...
Weren't you in a hurry?
And I know Meizuo too.
-Hello?
-Hello? Meizuo.
Where are you?
At my friend's house.
Can you come over now?
I need you.
Okay. Right away.
Guys, I need to go somewhere.
We just arrived.
What's the matter?
It's an emergency.
Have some fruit.
Shancai's still living here?
Where else should she live?
I mean, she can handle your mom
and stay here.
She's so brave.
It's true.
I shiver every time I hear his mom's name.
Is his mom that scary?
Oh please.
Because of her,
many of her business rivals
went bankrupt and homeless.
If she dislikes someone,
she'll ruthlessly eliminate him.
Stop it.
You even called her an "old hag."
I...
Did I say that?
Why don't I remember that?
We all heard it.
Don't think you could bully me
just because I'm young,
you old hag!
What did you say?
Say it again.
Old hag!
Yes, I'm calling you that.
You're not welcome in my world.
Get out.
I said leave!
When she comes home
and discovers that person
is living in her house
and dating her son,
can you guess
what she'd do?
Si, what's your plan?
She's my mom. What can I do?
But if she threatens Shancai,
I'll stand in front of her
and protect her.
My mom just comes home a few times a year.
I'm sure I'll think of something
before she comes back.
Meizuo.
What took you so long?
-Do you miss me that much?
-Listen to me.
When we walk to the bar there,
we have to pretend to be very sweet.
Then you have to say that we have a date,
but you're late.
All right?
Who should I say that to?
To that guy you met before.
Him again.
Why?
Don't ask.
Hurry. I'll tell you later.
Sorry.
I'm late.
That's fine.
You're even late on dates.
What a good boyfriend.
Why do you say that?
I respect girls.
I'm never late.
Then why was today an exception?
Because...
Because of me.
He's never late.
But because he's younger than me,
I don't mind even if he's late.
Right?
What do you mean?
All right. Never mind.
Since we're here to drink,
let's order, okay?
You can't drink. Don't drink anymore.
Then I'll order soda.
You guys can drink.
Okay?
I want something strong.
Can you drink?
You should ask if I've ever gotten drunk.
What matters is your behavior
after drinking,
not the amount you can drink.
What an immature thing to say.
It's basic etiquette for a man
to behave after drinking.
Why is it even worth mentioning?
Fine. Since you can drink a lot
and behave very well,
it's my treat tonight.
No problem.
Wei Xun.
Hey.
Please give this gentleman a red dynamite.
All right.
Sir.
Why are you here on my date with Caina?
I'm here to talk to Caina.
Can't you see that we're on a date?
Very well.
I'll say just it in front of him
rather than behind his back.
Makes sense. Go ahead.
I don't want to talk about that.
Let's talk another time.
Why?
Why not today?
Because I don't want
to talk about that now.
-What is it?
You know what I'm talking about.
Yes, that's the one.
So I don't want to
talk about that. Please.
Your red dynamite.
Bottoms up.
Red dynamite has all kinds of liquors
mixed with chili powder.
It'll knock you down afterwards.
Meizuo, did you make a mistake?
This is a cocktail for women.
Let's give it to Caina.
-Sure.
-No, you can't drink that.
Why?
I can handle cocktails.
This guy is so cunning.
You want to prank me? No way.
You won't get drunk
even if you drink this all night.
Really?
-Then let's order another one.
-That's right.
You missed the first one.
Another red dynamite.
All right.
Caina ordered this for you.
It should work this time.
Drink it. Very good.
Do you like it?
Yes.
That's great.
You both like it.
Darn boy. It's so hot.
I've decided.
It's my treat tonight.
Wei Xun. Two red dynamites for them.
-All right.
-I'll die if I have another one.
Here.
Your red dynamite.
Drink it.
Why aren't you drinking it?
Why not?
Yes.
Come on, Meizuo. Cheers.
Wait.
What were we talking about earlier?
We were talking about what Caina
doesn't want to talk about.
I remember now.
You're wondering why Caina was fine
the day before,
but she left the next day, right?
Yes.
What are you doing?
I don't want to talk about it.
Can't you guys just drink?
Drink.
I know!
Isn't it obvious?
Caina doesn't like you.
She regretted what happened.
So she left the next day.
Isn't that normal?
Is that so?
Isn't that so?
Caina, is that so?
You were just playing around with me?
-I'll drink it if you don't.
-Hey, Caina.
Caina.
Hey, Caina.
I don't want to go home.
What are you doing?
Let go.
You let go.
Caina's my girlfriend. Stay away.
-Caina.
-What are you doing?
-What do you want?
-Are you all right, Caina?
-Caina.
Come on. Get up.
My head's spinning.
It hurts.
Didn't we agree to go buy reference books?
But...
I want to go home and organize
my old clothes.
Your clothes?
I want to sell them as secondhand items
at an online store.
I'll earn money
and the clothes won't go to waste.
It saves space and can help those
who need it.
That's multiple wins. I'm smart, right?
You're really thoughtful.
I also need to go and clean your house.
That's what you're worried about?
-I'll just call Mrs. Yu.
-Don't.
I'm a cleaner at your house.
I don't want to have special privileges.
All right. I'll go by myself.
Text me the books you want.
I'll send you the book list later.
DEAL COMPLETED
I sold them in two hours.
This secondhand online store is great!
What's going on?
Mrs. Daoming is coming.
Why is she suddenly coming back?
I have to leave now.
Welcome home, ma'am.
Nothing happened when I was away, right?
No, ma'am.
Everything's all right.
Did you prepare my bath?
Yes.
Who allowed you to use your phones
while working?
It wasn't me. ma'am.
Then who was it?
Stop hiding. Come out.
Aren't you Dong Shancai,
who refused the five million yuan?
Why are you a maid at my house?
Mrs. Yu.
Can you explain it to me?
I was the one who hired Shancai.
Based on my observation,
she works really hard
and doesn't slack off.
She does her tasks well.
I hope she can stay here.
I won't ever allow
this kind of inferior girl in my house.
This kind of girl doesn't use tricks
but relies on her hard work to survive.
What's wrong with that?
Mrs. Yu.
Don't argue with her because of me.
I'll leave.
You're working in the Daoming household.
You're under my authority.
You can't leave.
Ma'am.
Ever since she came here,
Si studies very hard
and his temper has been tamed.
Shancai is a good influence on Si.
Si is improving because of her.
So,
can't you make considerations
for Si's sake?
If you let Shancai take care of Si
and Si changes for the better,
isn't that also good for you?
Mrs. Yu.
I respect you because you've stayed
in this household for 60 years.
However,
it doesn't mean you can do
whatever you want.
I won't allow this girl to date my son.
I brought Zhuang and Si up
all by myself.
I saw how you destroyed
Zhuang's happiness.
I made a vow
to never let Si experience the same pain.
I won't let Shancai
leave this house.
Why are you interfering with this?
Let me remind you.
I'm the master of this house,
not you.
Mrs. Daoming.
Have you forgotten
Si's grandpa's last wish?
Then let me remind you.
He said
that as long as I live,
I'll take charge
of this household.
What if I insist on sending her away?
Then,
please...
do it over my dead body.
When will you stop crying?
It's so annoying.
Looking at you cry
makes me feel like I'm dying.
I feel so sad.
I'm so mad and embarrassed.
Plus--
All right.
Drink this hot tea.
Don't think about anything anymore.
Thank you, Mrs. Yu.
You protected me
and you defended me.
I'm not sure how I can repay you.
No, don't.
Don't do anything.
Don't cause any trouble.
I had a hard time saving you
from the lion's den.
Just stay here.
Understand?
Sorry.
I used to think
that you're a harsh
and unreasonable old lady.
I am.
Look at your ugly face.
Stop staring at me.
I won't look at you then.
By the way, Mrs. Yu.
How did you end up
at the Daoming household?
It's a long story.
When I was
19 years old,
I was living alone
and I needed to pay off debts.
I was in a difficult situation.
Si's grandpa knew about my situation.
So he paid off my debts.
And let me work in the Daoming household.
My life
was saved by Si's grandpa.
So I've decided
to take care of the Daoming family
my whole life.
I'll use my life to repay them.
Later,
Mr. Daoming,
Si's dad,
slowly grew up
and graduated.
Mrs. Daoming married into the family.
Then Zhuang and Si were born.
This family was happy for decades.
What kind of person is Daoming Si's dad?
Mr. Daoming
was really nice.
He's very smart since he was little.
At a young age,
he handled the Daoming family's business.
And he didn't disappoint.
He works very hard
all day and all night.
I often told him
to take care of his health.
Don't wear himself out.
But he said, "I can't.
The company's employees
are depending on me.
How can I be lazy?"
He's really an outstanding person.
Indeed.
But I
would have wanted him to slack off a bit
and worry less.
I think I've heard Daoming Si mention
that his dad already passed away.
When Si was in high school,
he got liver cancer
and passed away.
What happened afterward?
After Mr. Daoming passed away,
Mrs. Daoming handled the Daoming Group.
This family
changed as a result.
They weren't happy anymore.
It slowly became cold.
Zhuang
really grew up
to be a kind girl indeed.
But Si's temper
cannot be controlled by anyone.
When Si was in high school,
he'd always come home with wounds.
We only found out
when the school notified us
that he'd been getting into fights.
Mrs. Daoming was worried,
but because she was busy with work,
she didn't have much time.
So she hired a tutor to discipline him.
Si, you're home.
-Your face--
-You're so annoying!
But it was useless.
More incidents kept on happening.
I was worried and sad
about what was happening.
I really didn't know what to do.
I've always been worried about Si.
After you came here,
I realized
that Si has changed.
Did he?
I didn't do anything.
I only...
Initially, I really hated him.
Whenever I don't agree with his ways,
I would beat him up.
Like this.
That's what I did.
That's right.
After Zhuang got married,
nobody here would dare to do that to him.
No.
The first time when I beat him up,
I also risked my life to do it.
It's scary when I think about it now.
If you ask me to beat him up now,
I wouldn't dare.
Shancai.
You can't leave this house.
I, Mrs. Yu,
would risk my life to protect you.
How's that possible?
Don't worry.
I've got a great plan.
A plan?
Mrs. Yu, I think it's quite late.
-I'll go ahead.
-You can't go.
If you dare to leave,
the next time you see me
would be at my funeral.
Mrs. Yu.
How can you threaten me that way?
All right. Tell me your plan.
My plan
is called...
the act first, report later, undercover,
secret, shotgun wedding plan.
Do you understand?
You spoke too fast.
I didn't hear you clearly.
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Coleen Chua
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene