A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN 2018
EPISODE 13
Zhou Caina is probably
Shancai's most formidable opponent.
They're all her opponents.
Junior champion
of Chinese Delicacies Competition,
finalist of Le Cordon Bleu
Girls Competition...
Even without those titles,
Shancai is nothing compared to her.
You're still drinking milk?
Are you even listening to us?
Do you want some? It's in the fridge.
Get some for yourself.
Is that supposed to be funny?
If Shancai loses,
don't come complaining to us.
Did you guys forget?
She's the only girl
that dares stand up to F4.
What can't she do?
I believe she can do it.
Just wait and see Shancai
surprises everyone.
Attitude determines everything.
When you're cooking in the kitchen,
your attitude is what's most important.
-Have you read the Book of Songs?
-Yes.
"The elegant virtuous maiden;
the noble person would love to marry her."
From now on,
I'll train you well
and turn you into a star chef!
Only when you combine
the Book of Songs and cuisine,
you will be able to make food
that has culture.
Those who eat the food
will experience amazement
deep down in their hearts.
Bring out the scallions.
Okay.
Why did you squeal?
Ms. Zhuang, you stepped on me
with your heels.
I'm sorry.
Make a pot of steaming hot soy milk
and instill your love
for your family in it.
That's what touches hearts.
Appetizers aren't the main course,
but they can complement the main course.
They help people build up an appetite
and make the meal unforgettable.
You and your dishes
will be engraved into their brains.
As long as you follow these principles,
you will be invincible
in the world of cuisine.
But, you must work hard
and practice continuously.
That's how you will improve.
I'll record everything I know
so you can listen
and practice at the same time.
Remember,
no slacking off.
Okay, Ms. Zhuang.
BOOK OF SONGS
"Like a gem cut and filed,
carved and polished."
Vertical cut, pushing cut, pulling cut,
sawing cut, rolling cut.
"As if at the brink of a deep abyss,
as if treading on thin ice."
When the water boils, add some salt.
Let it boil again and add cold water.
Take out the noodles quickly
and put them in iced water.
"The peach tree is young and elegant;
brilliant are its flowers."
Use high heat for raw ingredients,
medium heat for cooked ingredients,
and low heat for mixing ingredients.
When the oil is about 120 degrees heated,
throw in the spices to flavor the oil.
"Blue-collared lad,
you’ve long been in my heart."
Whether it be classic plating,
free form plating,
landscape plating, or radial plating,
remember, you must treat
your food as a work of art.
Lover ducks meeting at Magpie Bridge.
Mushrooms and assorted vegetables.
Abalone, chicken, and pickled vegetables.
Steamed lobsters with garlic.
Today, we're going
to practice cooking chicken.
We're making braised
sliced chicken with eggs.
Now, take out a whole chicken.
Check if all the feathers
have been plucked.
Next, marinate it in the sauce
you prepared beforehand.
Massage the chicken
and let the sauce sink in.
Zhuang, are you doing yoga?
Si, good thing you're here.
Take a video of me
so I can show my friends in London.
Why are you wearing earphones?
I want to look professional.
Enough talking. Get ready.
-Ready?
-Yeah.
There's skill involved
in massaging the chicken.
Hello, Mom. I'm busy right now.
I'll call you back later.
There's a skill involved
in massaging the chicken.
Okay, make a circle
with your right leg three times.
Okay, now your left leg.
Now, relax your neck.
Turn to the right, three times.
Okay, let's relax your whole body.
Slap your body.
Now, put your hands up,
exhale.
Repeat after me.
All right, last of all,
lower your head between your legs.
Go low for me, come on.
Last three breaths. Repeat after me.
Zhuang,
why are you here?
-I was worried you would disturb Shancai.
-What?
I was just tucking her in.
"Nights of Azure Aea and Blue Skies."
"Famed Peony, Fairest Lady in Bliss."
-"Fine Wine in a Luminous Glass."
-"Famed Peony, Fairest Lady in Bliss."
"Shepherd Points
to Almond Flower Village."
"South of the River,
the Grass Grows High While it Rains."
"The Moon is Low,
Crows Caw in the Frosty Sky."
-"The Swallow Returns from Familiar Days."
-Wait.
It's just food.
Why are you giving the dishes
such complicated names?
These are all dishes inspired
by Tang poetry.
Shancai worked very hard on them.
Try the food.
They all taste great.
Which one is your least favorite?
Which one?
I guess, this one.
Improve the shepherd dish.
Okay.
Which has the worst colors?
-Zhuang. I don't want--
-Which one?
I guess, this one.
Improve the moon and crow dish.
Okay.
Which one is the most delicious?
"The Peony and Lady" one was the best.
That was a failed dish.
You probably only remember
that dish's name.
Nope.
This one was "The Bird Returns
from Familiar Days."
I liked this one the most.
It's "The Swallow Returns
from Familiar Days."
Don't be picky about the details.
You're right.
That chicken dish was impeccable.
Don't feel too proud.
Keep working hard.
Be diligent at all times.
-"As if at the brink of a deep abyss,
-as if treading on thin ice."
Ice cream?
Let's eat.
What's Shancai up to lately?
I think she's preparing for a competition.
Competition?
Good morning, you two.
I was going to class
to have you try this dessert I made.
Good thing I saw you here.
What a coincidence.
Please try this.
Let me know what you think.
This is so good.
Yeah, Shancai, this is amazing.
What is it?
"The Chinese Courtesan,
The Beautiful, Youthful,
Sweet-scented Dong Xiaowan."
It's just a sesame ball.
Normal sesame balls don't have culture.
This is different.
By the way, what is Dong Xiaowan?
Well, Dong Xiaowan was a person.
I guess you didn't know that.
Who's Dong XIaowan?
She was one of
the Eight Beauties of Qinhuai.
An outstanding cook as well.
Do you understand now, dear sir?
Shancai, what did you just call me?
Dear sir.
Li Zhen, what's wrong with her?
Ms. Zhuang said...
Ms. Zhuang said
I need to be lady-like at all times.
That's how I can be more elegant.
By doing so in daily life,
I can be more natural
during the competition.
Is this what you call natural?
It sounds like you're a machine.
You were cuter the way you were.
Really?
Did I go too far?
It's not like you're in a play.
It's not weird when Ms. Zhuang does it.
Why is it so weird when I do it?
It's fine. Shancai, just keep trying.
What competition were you talking about?
Chinese Cuisine Culinary Competition.
I'm participating in the contest
so I can pay Si back with the prize money.
My fair lady, I'm sure you'll win.
-Qinghe.
-Yes?
What did you just call me?
Gosh,
Shancai influenced me.
Now I'm talking weird.
You must work hard, my lady.
I will.
Why are you participating
in the cooking competition?
I saw your name online.
Because I need money.
Did you know there's
a contestant called Zhou Caina?
-Zhou Caina?
-Yes.
Her dad is the founder
of Double-X Real Estate Group.
My dad wants me to marry her.
She must be good then.
If I'm not mistaken,
she's competing because of me.
Why?
She knows I like cooking.
She wants to prove that she has
the same hobby as I do.
It's not just because
our families arranged it.
She's trying very hard. Do you like her?
She's very pretty,
elegant, and talented.
But I don't like her.
The person I like...
You know about that.
So, you're trying to tell me
I might be beaten
by your childhood friend?
I'm suggesting that you give up.
You won't win the prize.
Zhou Caina was a finalist
in Le Cordon Bleu Girls Competition.
She's going to win the competition.
Shancai, I know your capability.
There's a huge difference between you two.
If you compete with her,
you'll embarrass yourself.
THE EXTRAORDINARY ZHOU CAINA
Zhou Caina was a finalist
in Le Cordon Bleu Girls Competition.
She's going to win the competition.
She's so talented.
Even if I don't eat, drink, sleep,
and just study
for three years straight, I can't win.
How can I win?
I'm going to embarrass myself.
No.
I should go tell Ms. Zhuang
that I'm quitting.
Let me tell you.
I hate those people
who think that they'll lose
even before they enter the competition.
That kind of people
would never succeed no matter what.
Never mind.
Ms. Zhuang would beat me to death.
I'll just secretly leave
and explain everything to her later.
Are you running away?
I'm going to find a way to pay you back.
I thought you were a special girl.
But you're just another coward
who runs away when things get tough.
If I can't win, why should I compete?
You're so weak.
I'm not weak.
But how am I supposed
to compete with someone
who competed in Le Cordon Bleu
Girls Competition in high school?
-I don't want to disappoint everyone.
-What about disappointing me?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I let you down.
You're being ridiculous.
This isn't the Dong Shancai I know.
You don't have the right to say that.
You've never failed
in your whole life growing up.
Do you know how much stress I'm under?
Why do you care about what people think?
Just do what you want to do.
There's always a chance.
Why aren't you being mean anymore?
Why are you being so gentle?
Come to my room.
What are we doing?
Sleep. What else would it be?
Hurry up. I don't want you
to worry too much.
Your room is so big.
I'm kind of thirsty.
Do you want some water?
Here.
Are you tired?
Then...
Do you want to play?
You're very bold.
You tricked me!
I won't go easy on you.
One, two, three, four, five.
You didn't want me
to make it easy for you.
I won.
You cheated.
Hey, don't be a sore loser, okay?
-No.
-No?
You already got away with it a few times.
We're going through with it this time.
Don't make me look ugly.
Don't move. Or it'll ruin my masterpiece.
What are you drawing?
You'll see later.
Aren't you getting up yet?
Or, do you want
to play rock-paper-scissors?
Sure.
I won't lose this time.
Do you want to win so much?
Of course.
It'll be embarrassing if I lose again.
How about you take that spirit
and use it during the competition?
Do you think rock-paper-scissors
is the same as the competition?
Rock-paper-scissors is about pure luck.
The cooking competition is about skill.
Shancai,
I believe in you. You can do it.
You should believe in yourself too.
You're actually pretty cute up close.
I rarely compliment people.
You should be proud.
Let's play again.
Give it your best.
Daoming Si, thank you.
I'll try my best.
What? Shancai disappeared?
-Yes.
-Did you look for her?
I did.
I called the school and her family.
But, the weird thing is,
Shancai's luggage is in the hall.
Where's Si?
He's sleeping.
I didn't want to disturb him.
Shancai's gone and he's sleeping?
Hey, Daoming Si!
Who said you could take
these ugly pictures of me?
What? I think they're cute.
Cute? They're hideous.
Hey, what are you doing?
You can't rip them up.
They're mine.
It's my face.
I didn't give you permission.
Hey!
Calm down!
-Calm down?
-Hey!
I won't!
So, Si, how's Shancai doing?
It's going great.
My sister and I are very confident.
Really?
Ms. Zhuang thinks she'll win?
Especially that dish called
"The Bird Returns from Familiar Days."
It's better than any dish I've ever had
made by famous cooks.
Isn't it "The Swallow Returns
from Familiar Days"?
It's a famous poem by Yan Shu.
Whatever.
It's just chicken.
I don't understand
what the fancy name is for.
Food is not just for the taste buds,
it's a form of cultural exchange.
Shancai has really improved.
But, even if she cooked rat poison,
Si would gobble it up right away.
Shut up.
I'm very objective, okay?
It's really tasty.
Here. This is tasty too.
More importantly, this Zhou Caina
seems to be the most likely to win.
I read about her.
She's smart, pretty, and elegant.
I wonder if she has a boyfriend.
Just wait and see.
I don't care if she's Caina, Lina, Xiena,
or even Madonna.
Shancai's cooking skills
will not disappoint you guys.
Let's hope the judges
will be able to see her true talent
and appreciate her for being different.
Who said she's different?
Bye.
The competition is starting soon.
I don't know if Shancai has a chance.
Honestly, Chinese cuisine
is deep and profound.
It's not something she can master
in a short time.
But I think her basic skills
are very solid indeed.
Shancai's dishes are very natural
and they're free
from excessive processing,
which is a lot like her personality.
Maybe during the competition,
she'll be able to find her niche.
"Like a gem cut and filed,
carved and polished."
"As if at the brink of a deep abyss,
as if treading on thin ice."
"The peach tree is young and elegant;
brilliant are its flowers."
"Blue-collared lad,
you’ve long been in my heart."
QINGHE HAS SENT YOU A QQ MESSAGE
Shancai, what are you doing after class?
I need to practice cooking.
Done.
"The Swallow Returns
from Familiar Days," version two.
Please enjoy.
What's this dish called?
"The Return of the Double Swallows."
There's only one chicken. Why double?
Ms. Zhuang, you'll know once you try it.
This chicken...
It's magnificent.
One side tastes sweet and sour,
one side has the fragrance of oranges.
It's too special!
Shancai,
how did you come up with this idea?
My mom's signature dish
is sweet and sour pork ribs.
I dedicate this dish to her.
There's a lot of vitamin C in oranges.
They're healthy and nutritious.
I want to share this dish with everyone
to help people eat healthier.
Shancai, you're very smart.
After using the orange juice,
you didn't throw them out.
You used them as decorations.
I really think you can go
to the competition now.
Shancai, are you busy?
I'm sorry,
I shouldn't have said that yesterday.
I know deep down that I'm not good enough.
So I never thought that
I would be able to enter the competition.
But, I want to seize this opportunity.
I don't want to let down
the people who helped me along the way.
Is one of them Daoming Si?
He's one of them.
I never would've guessed.
I thought you didn't like him.
I don't know.
In the beginning, I really hated him.
Sometimes I still want to punch him.
But, he's always been by my side
in a very peculiar way
and I couldn't help but notice him.
When I want to run away,
one look at him gives me courage.
I don't know how this happened.
Shancai,
you can probably tell
that I like you, right?
I think we'd be great together
if Si didn't exist in this world.
I hate to admit that
I lost to a guy like that.
Tian Ye,
I wish you all the best.
In the future, you'll become a great chef.
You'll own a fantastic restaurant
and meet a wonderful woman.
For real. Because you're
a wonderful person, too.
Thank you.
Shancai,
I hope you'll find happiness.
All right, I have to go now.
Shancai, you can stay here.
Leave after I'm out the door.
Because I don't have money for the bill.
Just kidding.
I just don't want to watch you leave.
Bye.
What?
You're competing in
Chinese Cuisine Culinary Competition?
No wonder you've been so busy lately.
Shancai, that's awesome!
Who's your teacher?
The restaurant you work at?
No, it's Daoming Si's sister.
She and her chef have been teaching me.
That's great.
She seems to be very nice.
How kind of them.
Next time, invite her to our house.
Your mom will cook them some food.
I can't do that.
They're professionals.
My food could never satisfy them.
That's not true.
My mom's cooking
-is the best in the world.
-That's right.
My wife's cooking
is healthy and delicious.
-Really?
-Yes.
All right, Shancai,
do your best at the competition today.
Dad and I will watch it on the TV.
-All right?
-Okay.
-Go!
CHINESE CUISINE CULINARY COMPETITION
Ladies and gentlemen, hello.
Sponsored by high-end
smart kitchen electronics brand, Vatti,
and Nongfu Spring mineral water,
we will now begin the sixth
Chinese Cuisine Culinary Competition.
Our exclusive broadcasting platform
is Tencent Now Live,
streaming our content
right here, right now, live.
Now, let us introduce
our outstanding judges.
Experienced cuisine
and culture expert, Tu Xiaowen.
Cooking expert on Chinese cuisine,
Zhang Jinbao.
The pickiest food expert
of the South, Wu Lihua.
And the most beautiful senior
at Mingde, Tang Jingmei.
After our strict open audition,
a total of ten contestants have advanced.
One of them will be the winner.
The winner will receive one million yuan
and a set of Vatti high-end
smart kitchen electronics.
Our contestants are preparing
backstage right now.
Let's go there right now
and check out what they're doing.
After many rounds of elimination,
ten contestants have made it
to the final round.
All the contestants are now backstage
preparing for the competition.
Hello, I'm Zhou Caina, I graduated
from the University of California.
Nice to meet everyone.
Hello, I'm Xu Meixin, I graduated
from Sun Yat-sen University.
-Thank you.
-Hello.
My name is Li Fangru, I just graduated
from Chinese University of Hong Kong.
Hello, I'm Gao Xinting. Please support me.
I'm Dai Jingjing.
Please cheer for me. Thank you.
BACKSTAGE: MINGDE UNIVERSITY DONG SHANCAI
I'm...
Hi, I'm Dong Shancai.
-It's Shancai.
-Shancai!
-We're here. Shancai!
Go, Shancai!
Shancai!
What are you doing?
-Go!
-What are you doing?
-Look.
Mom, Dad, I'm on TV!
Shancai!
Hey, look!
-It's our daughter!
-Shancai said she's on TV.
What a cute girl.
Now, we'll hand it over
to today's host for the competition.
We've introduced all our contestants.
I'm sure our viewers have a good idea
of who all our chefs are.
Going into commercials now
and then we'll see who gets a head start.
That Dong Shancai is so funny.
She's such a dork.
In my opinion, the organizers
wanted someone funnier
so the audience would feel entertained.
Hello, I'm Zhou Caina.
Hello.
I know about you. You're famous.
I'm Dong Shancai.
I know you too.
-You're famous too.
-Me?
That's impossible.
We have a mutual friend, don't we?
I've heard Tian Ye say
that you're very special.
No, that's not true.
It's all right. Good luck.
Don't get eliminated in the first round.
Compared to those showoffs,
I like opponents like you more.
What the hell?
There are so many commercials.
Si, the official competition
hasn't started yet.
Just be patient.
It's been forever.
It's been like one hour, right?
It's only been five minutes, okay?
He's in love. Days feel like years to him.
That Caina looks even better in person.
You're watching someone else?
Si's going to beat you up.
I now announce
that the sixth Chinese Cuisine
Culinary Competition starts now.
CHINESE CUISINE COOKING COMPETITION
The first round of this competition
is stir-frying and slow stewing.
The contestants can pick
any ingredients they need
and complete their dishes
within two hours.
Four contestants will be
eliminated in this round.
We can see that our contestants
have chosen their ingredients.
They will have to work fast.
The main criteria for cutting
is to cut cleanly and precisely.
This can help the ingredients
suit the method of cooking.
The ingredients should be
of the same thickness and length.
This will ensure that the ingredients
will be cooked thoroughly
at the same time.
It seems like our contestants
have all decided to start
with the stewing part.
Zhou Caina is making a duck dish.
The duck is placed downwards in the pot.
Jinhua ham is used to give it flavor.
This should be a very healthy duck soup
with handmade fish balls.
Dong Shancai is now
frying the meatballs she just made.
She's probably making braised pork balls.
Shancai's making my signature dish!
When did you ever make that?
Once or twice.
The contestants are putting their pots
on the stove to stew.
They need to constantly check
the heat and be patient.
The first round has a two-hour time limit.
They have only 15 minutes left.
Excuse me.
Dong Shancai has finally moved
her pot to the stove.
Will her dish be done
within the time limit?
Excuse me.
Thank you.
I'm telling you, Shancai is only
using 50 percent of her skills now.
-Wait and see.
-What about Zhou Caina?
She's going to get eliminated for sure.
While waiting for the pot to heat up,
the contestants are now
starting to make their stir-fry dish.
Stir-frying is an important skill
in Chinese cuisine.
It is essential to control the heat,
mix the ingredients,
and add everything in the right sequence.
This affects the taste of the dish
and shows the contestant's skills.
We can see Dong Shancai's ingredients.
She's going to make crystal prawn balls,
a Shanghai cuisine.
On the other side,
Zhou Caina is placing crab into the wok.
She's making a Cantonese dish,
fried crab with chili.
Fried crab with chili may seem simple,
but it's hard to get right.
Zhou Caina is really something.
Shancai's crystal prawn balls
look so good!
I'm starting to drool.
Who will be able to advance
to the next round?
We are about to find out.
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Sophie Chang
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene