A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES:
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 32
You're an idiot.
Okay.
What do you plan to do?
Quietly look out for Shancai?
What do you mean?
Didn't Huaze Lei confess
to Shancai today?
Also, the problem with Xiaoyou
and Qinghe's families.
There are so many obstacles
standing in your way.
That's not important.
What's important is
Shancai's feelings.
But Shancai said
that she feels at peace
-with Huaze Lei.
-I don't want her to feel at peace!
I want us to be together.
Whether there are obstacles
or if Shancai's undecided
on whoever she likes,
I want to get her back.
Daoming Si, you're such a nice guy.
Why aren't you mine?
Xiaozi.
Fine.
I was just kidding. Okay?
I support you.
TALENT'S TEA SHOP
Your White Jasmine Dew.
I still remember the first time
you came here.
You didn't actually like milk tea.
But you ordered it
because of its unique name.
You still remember that?
Where's your friend Xiaoyou?
Why isn't she here today?
She's busy with her finals.
So she's got the day off.
I'll wait for you and take you home later.
Lei.
I'm grateful you brought me back
from the fishing village.
You decorated my place,
helped me with my assignments,
stayed beside me, and took care of me
during my most difficult times.
And the song you played
was really nice.
I really liked it.
I'm really grateful...
to you.
You really are a nice guy.
I did those things because I wanted to.
We can't be together.
Don't worry.
I just want to be nice to you.
Maybe there won't be an opportunity
for me to do so in the future.
Right now, these are
unforgettable memories for me.
Shancai.
This is the first time
I don't have to think about Si
and just be with you.
Are you used to living alone?
It's all right.
I keep myself busy as much as possible.
That way, I have less time
to think about it.
You sound like Jing.
Jing?
Since I left France,
Jing was alone.
Even though that was her decision,
I went there and left.
It'd be worse if I didn't go there at all.
I know.
When you enter someone's life,
she'll have expectations of you.
When you leave,
her life goes back to square one.
The disappointment and sadness
are even more unbearable.
You're right.
But I wasn't thinking clearly at the time.
I wasn't sure how to face her.
So I left.
But Jing didn't blame me.
She just said
she made herself busier
to tire herself out.
To numb herself.
Do you regret it?
I do.
I regret giving up on her so easily.
I regret not holding on
a little longer that time.
Shancai.
Do you get it?
Hold on a little longer.
If you do,
a lot of things might end up differently.
But if you miss that opportunity,
you'll regret it your whole life.
Regret?
Your decision
determines the outcome,
whether it's a happy ending or a sad one.
If you still don't know
what you want to do,
then hold on a little longer.
Just like Si.
Even though he's immature,
he's very sincere.
He's still holding on
to his love for you.
Didn't you say
that Si can recover as quickly as a dog?
I think that's how he is
when it comes to love too.
What do you think, Mrs. Yu?
Do I give out
powerful vibes?
What's wrong?
Is there something on my face?
Si.
Right now,
you're back at being your old self.
Of course.
I'm not like you,
who's a flickering candle.
You're joking around again.
You meant to say,
"A candle in the wind," right?
Silly boy.
Silly boy?
You can call me silly.
I'm going to do the silliest thing
I'll ever do in my life.
This boy.
Doesn't he still have
a lot of silly things
that he's never done in his life yet?
Lei, I want to tell you something.
Okay.
Shancai's mine.
Does that mean you're competing with me?
I accept your challenge.
Why are you smiling?
So you're not giving up on her?
That's right.
I can't let her be with another guy.
I want to win her heart.
Regardless if it's my mom or you...
Even if the whole world wants me
to give up on her,
I'd never leave Shancai.
In that case, let Shancai choose.
TALENT'S TEA SHOP
Hello?
Shancai, promise me one thing.
What is it?
Turn off your cell phone
for 48 hours starting now.
Turn off my phone for 48 hours?
Why?
I don't want to.
POWER OFF
Shancai, why did you turn off your phone?
Turn to chapter two.
Is there anything I can do for you?
Sorry, professor.
I'm looking for Dong Shancai.
She didn't come to class today.
Let's continue.
The number you are calling
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
Hey, have you seen Shancai?
The number you are calling
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
The number you are calling
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
Qinghe.
What?
Come here.
Wait for me.
What's the matter?
Where's Shancai?
Why do you want to know?
Cut the crap. Tell me.
I'm not telling you even if I know.
Tell me now.
All right. Let go of me.
Shancai...
Shancai didn't come to school today.
Hi, is Shancai here?
Shancai? She already left.
Shancai.
Shancai!
The number you are calling
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
The number you are calling
cannot be reached.
Sir, I want to report a crime.
There's a thief.
Dong Shancai.
No matter where you're hiding,
I'll find you.
I bought the moisturizer
you recommended in Canada
right after I returned.
Doesn't it nicely tighten
and moisturize your skin?
It's made from the finest herbs.
Safe and effective.
Look. I don't have fine lines anymore.
See.
Is Jiang Xiaoyou smart or what?
Yes.
Shancai, thanks for helping me
look for venues today.
You must come to the tea ceremony.
No problem.
However,
why did Huaze Lei call and tell me
to hold you up
as long as possible?
He said that?
Why?
I'm not sure either.
Huaze Lei is very mysterious.
Here. Have some fruit.
Thank you, Mrs. Jiang.
Shancai.
You haven't been here for so long.
Look. I prepared your favorite fruit.
-Eat more.
-Okay.
It's so sweet.
You're such a foodie.
I am and so are you.
This happiness
was almost gone because of me.
Yesterday, I was still thinking
if I should be true to myself.
But if I do that,
I might hurt people around me
and not be able to live with myself.
Hey.
What is Si doing?
Why isn't he back yet?
I have a feeling
that Si won't be back tonight.
You're trying to say something.
Tell me. What's going on?
Si called me yesterday
and asked where Shancai lives.
Is Si pursuing Shancai again?
No way.
Isn't Shancai with Lei now?
I'll call Si.
Hello?
Hello, Si.
Where are you now?
I'm coming.
Who's being so rude?
Who are you looking for?
Shancai stayed here last night.
But a guy picked her up earlier.
Lei.
You haven't told me yet.
Why did you ask me
to turn off my cell phone?
To avoid unnecessary disturbance.
Unnecessary disturbance?
You mean...
Daoming Si told me
he's not giving up on you.
What do you think?
I've already decided.
Are you sure?
Yes.
This decision was really hard to make.
I admit that I hesitated.
But since I already knew the outcome,
I can't just
blindly hold on.
I know Si has been looking for you
and waiting for you.
He's been holding on.
I'm going to work.
I'll go with you.
Shancai!
Don't go.
Don't go with Lei.
Don't leave me.
Si.
Shancai already made her choice.
Why should she stay with you?
Screw her choice!
Shancai.
I can't be without you.
I can't live without you.
Daoming Si.
Let's just give up.
Stop holding on anymore.
Absolutely not.
My life has no meaning without you.
When I'm awake,
you're all I think of.
When I close my eyes, you're in my dreams.
I can only think of one thing.
I can't live without you.
Shancai.
I've always done
what I wanted to do before.
But I don't know what to do anymore.
Please tell me.
What should I do
for me to continue loving you?
Si.
If your love brings problems to Shancai,
are you sure that will make her happy?
Shancai.
You know you're the only one for me.
Trust me.
I'll definitely make you happy.
Shancai.
If you're sure about your decision,
I'll support you no matter what.
Shancai!
-Faster. Go faster.
-Shancai!
Don't let me hear his voice again.
Shancai!
Daoming Si.
-My heart...
-Shancai!
...is going to break apart.
Shancai!
Stop looking.
-Don't get off if you've already decided.
-Shancai!
Don't give him any more chances.
Shancai!
Daoming Si!
You're such a fool.
Do you know how dangerous that was?
She looks like the one in the picture.
Let's go.
Wait. It's a misunderstanding.
Daoming Si, wait for me.
I won't leave you anymore.
Hey, Daoming Si.
Someone reported
that their meteor necklace went missing.
Is it with you?
Meteor necklace?
Yes, it is.
But I didn't steal it.
-Are you admitting it?
-I...
The person who reported it
said he was mistaken.
We're responsible to protect the citizens.
We'll thoroughly investigate
every crime reported.
I'm really sorry.
I reported it without checking properly.
-Please forgive me.
-All right.
Since it's your first offense
and you've regretted your actions,
we'll let you go this time.
Don't do it again, okay?
Thank you, sir.
Daoming Si.
Why did you do that?
What do you mean?
Silly girl, where did you go?
Dong Shancai, listen carefully.
No matter where you're hiding,
I'll find you.
Silly girl.
Why did you keep calling me that?
You're a silly boy, right?
Why were you hiding?
Didn't I tell you before?
No matter what happens,
I need to know where you are.
So you asked the police to arrest me?
You're so smart.
I almost got myself a criminal record!
Then what did you want me to do?
I almost went crazy looking for you.
You've been...
looking for me?
What did you think?
You didn't attend class or go to work.
You didn't go home.
Your phone was turned off.
Do you want me to die from stress?
Why did you disappear?
Thank you
for looking for me.
Daoming Si.
I thought you'd never come back
to me anymore.
I've always pushed myself into a corner
and trapped myself in fear and pain.
However,
even if I regret it later,
I want to hold on to my happiness now.
Are you hungry?
It wasn't me.
I'm sure it was you. I heard it.
The sound came from your stomach!
-Why are you accusing me?
-Just because...
All right. Since you looked so cute
when you accused me,
a chivalrous person like me
won't argue with you anymore.
When did I accuse you?
All right. Let's eat.
Why are you holding my hand so tightly?
I'm afraid you'll run away.
I'm thinking
I should have borrowed handcuffs
from that officer earlier.
Then you won't be able to run away.
Silly boy.
Let's go eat ramen.
Ramen?
Why should we eat ramen?
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking of eating ramen.
Then what are you thinking?
It suddenly feels like we're flirting.
What should I do to break the awkwardness?
I know.
You're thinking about me, right?
Stop being so narcissistic.
Goodness. What did I just say?
It's even more awkward now.
That's so funny.
How is that funny?
Are we eating or not?
-Wasn't it funny?
-Not at all.
-Okay.
-It was not funny.
Hey!
Sir, can you please stop the bus?
I'm begging you! It's very important.
Shancai.
Are you sure?
Lei, I want to give it a try.
Compared to trying my best and failing,
not trying at all would make me
regret it even more.
Excuse me.
This is your ramen. Please enjoy.
It looks so good.
-Okay, thanks.
-You're welcome.
Why aren't you eating?
I'm suddenly not that hungry.
It's such a waste not to eat it.
Okay, fine.
How is it? Is it good?
Yes, it's all right.
Hey.
Do you have a passport?
Yes, I do.
I applied for one
the last time I went overseas.
Then there's no problem.
What are you talking about?
Shancai, let's go to London together.
You mean...
that newly-opened London coffee shop?
I think we need to come up
with a plan soon.
My mom is not that easy to handle.
Wait.
Aren't we being too rash?
Don't you want to?
No.
I don't.
Why?
What do you mean?
I don't want to go to a foreign country.
I don't have friends there
and my English is bad.
I'm not used to Western food.
What if I get sick?
Then why did you get off the bus?
Did I misunderstand?
Why did you get off the bus?
Is this guy
pushing me to make things clear?
Can't I get off the bus?
I see.
Then I'll go ahead.
What exactly am I saying?
Daoming Si, wait!
I...
I want to say...
Good night.
That's it?
That's it.
Why are you looking for me?
I just want to tell you in person
that Shancai is mine.
Don't bother her anymore.
So you're together now?
Is Shancai your girlfriend?
That's none of your business!
I don't think she is.
I still have a chance then.
Don't you get it?
Tell me that you're giving up on Shancai.
I don't see why I should do that.
Huaze Lei.
Am I not your friend anymore?
You know I can't live without Shancai.
-You know I--
-I don't.
You...
I know you hurt her with your temper.
How could I hurt her?
Give up on Shancai, understand?
I'm not deaf. You don't have to shout.
I don't care what you think.
I'm warning you.
Shancai is mine.
I, Daoming Si, will be
responsible for her.
I'll take care of her.
I won't let her be with a guy like you.
A guy who has no conscience and loyalty.
Do you hear that?
Oh, all right.
What do you mean, "Oh, all right"?
What exactly...
What did you say again?
I said all right.
I'll give up on Shancai.
Why?
-So I can pursue Shancai?
-No.
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Coleen Chua
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene