A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 6
Fine.
If you don't know how to play Bridge,
you can set the rules.
I'll decide what you wager.
Is that fair?
They're setting the rules?
I'm never unfair to people.
You mean, we're not playing Bridge?
We could play Five-card stud.
What stud?
What can you play?
We'll compare hands.
What?
Compare hands?
We'll each pick a card
and compare them to see who wins.
Do you think this is kindergarten?
You said we could set the rules.
All right.
We'll compare hands.
-Why aren't they out yet?
-Who won?
I think so too.
Shancai could never win, right?
-Yeah.
There's something wrong with her.
Regardless of which game,
F4 has never lost before.
One round. Go.
Pick a card.
I only get one chance.
Which one should I pick?
We'll lose if I choose the wrong card.
I'm so nervous.
This one?
Or this one?
I can't decide.
Hey.
Are you done yet?
Ace of hearts.
You got the ace of hearts.
We won!
How about that?
We win, unless you get the ace of spades.
Which is impossible.
Your turn.
How is that possible?
Wait.
You shuffled the cards.
What if you're cheating?
Five of clubs.
Six of diamonds.
Eight of hearts.
Jack of spades.
Two of spades.
Ten of diamonds.
Three of clubs, nine of diamonds,
five of hearts, king of hearts.
Wait.
You don't have
the ace of spades. You lose.
That's because it's in your pocket.
Why is it in my pocket?
Who put it in there?
Do you think the champion team
of the World Bridge Competition
would lose to you?
Meizuo has impeccable eyes.
He's second to none.
No matter what we play,
you'll lose for sure.
So? Another round?
We lost.
What do you want?
This is between you and Si.
We'll back out of this.
What do you mean it's between them?
What about me?
Hey. What are you doing?
What will you do to Shancai? Hey!
Let go!
Let go of me!
Daoming Si, come at me if you want!
Don't touch Shancai!
Let go!
What are you doing?
So, what do you want from me?
Do I have to eat some slippers?
What do you want?
Treat me to dinner.
What did you say?
Stop pretending you can't hear me.
You did that last time at the airport.
Now you're doing it again.
It's infuriating.
Treat.
Me.
To.
Dinner!
Did you hear me?
QQ MESSAGE FROM DAOMING SI
See you at 12:00 p.m.
at the Jiangwan Stadium Plaza.
What does he want?
So weird.
Oh, it's Qinghe.
Shancai, are you okay?
Ximen and Meizuo just let me go.
I've been worried sick.
Did they make you eat something weird?
Should we go to the hospital?
I would rather eat slippers.
What?
You ate slippers?
No, I mean--
Hello?
Stupid Si.
He's going to find
a way to bully me again.
My phone is broken because of him.
I'm not going.
Let's see what he'll do.
SHANGHAI INTERNATIONAL COMMERCIAL HUB
Shancai, what do you think of this one?
It's nice. You can buy it if you like it.
We've been shopping for hours now.
You can't rush shopping.
It'll affect your decisions.
Shancai, look.
Isn't this one nice?
Here. Try it on.
This...
It's so expensive.
Don't worry about that.
Hurry up and try it.
-Hurry.
-Okay.
It's getting colder. You need new clothes.
You can't always wear your old ones.
I know it would look nice.
Even though you aren't
as pretty as your mom,
your figure is acceptable.
It's raining.
Is he waiting for me?
Mom, I need to be somewhere.
I'll meet up with you later.
Hey, I haven't paid for that yet.
Silly girl. We only have one umbrella.
How will I get home?
He's still there.
Why are you standing here?
What are you doing? Let go.
It's cold.
Do you know what time it is?
I've been waiting for three hours.
I never said I would come.
You lost. You don't get to decide.
You bought new clothes for our date?
It's only 799 yuan? That's cheap.
You should go home.
Why did you keep waiting?
I couldn't reach you on your phone.
I was worried you came
and couldn't find me
or that you had an accident.
I couldn't leave even
when it started to rain.
Fine.
-Let's go indoors.
-Okay.
Over here.
Let me hold that. Silly girl.
Where are we going?
-To get food.
-What?
Where are you taking me?
I know this place.
They have delicious food.
It's only 50 yuan per person.
Fifty yuan?
Are we having grass or something?
They have lots of options. It's great.
Let's go.
Can't you walk faster?
-Fine.
-You're so slow.
That's weird...
The shops aren't open here.
Thank god. Let's go.
-No.
-Why?
I know another place.
They have good noodles.
Let's go. Come on.
It's delicious.
-Hurry up.
-Fine.
What's going on?
Over there. This way.
UNDER RENOVATION
I know another place up there that's good.
-Come on.
-We're going up again?
We can take the elevator.
Hurry up.
ELEVATOR UNDER MAINTENANCE
DO NOT USE
Nobody dares to let me go hungry.
Food's more delicious when you're hungry.
What? Is this stupid elevator broken?
That's ridiculous.
Is anyone there?
Help!
-Hey.
Help! Is anyone there?
Hey. Help!
Help!
I think it's broken.
Are you kidding me?
What a stupid elevator.
Stop that, okay?
If the elevator falls, we'll die.
Then what are we supposed to do now?
My stupid phone is dead again.
Where's your phone?
I called you for four hours straight.
What do you think?
Then...
We'll have to wait here.
Hello, Li Zhen?
I'm Shancai's mom.
Yes. I'm her mom.
Did Shancai call you?
She's not picking up?
I know. I've been calling her too.
She hasn't picked up.
She hasn't called back either.
Okay.
If she calls you, let me know.
Okay. Thanks.
Hey. Help!
Can't you see we're stuck?
Hey.
Dear,
something's wrong.
Shancai hasn't called me yet.
She isn't picking up.
I called Li Zhen,
she hasn't heard from Shancai either.
She's really lost.
Where are you? Why aren't you home yet?
You're at the BBQ stand?
BBQ...
Can you bring some home?
With no pepper.
Okay.
Why am I crying?
Do you think I want to cry?
These onions are really something.
Hey.
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Your clothes are drenched.
You have a fever.
Try standing in the rain for four hours.
Lie down.
You should get some rest.
Try to stay conscious.
Someone will come for us soon.
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
But you're the one
who insisted on coming here.
If you didn't insist on coming here,
we wouldn't be stuck here.
What's so funny?
I'm hungry and tired
and I was in the rain for so long.
It's normal that my stomach is growling.
Okay.
Right now, I'm the only one
that can take care of you.
When you get home,
your mom will take care of you.
I haven't seen my mom for two years.
Two years?
My dad...
He died when I was in middle school.
My mom had to work in London.
When we called her,
we always got her assistant instead.
So we stopped calling.
It must be lonely living
in such a big house by yourself.
Don't say that.
I'm never lonely.
If I were you,
I would feel very lonely.
I would probably become rebellious.
Okay.
I admit it was my fault this time.
How can I make it up to you?
Hey.
That's not what I meant...
Hey. What are you doing?
It's nice to be young.
Is this the police?
My daughter is around 160cm.
She has a round face.
She had a big coat on.
What? Her main features?
She has a big butt.
How can you say that about her?
Hello, sir.
Yes, I'm her dad.
Yes.
My daughter is very pretty.
She's around 160cm.
She has big, round eyes.
Everyone loves her.
She has pale skin, and--
They won't find her like that.
-But--
-Mom, Dad.
See? She's home.
I was right about her having a big butt.
Shancai, you're home?
-How dare you?
-Mom, stop it.
-Stop it.
-How could you do this?
-You couldn't call us?
-Stop it.
You always hit me in the end.
-Get out of the way.
-Mom.
I was stuck in an elevator
-the whole night.
-You couldn't call us?
My phone is broken.
The elevator broke
and your phone broke too?
You're lying. You're a bad girl.
No, I'm not.
See? My phone is broken.
It is...
So you were trapped
in the elevator the whole night?
Yes.
All right, come out.
You didn't come home all night.
Do you know how worried we were?
-Sweetheart.
-We were worried sick.
-It's fine.
-Here.
Fine. You can use my phone for now.
Thanks, Mom.
Shancai, are you hungry?
The porridge is cold. I'll heat it up.
I'll get you a bowl.
Aren't you heating the porridge?
What's the bowl for?
I'm pouring water, okay?
-Silly woman.
-You're the silly one.
Who needs water to heat up porridge?
My house is small.
My parents are always bickering.
But they really care about me.
I don't know if anyone
will take care of him at home.
Or if his fever has gone down.
Hey, Li Zhen.
-Did Shancai's mom call you last night?
-Yes.
She said she didn't come home all night
and asked me where she was.
I couldn't reach her either.
-What about you?
-I couldn't either.
I called her all night.
She never picked up.
What happened?
Shancai has never been like this.
I know.
It must be Daoming Si.
He said if we lost,
he could decide what to do to us.
I waited all day but nothing happened.
He must have gone after Shancai.
Jerk!
Qinghe, wait.
Hey.
Shancai.
-Shancai.
-Quiet now, everyone.
-Class is starting.
The professor is here.
All right.
In the last class,
we talked about nutrition in food.
Today...
I heard Mr. Liu say you're sick.
How did you get sick on a date?
You get sick when you're weak.
Especially when you're exhausted.
What are you talking about?
Where did you go with Shancai?
Did you follow the plan we made for you?
We were trapped
in an elevator the whole night.
-An elevator?
Wow, so exciting.
How was it?
It was cold.
And Shancai gave me her clothes.
And I started feeling very hot.
I was sweating all over, so...
What happened in the end?
I thought something
would happen in the end.
But then...
The workers came and found us.
You're such a weird couple.
Weird?
I'm still mad at that elevator worker.
Class,
these are the six essentials
for the human body.
Now, I'll give you ten minutes
to read your book
and go over what we just talked about.
Xinhui.
Look at her.
I wonder how Daoming Si
punished her last night.
She shouldn't have challenged F4.
She dug her own grave.
I'm so mad.
Look how tired she looks.
Daoming Si must have
bullied her last night.
All right, that's all for today.
Class dismissed.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Your mom said you didn't come home.
Where did you go?
-I...
-Daoming Si kidnapped you, didn't he?
Did he make you do something weird?
Or eat something weird?
Shancai, don't worry.
I'm your humble servant.
I'll get them back for this.
That's enough.
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
It's not what you think.
Daoming Si didn't bully me.
All right, Shancai.
Stop pretending.
It's okay that you lost the challenge.
Yeah, Shancai.
If you told us earlier,
maybe we could've talked
Daoming Si out of it.
Shancai, Daoming Si is looking for you.
Come on, let's go.
Excuse me.
What do you want?
Here.
What is it?
I won't accept a gift from you.
Idiot.
Who said it's a gift?
It's your coat.
You forgot to take it
when you left this morning.
Hey. Snap out of it.
Last night,
did Shancai sleep with Daoming Si?
It says here in QQ Space
that they're dating.
To be honest,
I don't like this girl.
Can we stop talking to her?
Why?
If she's close to F4,
I want to be friends with her.
I can't take it anymore!
Shancai, you said
that Daoming Si didn't bully you.
But he did.
Did he?
Did he not?
Why did he have your coat?
He's a big guy.
Your coat is too small.
He probably wanted to ruin your coat.
Such a pervert.
"Shancai, I'm so cold.
Give me your coat.
Shancai, I'm so cold.
Give me your dress too."
His intentions aren't pure.
Li Zhen, isn't he disgusting?
You're exaggerating.
He's ridiculous.
Shancai, tell us.
Why did he have your coat?
I gave him the coat because--
Shancai.
Ever since school started,
we haven't really hung out together.
How about we go have some fun tonight?
Xinhui only hangs out
with a selective group.
You'll be there, won't you?
Are you too ashamed of us because
you're friends with Daoming Si now?
That's not true.
So, where are we going?
Tonight, let's have a ladies' night.
What?
So I can't go?
What are you looking at?
No wonder you came to school sick.
You couldn't wait
to declare your territory.
Declare my territory?
You went on a date
with Shancai last night.
And today, everyone says you're dating.
If I don't tell the world who I like,
I'd be waiting for someone to steal her.
-What are you doing tonight?
-I don't know.
-Where are you going?
-What are you up to?
-Chill at my place?
-Hey.
Good idea.
-You're leaving me?
-Okay.
Hey.
Shancai.
You can go dance.
I'll just stay here. It's fine.
It's okay.
I can't dance.
We'll just have our drinks here.
Okay.
Cheers.
-Let's go.
-Sure.
Why aren't you guys dancing?
We can't dance.
You're pretty and have nice bodies.
You're cool too, Shancai.
Tell me, how did you get
Daoming Si to like you?
Xinhui.
It's not like that with Daoming Si and me.
Daoming Si isn't my boyfriend.
Shancai, do you think we're stupid?
We saw Daoming Si give your coat back.
QQ Space says that you're dating.
He hasn't denied it.
Why are you denying it?
It's not true.
It's a misunderstanding.
Fine.
If Daoming Si isn't your boyfriend,
you should introduce him to us.
Do we have a deal?
Everyone heard it here.
Let's drink to it.
Let's thank Shancai.
Cheers.
This drink is pretty good.
I feel so hot.
I'm going to the restroom.
Shancai.
I like you.
Isn't that Shancai?
Yeah.
She's leaning on
the long-haired foreign pianist.
Isn't she your good friend?
She's crazy.
She's not good at anything,
but she's good
at throwing herself at boys.
Where am I?
You were drunk. Call me when you wake up.
Thomas.
Thomas?
Who the hell is Thomas?
-Hi.
We're friends with Shancai.
I'm Baihe. This is Xinhui.
What's your name?
Call me Thomas.
Nice to meet you.
Shancai, too.
-Let's take a photo.
-Okay.
Okay.
What?
That foreigner and I...
Hello? Thomas?
You're awake? I'll go see you.
Don't, I'm at school now.
Okay.
Last night,
how did I get to the hotel?
Where did my friends go?
They were drunk.
They asked me to take care of you.
I didn't know where you lived.
So I brought you to a hotel.
Hey.
Why are you so late?
None of your business.
You have your first class at eight.
You were almost late.
None of your business.
Wait.
You know my schedule?
I didn't. Ximen told me.
Go away.
Why are you following me?
Were you waiting for me there?
You wish.
I'm going to the administration building.
I just passed by.
The administration building?
That's in the opposite direction.
I like taking the long way there.
Whatever.
I'm going to class.
Wait.
Here.
What's this?
Next time you give me your clothes,
at least make it an expensive one.
It's getting cold. Put it on.
Do you need help?
No. I'm going to be late.
All right, class.
That's all for today.
Please send me your assignments.
Class dismissed.
Li Zhen.
When did you go home last night?
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't remember.
I had a bit too much to drink.
It seemed like
you were having a good time.
So I went home.
Okay.
Shancai.
Was it fun last night? Where did you go?
THOMAS
Hello?
Shancai, where are you?
Your school is so big.
I think I'm lost.
You're...
You're at my school?
Yeah. Where can I meet you?
The cafeteria.
Shancai, where are you going?
Translated by Sophie Chang at Netflix
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene