A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 46
-Where are we going?
-Up to you.
Can we go see a movie?
Or have afternoon tea?
Or we can just keep
walking around like this.
Was anyone around?
No.
That's good.
Daoming Si from F4 can be seen
tripping on the street like this.
It would be too humiliating.
Of course it would be.
You're not elegant enough.
I didn't mean to do it.
Of course you'd trip in those shoes.
How did you survive until today
if you're this clumsy?
Let's go.
-Where are we going?
-Where else?
A movie? Afternoon tea?
Let's buy some shoes first.
What?
Jump on. What else?
Do you want to trip again?
You're too heavy. I can't catch you.
Hold this.
I guess I'll have to take care of you
for a lifetime.
Don't...
LEFT FOOT, RIGHT FOOT
Shancai?
Gosh, I haven't seen you for so long.
Come. Let me see you.
Gosh, you're so pretty now.
You buy shoes from this shop?
Of course.
She's been coming here
since she started school.
She's like our brand spokesperson, right?
No wonder--
Shancai.
Those shoes on that shelf
have all the discounts.
New arrivals are over here.
Please have a look.
Choose the best shoes for her.
Goodness.
Is he your boyfriend?
He's so nice to you.
I'll get a pair for you to try on.
Okay.
TRENDING RIGHT NOW, 199 YUAN
They look great.
It's like they were made for you.
What do you think?
Surprisingly good.
Stop giggling. Come home with me now.
What are we doing?
Don't think you can get your way
just because we're getting married.
Mrs. Yu will take
measurements for your dress.
What were you thinking?
Look at your figure.
No normal person would be interested.
Shut up.
Shancai, you're here.
You've been eating well, haven't you?
You're gaining weight
in all the right spots.
Mrs. Yu, you're saying
that I've gained weight.
No.
You look great like this.
You seem to have a lot of energy.
I'll make you the best dress ever.
So that you can be
the center of attention
at your engagement and wedding.
Thank you, Mrs. Yu.
I know I can trust you.
You know,
I've been waiting for you to come.
I like it when you are here in this house.
Thank you.
I'll have to learn about everything
in this household.
You'll have to help me with that.
I'm actually grateful to you.
Only you can control Si.
By the way, it's getting late now.
You should just stay here after dinner.
You can stay in Si's room.
Mrs. Yu.
How can a nice old lady like you
say something like that?
This is totally natural, isn't it?
Why are you so shy?
Also, don't call me an old lady.
You silly child.
Are you guys done yet?
We are.
Si.
You can take her away now.
Come on.
What?
Hey!
No questions asked.
-Come on.
-You...
Did you set this up together? Hey!
Ximen, I have a gift for you.
A special gift?
Not really.
I just wanted to have it with you.
A cake?
Yes, it's really good.
You girls love to have things like this.
Us girls?
Xiaogeng likes cakes too.
What? Are you mad?
No.
It's silly to be jealous of exes.
Right now, it's about us.
We're having cake together now.
I don't really like sweet things.
But I like you,
so I'll try it.
This cake is like us.
It's not too sweet.
What about you?
Do you have a gift for me?
No.
Well, I didn't want anything.
That's not what I meant.
I'm happy just to be here with you.
Really happy.
Okay.
-Xiaoyou?
-Yes?
This is our first date.
I want it to be a special memory.
It was special.
I'll never forget tonight
because I was with you.
Ximen, what's going on?
You seem flustered.
My dad texted me. I need to call him.
Wait for me right here.
I'll be right back, okay?
-Hello?
-Qinghe.
Why didn't it light up?
Did it not?
It's probably not connected.
Or the wire might be broken.
The wire is broken?
No.
I was wrong. Nothing's wrong.
Install the controller onto the switch.
Turn on three from the 36th to 16th floor.
Turn on four above the 26th floor.
Turn on everything apart from the far
left and far right above the 40th floor.
Set the time and go. Is it that hard?
If you can't even do this,
how can you be a part of F4?
Chen Qinghe, I'm telling you,
I, Ximen Yan,
am the perfect boyfriend.
But you ruined my date tonight.
You're an idiot!
Ximen, you seem distracted.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. They took care of it.
That's good.
I can't even do this small task.
What's wrong with me?
I knew it.
Perhaps God didn't want Ximen to succeed.
They're a couple. What's wrong with that?
They have flowers over there.
I'll buy some for you.
Ximen.
No need.
Tonight was wonderful
because I'm happy just to be with you.
I never thought I would be so happy.
To be able to hold your hand tonight
is everything I want.
Xiaoyou.
Wow!
Ximen, look! It's so beautiful!
It must be a surprise for a girl
from her awesome boyfriend.
That's so creative and sweet.
It's amazing.
Wow.
That's so romantic.
Nice job, Ximen.
Yeah.
Ximen.
It's okay.
Even though you didn't get me a gift,
we saw such a beautiful sight
thanks to somebody else.
How lucky!
Somebody else?
Yeah.
Let's take a photo.
Don't open your eyes.
Okay.
Three,
two,
one.
It's so beautiful.
How's that?
Do you remember when
we were watching meteors together?
I found it. Come and see it.
-See what?
-Come and take a look.
Do you see it?
Yes. It's so beautiful.
It'd be nice if I can see it every day.
Then close your eyes and make a wish.
Maybe it'll come true.
How would you know if you don't try?
All right.
This gift has a special meaning.
Because you're the only one I'm willing
to trade all the meteors in the sky for.
Before we get married,
I want to give you some special memories.
You're so bad.
Why?
I won't be able to forget this.
So I guess I'll have
to follow you forever.
Where else would you go?
You can only be with me.
I survived with all my strength.
We can't let ourselves down.
Don't forget.
I'll be a good guy to you.
I'll listen to you.
Really?
Of course.
But I also want you
to do something for me.
Of course, there's a catch.
I knew it.
What's the catch?
The catch is that
you have to be with me
for the rest of your life.
Guess what?
This is the happiest
I've been in this lifetime.
TALENT'S TEA SHOP
Your Peach Red Royale.
-Thank you. Come again.
-Okay, thanks.
Xiaoyou, Talent's Tea Shop
is doing better and better.
We're going to open more chain stores.
-That's great.
-You've been a hard worker.
I want you to take care of this store.
You'll be the manager. Would that be okay?
Really?
Thank you so much. You can count on me!
Good luck.
PLEASE TAKE A LOOK, FRIENDS
WE'RE HIRING, BENEFITS INCLUDED
Your drinks are ready. Come again.
Thank you.
All of you are here.
Ximen, you're here.
This is Xiaoyou's first day
as the manager.
Ximen wanted us all to come support you.
He also said
we have to break the sales record today.
Thank you, guys. Thanks, Ximen.
We're about to order now.
Remember Talent's Tea Shop's
signature drink?
-White Jasmine Dew.
-Peach Red Royale.
Talent's Tea Shop
-is the best tea in town!
-Is the best tea in town!
Ximen reminded us countless times.
All right.
Let's find a seat then.
Xiaoyou was awesome.
It was her first day
and sales reached more than 20,000 yuan.
Applause, please.
Thank you, guys.
This is my treat.
-For Meizuo.
-Thanks.
Daoming Si.
Here.
To Xiaoyou's first
successful day as a manager.
Cheers.
-Cheers!
I invented this new milk tea
using the best tea leaves.
Can you guys guess
what kind of tea leaves I used?
Lei, you first.
Mine is Moqi. It's really good.
Yes.
Meizuo.
This is Tungting Kiwi.
You're right.
This is probably Four Seasons Green Tea.
No.
Shancai, try it for me.
It's green tea with Yakult.
Shancai got it.
Shancai is an expert.
She managed to win Si's heart over.
Who would've thought that
the big-eyed, stubby girl with no grace
would look so pretty and cute now?
I wish I could kiss her.
I won't be able to see
Shancai anymore abroad.
Are you jealous?
Yes.
I am jealous.
Especially of you.
Then I have to kiss her.
Hey! Watch it!
-Lei!
-Calm down.
-What's your problem?
-It was just a kiss.
It's fine.
Then I'll kiss Xiaoyou then!
Come here, Xiaoyou.
Calm down.
Stop it!
-Come here, Xiaoyou!
-That's enough! Cut it out!
-Come here!
-Daoming Si!
Look at that.
What are you doing, dear? You're so slow.
I haven't worn a suit in so long.
I can't get this tie right.
It's either too long or too short.
-Come here.
-It's crooked.
Let me help you.
-The food is ready.
-That's good.
It smells amazing.
-We have a lot of food.
-That's a lot.
-Nice.
-Mom, I made your signature dish,
sweet and sour pork ribs.
When Daoming Si gets here,
he'll start drooling.
Dear, our Shancai is wonderful.
She's pretty, obedient, has good grades
and is really good at cooking.
How lucky are we?
I think the Daoming family is lucky.
What's wrong?
My precious daughter is getting married.
She won't be at home anymore.
I won't see her anymore.
I feel sad whenever I think of that.
There, there.
Mom, you'll see me all the time.
Even if I get married,
I'll always be by your side,
forever and ever.
You're my dearest mom.
Aren't you moving to London
after you get married?
I haven't graduated yet.
Before I do, I'll be in Shanghai.
Even if I do go to London,
I'll tell Daoming Si
that we shouldn't live there.
We should live here with you.
-Okay.
-Don't be silly.
When you're married,
you can't live wherever you want.
Of course I can.
Daoming Si told me that
he would do whatever I want him to do.
I can get him to do whatever I want.
Even if he picks on me,
I'll do what I did when I first met him.
I'll knock him down.
That's nice.
See our daughter? She's just like you.
Well, I'm not surprised that she is.
-You're the best mom ever.
-You're the best wife ever.
That's more like it.
It's already 12:30 p.m.
Why aren't Daoming Si
and his mom here yet?
It's hard to park in front of our house.
We should've told our neighbors
and just had them park
in front of their house.
This is my fault.
-All my fault.
-It's not.
They have a driver.
They don't drive themselves.
That's true. I totally forgot.
Did they forget
the directions to our house?
That's impossible.
-His mom came last time.
-Yeah.
It's fine. I'll call him now.
-Just ask him.
-Okay.
Hey, don't eat just yet.
We won't.
We're just checking them out.
So much food.
Hello? Daoming Si?
It's not Daoming Si. It's me.
Mrs. Daoming.
-Mrs. Daoming?
-I just wanted to know
if you're almost here.
My parents and I are waiting for you.
I'm busy today. I won't be going.
But we agreed to it.
You and Daoming Si were coming today.
I just said that
because Si was with you.
I was worried he would be tricked
into having a wedding
and doing something he would regret.
Now, Si is back with me.
I've talked some sense into him.
He won't be so impulsive anymore.
After listening to me,
he decided to go back to London with me.
He'll never come back to Shanghai again.
Dong Shancai,
you should give up on Si.
It'll never happen.
What is it, Shancai? What happened?
Mom.
Mrs. Daoming said
she won't be coming today.
That day,
she tricked us.
What?
She lied to us?
She won't be coming?
That's so rude. What is that witch doing?
Shancai cooked so much food for them.
And they're not coming?
I'm just furious.
What is she thinking?
Does she think we're stupid?
That our daughter is stupid?
I have to go talk to her.
I have to set things straight.
Shancai, let's go to their house.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
Dad, Mom.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
They're the ones at fault.
What are you sorry for?
Because of our relationship,
you've been worried and angry.
But it's not your fault, right?
Dad, Mom.
Promise me one thing.
From now on,
let me deal with problems
concerning Daoming Si and I alone.
No matter what happens between us,
I never want you
to be insulted like this again.
No matter what Mrs. Daoming
does to separate us,
I'll be brave and deal with it.
Who came up with this stupid idea?
It was Meizuo.
He said that it was a hat party
and we should wear hats
to give Si our blessing.
But these dog hats are hideous.
This is a bachelor party hat, okay?
I think I'm so creative.
Who would know that
Si would be the first to get married?
If you're jealous, cheer up a bit.
Stop being sad about your breakup, okay?
Is Meizuo really sad?
This is called putting on a brave face
and crying at home when I'm alone.
Breakups are really sad.
You should save your tears.
Cry when Si gets here.
All right.
But why isn't Si here yet?
Shancai?
Shancai, what's wrong?
Daoming Si...
He won't be coming.
You mean,
Si and his mom didn't go to your house
to talk about your marriage?
No.
They said they would come this noon.
We prepared lunch.
But they didn't come at all.
I called Daoming Si and his mom picked up.
She said that...
she never wanted us to get married.
She's sending Daoming Si to London.
He's never coming back.
I'll call him.
Did Si already go to London?
No.
Hello?
Mrs. Yu? It's me, Ximen.
Why is it you who picked up the phone?
Si is too busy to pick up.
Mrs. Yu, what are you talking about?
We're holding him a bachelor party
and waiting for him to come.
I'm telling you one more time.
We're busy.
Si is busy.
He can't pick up.
Stop calling us.
Hello? Mrs. Yu?
Hello?
Starting today,
if anyone asks about Si,
don't say anything.
Don't pick up any phone calls.
Let the secretary do it.
Yes, ma'am.
Mrs. Daoming.
Aren't you worried about Si?
Mrs. Yu sounded weird.
She didn't go to Shancai's house today.
That's her way of stalling.
She's stalling for time.
Stalling for time?
What is she trying to do?
Regardless, the most important thing is
to find Si.
How do we do that?
Mrs. Yu gave us a hint.
Si is at home.
What should we do?
We should go there to check it out.
I'll go with you.
We have to sneak in.
You shouldn't come.
When we find him, we'll let you know.
What should we do?
Same as usual. Go in from the back door.
Who is it?
What took you so long?
I knew it was Mrs. Yu.
We bumped right into her.
I distracted the security guards with tea.
I've been waiting for hours.
Come with me.
What happened to Si?
She locked him up.
Come on.
I thought that
since you have all graduated,
you wouldn't be so stupid.
Yet, you're sneaking into our house again.
Why does Si have
terrible friends like you?
Mrs. Daoming,
even if we're terrible,
we would never hurt our family members.
You're saying
that I'm hurting Si?
What are you doing right now then?
Are you pretending to be a nurse?
When can you finally grow up
and think like adults?
If you see us as adults,
you should respect Si and accept Shancai.
Do you respect me?
I couldn't let Si
be with someone whose background,
intelligence, and appearance
are so clearly beneath him.
I think Xiaozi is the best match for him.
Xiaozi, this one looks nice.
Do you want to try it?
Mom.
Why are we still trying on dresses?
I told you.
He doesn't like me.
It's Shancai that he likes.
There's no love between us.
How would we get married?
Xiaozi, you're both young.
But you can't be too impulsive.
The situation right now
is that you're both the successors
of huge business empires.
If you two get married,
it'll bring benefits to our families.
Is that all your care about?
Don't you like Si?
I do like him.
But he doesn't like me.
Xiaozi.
If you like Si,
this is your best chance.
What do you mean?
If this happened a few years earlier,
Daoming Feng wouldn't even
consider our family.
But now it's different.
For the past two years,
her hotel hasn't been doing well.
She needs your dad to save her business.
Your dad also needs this opportunity
to get more resources from Daoming Feng.
But what if I said
I don't like Si anymore?
Xiaozi.
-Don't lie.
-I'm not lying.
I just don't understand.
If working together benefits both parties,
why is marriage the only solution?
Why can't we just work together?
Because we can't trust Daoming Feng.
We can't trust her?
Daoming Feng has a very aggressive style.
She has many enemies in the market.
Why should we help her
without getting anything in return?
But if Si is part of our family,
it would be a different story.
Xiaozi.
if you don't want to marry him,
I won't force you to.
If Daoming Group goes out of business,
to our family,
it would just be a small hit.
Your dad has been doing
very well these years.
He can find other business partners
to work with.
But if Daoming Group crumbles,
Daoming Si will have nothing left.
He'll be just another guy.
Could you let that happen to him?
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Sophie Chang
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene