A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 18
Ximen.
Isn't pleasing girls
one of the things you do best?
Pleasing girls is not the same
as apologizing for Si.
Hey, guys. Are you guys looking for me?
-Where's Shancai?
-Shancai?
She didn't come to our previous class.
I'm not sure what happened to her.
She's also not answering her phone.
That's not like her at all.
When was the last time you saw her?
After class earlier,
she left with Shunping.
Shunping?
Yes. He's our high school
classmate's brother, Zhibu.
I see. Let us know
when Shancai comes back, Xiaoqing.
Sure.
Don't call me Xiaoqing anymore.
Hello?
Qinghe, didn't I tell you to call me
when Shancai gets back?
I've waited all afternoon.
I didn't forget. Shancai
didn't come to class all afternoon.
And I couldn't reach her phone.
I'm not sure where she went.
Come here now.
Okay.
I'll be right over.
Shancai didn't come back
the whole afternoon.
That's so unlike her.
I think something happened.
Do you remember who Qinghe said
Shancai left with earlier?
Apparently, the guy's name is Shunping.
I'll go ask the office about him.
-All right, Ximen.
-Hey.
Were you able to contact Shancai?
Ximen called earlier
and said that Shunping
has dropped out of Mingde University.
But he came to see Shancai this morning.
I don't feel good about this.
You said that your high school classmate
is Shunping's brother.
Do you have his number?
Let me see.
Si's phone is turned off.
Yan Zhibu's phone is ringing.
Hello?
Are you Yan Zhibu?
-You're here.
-Mr. Liu, is Si home?
Si sits in the library
every time he comes home.
He doesn't look happy.
What does he do in there?
He checks the stock market
or reads books.
Or plays games or takes naps.
He doesn't want to speak to anyone.
Boss.
She's awake.
What are you doing?
Stop struggling.
You won't be able to escape.
Boss.
Let's do it.
Be patient. Let's take her picture first.
Stop moving around.
Boss.
She doesn't look pitiful enough.
One more shot.
No. I don't think
now is the best time to sell it.
-I still want to wait. And tomorrow--
-Si.
-What's up? Did something happen?
-Why won't you answer your phone?
I'm not in the mood. What happened?
Shancai's missing.
Boss.
Shunping, you're here.
Why did you tie Shancai up?
Shunping.
What are you doing?
Shunping, we did that just in case...
Boss, I don't get it.
This was not the plan when you asked me
to approach Shancai before.
Boss.
Do you remember Daoming Si,
the one who broke your leg?
How can I forget?
Why? Did you see him?
No, my brother did.
He was beaten up by Daoming Si
at his high school reunion two days ago.
He was even hospitalized.
He was beaten up?
Why?
Apparently because of a girl
named Shancai.
She's Daoming Si's girlfriend.
Shunping.
I think you should become friends
with that girl named Shancai.
And convince her
not to be together with Daoming Si.
All right.
Thank you.
Shunping?
Shancai, we meet again.
Shunping.
What happened to your face?
I had an encounter with Daoming Si today.
Tell me about it.
What happened?
That guy is too arrogant and dominating.
He doesn't know how Shancai feels.
I couldn't contain myself
so we had a fight.
He was also very arrogant and dominating
when I met him before.
He's so annoying.
That kind of person
needs to be taught a lesson.
Shunping, can you arrange for me
to meet Shancai tomorrow?
Sure. But why?
Nothing.
I just want to have a chat with her.
Maybe I can convince her
to leave Daoming Si soon.
That's a good idea.
-I'll set it up.
-Okay.
How did Daoming Si treat boss before?
Have you forgotten?
Shunping, do you plan to betray us?
Of course not.
A person like Daoming Si
doesn't deserve to be forgiven.
Boss' leg
was crippled because of Daoming Si.
I've already taken a photo.
I'll send it to Daoming Si.
He lied to me.
Shunping, who said he wanted
to be friends with me, to protect me,
lied to me.
Why did this happen?
Boss.
I want to talk to her alone.
May I?
Don't worry.
I won't let her go.
Don't forget.
I'm on your side.
Sure.
Don't take too long.
Okay.
Why?
For what?
Why are you doing this?
I trusted you.
Why?
Liar.
Jerk!
Scum!
Say whatever you want.
If that makes you feel better,
do it.
Why are you doing this?
I think boss wants to use you
to deal with Daoming Si.
Daoming Si crippled his leg.
He needs to pay for it.
When I was in junior high school,
I didn't like to be in school.
I didn't like being with that stupid Zhibu
at home even more.
So I went out and did some part-time job.
But I also got into a lot of trouble.
I met boss at a bar later on.
He helped me with my problems.
And he even convinced me
to go back to school.
And then one day,
that arrogant guy, Daoming Si,
argued with boss at a bar.
He said boss is a rascal
and that he's useless.
Boss and his men got mad
and had a fight with Daoming Si.
But Daoming Si went crazy
and beat everyone up.
He also broke...
Boss' leg.
Because of that,
everyone got arrested by the police,
even Daoming Si.
But boss's leg
would never ever recover.
Shouldn't Daoming Si
take responsibility for this?
Shunping.
What you're doing is against the law.
You'll be expelled by the school.
Do you know that?
Even though I got into Mingde University,
I couldn't take
the pressure of the competition.
It seems like everyone is doing better
than me.
That's why I dropped out a long time ago.
So you approached me on purpose
in order to avenge boss?
I don't understand.
Why would a nice girl like you
be with a bum like Daoming Si?
A person like you
even dare to call Daoming Si a bum?
Even though Daoming Si seems overbearing,
he's not the person you say he is.
You saw boss's leg.
Isn't the truth right in front
of your eyes?
If you want her to live,
come alone to this place immediately.
What is it? Is there any update on her?
"If you want her to live,
come alone immediately--"
Don't follow me.
Actually, I feel sorry for you.
Because when people get acquainted
with Daoming Si,
that is the beginning of their bad luck.
My bad luck is not because of Daoming Si.
It's because I trusted you.
Your hypocrisy makes me sick.
I thought you would understand me.
Turns out, I was wrong.
Don't worry.
After boss deals with Daoming Si,
he'll let you go.
You won't succeed with your plan.
Because Daoming Si won't come.
He will.
He'll come here.
He confessed his feelings
for you that way yesterday.
So he'll surely come.
Daoming Si.
Please don't come.
This is my karma
because I didn't believe Daoming Si.
Shunping, why did you remove the tape?
What if she screams?
Nobody would come to such a remote place.
Don't touch me!
Watch it.
If not for Shunping,
we would have already beaten you up
and broadcasted you crying live
to Daoming Si.
I won't let you see me cry.
You despicable people.
You're quite tough.
Speaking of being despicable,
your man is even more despicable than us.
Last time, he beat us up
until we passed out at the bar.
I thought you had a big feud.
He beat you up until you passed out?
That's because you people were useless.
Can't you win over Daoming Si
if you don't use such despicable tricks?
Bitch! Shut up!
Scalawag.
Scumbag.
You already lost to Daoming Si
when you used such dirty tricks.
I'm telling you.
Daoming Si won't come here.
Then we'll just kill you!
-We'll see if he comes--
-Wait. Boss.
The goal is not to harm her.
The goal is to lure Daoming Si here.
I'm not Daoming Si's girlfriend.
If you don't believe me,
then just wait here until you die
with those hilarious expressions
on your ugly faces.
This wench's mouth is quite tough.
If you dare kick her,
you'll regret it
for the rest of your life.
All right.
Let's do this right now.
Stupid boy.
Why did you come here?
Foolish guy.
Stupid boy.
You can choose to fight back,
but I think you shouldn't.
You wouldn't want...
to see her get hurt, right?
Don't look at me with your filthy face.
Close your eyes.
What are you waiting for?
Kill him!
Aren't you stupid?
Don't you fight at all?
Fight back.
Fight back!
I don't feel anything at all.
Is that all you got?
Don't you have anything more powerful?
Beat him up!
Stop!
Stop it!
Daoming Si!
Daoming Si.
Where are you going?
It's dangerous over there.
Daoming Si!
You hate me, right?
I don't hate you.
Whether you like me or hate me,
it doesn't matter anymore.
Bye.
Daoming Si!
Wait!
It's all my fault! Don't go!
Don't go!
Daoming Si!
Don't...
Don't go!
-She's awake.
-Shancai.
-You scared us to death, Shancai.
Shancai.
-Hurry.
-Come on.
Come on.
Dad.
Mom. Where am I?
You're at the hospital.
The police called and said that
you and Daoming Si were found
at an old warehouse behind the school.
You both were hurt
and were sent to the hospital.
Tell me. Who beat you up?
I'll take care of him!
What are you doing?
She just woke up. Why are you yelling?
-Tell me.
-Shancai, tell me.
Who beat you up? I'll take care of him!
Daoming Si.
-Daoming Si?
-Where's Daoming Si?
-Shancai.
Stupid boy.
Why did you come here?
All right.
Let's do this right now.
Don't look at me with your filthy face.
Close your eyes.
Please don't run in the hallways.
Huaze Lei.
Huaze Lei. Where's Daoming Si?
Someone who never got beaten up
by anyone before.
Someone who could fight really well.
Someone who could win
even if a lot of people ganged up on him,
why didn't he fight back
because of me?
Stop!
Stop it!
You stupid boy!
Why didn't you fight back?
If I fought back,
then I would really lose.
Daoming Si!
Wake up, Daoming Si!
Come on. Wake up, Daoming Si!
Help!
It's too late.
Si passed very peacefully.
I never thought
that Si passed away just like that.
No.
Daoming Si, I won't allow you to die!
Wake up!
I haven't even apologized to you!
Even though you have a bad temper,
I still...
I still hope that you'd be alive.
Daoming Si!
Wake up!
You did so many bad things to me.
I haven't dealt with you yet!
Wake up!
What are you talking about?
Is this how you treat a patient?
Did you see Shancai's expression earlier?
I almost couldn't contain myself.
"No. I don't want you to die!"
Daoming Si.
Daoming Si, you tricked me.
Do you want to scare me to death?
-I'm going to kill you.
-Don't do that.
I'm going to kill you.
You and Huaze Lei tricked me.
Hey, what were you thinking?
Is this how you treat a patient?
I broke three ribs.
I'm hurt all over.
Yet this stupid girl is sitting on me.
Who told you to play such a prank?
Miss.
How long will you sit on me?
It hurts.
By the way, the police are already
taking care of those gangsters.
I think Si has already paid
for what he did before.
I'm not who I was anymore.
What was he like before?
Huaze Lei. How was Daoming Si before?
The old Daoming Si was quite absurd.
Absurd?
Isn't he also quite absurd now?
Compared to how he used to be,
the new Si
is Mr. Virtue.
What are you looking at?
You're lucky you met the new me.
That's right.
The old Si always looked for trouble.
And he was never motivated.
Good thing we were able to change him.
We helped him study
at the library every day.
Good thing that he's naturally smart.
He got into Mingde University
with a very high score.
He got into Mingde University indeed.
But he's not naturally that smart.
All right.
Are you planning to talk
about my past all night?
You ungrateful guy.
You forgot all the times
we were with you before.
You...
Never mind. Let's go.
Let's give them some quality time.
Bye.
Why aren't you saying anything?
What's with that attitude?
Is that how you treat a patient?
Do you think you're so great?
Why was I so nosy that I risked my life
and got hurt all over just to save
an ungrateful and stupid girl like you?
You're the stupid one.
You even dare to say that to me.
If you didn't cause trouble before,
how would you get hurt?
Cut it out. Stop babbling.
You just know how to fight
with people all day.
-Don't you know how to comfort a patient?
-Because...
What...
What are you doing?
Because I had a dream.
I dreamt that you died.
Then I thought you really died.
I thought you wouldn't come and save me
because I said those things to you.
I never thought you'd still come.
And you got beaten up so badly
by those scums
and turned out this way.
Sorry.
Stop looking like that.
You're already ugly as it is.
Didn't I tell you before?
Even if you went to Mars,
I'd still go after you.
You wouldn't be able to get rid
of me in this life.
Stop struggling for no reason.
Stupid boy.
Your face is so ugly right now.
Are you planning to laugh or cry?
It's none of your business.
It's good that they came back safely
even though they were hurt this time.
But it was really dangerous.
That's right.
If you think about it now,
we almost weren't able to change
the old Si.
There were times when
we almost fought with him.
It's good we didn't give up.
How could we give up on him?
He has helped us a lot.
We can't let this kind of thing
happen again.
Even though he's very headstrong now,
he has learned to respect himself
because he found someone he loves.
Hey.
Who are you?
I'm Shunping, the one who beat up
Daoming Si so badly.
What? You want me to come visit you daily?
-No way.
-Why not?
I need to work. How will I have the time?
You ungrateful woman.
I'll double your salary. Come here.
Don't always use money to buy people.
You morally-corrupt bum.
Then how would you repay me? Tell me.
Shut it.
Lie down and rest.
Why are you here?
Haven't you done enough?
Your friends are all by the door.
What can I do to you?
Don't worry.
Shancai.
Before I surrender myself,
I want to apologize to you.
Boss was already arrested
because of what we did to you.
I'll also surrender myself for what I did
and accept my punishment.
I'm really sorry.
It's too late to apologize now.
Get out.
Shancai.
If you're not the girl Daoming Si likes,
I'd hope we can become good friends.
It's really a shame.
I originally wanted to beat him up.
But I'm not mad anymore
after seeing his pathetic face.
You still want to beat people up?
Ouch! You violent girl.
Why did you hit me where I'm hurt?
Sorry. I didn't do it on purpose.
I...
This is the most touching love story.
A firm and unyielding man like Daoming Si
risked his life for the woman he loves.
Shancai, you must've done a lot of good
in the past to get a man like Daoming Si.
This man is strong,
handsome and responsible.
What do you think, Shancai?
What do you mean?
-Why are you telling me these things?
-Shancai.
What do you want?
I mean it.
You should treat each other well.
You should help one another.
That's right.
With a manly guy like Daoming Si,
even if aliens came to Earth,
he would not let them hurt you.
And Daoming Si is not right in the head.
He won't look for another woman.
He would risk his life and save you
when you're in trouble.
Stop it.
I...
Take this limited edition Daoming Si now.
Even though his brain
doesn't work that well,
you're not that smart yourself.
-I think you suit each other.
-Hey.
Don't come any closer.
Shancai, don't you like
a manly guy like Daoming Si?
Si is invincible.
Hey.
I'm manly too.
And...
But...
Then...
-Daoming Si is...
-Damn girl.
What are you trying to say?
And...
But...
Then...
I think
of Daoming Si...
as a dog.
Lei, stop laughing.
But I can relate.
A dog?
Si, be strong.
Of course we can't evade it.
We have to face it head on.
Mr. Wu, don't think too much.
You won't suffer any losses.
We prioritize the bonuses for our members.
You can't earn less even if you want to.
Of course. You can find me
any time you call this number.
I'll help you resolve your problems.
That's good.
It seems that your job
is going smoothly lately.
I already have a plan.
When I receive my first salary,
I'll add them to the stock immediately.
Be careful.
Is she still in the bathroom
after such a long time?
Did you remind her not to get
her wounds wet?
I did.
We really have to thank
Daoming Si this time.
He even got his face hurt
to save Shancai.
Shouldn't they settle the things
between them already?
I think so too.
Shancai, hurry.
It's too humid in the bathroom.
It's not good for your wounds.
Congratulations on getting discharged.
Si's recovers just like a dog.
A dog?
Don't mind being called a dog.
Dogs are nice.
Maybe Shancai was complimenting you
for being as cute as a dog?
Don't let me hear you say
the word "dog" again.
Or else I'll kill you.
I think you were really traumatized.
How can you understand how I feel
when the girl I risked my life for
said,
"I think of Daoming Si as a dog."
I think
of Daoming Si...
as a dog.
She said I'm like a dog.
That damn girl.
I think Si is going to explode.
I told you he shouldn't
be discharged so soon.
I'm going to sleep.
But Shancai is really stubborn.
Innocent girls like her are annoying.
They have
a lot of unrealistic expectations
on relationships.
Falling in love relies on
that sudden feeling of love.
Lei, what do you think?
Me?
I don't have any feelings at all.
I think we're the only normal guys here.
There's nothing we can do.
We can only help Si
make the innocent Shancai
give in.
Didn't you just get discharged?
Have you rested enough?
Why are you in such a hurry
to come to school?
I was afraid I won't be able to catch up.
-I may have a lot to catch up later.
-I can lend you my notes.
Thank you.
But it's better for me to come to class.
Shancai, are you all right?
I wanted to visit you after class.
Then give you my notes
for the past two days.
Your notes?
Your notes are useless.
Nobody can understand them.
Shancai would be confused.
I wrote my notes carefully for Shancai.
Don't say things you don't know.
All right. I need both of your notes.
Shancai, is it okay
not to bandage your wound?
I think it's fine.
It feels fresher this way.
Where's Daoming Si?
He was discharged yesterday.
He's taking a sick day today.
His wounds have not fully recovered yet.
Right.
Your wound might get infected this way.
I don't want to be all bandaged up
like a mummy.
-So I...
-But your wound might get infected.
The air is really polluted.
What happens if it scars?
Do you bring this stuff
with you all the time?
Wouldn't you?
So Daoming Si's been discharged already?
That's great.
This is the first time
I've seen Si like that.
We grew up with him
and we're all so surprised.
We can see how much he really likes you.
You can see it too, right?
Come on. I'll put it on for you.
Lei.
I really envy you.
You and Jing shouldn't feel awkward
with each other now, you know?
But I still don't know
how to face him with confidence.
It seems so hard.
Just take it slowly.
You and Si can just take it slowly.
It'll be all right.
Really?
You two seem cozy.
What are you doing?
Stupid boy.
He's helping me put on a Band-Aid.
Didn't you take a sick day?
I got bored sleeping at home.
So I came to school instead.
Your ribs haven't healed, right?
Can you move around like this?
So what?
My ability to recover is just like a dog.
I told you it was just a metaphor.
It's just a figure of speech.
An interesting figure of speech.
Did I ask for your opinion?
I'll get going then.
I didn't tell her what you wanted me to.
Just tell her yourself.
Hey.
What is it?
Do you know what day it is on the 31st?
You don't know?
How dare you? It's my birthday!
Well then.
Happy birthday.
We have a birthday party every year.
You have to bring a gift.
What? How can you act like this?
You even asked for a gift?
-Would you give me a gift if I didn't?
-Of course.
All right. Then bring it.
This is your fault.
You have to make it up to me.
By the way, my mom will be there too.
Wear something nice.
Your mom?
-Your mom would be back from overseas?
-Yes. I'll introduce you to her.
What?
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Coleen Chua
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene