A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
EPISODE 12
Si, how are you doing in London?
I'm bored to death here.
How is that possible?
There must be
a lot of pretty girls over there.
I don't see any.
Oh, please. How can you live abroad
with that kind of negative attitude?
Why don't you just come back here?
We also lack one member for Bridge.
Now you realize how important I am, right?
You've always been important.
Please.
We haven't found any place
with bigger space
and privacy than your house.
Hey, you guys are so sensible.
Daoming Si, that's your only role.
Cut the nonsense. Where's Lei?
Lei, Si is looking for you.
What's up?
What do you mean, what's up?
Tell me clearly.
Why am I the one whom Shancai likes?
Can't you figure it out yourself?
If I can do that on my own,
why do I need to ask you?
Then come back and find out for yourself.
Have you seen her lately?
How is she?
I haven't seen her much.
When I see Qinghe,
he said that when Shancai is not
in school, she's at her part-time job.
You still remember?
Have you forgotten who I am?
-I see Shancai now.
-Where? Now? Let me see her.
SHEN NONG VILLAGE, PLANTS
Grandma.
This is the list of herbs I want to buy.
Thank you.
Oh, sure. Let me see it.
ID CARD, DONG SHANCAI
-"Shenwei leaf."
-Grandma.
What's up with this ID card?
That day, a young girl left her ID card
here because she didn't have enough money
to pay for the Shenwei leaf.
-Do you know her?
-She's our kitchen assistant.
So you're her friend who participated
in the chef qualification exam.
Yes.
In order to save your Shenwei leaf,
she even got into an accident.
Tian Ye, why are you still here?
This is yours.
ID CARD, DONG SHANCAI
Why is it with you?
Why are you so careless?
Even if you were anxious
to get me the Shenwei leaf,
you must be careful too.
If I knew that would happen,
I'd have just taken the exam next year.
It's fine.
It didn't hurt at all.
All right.
Actually, it's all my fault.
I was the one who ruined the ingredients.
And I even scolded you.
But Shancai,
I really want to thank you.
Let me buy you dinner.
Sure.
Congratulations on becoming a chef!
-Cheers.
Why do you look happier than me?
Of course I'm happy.
Your parents must even be happier
to have such a talented son like you.
My mom passed away when I was very young.
My dad actually doesn't want me
to become a chef.
Why?
I know he has his reasons.
However,
I won't easily give up
on something I really like to do.
Yes, I would do the same if I were you.
What kind of life do you want to live?
I want to live a simple life.
Then have my own dream.
And work hard
to make the people around me happy.
-Shancai.
-Yes?
I think we're so alike.
And we have a pre-destined connection.
Are we so alike?
Yes.
You mean we're both very frugal
and work very hard, right?
We're both fighting for survival.
I really hope I can be as brave as you.
You? You can definitely do it.
All right. My house
is just straight ahead.
Let me walk you there.
There's no need. I'll just go by myself.
Then...
Shancai.
No matter what happens in the future,
I hope that you can be beside me
whenever I'm cooking.
I'm your kitchen assistant, right?
Don't worry.
I won't just quit
and work in another place.
That's not what I meant.
-I mean--
-What he means
is that he wants you
to become his girlfriend,
and not a poor kitchen assistant.
Daoming Si?
What are you doing here?
Aren't you supposed to be in London?
Because I went to London,
you went on a date with this liar?
What are you talking about? What liar?
He's been deceiving you
from the very start.
Why is Tian's Chinese Medicine's successor
pretending to be poor
and doing a part-time job?
How is that possible?
He obviously lied to you.
You can't even be honest with her,
yet you want her to become
your girlfriend?
Maybe you've misunderstood.
I didn't misunderstand anything.
You were deceived.
TIAN'S CHINESE MEDICINE SUCCESSOR
TIAN YE TO INHERIT FAMILY BUSINESS
Tian Ye,
is that really you?
Shancai. Listen to me.
You're rich,
yet you told me
that we're both fighting for survival.
Do you take me for a fool?
No, Shancai.
I meant that I need to fight my family.
I really respect you as my colleague.
Actually,
it doesn't matter
whether you tell me the truth or not.
I just feel
that you didn't treat me as a real friend.
No, Shancai.
-Let me explain--
-Hey.
You're so full of it.
Shancai.
Are you stuttering?
I'll go first.
You're a stupid girl. If I'm not here,
you'd be easily tricked by guys.
-How can you believe someone so easily?
-I was born this way.
-So what?
-That's why I said you're stupid.
I'm stupid?
Don't feel too good about yourself.
Do you think you're that smart?
If I wasn't there earlier,
you could've been tricked by that guy.
Fine. Even if that happens,
it has nothing to do with you.
-Can you just mind your own business?
-No.
Now it has nothing to do with me?
Why does it matter?
Didn't you go to London
and never plan to come back?
Why are you here now?
I...
I miss my country, my friends,
my hometown. Am I not allowed to be here?
Daoming Si, you're here.
Shancai and I missed you.
Who missed him?
Why are you here?
Didn't you open the door for me
to come inside?
-I--
-Hey. Where are your manners?
Daoming Si can come here if he wants to.
Daoming Si, welcome.
It has been a while.
Hi, ma'am.
Why do you look so pale? Are you sick?
I just came back from London.
I still have jet lag.
London?
That's so far.
You must not be feeling well.
Come here and have a seat first.
Have a seat.
Sit down and rest here for a while.
You rude girl.
Why are you just standing there?
Get him some water.
Can you get some fruit for him?
I'll get some tiger balm for you.
Sit and rest here first, okay?
So you were abroad.
That makes me feel better.
I thought you had a fight with Shancai.
Are you two all right?
Mom, what are you saying?
Fine. I won't keep asking you.
I'll just talk about something else.
Daoming Si,
what do you want to specialize in?
Dear, why are you asking him that?
Can't I ask about that?
He's rarely here.
What did you do in London?
-Strolling around.
-Strolling around?
-Where did you go for a stroll?
-At home.
At home...
Dear, it's really late.
Daoming Si has been yawning
all this while.
Maybe he wants to rest now.
Are you sleepy?
Do you want to rest already?
I wish there's a bed
I can lie down on right now.
Then just spend the night here.
Okay.
You...
Hey.
Get lost! Your bed is over there.
Get over there.
You're so strange.
-Why are you sleeping in my room?
-Because you have to take care of me.
-I--
-What if I feel thirsty
in the middle of the night?
I'm not your maid.
Why are you laughing?
Your dad's legs are so short.
Just pretend it's a pair of capri pants.
What else can I do? My handsome self
just needs to deal with it.
I think the person
Shancai really likes is you.
-Hey, Shancai.
-Hey.
What are you doing?
My parents are just in the next room.
Don't think of doing anything.
Oh, please.
You should refrain
from doing anything to me.
Hey.
If I didn't come back, can you imagine
how Tian Ye would have tricked you?
Did you come back
just to expose Tian Ye's lie?
Of course not. I have better things to do.
Did you go on a date today?
Why are you even nosier than my mom?
Did you two hold hands?
Or kiss?
No.
Is that true?
Never mind if you don't believe me.
How have you been for these past few days?
What did you think
about me not being here?
What do you mean?
Did you feel more carefree
or a bit sad?
Never mind.
I don't care what you think.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
Hey! Why didn't you knock?
-Sorry.
-Why aren't you dressed?
My clothes are dirty.
I'll ask my dad to give you
something to wear.
Never mind. I don't think I can carry
the uncle-style clothes your dad wears.
But you can't go out
without your shirt on.
Why not?
My perfect abs cannot be seen
just by anyone.
You don't have abs.
Hey.
Come here. Look clearly.
-Aren't these abs?
-You--
Sorry to bother the two of you.
It's so nice to be young.
Get out!
Close the door!
Isn't that Daoming Si?
It's really him.
-You...
-He isn't in London?
Weren't you in London?
I only asked for a few days leave.
Should I report that to you?
Also, I was afraid this stupid girl
couldn't live without me. So I came back.
Who couldn't live without you?
Last night,
-I slept together with Shancai.
-What?
You slept together with Shancai?
No. Yesterday, my mom wanted him
to stay over at my house.
Your mom already agreed?
Aren't you going too fast?
Li Zhen, let's go.
-Zao Yue.
-Present.
-Liu Bozhen.
-Jin Jinqiao.
-Present.
-Zhang Chi.
Chen Qinghe.
-Qinghe.
-Isn't Chen Qinghe present?
Qinghe.
-Yang Yang.
-Present.
-Hey, your name is being called.
-Li Zhen.
-Present.
-Zao Bowen.
-Huang Mongtian.
-Present.
-Zhang Yawen.
Hello, Ximen? Where did you three go?
Si, we came to London to see you.
We just landed. Where are you?
What? I came back to Shanghai.
Come back here.
We can't. Because of you,
we enrolled in a school in London.
-We already paid the tuition fees.
-I don't care. Come back here.
No.
Lei said that he's not coming back anymore
if you're not talking to him.
Who says I'm not talking to him?
I have a lot of things to tell him.
Ask Lei to come back.
What do you want to tell me?
So it's a prank?
So what do you want to tell me?
Lei.
What happened before...
Which one?
Regarding the Spiderman.
I don't mind.
However, I think you still owe me
an official apology.
Si, you're my good friend.
But you should really
apologize to Lei for that.
I want to film this historic moment
where Daoming Si apologizes.
Go away.
Lei.
Regarding Spiderman
and me forcing you to go away,
they're all my fault.
I'm officially apologizing to you.
-He's bowing.
-What are you doing?
I'm not dead yet.
This moment is so precious.
I want to post this.
-It'd surely be a hit.
-Definitely.
Hey, don't you dare.
Stand properly.
I want to officially apologize to you.
-Okay.
-Hey, don't go too far.
I'm telling you. Don't go there.
-Come on. Delete all of it.
-I don't want to.
Qinghe, what's wrong with you?
You haven't been paying attention
at all today.
How is Daoming Si better than me?
Originally, Shancai's parents said
she and I were made for each other.
We're like a nutritious
and delicious dish combined together.
Why did they choose
a different son-in-law?
I feel like a battery pack
without any juice.
A balloon with a hole.
A dried up cactus.
My world is full of darkness.
I'm dying.
Do you know how Daoming Si
is better than you?
He doesn't act like he's dying like you.
You're right.
I can't let Daoming Si see me like this.
Shancai isn't married yet.
I still have a chance.
I especially liked
Professor Tian's class today.
Meizuo, how about you?
Are you talking about the topic
"the most irresponsible company
treats its employees leniently"?
Yes. I think he really
made a lot of sense.
If a company wants to improve,
it must be strict with its employees.
I think it depends on the situation.
As long as they have a common goal,
the employee can work hard to achieve it.
Lei, what do you think?
Me?
I think it's creativity.
Only creativity is irreplaceable.
-Si, what about you?
-Me?
Determination.
Regardless of what anyone says.
Once you're determined to do something,
you have to stick with it
no matter what happens.
You're talking about your feelings, right?
It's the same thing.
Oh, no! It's my sister.
My sister is calling me! Quick!
-Let me do it. I like Ms. Zhuang.
-Help me.
Hi, Ms. Zhuang.
Ask my brother to talk to me.
He says he's not here.
Stop it. I know he's right beside you.
Ask him to talk to me.
No. He's really not here.
Do you want to leave any message?
You can talk to me first, or Lei,
-Hi.
-or Ximen.
Hello, Ms. Zhuang.
All right. You're not letting him
talk to me, right?
Then I'll sing.
The most beautiful woman in the world
Is named Daoming Zhuang
-Si suddenly appeared.
-Hey.
-We'll get going first.
-...narcissist
-You can do it.
-Ms. Zhuang
Hi.
Are you tired of living?
Do you want me come and beat you up?
You went back to Shanghai
without telling us.
Do you know how mad Mom is?
All right.
I'm sorry.
It's not a big deal.
-Why are you so mad?
-Do you think I want to be mad?
I was worried about you.
Worried?
I'm not a kid anymore.
What's there to be worried about
even if I come home by myself?
And I need to go to my classes, right?
All right. I have something to tell you.
Listen carefully.
Inhale deeply and exhale
three times first. Come on.
Okay.
Mom will be back in Shanghai
for your birthday this year.
What?
You know what I mean, right?
What do you plan to do with Shancai?
You should know
that Mom wouldn't like her.
Then tell me.
What type of girl does Mom like?
Somebody like Teng Tangjing or me.
Then what type is that?
Elegant, classy, smart, talented.
Someone who shines when she's outdoors.
Someone who's virtuous when she's indoors.
Someone well-mannered.
Shouldn't you start thinking
about what you should do?
Si, what are you so busy with?
It's almost the end of the year.
Didn't we say we'll practice
for next year's
Asian Games Bridge Competition?
Wait. I'll be right there.
What are you doing?
I'm looking for something
for Shancai's makeover.
-Shancai's makeover?
-Why a makeover?
Because I want to turn her
into a girl that suits me.
Haven't you two always been a good match?
Shancai, it's time.
Let me do it.
Shancai, I'm sorry.
I know you're still mad.
But I really don't want to lie to you.
Tian's Chinese Medicine
is indeed my family's business.
I didn't think that was important to you.
Because I'm still me.
I didn't tell you before
because I didn't want to get
special treatment at work.
I want to make friends
with people for who I am.
I overreacted.
Thank you for being honest with me.
Then you're not mad anymore?
Yes.
Dad, Mom, what happened?
Mom, why are you crying?
Ask your dad.
He did something wrong and he even
threw a fit when he got home.
Dad.
What's the matter?
Your dad
lost one million yuan.
One million yuan?
He earned some money with the investment.
So he put in the company's money as well.
He lost everything in the end.
Now we have to return the money
to them immediately.
Dad.
Is this true?
Say something.
Shancai.
I was blinded by greed.
I shouldn't have been too greedy.
I wanted to get rich overnight.
Dad, how can you do that?
Dear.
I'm sorry.
I just want to let you have a chance
to wear nicer clothes,
to live in a bigger house.
I did everything in order
to make you live a happier life.
Don't say anything anymore.
Let's get divorced.
Mom.
Dong Danian.
I'm really disappointed in you.
You don't understand me at all.
Even if you have money,
I won't let you buy me a big house
or a nice car.
I love you for who you are.
Because you're kind and honest.
You have a sense of responsibility.
But today, just for a little profit,
you committed such a big mistake.
I want to get a divorce!
Mom! Calm down!
Dear, I didn't do it on purpose.
I'm sorry.
Shancai.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
Dear.
I'll do anything you want.
If you really want to get a divorce,
I'll grant you that.
Dad!
Who wants to divorce you?
Just promise me
you won't ever do it again.
I won't. I promise I won't do it anymore.
I know I was wrong. I won't do it again.
But what do we do now?
We have to return so much money
to the company.
We might only have one or two
hundred thousand yuan altogether.
What do we do?
Don't worry.
Let me think of something.
I'll think of something.
Daoming Si.
What happened?
My husband is so embarrassing.
-I'm sorry about that.
-Mom, stop it.
Daoming Si, go home first.
We have a lot of things to settle.
BANK OF COMMUNICATIONS
This card has one million yuan.
The password is six zeroes.
You can use it first.
What are you doing?
How can we use your money?
Dad, Mom.
-We can't accept it.
-Why not?
I earned this money
from the stock market on my own.
Would it be a problem if I lend it to you?
I don't want to take advantage of you.
Use it first. Just pay me back later.
What other options does your dad have?
He might go to jail for this, you know?
Take it.
Daoming Si, well...
Thank you so much for helping us.
How should I pay the money back to you?
Come to my house
after school tomorrow, okay?
What?
See you tomorrow. Bye.
Ma'am, sir, I'll take my leave.
Get a good rest tonight.
All right.
Hey.
Daoming Si!
What?
What did he mean by that?
Daoming Si.
Thank you.
Even though I don't have
enough money to pay you back now,
but I'll think of something.
I'll earn money and pay it back to you.
I have an idea for you
to pay the money back sooner.
What do you want to do?
Guess.
I'm warning you.
I rather eat slippers.
There's a competition.
The winner can get one million yuan.
One million yuan?
-How is that possible?
-What?
It's fine if you're not interested.
Think of your own way
to pay the money back to me.
Wait.
What kind of competition is it?
Let me see.
This one.
Let me see it again.
-You can't.
-I just want to look at it.
Let me see it.
"The Chinese Cuisine Cooking Contest
integrates the essence of Chinese culture
and creates a new attitude for food."
It sounds really difficult.
But it looks interesting.
I can try it.
Are you joining this contest?
You...
I can get the prize and learn
new things at the same time.
I'll try my best.
That's the Dong Shancai I know.
Is there anything else?
If not, I'll get going.
Wait.
-What about the interest?
-What?
The interest?
You're ridiculous.
Of course there's interest fee.
How much do you want?
What do you want?
The interest is a kiss on my cheek.
Are you a person of integrity or not?
What?
You want Shancai to join
the Chinese Cuisine Cooking Competition?
-The competition sponsored by your mom?
-That's right.
-Si, are you serious?
-Of course.
The inspiration came from my sister.
And Jing.
But this competition
is only done once in three years.
If she wants to win,
she must have exceptional cooking skills
and she needs to have
a famous chef's recommendation.
Shancai doesn't seem qualified
to participate in it.
I'll find a famous chef to test her.
Is it that hard?
So you want to use this opportunity
to train Shancai?
I want to use this opportunity
to let Shancai improve
and also to let my mom accept Shancai.
Isn't this killing two birds
with one stone?
That's a good idea.
Even so,
the competition would be fierce.
Aren't you afraid she'll be humiliated?
That's not a problem for Shancai.
You don't know how fierce she is.
She can make the impossible possible.
But we have less than a month
before the competition.
Do you have enough time?
How would we know if we don't try?
Hello?
Yes, I'm Shancai.
May I ask who's calling?
Ms. Zhuang?
How unfortunate I am.
I have such a stupid brother.
He begged me to come back
and help you with your training.
So you came back just for me?
Yes. What do you think?
How would you prepare for the competition?
I'm not sure where to start.
I don't think I'll succeed.
Let me tell you.
I hate those people
who think that they'll lose
even before they enter the competition.
That kind of people
would never succeed no matter what.
But a great teacher can produce
a brilliant student.
If someone great like me teaches you,
as long as you're not too bad yourself,
you can still win the competition.
I'll do everything I can to help you.
-Thank you, Ms. Zhuang.
-Okay.
Let me hear about your skill level first.
What's your specialty?
-I can cook sweet and sour pork.
-What else?
Kung Pao chicken, shredded pork
with dried bean curd,
Napa cabbage with dried shrimp,
shrimp with green peas.
Stir-fried tomatoes with egg.
Boiled Chinese Broccoli.
These dishes are basic!
I think a lot of people
don't know how to cook them.
Do you know
that you're joining an international-scale
Chinese cuisine cooking competition?
It's not a competition
where you compete with your relatives.
Then I'm doomed to fail?
Do you know
what's the most important factor
required to win this competition?
Do you know how I won
the competition before?
How?
It has the essence of Dong Xiaowan's
hair and posture, graceful and elegant.
Fragrant, flavorful, enticing,
and gold in color.
That sounds incredible.
-What is it?
-Silly girl.
-It's a pumpkin pie.
-What?
-Pumpkin pie?
-That's right.
How small of a bowl is it?
Stupid girl.
Dong Xiaowan is a woman, not a bowl.
Then how did you think
of cooking such a thing?
There was a reason, of course.
-Did you fight with someone again?
-Why do you care?
Stupid boy.
I need to discipline you.
As a big sister, I had to take on
the role of disciplining Si
since my parents were not around.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey.
I'm invincible. How can I lose to you?
What are you doing?
I know he hates
the flavor of pumpkins the most.
So I intentionally learned how to make
pumpkin pies to punish him.
That's your punishment.
So what happened?
What happened was Si didn't want
to come home anymore.
And even our helpers ended up
eating pumpkin pies every day.
I'll get rashes whenever I see
pumpkin nowadays.
What does that have to do
with the competition?
We're talking about feelings.
Not really.
Do you know why I seem
so sensible and full of substance?
And so ahead of the times?
That's because I've always
read about Chinese history
and understood food very well.
So when they a presented pumpkin pie
as the topic in the competition,
I can use a completely different
point of view to win the competition.
Really?
I want to do that too.
Think about it.
The pumpkin pies made by those girls
didn't contain any cultural heritage
in the flavors they presented.
Unlike mine,
it was full of international charm
and elegance.
So who else could the winner be, but me?
-I need to be like you too.
-Of course.
-Are you feeling more confident now?
-Yes.
Thank you for your pointers.
-I'll work extra hard.
-Very good.
THE BOOK OF SONGS
Here. Read The Book of Songs first.
After you're done,
you'll be greatly enlightened.
And your entire soul will be promoted
to a whole new level.
THE BOOK OF SONGS
Ripped by gabbyu @ Subscene
Translated by Coleen Chua