A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 8
It's just shocking.
I never thought she was like that.
I thought we were friends.
You know?
Is that what you call friendship?
She betrayed you without any guilt.
Yeah. We almost took the blame.
Who does she think she is?
All right. Settle down now.
This is a reminder.
Turn in your group report
by the end of the month.
Please work together in groups
since you'll be getting the same grade.
Professor.
Can we switch groups?
What? Why?
We don't want to work with a liar
and get the same grade as her.
-Yeah.
Who wants to work with her?
Is this about the Weibo rumor?
Yes, professor.
Li Zhen fabricated that rumor.
You can ask Shancai.
Shancai,
tell everyone what happened.
Professor,
Li Zhen did spread the false rumor,
which caused me a lot of trouble.
I went out with a few female classmates.
We had fun and got drunk.
Before Li Zhen went home,
she asked a foreigner
to take me to a hotel.
To assure her that I was okay,
that foreigner friend
took a picture of me in the hotel room
and sent it to her.
Li Zhen accidentally
posted the photo online.
Those Internet trolls
left terrible comments on it.
Li Zhen knew that she made a mistake.
She didn't know what to say.
That's what caused the misunderstanding.
Li Zhen, is that true?
It's true.
It had spread all over the school.
Why didn't she say anything?
-Li Zhen.
-Yeah.
-Because I...
-Because she's mad at me.
When I was at Jing's birthday party,
I didn't answer my phone.
She was outside in the rain all night
and couldn't get in.
I was the one who invited her.
I should have waited for her.
The next day, she caught a cold.
She looked pale and ignored me.
I have to go now.
I was stupid and didn't notice.
I even told her how fun the party was.
It was all my fault.
But now I know that
I need to treat the important people
in my life better than others.
Professor,
we won't fight anymore.
Everyone, please don't be mad at Li Zhen.
We'll study hard from now on.
Okay. Please sit down.
Classmates should get along
and be nice to each other.
I hope nothing like this happens again.
Let's start the class.
Shancai would never do that.
Shancai,
why did you stand up for me
even though I did something so mean?
Because I know you.
We don't want to become despicable people.
Do you remember?
When school had just started,
you said to me...
Shancai, it's good that I know you,
I'd be so lonely by myself.
We'll be best friends from now on
for the next four years.
I feel the same way too.
I'm glad that I know you.
Shancai, I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
It's all right.
It's fine.
Shancai.
Someone's here for you.
See you later. Bye.
Give me your phone.
For what?
Just give it to me.
Here.
-This isn't my phone.
-Idiot.
I'm giving you this phone.
I broke your phone, didn't I?
You're the idiot.
I don't want this phone.
Give me my phone.
Hey!
Give it back.
Give it to me.
What are you looking at?
-Give me my phone.
-Shut up.
If you don't take it,
-I'll smash your mom's phone.
-You--
Try to explain that.
How do you know I have my mom's phone.
I went to your house yesterday
to ask your mom for your number.
She told me.
You asked my mom for my number?
Your mom asked me for my number
and added me on WeChat.
She told me to take good care of you.
I can't believe her.
Anyways,
I need to be able to find you
at all times.
Understand?
What's your problem?
I'm not a dog. Why should I listen to you?
Of course, you're not a dog.
Dogs are much more obedient.
Daoming Si!
The couple's bickering again?
Who's bickering with...
Lei!
Hi, I'm back.
He just arrived this morning.
He called us when he landed.
Si, we should get together tonight.
Sure.
Shancai, long time no see.
Welcome back.
Hey.
Shancai's my girlfriend now.
No, I'm not.
-Stop saying that.
-Really?
What a pity.
A handsome bachelor like me
just got taken.
It is a pity indeed.
It's a pity because we'll never
have peace and quiet again.
Yeah.
They bicker more in a day
than we do in a year.
Cut it out.
Let's go to class.
Hey.
It looks like a fan, it feels like a fan.
It is a fan, so why isn't it working?
Because it isn't plugged in.
You're so smart!
Even an idiot could answer that.
Lame.
-Hey, Shancai.
-What's going on?
What are these appliances...
-How can you afford them?
-Of course, we can't.
They're all from Daoming Si.
Daoming Si is really a nice person.
-Yeah.
-Daoming Si...
Who said he could give us these?
I never agreed.
Shancai, come back.
We have a lot of boxes to open.
Do you like them?
I picked them out myself.
I hate them!
Why are you yelling at me?
Your roof might blow off.
Our house is unlivable anyways.
You gave us so many appliances,
we can't even walk in here.
Are they that big?
I thought they would fit.
Maybe you could sleep on them.
You're ridiculous. I can't talk to you.
If you can't talk, let's meet up.
My driver will pick you up in ten minutes.
What?
"If you can't talk, let's meet up."
What kind of logic is that?
All girls like sweet talk.
Before Si learns how to do that,
he should just shut up.
Yeah.
Where's Lei?
I haven't seen him for a while.
He said he needed some air.
He'll be back soon.
I feel like Lei came back
as a different person this time.
How is he different?
-You don't know?
-Yeah.
Hey, over here.
-Hi.
Who is it?
Are you a turtle? What took you so long?
How dare you say that?
Let me get this straight,
why should I show up
-whenever you want me to?
-Because I want to see you.
Who do you think you are?
Hey, Shancai.
This is Kiki.
I finally get to meet the F4.
When can I play Bridge with you?
If you want to play,
Lei can bring you here anytime.
-We're okay whenever.
-Really?
That's great.
Come on.
Why are you spacing out?
Sit down.
This is yours.
What are you doing?
Here.
Wipe your mouth.
What did Lei do in Paris?
He's changed so much.
I think he grew up.
But we don't know
how long he'll be like this.
Something's wrong between him and Jing.
I'm going home.
Now?
You just got here.
I just came to tell you
to get all those appliances
out of my house.
Or I'm throwing them out. Bye.
-I'll walk you out.
-No, I can go by myself.
Hey.
Huaze Lei has totally changed.
What happened between him and Jing?
What the hell?
He's sitting there
just like he used to.
It's like nothing has changed.
What are you looking at?
A plane just flew by.
-You and Jing--
-You're dating Si?
I'm not.
I never agreed to it.
It's all his idea.
Good.
Shancai, be my girlfriend.
Am I not better than Si?
Are you...
Are you really Huaze Lei?
I'm just kidding.
Did you believe me?
You're so cute.
Kidding?
I can't steal Si's girlfriend.
He's my brother.
Are you disappointed?
How about
we secretly date behind Si's back?
Doesn't that sound exciting?
Did you believe it again?
Class is starting.
I need to go.
Shancai,
you're even prettier now.
Thanks.
-Hey. What are you doing?
-Come with me.
I'm busy.
I need to work.
-I'm not rich like you.
-Shut up.
-I've already told them you're not going.
-What?
INTERNATIONAL DEPARTURE
Hey. Wait.
Where are you taking me?
-On a trip.
-A trip?
I didn't agree to that.
-I didn't tell my parents--
-They already gave me permission.
I told the tea shop too.
It's the weekend, so you don't have class.
I brought everything you need.
Your clothes and your passport.
Any other questions?
If not, let's go. Everyone's waiting.
Everyone?
Hey.
I'm warning you.
When we get to the island,
don't run off on your own.
-Is it dangerous there?
-Yes.
You're a ticking time-bomb.
-You might hurt someone.
-Daoming Si.
Passengers, we have come across
some turbulence.
For your safety, please stay in your seat
and fasten your seatbelt.
Thank you.
Strike a pose.
Where do you want to go first?
You decide.
-Really?
-Of course.
You scared me.
Who said you could look at another man?
That's none of your business.
-Are you jealous again?
-Of course, I am.
It's so beautiful!
It's like a postcard.
Do you like it?
It's the best room in the hotel.
The sky and sea are so blue.
It's wonderful!
Shancai,
this is our room.
What? I...
We're staying in the same room?
Don't worry.
It's the same room,
but we'll sleep in separate beds.
That's not what I mean.
What do you mean then?
I...
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
-Cheers.
Here.
Meizuo.
-Yeah?
-Perform for us.
All right, listen up.
3.14159
384626.
Lei.
Lei...
Your friend is so amusing.
What about me?
Am I not amusing?
Don't you play the violin?
When will you play it for me?
Only special people
can hear me play the violin.
How do I become a special person?
You need to like me more.
Do I not like you enough?
That's not fair. I like you a lot.
You're so naughty.
He came back from Paris as a real man.
Looks like now we only need
to wait for Si to grow up.
Shancai,
will you wait for him?
Stop it.
Shut up.
Try it.
-The chicken is really good.
-I agree.
One, two, three, cheese.
I know I'm attractive,
but do you have to keep staring at me?
Who was staring at you?
You're so full of yourself.
Aren't you sleeping
on that bed over there?
Why? Can't I sit here for a while?
Don't worry.
I do like you,
but before you like me back,
I won't do anything to you.
I'd never touch a woman
without her consent.
I think...
Your legs are sticking out.
Do you want to sleep over there?
It's fine.
How about you just say you like me?
I don't know how much longer I can wait.
Or do you want to sleep
on this tiny bed with me?
No!
Lei,
what's up with you?
Ever since you came back from Paris,
you've totally changed.
Are you worried about me?
It's normal to be worried
about friends, isn't it?
It's because of Jing, isn't it?
What are you doing?
Ten minutes.
No, five minutes is enough.
I'm fine during the day,
but I can't deal with it at night.
Can you give me a hug?
Why don't you ask that girl to hug you?
I don't want to be touched
by a woman I don't know.
This is the first time
I've seen Huaze Lei so vulnerable.
And I realized that
I never gave up on him.
Shancai...
I found out that Jing
doesn't need me.
Jing and I lived together
in Paris for a while.
I still remember
the look on her face
when she saw me that day.
We stayed at home when we were free.
We never got tired of it.
It was our own little world.
It was the best time of my life.
But
it didn't last very long.
She went to school during the day
and interned at a law firm at night.
I was alone all day without her.
She smiled less and less.
She became more tired.
She built a wall around her.
Even if I had turned into air,
I couldn't find a way in.
You know how
I was slightly autistic before.
Jing led me out of the shadows of autism.
But I never changed.
I was still the child
who hid in the corner.
I couldn't do anything
for the girl I loved.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why I'm telling you all this.
Thank you for listening to me.
Did you find her?
No.
Where did she go at this hour?
She's not picking up her phone.
How about we split up and look for her?
Sure. Okay.
Where did you go?
Why weren't you picking up?
I couldn't sleep,
so I went for a walk on the beach.
I forgot to bring my phone.
Idiot. Couldn't you leave a note?
All right. Don't worry.
It's fine now.
If you do that again, I...
-You'll what?
-Shancai, do you know what Si did?
He came to my room and yelled,
"Shancai drowned in the sea!"
I had to come out and look for you.
That's enough.
Go to bed.
Fine.
We all know whom Si loves more.
-We'll give you some privacy.
-Let's go.
What are you still doing here? Go to bed.
Did you know that Huaze Lei
didn't come back to the room last night?
I asked him and he said
he was at the beach all night.
You would think that he had a mistress.
He's probably just shy.
Really?
Where did you go?
I couldn't sleep,
so I went for a walk on the beach.
Huaze Lei doesn't seem happy lately.
-Why?
-I...
Lei.
Did you see Shancai
at the beach last night?
Yeah.
I was there thinking,
and she came out for a walk.
She saw me and we chatted for a bit.
Oh.
TENG TANGJING, EXCHANGE STUDENT IN FRANCE
EXPECTED TO WED THIS YEAR
"Teng Tangjing, an exchange student,
fell in love with the son
of the mayor of Paris.
They are expected to get married...
by year-end."
Did you know about that?
Yes.
It's big news in Paris.
Is that why you came back?
Lei, do you not care?
Jing's about to marry someone else.
Why should I care?
Everything's over now.
That's why he's changed so much.
He must be shocked by Jing's engagement.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Really?
You don't look okay at all.
I want to know too.
Will I get better?
You will.
You'll get better.
Because
you're a wonderful
and very talented person.
How could you not get better?
Why are you crying?
I told you I'm okay.
Go back to your room.
Don't worry about me.
I don't know...
I just can't stop thinking about you.
I'm always wondering
why you're so unhappy
and what will happen between you and Jing.
I'm also wondering...
why you can't be happier.
Why aren't you the one I love?
Si.
Daoming Si!
Wait.
Listen to me.
Everything's clear now.
What is there to say?
No, it's not what it seems like.
Don't touch me!
Dong Shancai, ever since the beginning,
I've liked you and only you.
But what about you?
I'm sorry.
Let's pretend we don't know each other.
Si.
You have no right to talk to me.
I can't believe Si just left without us.
Wasn't everything fine yesterday?
Something must've happened.
Lei, did you see Si?
No.
We'll ask him when we get back.
Let's go.
Come on.
It's not ready yet.
-Shancai, welcome home.
-Welcome home.
Are you tired from your trip?
You look exhausted.
Of course, she is.
The pictures she sent were beautiful.
She must have had a lot of fun
and stayed up late, right?
Right?
It was very beautiful.
Shancai, tell me.
What happened between you and Daoming Si?
Did you guys create
some beautiful memories there?
This is your daughter
you're talking about.
Girls need to protect themselves.
Right?
What were you thinking?
I meant candle-lit dinners,
holding hands, and embraces.
Daoming Si is such a handsome young man.
-It must've been so dreamy. Wasn't it?
-That's exaggerating.
Our daughter is the best.
Even that Daoming Si guy doesn't
deserve her, you know?
Dad, Mom,
stop talking about Daoming Si.
It's over.
What do you mean, over?
Isn't he trying to win you over? Shancai?
That's enough.
Stop pestering her.
She's clearly not happy.
But didn't Daoming Si come
to our house just a few days ago?
How is it over already?
I have to know the reason.
What if our daughter
got dumped or abandoned?
What can you do?
Then I hope that
he grows shorter every day.
Which part?
His hair.
If he's bald,
he won't get a new girlfriend.
Good thing I have a lot of hair.
Idiot.
AUDIO MESSAGE FROM DAOMING SI
I need to be able to find you
at all times.
AUDIO MESSAGE FROM DAOMING SI
Do you like them?
I picked them out myself.
AUDIO MESSAGE FROM DAOMING SI
Why are you yelling at me?
Your roof might blow off.
AUDIO MESSAGE FROM DAOMING SI
Are they that big?
I thought they would fit.
Maybe you could sleep on them.
AUDIO MESSAGE FROM DAOMING SI
If you can't talk, let's meet up.
My driver will pick you up in ten minutes.
Daoming Si was so nice to me,
but I hurt him.
Maybe
he hates me now.
I didn't like him anyway.
A lot of bad things happened.
But maybe this is the best ending.
Hello?
Yes.
I need to tell you something about Si.
Translated by Sophie Chang at Netflix
Synced and uploaded by
gabbyu @ Subscene