A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
METEOR GARDEN
EPISODE 11
Tian Ye.
This is Yang Rong.
She graduated from cooking school
with the best grades.
She'll help you in the kitchen.
I remember you told me
that she would be here before noon.
It's already one o'clock.
Sorry, I'm late. I was stuck in traffic.
If you can't be here on time,
I won't work with you.
But, Tian Ye,
I spent a lot of effort poaching her.
If you kick her out,
who's going to take the job?
I'm sorry. I'll never be late again.
Please give me another chance.
What's your name?
I'm Dong Shancai.
You're here to try out for the job, right?
Can you start today?
-No problem.
-No.
I just read her resume.
She has no experience.
Attitude is more important.
Si.
Mom called me.
She wants me to bring you
back to London this time.
I have already refused for you.
Zhuang, I've decided.
Decided what?
I'm going to the UK.
Didn't you say you'd never go?
Well, I changed my mind.
I made up my mind
before the Bridge competition.
When the competition is over,
regardless of the outcome,
I'm leaving for the UK.
I'll take a look at the schools there.
If I like it there,
I'm going to study there.
Is this because of Shancai?
Zhuang, I don't have to explain.
I can go wherever I want, whenever I want.
The faster, the better.
By the way,
can you help me with the application
and my passport?
You're this easily defeated?
That's not the Daoming family spirit.
I can finally rest.
I'm getting old now,
I can't deal with this.
-Thank you, Mr. Gao.
-Thanks.
I'm going to retire soon.
You young people should work hard.
Tian Ye.
You're going to take over
as the head chef soon.
I don't know if I'll pass the exam.
Hey, try the pork ribs I just made.
That smells amazing.
You can cook?
My mom has a takeout restaurant.
So, I learned a bit from her.
It's pretty delicious.
It looks good too.
Which school did you go to?
I go to Mingde.
-Mingde?
Only elite students go there.
Why did you come to help in the kitchen?
I major in nutrition
and my mom cooks for a living,
so I'm happy when I'm in the kitchen.
I can learn so much here.
We sure have a lot of elite students here.
This is our sous chef,
Tian Ye.
He's also an elite student
in business school.
You guys should go ahead and eat,
I'm still cutting onions.
I'll come over later.
Daoming Si is gone.
Will F4 break up?
-My heart has left with Daoming Si.
-What?
Hey, Shancai.
Shancai!
-What?
-Have you heard?
-Heard what?
-Daoming Si is going to London.
London? You're going to London?
It's not a big deal.
My mom's business is there.
It's totally normal for me to go there.
Liar.
You hate it in London.
Are you trying to avoid Lei and Shancai?
Why would I avoid them?
Si.
Just so you know,
I'm not going to London
because of you. It's my plan.
I'm going to come back a better man.
Yeah right. You won't last two months.
You're going to London?
Yes. Got a problem with that?
Shancai, he's not sure yet.
Talk some sense into him.
I've made up my mind.
No one can persuade me.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why would I tell you?
Without me in the way,
you can finally date him.
Isn't that right, Lei?
You should get right to it.
When I get to London,
I'll find a blond girl
and we'll go on dates
by the River Thames every day.
It will be so romantic.
Fine.
Go then.
I'm happy you're leaving.
I'll live happier without you.
Goodbye forever!
Shancai, bring over the soup.
Okay.
Be careful!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Hello, sir.
-Daoming Si?
-Where's Shancai?
She has the night shift today.
She's probably at Frankie's Restaurant.
Frankie's Restaurant?
Thank you.
You've been distracted all day.
What's wrong?
I...
Shancai, there's a boy here for you.
-For me?
-Yeah, he ordered a lot and won't eat.
He said the food isn't fresh.
He demands to see someone in the kitchen.
He's just here to cause trouble.
I'm here for Dong Shancai.
Have her come out.
Sir, excuse me.
Dong Shancai works in the kitchen,
she can't come out here.
If she doesn't come out, I won't leave.
What are you doing here?
Sir, you said that our food isn't fresh.
Which dish was it?
That's not the point.
I'm here for her.
Restaurants are for eating.
If you're here to see her,
please wait until she's off work.
You're getting in the way of our work.
By the way,
our restaurant has always
been known for our fresh food.
-Please don't hurt our--
-That's enough.
I didn't come here to listen to you.
I'm here for Shancai.
Aren't you going to London?
What happened to your arm?
It's just a small burn.
It's none of your business.
Can't you learn how
to take care of yourself?
You're taking on too much work.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why should I tell you?
Is it any of your business?
Let's go.
Hey!
You can't just do whatever you want.
You're so immature.
Sir, please have some respect.
She's my employee.
Giving her problems
is causing us problems.
Who the hell are you?
You have no right to talk to me.
Daoming Si.
I work here.
Please respect my job and my colleagues.
What do you mean?
I mean...
Please leave.
I was going to say goodbye before I left.
Looks like there's no need.
Daoming Si.
Dong Shancai.
I'm never coming back.
Goodbye.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry for causing so much trouble.
I thought he was just a picky customer.
That Daoming Si...
Is he your boyfriend?
No.
He's none of my concern.
I didn't say goodbye properly
to Daoming Si.
Maybe in the future, I'll regret it.
But perhaps it's better for us this way.
TALENT'S TEA SHOP
Didn't you break up with Daoming Si?
Why are you still mad?
I don't know.
I don't have the right to be mad at him.
But when I heard he was going to London,
it was just too sudden.
I can't accept that
he's leaving so quickly.
You care about Daoming Si.
That's impossible!
His actions are unbearable.
I know.
He went to see you
because he wanted to get back together.
But, you guys argued again.
Shancai, you're home.
You're home, sweetheart.
Why do you look so sad?
What are you up to lately?
You've been coming home late.
I found a new part-time job.
Part-time job?
What is it?
Is it hard work?
-Will it affect your studies?
-No.
It won't affect my studies.
It will help me learn some skills.
Really?
Yes, I'm helping in a restaurant kitchen.
I've arranged my schedule.
Don't worry.
Working in a kitchen?
There's fire in the kitchen.
Should we be worried about you?
Our daughter has perfect skin,
what if she gets burnt?
Don't worry.
Mom, don't I cook with you all the time?
Fine.
I guess with better cooking skills,
you'll be able to cook for us.
Sounds good.
Shancai will be able to take
our restaurant to the next level, right?
Take these clothes inside.
She's working now,
don't make her do chores.
She still has to do her chores.
You shouldn't spoil her.
A, C, W,
X,
D,
B, D...
You got three out of ten.
What?
If that's true,
how am I supposed
to get your super memory?
You wanted me to train you.
Have you lost hope now?
Why do you want a super memory?
I'm a part of F4.
I have to work hard to improve myself.
I can't ruin our reputation.
Didn't you quit?
Now you've joined F4 again?
I...
Hey.
Daoming Si, tell them, am I a part of F4?
Si, what's wrong?
You look mad.
I guess it's because someone isn't here.
We should have invited Shancai.
She can't come.
She's working right now. It's tough work.
I really admire Shancai's energy.
I would work with her,
but I have too many classes this semester.
Why would you bother Shancai
when she's working?
None of your business.
None of my business?
Everything about Shancai is my business.
Why is it your business then?
Aren't you going to London?
Qinghe, you have the F4 spirit.
Since Si is going to London,
I guess you can join F4 now.
-I have already joined.
-Shut up!
Hey, Xinhui,
did you know that Daoming Si
is leaving tomorrow?
Isn't his flight today?
I wonder if the plane has taken off?
Shancai.
You're not sending him off?
Of course not.
I thought you like him.
Who likes him?
You keep saying that you like Huaze Lei,
but the truth is, you like Daoming Si.
Why can't you admit it?
That's nonsense.
Who knows when he'll be back?
Are you really giving up on him?
Did you know?
When we were fighting,
Si got drunk one time.
I took him to my place.
I thought he would like me.
But he told me,
I was different from you.
He said that Shancai
wouldn't betray her own heart.
So do you want him to leave?
Si.
Don't miss us too much in London.
I emailed you our pictures.
You can look at them when you miss me.
Who wants to see your face?
I'm not a woman.
You guys are like little girls.
He won't be gone forever.
Zhuang, we don't care about Si,
-but we'll miss you.
-Hey.
With you gone,
nobody will yell at us or kick us.
-We'll feel so lonely.
-Really?
I'll miss you too.
Give me a hug.
Okay.
I want one too.
You're such a good boy.
So? You don't want a hug?
Silly kid.
Have you said goodbye to Shancai?
Whatever.
Why should I say goodbye
to that ugly thing?
I'm an elegant, beautiful,
graceful and gentle woman.
How can you be so rude to me?
You're elegant?
That hurts!
Little brat.
Have I not hurt you enough?
Huaze Lei will take care of Shancai.
Isn't that great?
Okay, Si and I need to board now.
Goodbye now.
Take care, Zhuang.
-Don't miss me.
-Bye.
-Safe flight.
Si, wait.
I have something to tell you.
What?
-What are they talking about?
-I don't know.
Welcome, passengers.
-Thank you for flying with us.
-Please fasten your seat belt.
-We're about to take off.
-Seat belt.
Please fasten your seat belts
and switch your phones to airplane mode.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Have a delightful flight.
Lei...
That son of a bitch.
What did you say?
Hey! I need to get off.
Stop it.
I'm warning you. Sit down.
Don't embarrass me.
-I don't care. I need to get off.
-Sit down!
-I don't care.
-Sit!
-I'm getting off!
Brat.
You're an arrogant,
green shoe-wearing, pineapple head.
You think you're popular at school
so you can do whatever you want.
You're just a jerk.
Give it back.
Hey. Give it to me!
Hey!
Give it to me!
What do you want?
Here, it's your coat.
Sorry.
I'm late.
If you say you didn't do it,
I believe you.
Why do I suddenly feel disappointed?
I thought you like Daoming Si.
No. I don't like him.
I don't like arrogant and pushy people.
I just...
What's wrong with me?
Zhuang and Si are here.
Where's Mom?
She's working in New York.
Where's Yuanzi?
She went to New York with Mrs. Daoming.
Oh.
Zhuang, since Mom's not here.
I have no reason to be in London.
We should go back to Shanghai now.
What?
You said you wanted to study here.
Then, you made a scene on the plane.
Now, you want to go back?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Do you want to get beaten up?
Hey.
You were the mean one.
You made me pass out on the plane.
Are you even my real sister?
I told you, I was a gift
from the phone company.
But for real,
I've enrolled you in a lot of...
a lot of international finance classes.
You better stay in London.
Or what will I tell Mom?
What will you tell Mom?
Did mom send you to control me?
Stupid boy.
You don't understand anything.
If it weren't for me,
Mom would've flown to Shanghai
and kicked your butt.
Mom is too busy.
She doesn't have time for me.
That's true.
But, remember,
Mom wants you to take over Daoming Group.
She can't be here with you,
but whatever you say or do
is totally under her control.
You know that, don't you?
Of course I do.
But...
so what if she disagrees?
I won't let her control my life.
He's all grown up now.
Nothing happened between Shancai and I...
that night.
I think the person
Shancai really likes is you.
LOG IN
FRIENDS
FRIEND: I WON'T TELL YOU
What's your name?
I won't tell you.
Why can't you tell me?
What's your name?
I told you.
I won't tell you.
Hello?
Is this Frankie's Restaurant in Shanghai?
I'm looking for Dong Shancai.
She works in your kitchen.
Okay.
-You are?
-I...
I'm her dad.
There's an urgent family matter.
Hurry up.
Hello, Dad?
Why aren't you talking?
Is his phone reception bad?
Dad, if you don't talk, I'm hanging up.
Hello?
It's me.
How's work? Is it tough?
Do you have enough money?
I hope they're not bullying you.
Sorry, you have the wrong number.
That dumb woman.
She hung up on me!
But...
It's not her fault.
She didn't know it was me.
FENG SHUI INN
Si!
You're back in London!
Yes.
I'm here to have some food.
We're not open now. No food for you.
Yue, you can cook for me.
Pretty please?
-Please, Yue?
-Okay.
-I'll set it up for you.
Si.
Si,
I haven't seen you
since you started college.
It's been four years, right?
Yes.
I've been longing for your cooking.
It's my favorite since childhood.
Please enjoy.
These are all your favorite dishes.
Kung Pao chicken, braised eggplant,
and sweet and sour pork ribs.
Dandan noodles, too.
I'm starting to drool now.
You've grown up so much.
When your mom first brought you to London,
you were only six.
You didn't have money
and you were in front of our restaurant
trembling with hunger.
What a poor sight.
But, you were so cute.
Good thing I met you, Yue.
After you had my cooking,
you refused to go home.
Your parents were so worried.
They looked all over London.
The police almost brought me in.
I couldn't help myself.
My parents were always busy
and took me all around the world.
It was so irritating.
By the way,
my mom never cooked for me.
I'm glad you like my food.
You're always welcome here.
Thank you, Yue. You're the best.
Honestly,
you're a lot like my son-in-law.
You look mean and immature,
but actually,
you're very nice, kind and adorable.
He must be handsome.
Of course.
Then...
who's more handsome?
Me or him?
You are
pretty much the same.
-I'll prepare dessert.
-Okay.
You don't know how hard
other people have to work.
-You're a parasite of society.
-Shut up!
Look familiar?
This sweet and sour pork rib
doesn't look good at all.
If you don't want it, throw it away.
Why do I always think of her
when I have sweet and sour pork ribs?
TIAN YE IS TAKING OVER THE FAMILY BUSINESS
Shancai, can you taste this for me?
Of course.
It's lobster.
It looks amazing.
What do you think?
It's very good.
Hey,
what's this called?
You've been working on it for five hours.
It must be very complicated.
Yes.
It's a famous French dish
called Lobster Thermidor.
Only a few chefs know how to make it.
Qian is one of them.
Who's Qian?
Qian is the best chef in China.
Every year, he inspects
the restaurants in Shanghai.
I've worked here the past year
to receive his approval
and become the head chef.
That's wonderful.
The sauce must be hard to make.
Exactly.
This fish soup
has abalone, sea cucumber,
shark tail skin, yak-skin gelatin,
king oyster mushrooms, pork tendon,
and many other ingredients.
It takes three hours to make.
I found this formula
after trying for three months.
Just the sauce takes that long?
To be honest,
there is a shortcut.
There's a special ingredient
called Kamio leaf.
It can replace the sauce.
Then you can just use that.
Why trouble yourself?
It still tastes different.
Chefs like us shouldn't be lazy.
Kamio leaves are incredibly rare, too.
Is that so?
When are you taking the exam?
-Tomorrow.
-Tomorrow?
I was kind of nervous,
but you said it's good, which helped me.
Tian Ye, you work very hard.
I'm sure you'll be the best chef ever.
All the best tomorrow.
No way.
-What should he do?
-I don't know.
What should he do?
He's doomed.
What's wrong?
What happened?
Tian Ye is doomed.
He fell asleep this morning
and the fish soup cooked for too long.
The flavor is all wrong.
There's only two hours left
until his exam.
He's trying to make the soup again,
but there's not enough time.
-Good luck.
Tian Ye.
I'm so stupid.
I spent the whole year here
just for this day.
Don't freak out.
We'll find a way.
I need three hours to make the soup.
It's impossible.
Can you postpone it to tomorrow?
There's no tomorrow!
There's a special ingredient
called Kamio leaf.
It can replace the sauce.
Tian Ye, make the Lobster Thermidor.
I'll go get Kamio leaves for you.
This...
Shen Nong Village?
PLACES TO BUY KAMIO LEAVES
ONLY AT SHEN NONG VILLAGE
SHEN NONG VILLAGE HERBS
Hello, I need Kamio leaves.
How many do you have?
How do you know we have them?
I looked it up online.
This is the only place in Shanghai.
You're lucky. We have one left.
-How much is it?
-1,500 yuan.
That expensive?
Tian Ye, I got the Kamio leaves.
SHEN NONG VILLAGE HERBS
Dong Shancai, where are you?
There's only 30 minutes left.
Wait for me. I'm almost there.
The Kamio leaves...
What should I do?
Young lady,
are you okay?
Do you remember me?
-Out of the way!
-Hey!
Watch out!
Tian Ye, is there still time?
What happened, Dong Shancai?
I'm fine. Go cook.
There's no time left.
Tian Ye, very good job.
You're still young,
but this lobster is marvelous.
You have great potential.
Qian, you're too kind.
But,
if this sauce
wasn't made from Kamio leaves,
it would taste even better.
Tian Ye, where did you learn how to cook?
I haven't received professional training.
I've loved to cook since middle school.
So, I did part-time jobs in restaurants.
That's how I gained experience.
Tian Ye did a lot of part-time jobs,
just like me.
Tian Ye.
-I guess his life
-Good job.
-is just as difficult as mine.
-Your future is very bright.
Take care.
Congratulations, Tian Ye.
From now on, you're the head chef
of Frankie's Restaurant.
-Head chef!
If it weren't for your Kamio leaves,
I wouldn't be able to pass the exam.
This is all because of you.
Shancai,
thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm happy that they saw
how talented you are.
"I'm happy that they saw
how talented you are."
Congratulations, Tian Ye.
Congratulations.
Head chef.
-Head chef!
-Head chef.
-Congratulations.
-Head chef!
Subtitles by Netflix
Translated by Sophie Chang
Ripped and synced by
gabbyu @ Subscene