A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
FABIENNE BÉRIOT FOUND DEAD IN HER HOME
[J'accuse whimpering]
It's my fault, Ben.
You were right.
I shouldn't have involved her.
About that…
I don't want to find you dead.
What should I do?
Should I quit?
Give up and let him win?
Or should I say, "Sorry. Sorry again
for the trouble, Mr. Pellegrini"?
"Sorry, sir."
Again!
[Benjamin] You have a life, Assane.
You have a wife and a son.
And his birthday is today.
[J'accuse whimpers]
I thought you had something planned.
You promised Raoul.
[Assane clicks tongue]
I don't feel like it.
Well, yeah, but if you don't,
then he's beat you.
[soft music playing]
[J'accuse whimpers]
What are you doing?
He's very sweet.
Just don't mention you-know-who.
[Benjamin] Who?
- Pellegrini!
- [barks]
[door closes]
Youssef? Honestly, it's so shitty
you got pulled from the case.
It's not a big deal.
And besides, paperwork is my passion.
- All right, ciao.
- Ciao.
[indistinct background chatter]
[door closes]
Okay.
Who is this guy?
Luis Perenna,
Sernine.
The Louvre…
Okay, Sernine, 813, Perenna…
The Tiger's Teeth…
THE OTHER EDITION
[Guédira] Salvator…
Of course, of course.
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
Wait, no, wait…
[Guédira sighs]
The Queen's Necklace…
Shit! What am I missing here?
Salvator, The Seven of Hearts…
There's got to be a link.
[suspenseful music playing]
- [cell phone alarm ringing]
- [distant siren wailing]
[Guédira sighs]
11TH DECEMBER:
MAURICE LEBLANC'S BIRTHDAY
[chuckles softly]
[Belkacem] It's crazy.
They've got nothing in forensics.
The guy robbed the Louvre,
and you've got basically nothing on him.
Either he's the luckiest guy in France…
- Or the greatest thief in the world.
- Don't you start!
Guédira had a lead.
Guédira's no longer on this case.
Don't make me take you off.
Okay, but where is he?
It's not like I fired him.
He texted me saying he was sick.
- Did he look sick to you yesterday?
- Honestly…
I think he always looks sick.
All right…
If this guy's in Paris,
we're gonna get him.
[children shouting]
[church bells ringing]
[distant siren wailing]
[dramatic music playing]
[horn blares]
[tires screech]
[distant siren wailing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[doorbell rings]
Papa?
[Assane] Happy birthday, son.
What have you been doing?
Oh, nothing.
- I missed my bus, so I ran here instead.
- Ah.
What's this?
Open it.
[Assane laughs]
[Claire] What is it?
Oh, let me.
There you go.
There!
- Um, Assane, remember, he's 14.
- [Assane] So what?
You don't like it?
Well, I really like the Lupin books,
but I'm not so sure about this.
Well, I'm sure.
You're gonna love it. Trust me.
Because it's not over.
We gotta go or we'll be late.
We're late?
- Surprise!
- Okay, then, you boys have fun.
You're not coming with us?
Uh… No, no, no. I'm not coming.
I have plans.
Hmm… A doctor's appointment?
- Did you snitch on me?
- [Assane chuckles]
- If you wanna ask me a question, ask it!
- I don't have questions.
- Nothing to hide. What do you wanna know?
- If you're coming.
- The train leaves in an hour.
- What train?
Our train.
I got you a ticket.
[Claire sighs]
You're a pain in the ass, Assane.
It's like you never leave me
any choice on these things.
[Assane] Mm-hm.
Mm-hm?
He never lets me know.
Even when he's three hours late
or blows me off.
Does this happen a lot?
[Claire sighs]
- Too focused on his work?
- What?
His work, yeah.
I guess you can call it that.
- [therapist] What does he do?
- Oh, it's better if you don't know.
Let's just say,
if you run into him on the street,
better watch your wallet.
Come to think of it,
I barely know what he does.
[policeman] 295, here.
[Assane] So, you're the two they sent?
- [woman] Yeah.
- [man] Yeah.
I got two of my guys on the inside.
You better check the windows.
The perp could sneak out.
They're still inside?
There are four of 'em. Three took off
on a scooter, one's inside. I'll get him.
- [woman] You don't want us to go with you?
- Kid on foot. I can manage.
- You two check the windows.
- You got it.
Thank you.
[door intercom chimes]
- [woman] Yes?
- Good afternoon, ma'am. It's the police.
- Can you open up, please?
- [woman] Who is it?
It's the police.
- [woman] Right, come in.
- Thank you very much.
No need to worry. I have two of my cops
standing guard downstairs.
Everything will be fine. You're safe now.
See?
Did they take anything?
I… don't think so, no.
You're lucky because the apartment
downstairs was totally cleaned out.
They took everything.
- [woman] Really?
- Oh, yeah.
- Do you have an alarm system?
- [woman] No.
Oh, no. That's not good, ma'am.
Not at all.
They're going to come back.
Oh, you think so?
Oh, I know so!
These guys will never stop.
If they haven't finished the job,
they'll come back,
stuff their pockets and take everything.
But you'll stay, right?
No, ma'am.
I can't stay here.
It's not possible.
We're understaffed. Most of us
are sent to the bad neighborhoods.
- There's nothing left for the good folks.
- My God!
That's right. Tell me about it!
- There might be a solution.
- Yes, tell me.
It's complicated.
Please, tell me.
If you have some items of real value,
leave them with me.
Yeah, I think it's for the best.
Leave them with me.
I'll put 'em in the station,
safe and sound, in the evidence room.
They'll be safe.
And then you'll pick 'em up
after we finally catch these guys.
Yes. Let's do that.
It'll mean a lot of paperwork for me, but…
Oh, will you? Please!
[Assane chuckles softly]
All right.
Let's do it.
[woman chuckles]
Uh, ma'am…
Just the most valuable.
[clock chimes]
[Assane sighs]
[door opens]
Ah, there it is.
My husband gave these ones to me.
He assisted with the extraction
of diamonds in the Belgian Congo.
- The good old days.
- The locals were sitting on a fortune.
They didn't even realize it.
- We just helped ourselves.
- Their loss, right?
[woman] Hmm.
- Should I take the earrings too?
- Oh! Yes, please.
[woman] Thank you. I…
I have one last favor to ask you.
I have a Fabergé egg.
Huh? You do?
But, ma'am, I can't take it all.
For me?
- You drive a hard bargain.
- I know.
All right.
- A souvenir from the Belgian Congo.
- Thank you.
- [Assane chuckles]
- Oh!
You are a gentleman.
[Assane laughs]
- [therapist]This man's your soulmate?
- "Soulmate" might be a bit of a stretch.
[therapist] Well, those are your words.
During our last session, you said to me,
"Assane is made for me,
whether I like it or not."
"He's my soulmate."
So, you believe in soulmates?
[lighter clicks]
[Claire] Let's just say
when I'm in his arms and he's holding me,
I can believe that.
When I'm exhausted, I've made dinner,
and he's three hours late,
it's more complicated.
[ticking]
[Claire]
I keep telling myself it'll get better,
and there are moments…
[Claire sighs]
…when it's good.
We talk about the future and…
All of a sudden,
it's like he can't help himself.
He does something that could ruin it.
A vicious cycle?
[Claire] I'm not sure
I'm even in love with him because…
we've been together for so long.
We have fun, we've…
we've been through so much.
He's my best friend, but…
I don't think he's my soulmate.
You don't owe him anything.
You're not married.
You don't have children.
[alarm rings]
[Claire] I'll talk to him tonight.
And I guess we'll…
Well, we'll see.
You'll see what?
If he cares about me.
[door buzzes]
[distant horn blares]
- Can you believe it?
- [woman] Ah!
- You didn't see him?
- [woman] No.
- [Assane] He got out through the roof.
- Shit, damn it!
- You didn't see him up on the roof?
- [woman] No.
We don't even get paid enough
for this shit. I mean, am I right?
He dropped this making his escape.
- Wow, look at that.
- Yeah.
- Not bad.
- Tell me about it!
I'm taking this to the station
as evidence.
- Okay.
- I'll do the paperwork.
- There goes my afternoon.
- Thank you.
- It's my pleasure.
- Have a good day.
- Yeah.
Bye! Thanks for having my back.
You'll look good in my report.
- Take care.
- Yeah.
- Don't work too hard. Goodbye!
- [woman] Thank you.
[Claire]
Hey, can we see each other tonight?
We need to talk.
What do you mean, I sound serious?
No.
This is how I talk.
It's important.
Can we get some dinner?
Seven o'clock, okay.
But pick a quiet place, Assane.
Not too much, okay?
Okay. See you.
[indistinct PA announcement]
[whistle blows]
- [Claire] Which seat, Assane?
- [Assane] Eighty-five.
Eighty-four, eighty-five, eighty-six…
- Here it is.
- [Claire] Here?
- Yeah.
- Okay, looks good.
[train horn blows]
You know, Le Havre, it's not so great.
We're not going there.
- We're not? Where are we going?
- Under the Fréfossé fortress.
[Claire] Ah!
"Downstream from Étretat,
the maidens' room."
"Under the Fréfossé fort."
- "The hollow needle."
- Exactly.
We're going to Étretat.
- There's an Arsène Lupin celebration.
- Oh, yeah. That's why I love you.
- [Claire laughs]
- You see?
Well, yeah.
I've known this man for 25 years.
Of course, when I met him,
he asked me to read The Hollow Needle.
Obviously, I remember some of it.
- Some of it?
- Some of it.
Hang on.
Two feet on the letters in the stone.
Measure 19 fathoms.
Then turn the cross.
Then you must climb
to the top of the 44th step.
Then, on the 357th,
you will find…
[Claire and Assane]
…the treasure of Arsène Lupin!
[all laugh]
You guys are totally crazy.
- [Claire laughs]
- Yeah, crazy, but connected.
- [Benjamin] This place is okay.
- It better be.
We're here to celebrate.
- I thought you were scouting the location.
- [chuckling] I told you.
The more money there is…
The bigger the patsies are. I know.
I found the perfect place for my shop.
A large ground floor space
in the flea market
for the clients who are normal,
and a basement for the clients…
who aren't normal.
Closest police station?
Not close.
That's perfect.
- I know.
- We're good.
[jazz music playing]
First sale for the shop.
- A Fabergé?
- Of course. Why not?
[Benjamin chuckles]
We're on our way, my friend.
[Benjamin clears throat]
[footsteps]
[Benjamin]
Ah! I've just figured out why we're here.
- That's not why.
- Yeah.
I'll be right back.
[Benjamin sighs]
[Assane and Juliette laugh]
You gotta stop following me.
[Juliette laughs]
Are you kidding me?
You're following me.
Why are you here?
You look good.
[chuckles] You know I'm taken.
[chuckling] And that's a problem?
It never used to be.
- It was a mistake.
- Why are you second-guessing this?
- Does it look like I am?
- No, and that's the problem.
Oh, it's a problem?
Then it's a big problem.
[Juliette laughs]
[Assane laughs]
- I can't keep doing this to Claire.
- Claire?
[Juliette laughs]
Even her name sounds boring.
I can't imagine the rest.
I'm a good guy, Juliette.
Oh, no. No, not at all.
You're not a good guy at all.
That's what I like.
- No.
- [scoffs]
I see…
I won't keep waiting for you.
Well, you could stop waiting.
I love Claire.
And I love you.
So, what do we do, huh?
I won't let you go.
I'm sorry.
[Juliette sighs]
[music playing through headphones]
It's nice to get away with you two.
It's cool.
[cell phone dings]
The doctor?
First of all, his name's Marc.
And it's none of your business.
And have you seen Marc
since the last time?
I said it's none of your business.
She hasn't seen him.
Hey!
[Assane laughs]
Okay, picture time.
[Assane] Okay.
Okay…
[camera clicks]
- [camera clicks]
- Wait, let me see.
- [Claire] Wait.
- [Assane] Let's see.
- Get your hands off!
- Hey, show us.
- We wanna see.
- [Claire] Fine!
So, how's it look?
Wow, he loves himself!
I can't believe this.
[Assane chuckles softly]
I am pretty good-looking,
and you're not bad yourselves!
[Assane laughs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[cell phone rings]
Where are you?
[man] I've found him. We're on the train.
Did he see you?
I don't think so.
But he's with his wife and kid.
You can leave them alone.
But him, get rid of him for good.
Don't let me down.
Yes, sir.
[indistinct chatter]
[lighter clicks]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Raoul ♪
[Assane] Bravo!
- [Assane laughs]
- [passengers clapping]
- [Assane] Thank you, everyone!
- Assane, enough!
[Assane] Bravo.
[Assane laughs]
That was fun, right?
Are you ready?
Look at this! You recognize him?
- For you.
- Okay, it's nice.
- Take your time. Dig in.
- [Claire] Hmm!
- Marble cake, my favorite.
- We don't have any drinks. Hang on.
- I'll go grab some.
- It's not a big deal.
No, no, I'll be right back.
Hello, sir. Your ticket, please.
Thank you. Hello.
- Hello.
- Your ticket, please. Thank you.
Are we almost there?
- Um… in 20 minutes.
- Thank you.
[inspector] Hello. Your ticket, please.
Thank you.
[suspenseful music playing]
[train horn blares]
[horn blares]
[groaning]
[grunting]
Motherfucker!
[panting]
Where's Papa?
He's back.
I couldn't find any drinks,
but champagne's on me in Étretat.
Okay. Where did you go?
- I got in a fight.
- What?
Yeah, but listen,
I met a guy who said to me
The Mysterious Traveler is
the best story of Arsène Lupin.
- So? It's good.
- [Assane] But it's not the best.
So, I explain to the guy.
And I tell him nicely and politely.
He got worked up
and he took it all wrong. And, well…
Ridiculous.
Yeah, I agree. It's ridiculous.
The guy…
Anyway, it's all over.
It's all done.
We had a scuffle, but nothing serious.
Just some exercise.
It's okay.
I promise.
[Claire] I hate you.
You don't like it?
This place just opened up.
It's the restaurant.
Who cares, Assane? That's not the issue.
I asked you to pick a low-key place,
and this is so fancy.
Well, so what?
[Claire sighs] Well, so what?
Thank you.
I wanted a nice, quiet place to tell you
what I need to tell you tonight.
- But this is quiet.
- [waitress] Wine, madam?
Um, no, thank you.
Sir?
So quiet.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
[soft piano music playing]
I'm sorry.
We can leave.
- Can I get the check, please?
- No, no, no!
- Hmm?
- [Claire sighs]
Well, tell me.
What?
You look stressed.
Tell me what this is about.
I'm pregnant.
What did you say?
[Assane chuckles]
You're having a baby?
- Well, yes!
- You're having my baby?
[Assane laughs]
[Claire chuckles]
I'm going to be a dad?
- Is that what you're telling me?
- Yes.
You know that's a good thing?
- I don't know.
- [Assane] But it is!
You're having doubts?
That's what the look is?
[Assane laughs]
I'm going to be a dad!
- [whispering] Assane!
- [Assane] I'm a dad!
[Assane laughs]
A dad! She'll be
the best mother in the world. Just watch!
- [applause continues]
- [Claire chuckles]
I'm going to be a dad!
You're right.
This place is pretty loud. Let's go.
Okay!
Thank you!
[PA] In a few minutes,
we'll be pulling into Le Havre station.
Connection to Étretat on track four.
Please make sure not to leave
any of your belongings on board the train.
We wish you a pleasant day.
That's funny. What a coincidence!
I see you're also going to Étretat.
- [Raoul] Are you a fan of Lupin?
- A huge fan. And you?
I love it. My dad showed it to me.
[man] Oh…
Your father has great taste.
- Do you know each other?
- No.
A bit.
[Assane sighs]
[whistling sound on cell phone]
You got a text, boss.
Is it my wife?
Uh, no. Unknown number.
What's it say?
Let's see.
"Hello, it's Paul Sernine."
"My train's pulling into Le Havre."
"Let's grab coffee.
I'm in a beige raincoat."
Another nut job who got my number.
"Thank you for the pen at the Louvre."
Get Le Havre on the phone now!
[Assane] You two go ahead, okay?
Okay, Raoul, let's go.
Thank you.
I'll catch up.
I just need five minutes with this guy.
- I'll see you?
- I'll see you.
[train brakes screeching]
You're going to get up,
and we're going to get off quietly,
Assane.
[indistinct station announcement]
Don't try anything stupid.
Do you know The Mysterious Traveler?
[policeman] Sernine, freeze!
Don't move! Put your hands up!
I said hands up!
Hands out. Take your hands out!
Beige raincoat, that's him.
- Now you do.
- [policeman] I said take your hands out!
Get on the ground!
Go on, easy.
There we go.
What's this?
He's got a gun.
What's in your pockets?
What's this?
[seagulls crying]
[Claire]
So, what happens to Lupin in the end?
Nobody knows. He never got caught.
That proves it's fiction. In real life,
Lupin would get caught right away.
Unless he knew when to stop.
Ah!
- [Claire] Oh!
- [Assane] Ah!
- [Claire and Assane laugh]
- All right!
Anywhere else, it'd look ridiculous.
- But here, it's cool.
- Yeah, I agree.
- I'll be back.
- Wait. Where are you going?
- [Raoul] To see the needle rock.
- [Claire] Don't go too far.
[Assane] So, when are you due?
I think around 11th December.
No?
Yeah. Is that a problem?
What?
Well, December 11th!
Claire, December 11th
is Maurice Leblanc's birthday!
Ah!
- Okay, so what are you saying?
- It's a sign!
- Don't say you want to name him Maurice?
- [Assane] Well, why not?
No, not Maurice.
[Assane laughs]
No, not Maurice, but Assane Junior.
- Assane Junior?
- Yeah.
- Are you crazy?
- I know that's a no.
Arsène.
No, not Arsène.
I don't know what his name will be,
but I'll love him.
And I'll protect him any way I can.
So, no more fuck-ups?
[Assane] No more fuck-ups.
I promise.
Got it.
- Raoul.
- Raoul?
- [laughing] Yeah!
- No, not Raoul!
- [Assane] Raoul is good, right?
- [Claire] No! No!
[Claire] Assane,
who was that guy on the train?
What was that about?
Stop.
I knew it was weird.
I'm not an idiot.
Assane!
Answer me!
I'm sorting something out, Claire.
Something important to me. And Raoul too.
It's about my dad.
Who you refused to talk about
for 25 years, who I know nothing about!
- What does that have to do with anything?
- I must finish this, then I can tell you.
Then no more secrets.
I know I've said this so many times.
- So, why should you...
- Yeah.
I know you have no reason to believe me.
- But this time, it's true.
- It's true.
I know. This time, it's true, as usual.
You've told me that a hundred times,
but it's… it's really not enough.
Assane, I need more.
And you have nothing to say.
But that's not what matters
right now, Claire.
What matters is Raoul and you.
Give me a chance.
One more.
Hang on. Where's Raoul?
I don't see him.
Raoul?
[Belkacem] That's not our guy.
He had a stone from the necklace.
Bring him back to Paris and question him.
- Where are you going?
- We're getting Sernine at Le Havre.
You're one step behind.
They let the guy go. It wasn't him.
- But he had the gem.
- And he was armed.
He has a gun license, and an alibi
for the night of the burglary.
So, the stone…
Someone put it in his pocket. That's all.
- Whoa! Wait a minute.
- Wait? Wait for what?
For us to waste two weeks
on more false leads?
The guy was clearly framed.
So, now we figure out who framed him.
Go through the list of train passengers.
Recover the surveillance footage. Okay?
Just do your fucking job.
I can't do everything!
What is this crap?
We can't even question him?
- This is fucking bullshit!
- What do you want me to say?
Get me the list of passengers
on the train.
There could be hundreds.
It'll take forever.
Guédira should be doing this.
Where the fuck is he?
Raoul!
[Claire] Raoul!
[children shouting]
[ringing tone]
[Raoul] Hey, leave a message.
[child screams]
[children shouting]
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Have you seen a 14-year-old boy,
light brown skin, wearing a top hat?
[inaudible]
Light brown skin, with curly hair? No?
[indistinct chatter]
[laughter]
[seagulls crying]
[Raoul groans]
[Claire] Raoul!
[tires screech]
[Guédira] Lupin?