A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
[men shouting in distance]
Noyau!
[door buzzes]
[suspenseful music playing]
[prisoners shouting]
This is your new roommate.
What are you in for?
[ticking]
2 DAYS EARLIER
[Benjamin] No, I wouldn't have called you
if it wasn't important.
That's impossible. Look again.
I spent all night looking at it!
[Benjamin sighs]
The clasp is original.
The setting is original.
No marks on the gemstones.
I guarantee you
this necklace has never been taken apart.
If so, the story about the gems
scattered across the world is bullshit.
And that means
the necklace never left Pellegrini's safe.
- Why would they lie?
- [Assane] I don't know.
And they could have lied about the rest,
including the charges against my father.
For 25 years, I believed my father
was a thief. I grew up with that.
For 25 years, I've been wrong.
Just calm down, Assane.
You have the necklace.
You made it out. Who cares about the rest?
About the truth?
No, I'm not saying that. You never listen.
You told me
after this necklace you'd stop,
that Raoul needed his father.
- Pew! Pew, pew!
- [Benjamin] Think about him.
[Assane] I am.
And he deserves to know
who his grandfather was.
Take out the stones.
- Assane…
- Take them out.
- I know what I'm doing.
- [Benjamin sighs]
What's up?
Hey, big guy.
- You got something?
- Who, me?
- Of course not.
- [Raoul scoffs]
He doesn't trust me!
[chuckles] Well, that's kids, you know.
[distant baby crying]
- [banging on door]
- [man] Police! Open up!
[banging on door]
Inspector Dumont! Open up!
[motorcycle revving]
Gonna make me break down the door?
[distant shout]
Sit down.
How old are you?
Sixteen.
- You live here alone?
- With my mom.
- She's home soon.
- Huh?
Well, then, let's wait for her.
[Dumont sighs]
Go pack your things.
You're going to social services.
You hear me?
Get moving! Grab your stuff!
[distant thunder rumbling]
[suspenseful music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
What's taking you so long?
[distant baby crying]
[siren wailing]
[indistinct voice on radio]
[Assane whimpers]
You have to work
on your escape techniques, boy!
[indistinct chatter]
[door closes]
[Juliette] Hey, Mom.
- Hello.
- [Juliette] Just passing through.
I'm going to the foundation after this.
I heard they found your father's necklace,
but it was a copy.
This must be driving him crazy.
Well, you seem broken up about it.
[Mrs. Pellegrini laughs]
Nobody's worried. The police have a lead.
That's what the papers say, but he owns
most of them, so I have my doubts.
- [cell phone dings]
- Gone, just like 25 years ago. Bad luck.
[Juliette] Hmm. Bad luck, yeah.
The whole thing
really upset him back then.
I'm sure it'll be worse this time.
Anyway, so how are you?
I'm fading away slowly.
In this prison of gold
your father gave me.
Well, he did bring you these orchids, Mom.
At least they aren't chrysanthemums.
[Juliette] Stop it.
He doesn't hate you, Mom.
No, he's afraid.
I know where the bodies are.
Be careful, Juliette.
You adore each other, but as you know,
you're either with him or against him.
[Juliette chuckles softly]
Goodbye, Mom.
Goodbye, Juliette.
[elevator dings]
Goodbye, François.
Mrs. Pellegrini?
Someone left this letter for you.
- Oh, thank you.
- My pleasure.
LUXEMBOURG GARDENS, 14:00
NO POLICE
- Goodbye.
- Bye, madam. Thank you.
Yeah, I want well-done, no onions.
That's all. Thank you.
That's right.
I want well-done, no onions. Thank you.
Bye-bye.
[distant siren wailing]
[children shouting]
Looks like we're both in a hurry.
How much do you want?
It's on the house.
I don't want money.
I want answers.
Oh, Assane…
First I can't see his face.
Now we can't hear anything!
- He's covering the microphone.
- Fix it, goddamn it!
- Okay.
- I wanna hear what they're saying!
Attention all units,
the thief from the Louvre is in the park!
No one intervene until he moves.
Understand?
I said "no police," Juliette.
- You're the one who stole the necklace?
- I'm asking the questions.
Why did you lie to me?
I lied? About what?
The necklace.
It was never taken apart,
so my father never stole it from you.
That's true.
The truth is
that it was never taken apart, yes.
My father and I got this idea
of gemstones scattered across the world
to build up the buzz
before we had the auction.
Daddy bought back the necklace intact
from a jeweler
in South Africa five years ago.
- That doesn't make sense.
- I swear to you.
- Assane, look at me. You know me.
- Stop.
Shit, they know each other.
Look. It's collusion.
I'm sure they know each other.
The Pellegrini woman is playing us!
Belkacem, I wanna hear
what they're saying. Move in closer!
Get between them and the exit.
[Juliette]
If my father finds out, you're a dead man.
Give back the necklace
and I'll tell the cops I don't know you.
Tell me my father was innocent.
I would love to tell you that,
but he was guilty, he signed a confession.
I don't think you know your father.
[ducks quacking]
["Sway" playing]
Okay, he's moving.
Everybody get on it. Bring him in!
[man shouting]
Stop him!
- [Belkacem] Don't let him get away!
- [man] Cut him off! Get him!
Over there! In orange,
on the delivery bike! Fucking get him!
There he is, there he is!
Out of the way!
Okay, cut him off!
- There he is!
- We can't let this motherfucker get away!
- [Belkacem] We're on him.
- We'll bring him in this time!
♪ Like a flower bending in the breeze... ♪
He's heading for the Senate.
Cut him off at the exit!
This can't be happening!
[man] Stop! Stop! Police!
Get off the bike!
♪ Sway with me… ♪
Shit, how did he do it?
You guys, to the Senate!
It's not fucking possible!
He's headed for the observatory.
Exit six, Observatory Street!
Let's go! Everyone go!
[siren wailing]
♪ When we sway, I go weak… ♪
[tires screech]
Get your hands in the air!
Police, police! Don't move!
[delivery man groans]
- [Belkacem] No more running!
- Don't move! Don't move!
It's not him.
One burger, well-done, no onions?
[Belkacem] Stop, don't move!
Everyone get off the bike!
[man] Take the mask off!
Which one is he? Fuck!
- Police! Stop!
- Which one?
- [man] Take the mask off!
- [captain] Lock the park!
No one gets out! Understand?
This is impossible! Where is he?
Fuck!
[sniffs deeply]
FOR ASSANE
[Babakar] "My son, I'm ashamed."
"But I'm guilty of what I'm accused of."
"I wanted to give you a better life."
"I failed."
"So, I hope you will forgive me."
"And remember,
the truth can always be found
in libraryes."
"And don't comit the same mistakes I did."
"I love you."
"Papa."
De Gaulle with only one L?
Be careful, Assane. Spelling is essential.
[chuckles] What would your mom think?
[suspenseful music playing]
INTERIEUR.GOUV.FR
HOMELAND SECURITY
KILLED HIMSELF IN HIS CELL
- I make spelling mistakes all the time.
- Hey, we all do it.
But my father never did,
let alone twice in a row.
- Yeah? And?
- Look at this.
- "Comit" and "libraryes."
- [Benjamin] Sure.
- And?
- I checked it out.
[Benjamin] Hmm.
[Assane] There was a guy in prison
with my father named Étienne Comit.
C-O-M-I-T.
Guess where he worked?
- At the library?
- Exactly.
[Benjamin whistles]
Wait a second, Assane.
That's called a, um… coincidence.
Are you serious?
Two spelling mistakes and there's
a hidden message? You're reaching.
You don't understand.
It's all been right here.
I could have proven his innocence
25 years ago, thanks to Comit.
But I did nothing.
You know what? You're right.
You have doubts, you need answers.
See this to the end. Go see Comit.
- Where is he now?
- Still in prison.
- Perfect. Go visit him.
- He's sick and doesn't leave his cell.
- Well, okay…
- I got another way in.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, yes.
- No, no, no.
- You said, "See this to the end."
I gotta meet with Comit.
Oh, fuck. Shit!
Assane!
Wait!
[gate buzzes]
[guard] Visitor. Djibril Traoré.
Hey, cousin. What's up?
Have a seat.
What makes you think
you and I are cousins?
I don't have cousins.
Well, you have one now.
And your cousin has a present for you.
You… get out.
And I stay in your place.
[Djibril laughs loudly]
Hang on. Are you… totally stupid or what?
Oh, I know!
So, uh, the guards won't notice
anything is going on
because you and me look so similar,
we're practically twins.
[Assane chuckles]
[watch beeps]
[prison alarm rings]
- [watch beeps]
- There.
The guards just changed shifts.
And the other inmates?
You've been here with the new arrivals
for about a week now.
And tonight, you'll get your transfer.
And nobody knows you
in the prison you're headed to.
Sure,
but you're forgetting something, right?
Oh, shit, the handcuffs.
"Oh, shit, the handcuffs."
I'm so stupid.
How did I not think of that?
- You know the handcuff trick?
- The handcuff what?
Well, now you do.
Hey, guard! We're finished.
Hey! I know why you're here.
If you deal so much as a joint,
I'll find you.
I got you out of here.
I can get you back in.
- See you, cousin.
- Go ahead.
Noyau!
[gate buzzes]
[distant voice on PA]
Give Auntie a kiss for me!
- Noyau!
- [gate buzzes]
[door buzzes]
[prisoners shouting]
[man]
I realize it's difficult here at first.
But I know you'll get used to it.
We respect all individual faiths here.
But on a personal level,
there was one book
that brought me some answers
and some comfort.
Welcome, my boy.
THE HOLY BIBLE
[Laugier] Madame Pellegrini, one thing
still bothers me about this situation.
We had no audio, but based on the video,
we got the impression
you two might have, um…
well, that you knew each other.
[Juliette chuckles]
And I, Captain, have the impression
that you're treating me like a suspect.
- Am I being accused of something here?
- No, of course not.
If that's the case, there's no problem.
You can detain me. I'll call my lawyers
and you'd be fired within the hour.
Shall we do that?
- No, hang on...
- I suggest you change your tone.
And focus on your investigation.
I'm just asking what you said
to each other. That seems reasonable.
Absolutely.
I told him that, um…
I told him the officer
working in this case was a total moron
who brought me a necklace made of plastic.
Aren't you taking notes?
Find our necklace, Captain.
You wouldn't want
to disappoint your superiors, right?
- No, madam.
- [Juliette] Well, that's great.
Thank you.
[sighs]
[indistinct PA announcement]
I made coffee if you want some.
Thanks a lot.
[prisoners shouting]
[shouting gets louder]
[applause]
[inaudible conversation]
Hello.
Do you know a guy named Comit?
Étienne Comit.
- What do you want with Étienne?
- Nothing. We have a mutual friend.
And who is your friend?
I'm quitting.
Bad for my health.
Interested?
Cell 241.
[prisoners shouting]
Look into him. I wanna know everything.
[phone ringing]
[Guédira] Tell us about the guy.
[Vincent] His name was Luis Perenna.
I'd never seen him before.
- 241, Comit, Leroy.
- [prisoner] Yeah.
[guard] Yeah, open it. I'm coming.
- Where's Comit?
- Infirmary.
When's he back?
The way he looks,
I don't think he's coming back.
Thanks so much.
[door slams]
[Assane groans]
Okay, who are you?
- Tell me.
- Djibril. Djibril Traoré.
Huh! Djibril was getting me
1,000 euros of dope.
- You're gonna get it to me in three days.
- Three days?
Is that too much time, Djibril? Huh?
- It's fine.
- Oh, it's fine.
- Three days is fine.
- [door buzzes]
[guard] What's going on here?
What?
[prisoner whistling "Alouette"]
[knock at door]
- Just got here. Already something wrong.
- Fine, Marc. I can handle it.
Take a seat.
Okay, what's wrong with you?
It started in my stomach.
Hasn't gone away.
Mm-hm.
I thought I might be pregnant.
- Hmm.
- I don't think it's that.
Probably not. Unlikely even.
And I figured a…
a night in the infirmary,
for observation, may be good.
[inhales deeply]
Well, listen… I know it's hard at first.
But a big boy like you,
he'll get used to it. Yeah?
My night in the infirmary?
You'll have to try harder.
- Okay.
- [Guédira] Got a minute?
- I'm meeting the boss.
Please, come here.
I've found something incredible.
Look.
Paul Sernine.
Luis Perenna.
- What are you doing?
- [Guédira] Don't you see it?
Anagrams for Arsène Lupin.
- And?
- [Guédira] And it adds up.
Must be a connection
between the thief and Arsène Lupin.
We should follow this lead.
Should I go tell Laugier?
Yeah, sure. Great idea.
Especially if you wanna look stupid.
Laugier's in a great mood.
Seriously, Youssef, what is this?
What's next? D'Artagnan and The Three
Little Pigs? Go do some real work.
[Laugier] We had this guy
and now he's gone. We need to do better.
This guy puts on a delivery costume,
and we're dead!
It's a disaster!
This guy is screwing with us!
We're nowhere! We're lost!
This investigation is bullshit!
[prisoners shouting]
- Quick question.
- What do you want?
- How am I supposed to get you the dope?
- What the fuck are you doin'?
I'm just curious.
Are you stupid? He swallowed it,
then pulled it out of his ass.
Ah! There you go.
That is exactly
where you can put your money.
He has a death wish.
[Assane groans]
[prisoners shouting]
[nurse] There you go.
I suppose you did this to yourself?
Yeah, a stupid accident.
I was shaving… and I slipped.
Oh.
[nurse sighs]
Well, I'm gonna keep you overnight.
Well, all right.
But you're gonna have to make
some friends. It's useful here.
Hmm?
[Assane] Good night.
[sighs]
[whispering] Étienne?
Étienne?
- Étienne?
- [breathing deeply]
My name is Assane Diop.
My father was Babakar Diop.
You were in prison together.
[door opens]
[inaudible conversation]
Étienne?
[weak voice] Babakar?
Yeah. You remember?
Yeah, maybe, yeah.
- Isn't he the one who stole a necklace?
- Yes…
Well, no.
That's why I'm here.
He was wrongfully accused.
I don't know your father.
No.
- That's impossible.
- Yes.
What do you mean?
He was alone in his cell.
Under surveillance.
I only saw him once because…
I brought him a book
when I worked in the library.
But that's all.
No. There has to be something else.
- Huh?
- [breathing weakly]
Please, try to think.
Étienne…
[inaudible conversation]
When he returned the book, he told me…
Yeah?
He said that if someone came
on his behalf someday,
he wanted me to give it to him.
He said that all the answers were inside.
And you still have the book?
Maybe I do.
Look through my things.
[Assane groans]
[church bell ringing]
You don't wanna play?
This came this morning. From your father.
The guards found it
when they cleaned his cell.
Are you familiar with the Andrésy school?
It's one of the best private schools
in France.
Apparently, someone wants you
to attend it next year.
A generous donor has already paid.
Assane,
you'll get a great education there.
You can become something.
You have to take this chance.
Nothing's set in stone.
I'm glad you like it, by the way.
[melancholic music playing]
[Babakar] "My son, I'm ashamed."
"But I'm guilty of what I'm accused of."
"I wanted to give you a better life."
"I failed."
- 241!
- [prisoner] Yeah?
Shit, clean sheets. Better than the Ritz!
- Where are Étienne's things?
- Second shelf.
[indistinct chatter]
- Right.
- Good luck.
[prisoner] Anksi?
THE EXPLOITS OF ARSÈNE LUPIN
[Claire] How was science class?
- Raoul, I'm speaking to you, sweetie.
- Hmm?
- [Claire] Did your science test go well?
- Mm-hm.
- That the book you got from Papa?
- [Raoul] Mm-hm.
- [Claire] Wow, he scribbled on every page.
- Hmm.
You prefer reading to video games?
What do you know!
[suspenseful music playing]
"Am…"
"Innocent…"
TRAP
[distant clank]
"Am innocent,
trapped by Anne
Pellegrini."
[groans loudly]
Bogdan hopes you enjoy your meal.
He'll tuck you in tonight.
[prisoner shouting]
What the hell is this?
Lock him up. Everyone back in their cells!
[Juliette] This is gonna sound
like a weird question, but I, um...
I need to know
if…
Well…
Was it really Babakar
who stole the necklace 25 years ago?
What?
The foundation is in trouble
because a necklace worth millions
was stolen
and you're pissing me off with something
that happened God knows when?
Of course he stole that necklace!
[Hubert sighs]
Forgive me.
I'm sorry, darling.
No. I'm sorry.
[Hubert] I spend my days
being attacked by almost everyone.
And when it comes from you…
it hurts so much more.
You're with me.
Hmm?
You're with me?
Yes, yes.
[prisoner shouting]
Look who it is.
Come on. Let's do this.
[prisoners shouting]
Here!
[Assane groans]
Tonight.
This is ridiculous.
Are you in love with me?
[Assane chuckles]
How is he?
Can I have a minute?
Thank you.
How's it goin', buddy?
I think she likes you.
Did you find the book?
Mm-hm.
Great.
Can I ask you something?
Anything you want.
I don't care how you do it,
but make my wife smile.
I won't be able to anymore.
Promise.
Okay.
Thanks for the book.
I have what I need.
Now I can clear my father's name.
Lovely to meet you.
You need to hang on, Djibril.
Thank you.
Good night.
[prisoner whistling "Alouette"]
ARSÈNE LUPIN IS IN PRISON
[Claire] Raoul.
Let's turn off the light
and put down the book.
Come on.
Good night.
[gate buzzes]
All right. Done.
Hey, if you find a clue in Harry Potter,
call us, okay?
[police officers laugh]
- See you tomorrow.
- Give me a lift, Christian?
- Yeah, my pleasure.
- Cool.
See you tomorrow, Youssef.
[distant siren wailing]
[sighs]
DECEASED
[ominous music playing]
No!
Help him! Somebody help!
- [alarm blaring]
- [prisoners shouting]
All good? It's done?
Is there a problem?
No, actually,
it was too easy.
The bastard wasn't in his cell.
I don't know how he did it.
But I found him
across the hallway in the showers.
He hanged himself.
[beeping]
[siren wailing]
[Raoul] "Of all the arts,
illusion is probably the most subtle."
"It always requires a minimum of finesse."
"And usually, a good dose of courage."
[slow, rhythmic heartbeat]
[Assane] "And finally,
no matter what tactics are used,
and by all means necessary,
it's the outcome that matters."
[siren wails]
[siren stops]
- There's no need to wake half of Paris.
- Yeah.
[Raoul] "And, obviously,
the thrill of having fooled the world."
THE ESCAPE OF ARSÈNE LUPIN
[gasping]
[indistinct chatter]
Hello, sir.
[Assane] Oh!
[Assane chuckles]
[maid chuckles] Pardon me.
[Assane] Excuse me.
[lock beeps]
Assane.
Assane!
25 years ago, you framed my father.
I know you did.
What did you do to him?
Assane…
I made him sign a confession.
- But you know that I'm innocent!
- That isn't the issue.
- Of course it is!
- Babakar, trust me.
It's better to be guilty and free
than innocent in prison.
Just sign it. Think of your son.
For Assane.
[Anne] His confession was supposed
to guarantee him a reduced sentence.
I was told the judge would be receptive
to your family's situation.
An immigrant from Senegal
raising his son alone in France.
But the judge was strict.
Your father couldn't accept it
and he hanged himself.
The confession
that should have saved him was his doom.
[sighs] I was naive.
There were agreements made.
Agreements are only good for people
like you. Never for people like my father.
After your father's death,
I helped you, Assane. I helped you.
I did it from a distance.
From a distance, but I helped you.
It was you?
The generous donor?
[Anne] I felt responsible
for the situation you were in.
I wanted to earn your forgiveness
and your father's.
- I did it for your father.
- For my father?
You accuse him, you drive him to suicide
to ease your conscience?
I didn't accuse him of anything!
A police officer swore to me
that he would help him!
- That's the whole story.
- Which officer?
[Anne] He lied to me!
[Assane] Which officer?
- No, that was such a long time ago...
- No!
Tell me now!
What's his name?
- [Anne] Dumont. His name was Dumont.
- Open.
[Anne] Inspector Dumont.
Dumont knew my father trusted you
and he used that against him, huh?
Why would he do that?
I don't know.
It's been years and I don't know.
[inhales deeply]
Assane,
I swear to you.
[indistinct chatter]
- Look at this. Where are you going?
- I think he's lost.
[chuckles] See his costume?
Kind of looks real. Where'd you get it?
[boy] I didn't know
they let janitors through here.
Let's be polite.
It's not how we treat new students.
Don't make me tell the director.
Excuse them. Born with silver spoons
in their mouths and shit for brains!
Benjamin Ferel.
- Assane Diop.
- Nice to meet you, Assane.
[footsteps on stairs]
[Benjamin sighs]
[chuckles softly]
- [purring]
- [indistinct voices on TV]
[door closes]
[Étienne] Can I ask you something?
I don't care how you do it,
but make my wife smile.
[wind whistling]
LIEUTENANT GABRIEL DUMONT
PARIS REGIONAL POLICE