Subtitles by explosiveskull
Good boy.
Aw.
Watch it. Watch it.
Frank, no.
Told you not to do that.
- Spare any change?
- Whoa! Uh, s-sorry, man.
Uh, I don't have any money.
I just...
Yeah, right.
Whoa. Sorry, bro.
Watch it, man.
Hey, stop global warming?
So sorry. No speak English.
- Okay.
- So sorry.
Excuse me.
Would you like to sign this
to stop global warming?
Shut up!
♪ I'm having bad dreams
♪ I lie awake...
Oh, you're taking forever!
She's back?
- Out.
- I'm not sleeping in my car again.
- It smells like Hot Pockets and feet.
- Get out.
I just want clean underwear.
It's my room, too.
Oh, my God. Answer me, Ryan.
Oh, my God.
Answer me, Ryan.
What?
Ryan, dude, oh, my God.
Get over here right now, man.
This is crazy.
Oh, my God.
You're not gonna believe this.
Fool, I understood
two percent of that.
Dude, just come now!
Where?
- Dude! Dude.
- What?
- You need to get in here right now.
- Huh?
- This better be good, man.
- It is.
Come on, come on.
- Whoa.
- Right?
.7 millinewtons of energy.
God, that's...
that's, like, huge.
- When?
- Uh, yesterday. 12:01 a.m.
Damn, this is crazy, man.
Yeah, but, Ryan, we have no
idea what set the device off.
Like, lab was locked.
It's almost like it decided
to fire on its own.
That's it! I've had it!
Oh, shit.
Hey.
Wh-Where you guys going?
- It's churro day at the cafeteria.
- Nom, nom.
Dean Bronson, hi.
Love the tie.
Uh, are those cats?
Turkish angora.
Uh, d-don't change the subject.
- What subject?
- That.
We've had four
rolling blackouts,
fried electrical circuits,
broken bulbs all over campus.
And it's all because of
your little science project.
- It's my thesis project.
- It's an abject failure.
This university's
science department
prides itself on pioneering
forward-thinking ideas
that yield results.
Results that lead to patents.
Do you see how it works?
So, it's just about money?
Yes, Mr. Phan.
I hate to shatter
your illusions,
but somebody has to keep
the lights on around here,
something you seem
hell-bent on stopping!
Literally! Consider this joke
of a project suspended,
effective immediately.
- What?
- That's right.
I've already called
Professor Boner.
It's pronounced "Bonner."
And he's in total agreement
with my request.
I'm sending security
to come and collect
this energy-sucking doohickey
by 6:00 today.
You can't just take her.
Watch me.
I suggest you wrap up
whatever business
you have left here, capisce?
Hello?
What the hell?
Hey, shit bags.
While you were off
playing games,
our project got shut down.
I hope you're happy.
What is wrong with you?
- Why are you sneaking up on me?
- I was bringing you a...
Well, now it's covered
in bacteria,
so that's two dollars wasted.
So ungrateful.
Good boy.
Frank, no.
Told you not to do that.
Ouch!
Dude, what's your problem?
I'm so sorry, man. I...
So sorry.
Dick.
Sorry, bro.
Shut up!
♪ I'm having bad dreams
♪ I lie awake...
Oh, you're taking forever!
Out.
Ryan.
Dude, I am tripping right now.
Yeah, no shit.
No. No, no, seriously.
I'm having that thing.
You know?
What's it called? When you feel
like you've already
lived through something before.
- Déjà vu?
- Yes, that.
I feel like I've totally lived
through this day already.
Oh, my God. Answer me, Ryan.
Ryan, dude, oh, my God.
Get over here right now, man.
This is crazy. Oh, my God.
I-I got to call you back.
Okay. Just breathe.
Just breathe.
Listen to me.
The day reset
when you died, right?
Yeah. Some psycho dude
in a baby mask attacked me.
But it was just a dream, right?
- Tombs is dead.
- So is Lori.
Then who's the killer
this time?
Uh, hello.
Will someone please explain
what the hell is going on?
Okay. Recap.
So, I was stuck
reliving the same day,
Monday the 18th,
over and over and over again
until someone wearing
a Bayfield Baby mask
murdered me on the night
of my birthday.
I had no idea who it was
because I was
such a crazy bitch
and so many people
hated my guts.
So, at Carter's suggestion,
I made a list of suspects.
Turns out it was
my roommate, Lori,
who kept on helping
a serial killer escape
from the hospital,
hoping it would look like
he murdered me when, in fact,
it was her all along,
and all because she was jealous
of an affair I was having
with my college professor,
Gregory, who was married.
Yeah, I know. Pretty shitty.
But, anyways,
I finally kicked Lori's
crazy ass out a window
and killed her, which broke
the loop, or so I thought.
But now it only looks like
it passed the loop on to you
and you're gonna be stuck
reliving this day
until we figure out
how to stop it.
Of course.
I'm still dreaming.
Wait. What?
It's like Inception.
It's a dream within a dream.
Bro, you're not dreaming.
- Ryan, we...
- Shh.
I'm trying to wake myself up.
There. See? You're not dreaming.
Why'd you hit my penis?
Why are you acting like this?
You smacked my dick.
That's rude.
- I barely touched you.
- Okay.
Show me where you died.
Back there. Storage closet.
Hey. Give me that.
I can handle myself.
You've died enough,
haven't you?
Mm.
- Bash his head in.
- Shh! - Shh!
- Samar, you asshole!
- Why'd you hit me?
Why do you keep
sneaking up on me?
Ah, I think
my cheekbone's broken.
What is happening in here?
Ryan broke my cheekbone.
- Was it him?
- No.
He was here when I died before.
What?
Where'd you get that mask?
It was just laying
in the hallway.
Somebody must have dropped it.
That's it. I've had it.
Wait, wait.
Where you going?
- Uh, churro day at the cafeteria.
- Nom, nom.
We've had four
rolling blackouts,
fried electrical circuits,
broken bulbs all over campus.
And it's all because of
your little science project.
Wait.
What science project?
The Sisyphus Quantum
Cooling Reactor.
We call it Sissy for short.
You see all these?
They're proton lasers.
And when they fire, they cool
the centrifuge right here
to almost below one nanokelvin.
So, basically, we're trying
to prove that time
can be slowed down
on a molecular level.
It hasn't worked yet, but we
did find some promising data
after the device fired
the other night.
When?
12:01 a.m. yesterday.
Monday the 18th.
Mm-hmm.
What?
You created the time loop,
dummy.
That's impossible.
That's not what Sissy
was designed to do.
I don't know what to tell you.
Well, maybe we're just
discovering
what it actually does.
An unintended reaction.
Maybe we thought
we were slowing time,
but what if we looped it
instead?
Now you're stuck in this day.
Congrats.
Oh, and by the way,
you're gonna die
again and again and again.
Carter, tell your girlfriend
to stop trying to scare me.
Oh, she's not my girlfriend.
- Well, wait, are you my girlfriend?
- Kinda.
Hey, guys, are you done talking
about your relationship status?
Because she just said
I'm gonna die.
And you need to figure out
how to close the loop
before the killer
finds you again.
But I don't know
how it happened.
It just fired on its own.
Oh, God.
Danielle, hi.
- Where were you?
- What do you mean?
You ditched our house meeting.
- It was canceled.
- When?
Um, after I kicked my murdering
roommate out of a window.
Exactly.
Who's gonna pledge Kappa
now that we have a death curse?
We're in crisis mode, Tree.
Ew. Who are these people?
Hi.
Uh, I'm-I'm-I'm Samar.
Hey, samosa,
my head's the middle one.
Anyhoo, call me
as soon as you're done
with your creepy little
Comic-Con meeting. Ugh.
Did she just call me "samosa"?
Yep.
- You think she likes samosas?
- Nope.
Guys, focus.
I don't want to die.
On the bright side,
you'll come back.
I died 11 times.
11? Hell no.
- That shit hurts.
- Wait a minute.
Guys, I have an idea.
We just need to find
the safest possible place
and wait it out there.
Where?
What?
There's... safety in numbers.
More like hiding
in plain sight.
Who picks a creepy baby
for a mascot anyway?
I knew I should have
gone to M.I.T.
He traveled!
Airball!
Is that you and your mom?
That's cute.
I was thinking.
It's ironic.
Here I thought I was stuck
in the same day
for some big cosmic reason.
You know,
facing my mom's death.
It had nothing to do with her.
Turns out it was just
some big scientific fluke.
That doesn't make it mean
any less, does it?
I guess not.
Oh, you got a little something
right here.
Yep, uh, uh.
Yeah.
Sorry. It's...
You're such a grandpa.
Yeah, well,
you fell for it, so...
Please make your way
to the nearest exit
in an orderly fashion.
This is not a drill.
Please make your way
to the nearest exit
in an orderly fashion.
Again, this is not a drill.
Hey, watch it!
Guys! Wait up!
Don't push me.
Hey, I can't find my phone.
Help! Help! Please!
Help!
- What was that?
- Down here!
Holy shit.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Well, damn. Good job.
- I have a little practice.
- What the hell?
I thought you were the killer.
You should have said something.
I was looking for you.
Well, who is it?
Only one way to find out.
What the fu...?
You sure you...
you don't have a twin brother?
Maybe you were separated
at birth.
Of course I'm sure.
- Oh, shit.
- "Oh, shit" is right.
Who are you?
Who you think I am, dummy?
It's you.
- Duh.
What the hell is going on here?
Look, I was trying
to close the loop,
but somehow I got knocked
into a parallel time loop.
We're all in serious danger.
The longer we exist
in the same dimension,
the worse things will get.
It's a butterfly effect.
You have to kill him.
- Me?
- He's going to create bigger problems
if you do not stop him.
Kill him now!
No, screw that. Kill him.
You're wasting your time.
Do it.
Dude, I'm your friend, not him.
Uh... you know what?
Screw this.
I'll just take care of it myself.
- Stop him.
- Wait. Ryan, maybe you should stop.
Look at him. He's crazy.
I'm the one who designed this.
I know what I'm doing.
You don't understand
what you're doing!
Shut up, fake Ryan!
Ryan, this doesn't feel right.
Ryan, stop.
But a parsec is a measure
of distance, not time.
Okay, so now you're gonna call
Han Solo a liar?
No, I'm saying
if a normal Kessel Run is...
Dre, help me.
Come on!
Whoa.
Dude, did you dose my Yoo-hoo again?
What did I tell you about
turning that thing on?
Turn it off now.
Turn it off now!
Just get him. Get him.
Get the man.
Get him, get him, get him!
- Back off! Back...
- Whoa!
- Ryan, just turn it off, man.
- Ryan, what are you doing?
Guys, take the wrench from him.
He's a college student.
It's just a wrench.
Don't be scared of him.
Okay, all right,
just unplug it.
Unplug the machine.
Unplug it!
Whoa.
No!
Shut up!
Oh, hey. You're up.
Yeah, I wasn't sure if you
wanted to sleep in or not,
- so I...
- ♪ Yeah, it's my birthday
- ♪ And I ain't gotta pick up the pho... ♪
- Tree?
No fucking way.
Hey, I-I folded
your clothes for you.
Ryan! Get in here right now!
Wait a minute,
you two know each other?
- Yes.
- No.
Ryan, you dumbass!
You sent me back.
- What?
- It's Monday the 18th.
I don't believe this.
I just got out.
How could you do this to me?
Uh... who's this
crazy white girl?
Maybe it was
a-a bad dream or something.
You're right.
It is a bad dream.
It's a nightmare!
This sucks!
It sucks the biggest mega balls
in the history
of shitty ball-suckery!
It...
I'm okay.
You sure?
Yes.
He just needs to fix this.
Now.
This is a joke, right?
I wish.
Look.
Ryan, we need to go
to your lab, turn on Sissy,
and figure out
how to send me back.
Uh, how do you know
about Sissy?
Oh, my God. Just...
Let's go.
Ándale, people!
Hey. Stop global warming?
A simple "no, thanks" would do!
Sorry!
This is the same day, same day,
same day, same day, same day!
♪ 62 bottles of beer on the wall ♪
I can't hear you!
♪ 62 bottles of beer
♪ You take one down,
pass it around ♪
- Keep going!
- ♪ 61 bottles of beer on the wall... ♪
Hey, you haven't returned
any of...
You are gay.
Wait, where are you going?
The lab's back that way.
I have some business
to take care of first.
You sneaky little beyatch.
That's weird.
What?
She was supposed to be here.
Who?
Uh, never mind.
She finally rolls in.
Where is it?
Where's what?
- Oh, hey, Carter.
- Hey.
Where's the cupcake?
What cupcake?
The one you made
for my birthday.
The one you poisoned.
Oh, that cupcake.
I'm serious.
Look, I don't know
what stupid joke
Danielle put you up to,
but there's no cupcake.
Sorry.
All right, I got to go.
I'm pulling a double for Jen.
She's got the flu.
Happy birthday, though.
Toodles.
Something's wrong.
What?
I don't know.
It's different.
- There were two of me?
- Yes.
That is how
this whole thing happened.
You know, this kind of reminds
me of Back to the Future II.
- Totally. Mm-hmm.
- Right?
- You know, with Marty McFly?
- Doc?
- The DeLorean?
- Sorry.
Are you serious? You've never
seen Back to the Future?
No, I...
- How do you...
- Wait.
Oh, my God.
Does this mean that...
Does this mean
that there are two of me?
I highly doubt it.
It's almost impossible to
create a holographic universe.
You're probably stuck
in a quantum cyclic dimension.
There's only one of you here,
because the other you
got knocked into
a parallel dimension
somewhere in the multiverse.
Okay, Ryan.
Thanks for clearing that up.
That was super helpful.
You never heard
the multiverse theory?
Do I look like someone
who knows what a multiverse is?
Okay, look.
This is our universe.
Okay? Now, look.
In theory, the universe
has six dimensions.
Now, if what you're saying
is true,
then maybe you woke up
on the same day...
but not in the same dimension.
That would explain
the anomalies.
So, how different
are we talking here?
Well, it depends.
Oh, shit.
I forgot our house meeting.
Danielle, I'm sorry. I just...
Hey, babe.
You doing all right?
Hi, Ry.
Hey, Danielle.
Did that look real?
I'm auditioning
for this year's production
of The Miracle Worker.
Did you know Anne Frank
was blind and deaf?
Uh... Helen Keller.
Excuse me?
Anne Frank was in the attic.
Oh.
Whatever.
All I know is acting blind
is probably harder
than actually being blind.
I mean, the skill set it takes.
Meryl Streep
taped her eyelids shut
just to prepare for a role.
Uh-huh.
Well. Somebody missed
our house meeting today.
Oh, um...
I'm sorry. I...
Totes kidding.
Birthday girls get a free pass.
Anyhoo, we picked
this year's charity.
Are you ready for it?
We're doing the
special needs art fair again.
Oh. Nice.
You do so much good, Danielle.
I-I really admire that.
Oh, please.
It just warms my heart
seeing all those little faces.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
Sometimes they try
to hug you too long,
and it gets
a little uncomfortable,
but you just get used to it.
And at the end of the day,
there is no greater gift
in life
than the love of a child.
Thank you.
Tree?
You okay?
Uh... yeah, I...
♪ Yeah, it's my birthday
- ♪ And I ain't gotta pick up the phone. ♪
- Sorry.
Hey, Dad. Um...
Uh... Yeah, yeah.
Sorry. I'm on my way.
I'll be there in a little bit.
I have to go. Um...
Wait, what?
You're leaving?
Uh, yeah. I have to meet up
with my dad for lunch.
It's a birthday thing.
Meet me in the lab at 3:00.
We are figuring this out
before it gets any worse!
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey.
- Sorry I'm late.
- It's okay, sweetie.
It's just been a weird day.
- Everything okay?
- Uh, yeah.
It's just... stuff, you know.
How's school?
Um, it's fine, Dad.
- Are you ready to order?
- Not yet.
We're still waiting
on one more.
One more? I...
Okay. I'll be right back.
Mom.
Mom!
Whoa!
Hi.
You're here.
Oh, you're really here.
Well, of course I'm here.
It's our day.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, God, I'm fine. I'm just...
It's good to see you.
Okay.
Try it now.
20 seconds.
Yo, is this normal?
Don't worry,
it's not gonna blow up again.
- Again?
- Ten. Nine.
Eight. Seven.
Six. Five.
Four. Three.
Two.
Stop!
Leave it.
- You told me to...
- No, I-I know.
I changed my mind.
This must be
the crazy white girl.
Hey, Tree. Wait up.
Hey. Hey.
Why the change of heart?
- Everything's different.
- Different how?
Wait, when were you
gonna tell me?
Tell you what?
About Danielle.
Yeah, what about Danielle?
Apparently you guys are dating.
Wait, I thought...
I thought you knew that.
I mean, you guys live
in the same house.
Uh, no,
I definitely didn't know.
But the bigger question is:
does she know?
Does she know what?
One of her closest friends woke
up in your bed this morning.
You don't think
that that's newsworthy?
Nothing happened.
I slept in Ryan's bed
last night.
So, why take me home?
Because you were...
you were wasted.
I was afraid
you were gonna fall
or choke on your own vomit
like Janis Joplin.
Okay.
It's fine. It's fine.
It's fine.
It's fine. This is how
it's supposed to be.
My mom's okay.
Lori isn't trying to kill me.
I mean, this is, like,
the better version
- of my life, right?
- What are you...?
She's in a sorority, Gregory.
She's...
Wait a minute. In this...
in this other dimension,
were we...?
I... I can't do this right now.
No, Tr... Tree!
Are you ready for this?
- I... No. Okay.
- Hold this.
And...
Oh, my God!
It's so weird.
Oh, my... this is amazing.
But I don't think you have
to get another one.
This is, like, the best...
None of these memories
are mine.
I know. I'm just borrowing it
for tonight.
What time you going
to the party?
Um... I, uh... I can't make it.
- Something came up.
- What?
I mean,
we've been planning this
for weeks, Tree.
No, I know. And I know
it's a surprise party.
I'm sorry. It's just...
You know, my parents
are in town, and I need to...
Ugh.
Our tuition dollars at work.
Anyhoo, who told you
about the surprise?
Was it Lori?
I swear, that girl really needs
to learn how to keep a secret.
I don't know
what's going on with you...
You know what, Tree, I'm just
gonna come out and say it.
I have been feeling
so extremely
- unappreciated by you...
- ...following a deadly shootout
- this morning that left one officer dead.
- Hello?
- I'm still talking to you.
- Tombs was the subject
of a nationwide manhunt
that ended after
a five-month pursuit
across four state lines
that left six female victims.
Oh, my God.
He's still here.
He's going to escape!
Call the police!
- Who?
- John Tombs. Just call the police.
- What?
- Wait! Don't go in there!
Shit.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Whoa. Drop the ax.
- Wait. I can expl...
- Drop it now.
He's escaped.
He's gonna kill someone.
- Face up against the wall.
- No, you don't understand. Lori...
I'm not asking again.
Please listen to me.
My roommate works here.
She set Tombs free because
she's trying to blame him,
but she's gonna kill me.
I don't know what kind
of shit you're on, lady,
but Tombs is down
in the O.R. right now.
Nurse just took him.
Was she tall,
dark hair and a ponytail?
- Ow!
- Let's go.
I know you think I'm crazy,
but you got to believe me.
Dispatch,
this is Officer Conrow.
Have an 11-55
at the hospital.
Need immediate assistance.
Come on.
I know it's you, Lori!
What? Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
I thought you were the...
Are you okay?
What the hell is going on?
- Who was that?
- Tombs escaped. He's trying to kill me.
No, Tree, that's not possible.
I just took him down
to the O.R.
What's happening?
I-I don't know.
Oh, my God, he cut the power.
Just stay calm.
Just stay calm. Shit!
Okay. Come on.
Come on.
Where the hell are we?
This must be one of the floors
under construction.
Come on. There's an emergency
exit on the other end.
Wait.
Grab that.
Okay.
Come on.
What?
Did you hear something?
All right, asshole,
let's see what you got.
Ha!
Shit!
Shut up!
Rookie move, Tree.
Oh, hey. You're up.
- What dimension am I in?
- Huh?
Danielle.
Uh, my girlfriend?
Same one.
- ♪ Yeah, it's my birthday
- Okay.
♪ And I ain't gotta
pick up the pho... ♪
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Never better.
Hey, I folded your clothes
for you, so...
Look, no offense, but how could
you possibly end up with her?
With who?
Danielle.
Uh, uh, she's nice.
Oh, "nice."
Wait a minute.
Isn't she, like,
your best friend?
Dude, did you hit
that fine vagine or wha...?
- Huh. Interesting.
- No, I wasn't trying to do any...
- Not as innocent as you look.
- But...
- What? No, I-I...
- You.
Meet me in your lab in an hour.
Huh?
I've got to get out
of these disgusting clothes.
Listen to me carefully.
I need to stay here
in this dimension.
Okay? So just close the loop.
Look, we have no idea
how this even happened
in the first place.
Well, you're all brainy
science people, right?
So you'll figure it out.
You realize we're messing
with things we have
no business touching, right?
Well, maybe you should have
thought of that
before you built
the big dumb thing.
Just...
just please do me a favor
and try to figure this out,
okay?
Please.
Look, this is gonna be
a trial-and-error situation.
We have to rule out
every variable
in order to narrow down
the correct algorithm
that will close the loop.
- Okay.
- Uh, it's days,
maybe weeks of work.
And if what you're saying
is true,
there's no way to keep
a record of our progress.
I'm not following.
Okay. Um...
Say we test, like,
dozens of variables.
By the end of the day,
the loop will reset, right?
So everything we learned
gets...
...erased.
There's no way for us
to track our progress
simply because we just don't
remember anything we learned.
And we'll be back
to square one.
Great.
I'm screwed.
Wait, no, I got it.
Okay, you said everything
resets but your memory, right?
- Yeah.
- All right, well, then...
you're just gonna have
to be a living record.
Wait, you mean memorize
everything?
- Yeah.
- That's genius.
- No. No, no, no, no.
That's not genius.
I'm not a scientist.
And hello.
I mean, you do realize
there's a killer after me,
right?
That means I'm gonna have
to die over and over again
until you guys figure out
how to close the loop.
I mean, I guess you could just
kill yourself
before they find you.
Wow. Another genius idea.
Um, better than being chased by
some crazy guy in a baby mask.
I mean, do you have
a better idea?
I knew you were gonna say that.
♪ All that I want
is to wake up fine ♪
♪ Tell me that I'm all right,
that I ain't gonna die ♪
♪ All that I want
is a hole in the ground ♪
♪ You can tell me when it's all right ♪
♪ For me to come out
- ♪ Hard times ♪
- ♪ Gonna make you wonder
♪ Why you even try
- ♪ Hard times ♪
- ♪ Gonna take you down
♪ And laugh when you cry
♪ These lives ♪
♪ And I still don't know
how I even survive ♪
♪ Hard times, hard times ♪
♪ And I gotta get
to rock bottom ♪
♪ Walking around
♪ My little rain cloud
♪ Hanging over my head
♪ And it ain't coming down
♪ Where do I go?
♪ Give me some sort of sign
♪ You hit me with lightning
♪ Maybe I'll come alive
♪ Hard times ♪
♪ Gonna make you wonder
why you even try ♪
- ♪ Hard times ♪
- ♪ Gonna take you down
♪ And laugh when you cry
♪ These lives ♪
♪ And I gotta hit rock bottom
♪ Tell my friends
I'm coming down ♪
♪ We'll kick it
when I hit the ground ♪
♪ Tell my friends
I'm coming down ♪
- ♪ We'll kick it
- LORI: Don't touch me.
♪ When I hit the ground
♪ When I hit the ground...
Come on, Bert, Bert, Bert!
Go, go, go!
Come on, go! You're up!
♪ When I hit the ground.
♪ Hard times ♪
♪ Gonna make you wonder
why you even try ♪
- Shit!
- ♪ Hard times ♪
♪ Gonna take you down
and laugh when you cry ♪
- ♪ These lives ♪
- ♪ And I still don't know
- ♪ How I even survive
- ♪ Hard times ♪
- ♪ Hard times, hard times
- ♪ Hard times
- ♪ Hard times ♪
- ♪ Gonna make you wonder
♪ Why you even try
- ♪ Hard times ♪
- ♪ Gonna take you down
♪ And laugh when you cry
- ♪ These lives ♪
- ♪ And I still don't know
♪ How I even survive
- ♪ Hard times, hard times ♪
- ♪ Hard times
♪ And I gotta get
to rock bottom. ♪
- Ow.
- Shut up!
Oh, hey. You're up.
- I wasn't sure if you wanted...
- "I wasn't sure
"if you wanted
to sleep in or not.
"I folded your clothes
last night.
Wasn't sure if that material
gets wrinkled."
Anyway, what the hell
are you always
looking for under that desk?
Uh... oh, just...
my mouth guard.
Yeah, I...
I grind my teeth at night.
Oh, mystery solved.
♪ Yeah, it's my birthday
- ♪ And I ain't gotta pick up the pho... ♪
- Ow.
Ow.
You okay?
Yep. Never better.
I don't know if you remember
my name or not.
You were, uh... you were
pretty wasted last night.
But I'm-I'm Carter.
Ow!
Hey, are you sure you're okay?
You're looking kind of pale.
No, I'm fine. I...
Mm.
Actually, I'm probably
gonna pass out.
What?
- Yep. Definitely passing out.
- What? No, uh...
You hit that fine vagine
or what?
Is she dead?
- Ryan, little help here, man.
- Oh, okay.
Hey, hey. It's okay.
It's just me.
Hey.
You okay? You really gave me
a scare back there.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
You still came.
Yeah, of course.
Why wouldn't I?
Oh, we got a hold
of your parents.
They're on their way.
No. They can't come here.
It's not safe.
What are you talking about?
Jesus.
Can I help you?
Oh, it's okay. He's a friend.
Sorry.
Visiting hours are over.
Oh.
All right. Well...
Thanks, Carter.
Yeah. Feel better.
So, I guess now you know why
I wasn't in your class today.
Pardon?
Advanced bio.
Uh, I'm sorry.
Are you in my class?
You don't look familiar.
I'm sorry.
My mistake.
Right.
Well, I'm Dr. Butler.
Nice to meet you.
Ms. Gelbman,
I've been having a hard time
pulling up
your medical records.
I know. I should be dead.
My results,
they don't make sense, right?
Yes.
They're highly alarming,
to be honest.
Wait.
What time is it?
Uh, it's almost 9:30.
- Why?
- She's about to die.
- Who?
- Lori.
- He's gonna kill her.
- What?
Listen to me. You need to stop
her from going down to the O.R.
I'm sorry. I don't know
who you're talking about.
Oh, really?
Well, maybe your wife does.
Go. Go!
Sorry.
Lori.
Who set you free?
Who are you?
Fine.
I go, you go.
Oh, hey. You're up.
I wasn't sure if you wanted
to sleep in or not.
Shut up!
I am so done with this shit.
Then you multiplied
the Euclidean vector
by the square root of pi
to the 17th power,
which then gives us
an axon point of .004,
a linear plane vector of 8.2.
Boom.
Damn.
Well, if these are all
the failed algorithms...
Then there's only one
possibility left.
- Holy shit balls. You did it.
- Oh, oh!
- What? It worked?
- Yes, yes, yes.
It worked?
Oh, my God, it worked!
We did it!
Why are we so excited?
We barely know her.
Honestly, I-I don't know
what just happened,
but that was impressive.
Thanks.
Let's do this.
Just so we're totally clear,
one variant closes the loop
in this dimension,
and the other one sends you
back to your original dimension
and closes that loop.
It's final decision time.
Stay here or go back.
I'm staying here.
Final decision.
Okay. Here we go, then.
Stand back.
Huh? Wait.
- What happened?
- Uh, uh...
Oh, the vector's off.
But you said
this was the right one.
No, the math was right.
Something else is off.
Guys, I have literally
been killing myself
to memorize this shit for you.
Failure's not an option.
What?
There's something
in hard drive.
It must be a virus.
Dude, did you open spam porn
again on the computer?
No.
Great. I have to manually
reenter all this code.
Okay, how long?
Six, seven hours.
Ryan, look at me.
I am on borrowed time here.
Understand?
Get it done.
Uh, yeah, I'm on it.
Tree, wait up.
Hey. Are you sure about this?
Of course I'm sure.
Okay, well,
what about the killer?
I mean, you said people
are gonna die tonight.
If you close the loop
and we don't help,
then they're dead for good,
aren't they?
I have to stay alive.
I can't go back
to that hospital.
It's way too risky.
Okay, so that's it?
You're just gonna walk away
and let a bunch
of innocent people die?
People die every day, Carter.
I can't be responsible
for everyone, okay?
I know how selfish that sounds,
but it's true.
Yeah, no,
that sounds incredibly selfish.
Are you serious?
That's not fair.
You have no idea
how hard this is for me.
I don't want to have to choose
between you and my mom,
but I have to.
What do you mean, "choose"?
Carter, we're together
in the other dimension.
I woke up in your bed
every morning,
just like this morning.
I did it over and over
and over again
until I fell in love with you.
But that version of us
is back there,
and my mom is alive here.
So I've made my decision.
Wh... What if you're wrong?
Huh?
What if you're wrong?
What if this isn't the life
that you're-you're
supposed to have?
So, what?
I'm just supposed to go back
to some dimension
where my mom's dead?
I can't.
I can't lose her again.
You already did.
And none of this is real
if it erases that.
You're just... you're living
someone else's life
that doesn't belong to you.
Y-Your pain,
th-that loss, that's...
that's what makes you you.
But you have the chance
to do something
other people only dream of.
What?
You can say goodbye.
Yoo-hoo.
Your girlfriend's calling you.
Better go.
What's her problem?
She just ditched
our house meeting.
Hello.
What were you guys
talking about?
Nothing. We were just... we
were going over school stuff.
Babe, don't forget,
I still need help
with my American lit paper.
I'm...
I'm really busy right now.
Carter, you promised.
I won't pass the class
without your help.
All right. Yeah, yeah.
That's fine.
You're the best.
There's the other
birthday girl.
Sweetie, what's wrong?
I'm okay. I...
You don't look okay.
I'm okay. I... Mom!
You're cold as ice.
Maybe we should go
to the hospital.
No!
No, we can't go there.
Look, I don't want
to freak you guys out,
but I need to get as far away
from campus as possible.
- Theresa, what is going on?
- Dad, please.
I promise to explain
everything later,
but I need you to trust me.
Okay.
We'll go.
Let's go. Come on.
Yeah.
Done.
Finally.
You guys ready?
Okay. Let's close this loop
once and for all.
Hey.
You know what
I'm craving right now?
- What?
- One of those giant cinnamon rolls
from that bakery in Morro Bay.
From our birthday last year?
You don't remember?
You ate two of them.
That wasn't me.
What, sweetie?
Hey, girls,
it's getting kind of late.
What do you say we find
someplace,
turn in for the night?
Okay, sounds good.
I think we're all
pretty pooped.
Lori!
Shit.
He got her, he got her!
No, don't shoot! Don't shoot!
You might hit Kay.
Hey, girls,
I'm gonna go get some ice.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Give me a hand.
Just tell me one thing.
Are you pregnant?
What?
No. Mom, I...
Okay, sorry.
I just had to ask.
It's not like that.
But it's a boy, isn't it?
No.
Yes.
I don't know.
It's complicated.
Trust me.
I can do complicated.
What is it?
Have you ever wondered what
your life would have been like
if you couldn't be with Dad?
What? No.
But what if you had to choose?
You know, what if...
what if being with him meant
that you would lose someone
that you were really close to,
that you would never get
to see that person ever again?
What would you do?
Well, we all have to make
hard choices, Tree.
That's life.
And sometimes the past
is pulling us in one direction
and the future is calling us
somewhere new.
But, of course, if I had
to choose, I'd pick Daddy.
I mean, without him,
I wouldn't have you, right?
But how did you know
that he was the one?
I didn't.
I took a chance.
I followed my heart.
That's kind of
how love works, Tree.
It's a leap of faith.
...Bayfield University
Hospital,
where a terrible tragedy
continues to unfold.
Details are still coming in,
but so far, we can confirm
three victims.
A nurse and a police officer.
The third victim, a student,
was killed while attempting
to subdue the suspect.
Back to you, Dan.
No.
What's wrong?
Come on, Ryan. Come on.
Hey, Samar, can you
- check 22-97-39 right there?
- Uh, yeah.
Over there.
No, the vector
needs to be adjusted.
Yo, it's Ryan.
Leave a message at the beep...!
Ryan, don't close the loop.
- You can't...
- I'm sorry.
- This voice mailbox is...
- Shit!
Tree, what is going on?
I can't let him close it.
You know,
I'm not sure about this ice.
It kind of smells like pee.
Tree?
Tree! Where are you going?
Tree!
Come on.
Come on, come on!
Pick up your phone!
- Yo, it's Ryan. Leave a...
- Shit!
Here we go.
Where is it? Come on,
come on, come on. Please.
- Oh, hey. You're up.
- Shut up!
I wasn't sure if you wanted
to sleep in or not.
That is the last time
I'm dying for you.
What?
How much longer
is it gonna take?
Thanks to your crazy memory,
it shouldn't take long at all.
I can have Sissy ready to go
in just a few minutes.
I need a little more time.
There's something I need to do.
Tree.
You sure you want to go back?
Can't spend my life
living in the past.
Got to take a leap of faith.
She finally rolls in.
Uh, Lori, hi.
Big night?
You could say that.
Um, look, Lori, I...
It's good to see you.
Wha...?
It's good to see you, too,
Tree.
He's not worth it.
I mean, trust me.
I've been involved
with a married guy.
I know what it's like
living a double life.
Always feeling like shit
about yourself.
But it's never too late
to change.
Someone once told me that
"every day is a chance
to be someone better."
Maybe this is your day.
Okay.
Thank you.
Take care of yourself.
Tree.
Hey.
Um... look, Danielle,
I feel really bad.
I've totally been
misjudging you,
and it's completely on me.
- I am so sorry that I've, like, made this...
- Nice.
Three-way.
He's kidding.
No, I'm-I'm not.
Nick's, um, shower was broken,
so I said he could use mine.
Right, Nick?
My shower's fine.
Right. Um, you know what?
Never mind.
Sorry for interrupting.
Bye-ee.
Ow!
What was that for?
For being dumb as a rock.
That's what.
Oh, really?
How can a rock be dumb?
They don't even have brains.
Ouch.
There's the other
birthday girl.
- Hi, sweetie.
- Hey, Dad.
Um, do you mind if I talk
to Mom alone for a minute?
Just some girl talk.
Oh. Well, sure.
I-I can go run some work calls.
Okay, thanks.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. It's fine.
Everything's fine.
Oh, shit, how do I do this?
Do what, sweetie?
What's wrong?
Mom...
I really want you to know
how much I love you.
Aw.
I love you, too, sweetie.
No, Mom, I'm serious.
You know, people say
"I love you"
all the time, but...
it's not until you can't say it
to that person's face anymore
that you really realize
how much you mean it.
You are so beautiful
and so amazing.
And I just hope I can become
half of the woman
that you are one day.
Are you kidding?
I'm the woman I am
because I had you.
You know, I never really
told anyone this before,
but when I was pregnant with
you, I was scared shitless.
No.
But then,
the moment I held you,
something inside of me
changed instantly.
The best kind of love
does that.
It changes you.
It makes you a better person.
Oh, God, I'm so stupid.
I really thought I could
have it all, but I can't.
Oh, honey, nobody can.
But guess what.
That's okay.
You'll get what you need.
I hope so.
Aw. Come here.
Aw.
Am I crushing you?
Nope.
You're always gonna be
my little girl.
♪ Happy birthday to you
♪ Happy birthday
to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday,
Tree and Mom ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you.
Make a wish.
You ready?
Wait.
Um, look.
I know this is probably
pretty confusing.
I mean, you guys have only
known me for a couple hours,
but I've known you for weeks.
You've all worked
really, really hard
to try to send me home.
So thank you.
Well, jury's still out
on whether you're totally nuts,
but, uh...
glad we could help.
Okay, Ryan, light her up.
S-So, in this other dimension,
do we...
do we know each other?
You could say that.
17 seconds.
16, 15, 14...
What did I tell you
about turning that thing on?
- Uh-oh.
- Wait. This isn't supposed to happen yet.
You're not supposed to come
until tomorrow.
Turn that thing off now.
No, don't!
- No, no, no, no!
- No, no!
No, wait, please.
You can't do this.
- And who are you?
- I am a student here.
Oh, well, keep this
little attitude up,
and we'll change that.
Get that thing out of here.
- No, please d-don't.
- Hey, watch it, beefcake.
- Don't. Don't.
- We spent 18 months on that thing.
Please, please don't. Please.
Well, don't manhandle her.
Take...
Well, where are you taking her?
My office, where it will
remain under lock and key.
Look, okay, it's a setback.
I get it.
Right, but we just
reset the day and try again.
No. You don't understand.
I keep getting weaker
every time I come back.
I don't know
how many chances I have left.
For all I know,
this could be it.
If I die again,
I could stay dead.
- Hmm, that's a problem.
- No shit.
Unless...
Unless we steal it back.
Steal it?
Well, I mean, you know,
it's not even
technically stealing, is it?
It's your property.
Whoa, whoa, guys,
I don't know about this.
Like, if we get caught
and I get expelled,
my parents are gonna hang me
by the nut sack.
I'm with him.
Except for the "nut sack" part,
obviously.
Are you kidding me? Are...
No. I'm sorry to throw
a bag of dog shit
on your front porch here,
but I...
This is all on you guys.
You created this mess,
so you're obligated
to help her out of it.
Besides,
if she dies again tonight,
that's blood on your hands.
That's a little dramatic.
He's right.
This is our fault.
So we fix it.
That's what scientists do.
We solve the problem.
So, Dean Bronson's office
is in this building here,
and the fastest route back
to the lab is this path here.
And check this out, guys.
Dean Bronson spends
every evening knitting in
the faculty lounge over here.
- Wait, what? He knits?
- I think he used to smoke,
and then his wife
made him quit, and, uh...
Oh, by the way, shockingly hot.
- Samar?
- Hmm?
Could we do the-the thing
we're...
- we're doing right now?
- Okay, okay.
Right. Sorry.
Um, okay.
So, we need to get the keys
to his office,
sneak over to admissions,
break into the dean's office,
grab Sissy,
wheel her back to the lab
without anyone from security
seeing us,
get Dean Bronson's keys
back to him
without him ever knowing
they were gone,
power up Sissy,
run diagnostics,
flip the switch, and bam...
Tree's back
in whatever wack-ass dimension
she came from,
and we... well, we just
saved the damn day.
Okay.
Sounds awesome.
- How do we do that?
- I don't know.
- Of course.
- Okay, well,
we obviously need a diversion.
So we just got to find a way
to distract Dean Bronson.
♪ You're beautiful
♪ You're beautiful,
it's true... ♪
Uh, she picked the ringtone,
all right? I...
Hey, babe.
Yeah, uh, you okay?
I-I have an idea.
- Okay.
What if we actually
go through...
With Ryan and them and...
- Danielle, hi.
- She's not...
So, we have
a little favor to ask.
I feel suspect at best.
Let's just put our face in.
Hey, baby.
Oh. Okay, sorry.
- Clearly, she's a little on edge.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's right.
- Give her some room to breathe...
Preach.
Can I help you?
Oh, perdón.
I appear to be, uh, very lost.
Roger Bronson.
I'm the dean of the school.
Oh, bonjour.
My name is, uh, Amelie Le Pew.
Oh. You must be with
the exchange program.
Ah, oui, oui.
Monsieur, may I know your face?
I'm sorry?
Oh.
- My. Oh, my.
- Oh, my!
What strong features.
Thank you.
You must be French.
Your hand smells like cheese.
I don't eat cheese.
Ah, I am, uh...
...uh, lactose intolerant.
Oh, quelle dommage.
Uh, uh... uh, where are you
trying to get to?
Uh, le café.
Oh, you must mean
the cafeteria.
- I'm happy to show you. Here, here. I can...
- Uh, whoa!
Oh, oh! Oh, don't move!
You'll trip.
Oh, marbles.
Marbles! Marbles everywhere.
Go, go, go, go.
Oh, boy.
Oh.
- Careful.
- Whew!
Whoa.
Pretty quick there.
Hold on, now.
Just stay put, okay?
I just need to, uh,
grab my keys.
Whoa!
Oh! Not the tapestry.
Oh, geez.
- Oh. Oh, Lord.
- Oh, oh, oh! Oh, no!
Oh, no. It's so dark.
Move toward the light.
Oh, sorry,
that was insensitive.
Come on.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- I'm trying.
Stop rolling. Okay.
You're not helping.
The other way.
- Sissy.
- Go, go.
Go around, go around.
This way.
Samar. Samar.
Okay, okay.
Here we go. Up. Up.
Oh, God.
Here's your cane.
You really must stop
wandering around.
- Gracias. Okay.
- Okay. Shall we?
Ah, forgot my keys.
- Oh, God!
- Oh, no, mon Dieu.
God!
Oh, that's a lot of blood.
Jesus, be careful
with that thing.
- I am so sorry.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, I don't think the cane
is a good idea for you.
You need a Seeing Eye dog.
Checkmate.
Hey. How's it going?
We're on it.
Guys, we've got less
than three hours
to make this happen.
Not gonna lie...
it's gonna be close.
Shit.
If I don't stop the killer,
Lori's gonna die.
Stay here.
What? Why?
Just promise me
you'll stay here.
Can I borrow this?
Uh, y-yeah, sure.
Okay.
W-Wait, where are you going?
Tree!
Sorry, bad timing.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, you can put it away.
Come on, put it away.
Okay, now slowly turn around.
This is a really bad idea.
There's a killer
on the loose here.
Go get help.
- What?
- Go!
She's got a gun!
Lori, move.
- What?
- Come on, we've got to move.
- What's happening?
- I'll explain later. Move!
What is this?
You're not blind.
I'm gonna kill them.
I'm going to kill them!
He's onto us.
Babe, can you also get
my sunglasses back?
I just got those.
Okay, okay, come on. Yes.
Get it open now.
Get it, get it.
Bash it in.
- Keep 'em out.
- We're trying!
Get it open now!
Oh, my God. If I get expelled,
my parents are gonna disown me.
Tree, will you please tell me
what's going on?
At first, I thought
he was trying to kill me,
- but it's you he's after.
- Who?
It's over, Gregory.
What? Why?
His wife found out
about your affair.
So he stole a page
from your old playbook.
He set Tombs free,
knowing that everyone
would think that he killed you.
And the secret of your affair
would die with you.
Bravo.
Well done, indeed.
Once a douchebag,
always a douchebag.
I'm sorry, do I know you?
Stay back, asshole.
Put your back into it!
Try harder.
You guys got to get back
into the gym, man.
Ryan, we can't hold it
much longer.
Come on, come on.
You hear that?
You're gonna rot in prison.
I don't think so.
You see,
there's one little detail
you failed to realize
in all this.
Oh, really? What's that?
Me.
Lori!
You really think
I was gonna let
a little whore like that
ruin my life?
Gregory, kill her.
Would you like
to do the honors?
Don't mind if I do.
Oh, wait.
I almost forgot.
I want a divorce.
Now, where were we?
Hey!
Aw, look who brought
a screwdriver to a gunfight.
Wait.
I have something
I need to tell you.
What?
You're screwed.
Turn it off, you bitch.
No. No, no, no, no,
no, no, wait. Wait!
Ready? Come on.
There you go. I got you.
I got you.
All right. Yep.
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
I guess this is a pretty good
place to get shot, huh?
I'll lift you up now,
all right?
- You're gonna be okay.
- You're good.
It's okay, it's okay.
You're okay.
Lori, I...
I'm so sorry.
For what?
You just saved my life.
I just...
I wish things
could have been different.
I'm sorry,
but we need to move her.
Hang in there, hon.
Hey.
- Hey.
- You okay?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine. I...
I thought I told you
to stay put.
Yeah, well...
sorry, couldn't help myself.
I think it's time.
I hope you realize I'm only
going back for one reason.
Oh, man.
My Yoo-hoo.
Danielle?
Who?
Hi.
Oh, my God.
I think I just shit my pants.
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah
♪ Stayin' alive,
stayin' alive ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah
- ♪ Stayin' alive...
- ♪ Ooh... yeah
♪ Whoo, well, you can tell
by the way I use my walk ♪
♪ I'm a woman,
no time to talk ♪
♪ Music loud and women warm,
I've been kicked around ♪
♪ Since I was born
♪ And now it's all right,
it's okay ♪
♪ And you may look
the other way ♪
- ♪ We can try to understand
- ♪ Uh-huh, uh-huh
♪ The New York Times'
effect on man ♪
♪ Whether you're a brother
or whether you're a mother ♪
♪ You're stayin' alive,
stayin' alive ♪
♪ Feel the city breakin'
and everybody shakin' ♪
♪ And we're stayin' alive,
stayin' alive ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah
♪ Stayin' alive,
stayin' alive ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah
♪ Stayin' alive...
♪ All you want
♪ Well, now, I get low
and I get high ♪
♪ And if I can't get either,
I really try ♪
♪ Got the wings of heaven
on my shoes ♪
♪ I'm dancin'
and I just can't lose ♪
♪ And now it's all right,
it's okay ♪
♪ I'll live to see
another day ♪
♪ We can try to understand
♪ The New York Times'
effect on man ♪
♪ Whether you're a brother
or whether you're a mother ♪
♪ You're stayin' alive,
stayin' alive ♪
♪ Feel the city breakin'
and everybody shakin' ♪
♪ And we're stayin' alive,
stayin' alive ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah
♪ Stayin' alive,
stayin' alive ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah
♪ Stayin' alive...
♪ All you want
- ♪ I'm stayin' alive
- ♪ Life goin' nowhere
- ♪ Somebody help me
- ♪ Somebody help me, yeah
- ♪ I'm stayin' alive
♪ I'm stayin' alive
♪ Life goin' nowhere
- ♪ Somebody help me
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Somebody help me, yeah
- ♪ Somebody help me, yeah ♪
- ♪ Life goin' nowhere
♪ Life goin' nowhere
♪ Somebody help me, yeah.
Just doesn't make any sense.
Yes, it does.
It acted like a slingshot.
When she jumped back
into this dimension,
the vacuum created
by the centripetal force
closed the loop.
Who throws away
a perfectly good churro?
Oh, no, don't.
Uh-oh. This looks bad.
Ryan Phan?
Uh, maybe.
I'm Dr. Isaac Parker.
I'm here on behalf of DARPA.
We'd appreciate it
if you'd come with us
to answer some questions.
All of you.
Are we in trouble?
Please, right this way.
Dr. Kalibato to Robotics.
Holy shit.
Sissy.
Hope you don't mind us
borrowing her.
What you've created here
is truly remarkable.
Suck it, Dean Bronson.
We've been having
some difficulties
understanding
how the device operates.
We figured you could help.
There's so many different
algorithms.
It'll be tough to find
the right one to make it work.
I might be able
to help with that.
Great.
So, we just need to find
a test subject.
Wait, you... you want to trap
somebody in a time loop?
That's messed up.
Unless they deserve it.
I think I have
the perfect recruit.
Subtitles by explosiveskull