♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece
of memory that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about
blooming flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever
stay with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 31=
Is this the construction site
of the Entertainment Center?
This is it.
Too bad.
Such a nice piece of land! The project
has been put on hold for over one year.
If your dad were here,
he'd be heartbroken.
To be honest, Yuzheng,
I really admire your father.
He had so much courage
to take this project.
I can see Mr. Lei's ambition
at that time.
This project
was so sensational at that time.
I've seen the design of the
Entertainment Center.
Now I've seen
the construction site as well.
Although time passed
and everything changed,
you can still see
(Foundation, February 2016)
how vigorous Mr. Lei
was to this project.
He was trying to
leave something great to Yutian.
Yutian was founded by my father.
In other word, it was his life.
What he did for
the Entertainment Center project,
is much more than what I did,
as his son.
I think
the Entertainment Center project
was envisioned in his mind
a million times.
Unfortunately, he cannot
see this anymore.
Siyang, how about
I restart this project?
Pretty hard.
I called it "hard"
not only because of the financial issue,
but also people.
Firstly, you have to convince the board
to restart
the Entertainment Center project.
Even the board agrees
to restart
the Entertainment Center project,
Lin Xiangyuan probably
will set obstacles in your way,
and put you in a dilemma.
I am well prepared.
I remember last time Jiang Jin
and Lin Xiangyuan
met you,
they promised you at the table that
they would operate this project well.
But with what we can see today,
I think, you already have the answer.
Besides, don't forget.
Though you are
the majority shareholder of Yutian,
you actually
cannot join the decision-making.
The first thing we have to do...
To prove that I was innocent?
Isn't it?
Siyang, I can understand
what you are talking about.
So it is better than
not to act and fail.
I need to go back to Yutian.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I will not only go back to Yutian,
but also let everyone know that
I, Lei Yuzheng,
will fulfill my dad's last wish.
I will build up a great monument
from this project.
Let's move on to the last item.
Regarding Lei Yuzheng's
apportionment as the assistant of
the chairman of board,
please vote.
Lei Yuzheng was arrested
for internal information leakage.
According to the law,
he must not be in the top management
within five years.
Everyone,
please allow me to speak a few words.
According to the law,
Lei Yuzheng
should not be in the top management
of a listed company.
But
it never says
he cannot work for the company.
So,
for the appointment of Lei Yuzheng
as the assistant of the chairman,
I agree.
OK, approved.
They didn't do the cleaning.
I remember that Mr. Lei
hated having a dirty table.
I will clean it up.
Don't bother.
Mr. Lei,
I just heard that you are back.
Weicheng, long time no see.
You're just the same.
Mr. Lei,
you still look great.
It's really nice to see you again.
You are back now, which is great.
The Entertainment Center project
can go ahead.
Seeing that project be held,
I was so sad.
Now, it is so terrible.
We really feel sorry
to your dad, Mr. Lei.
But we cannot find out any solution.
There is nothing we can do but worry.
You are all senior staff.
For the previous period,
I really appreciate your hard work.
If you can wait,
I believe,
as long as you keep working for Yutian,
it will become better and better.
Mr. Lei, what you just said
makes us feel secure and comfortable.
We look forward to the day when
the project is successfully completed.
Mr. Lei,
what do you think
Lin Xiangyuan was
thinking about just now?
Your opinion?
I think he was thinking about
why you are back so soon.
He invited me back to Yutian
a few days ago.
So having me back,
he should not feel surprised.
For what happened in the past,
I am terrible sorry.
I know, in my life,
no matter what I do,
I cannot pay it off.
Let the past pass.
But I have to tell you.
Before doing anything,
you should think well.
Please don't worry.
In the future, even if I get killed,
I will never make this kind of mistake.
Don't exaggerate your words.
I don't want to get you killed.
Hello, Mr. Lin.
One is the former CEO,
and the other is the current CEO.
It's going to be a tough competition.
One of them is going to lose.
You're right.
After all, Mr. Lei is from Lei's family.
Hares may pull dead lions by the beard.
Hard to tell who the "lion" is,
and who the "hare" is?
Lin Xiangyuan,
how can you fight with me?!
Mr. Lin,
Lei Yuzheng is back.
You look so worried.
Lei Ting passed away.
Lei Yuzheng is
the most majority shareholder of Yutian.
He is just back to his own company.
Don't be surprised.
Mr. Lin, you're really
holding your nerve.
Didn't you say that
he didn't want to come back?
To tell you the truth,
I invited Lei Yuzheng back.
So, Mr. Lin,
what are you thinking?
You just wait and see.
Don't you think that
Lei Yuzheng is back at this moment
with some purpose?
What purpose?
You're not afraid of him
to prove his innocence?
We have to pay more attention.
Xie, can you please use your brain?
At this moment, if Lei Yuzheng
were not in the building of Yutian,
will you know
what he is planning out here?
Right.
Mr. Lin, you are so thoughtful.
Why didn't I think of that?
That's why
I am the CEO,
and you are my assistant.
Of course.
You're the CEO. Definitely,
I'm not comparable to you.
Mr. Lin,
where are you going?
Lei Yuzheng is back.
I am going to meet him.
Qunfei,
doing cleaning?
Mr. Lin.
You're here to see Mr. Lei?
I brought two cleaners
to clean the office for Mr. Lei.
It's fine. No more cleaning.
I have cleaned it well.
Oh, Qunfei.
Have you gone through
the job on-board process?
I am not in a hurry.
After Mr. Lei
appointing me the position,
I will go through the process.
OK.
Don't wait until your
job position is determined.
I will require someone
to give you an access card.
So you can go in and out freely.
Do you think, for Mr. Lei,
he also needs one?
Qunfei,
you're really funnier than before.
No need to worry about Mr. Lei.
He can go in and out
without any access card.
You're right. I forgot.
I just thought
if Mr. Lei wants to get in Yutian
but someone stops him,
that would be so embarrassed.
Please tell Mr. Lei I was here.
Sure.
Such a big deal,
I will not forget.
Yuzheng,
you're back now.
What's your plan?
My plan?
To be honest,
this time,
I'm going to do only one thing.
Yuzheng,
no matter what you are going to do,
Uncle Jiang
will always stand on your side.
Thank you.
Then, Uncle Jiang,
I will come straight to the point.
I want to restart
the Entertainment Center project.
The Entertainment Center project
is not on the progress?
What do you mean to restart?
The Entertainment Center project
has been on hold for more than one year.
I was at the
construction site yesterday.
This is what it looks like now.
On hold? When was that?
Why didn't I know that?
Yuzheng,
this is my fault.
I was worried about you,
so a lot of things were not followed.
Uncle Jiang's negligence.
Uncle Jiang,
I know you are now the chairman.
You should be very busy.
You cannot focus on every detail.
So, today, I come here.
I don't blame you.
But for the
Entertainment Center project,
Mr. Lin and other directors
have different opinions.
My dad passed away.
I was not here.
So, such a big project being on hold
is inevitable.
I can understand.
Yuzheng, you can think like that.
I'm glad and relieved.
I
feel involuntary sometimes.
Restarting the project
must be approved by the board.
Don't worry.
I will definitely support you.
It is really nice of you to say that.
I believe that you don't want to see it
being given up.
You're absolutely right.
If the Entertainment Center project
can be completed and opened up
during your term of chairman,
to you,
it will be a great achievement, right?
Uncle Jiang
will definitely support you.
Uncle Jiang, I'm here today
for one more thing.
I hope you can help
convince Lin Xiangyuan.
Don't worry about that.
Though Xiangyuan is my son-in-law,
if it benefits the company,
he will not object.
He does not have shares.
So, for significant decisions,
he has to listen to the board.
Thank you. With your support,
it is already half done.
You're right.
And for the
Entertainment Center project,
Xiangyuan may have his own opinions.
For the future of Yutian,
he may also have his own vision.
But his purpose is to
let Yutian become better.
As a CEO,
he is very good.
He was promoted by me.
If he does a good job,
I will be proud of him as well.
Don't worry.
For restarting
the Entertainment Center project,
if I agree,
he will support me.
Mr. Lei, are you here now?
I just arrived. Where are you?
Mr. Lei, go straight,
and pass the washroom.
There is a back door.
I will wait for you there.
Excuse me.
Where is the washroom, please?
Go straight to the end.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Mr. Lei, I'm so sorry
to ask you to meet here.
Safety is the most important now.
What you asked us to investigate
is not a trivial matter.
If it alerts the opponent,
we cannot find anything anymore.
Besides,
it involves tens of millions of yuan.
If it's for money, your opponent
will probably do anything.
Good. I think I got a right person.
You're so professional.
OK. Then wait for my call.
Sir, this is your coffee.
I didn't order coffee.
The gentleman who just left
bought it for you.
Since Zhenrong passed away,
you seldom came here.
You're afraid of seeing these things,
and feeling sad, right?
I know.
You want to conserve
the memories of you and Zhenrong.
Shangguan, since when
did you talk like a poet?
Conserve...
Don't laugh at me.
I want to ask you.
Do you want a "killing spree"?
Don't play too many games.
It is not easy to be back to Yutian.
Don't you want to do something?
Fine.
If you don't want to talk about it,
just let it be.
But I came all the way here,
just to see a sword?
What are you doing?
You asked me
whether I want a "killing spree".
But I don't want to
be the person you kill.
You are the one to "kill".
Change.
I said I cannot do fencing.
I don't want to be a target.
Enough.
Done.
I cannot play
such kind of noble sports with you.
It's too plain.
Too plain?
Yes.
Shut up.
Don't...
I have heart disease.
Believe or not, if you keep
doing that, I will just lie down here.
OK, lie down.
Shangguan,
you're really
so afraid of death.
Feeling hurt?
Hurt?
It's fine.
Not hurt? Then, stand up.
Keep practicing.
Are you serious?
Be gentle.
I think I have talent.
Come.
Fanlv,
you become thinner.
Isn't it good to be thin?
Many people want to lose weight,
and they may not succeed.
This is not what I expect.
In my whole life,
I have no other expectation.
I only hope you
can be happy and healthy.
Dad, don't talk about this.
Yuzheng is back.
Maybe it's a good thing.
In a way,
it will bring
Lin Xiangyuan some restraint.
You want Yuzheng
to drive Lin Xiangyuan away.
After all, Lin Xiangyuan
is my son-in-law.
Today, Lei Yuzheng had a talk with me.
I have relieved.
I hope they can
forgive and forget the pass,
and manage Yutian well together.
So, dad wants to tell you.
Yuzheng is back now.
Between him and Lin Xiangyuan,
you should not do anything.
Dad is protecting you. Understand?
I know.
Your marriage with Lin Xiangyuan
is in trouble.
This is not a key problem.
Yuzheng is back.
Xiangyuan should be very clear that
his position is not stable now.
At this moment,
don't put him in any trouble.
Everyone has his own fate.
I'm not persuading you
to believe in destiny.
I just want to tell you that
everything has both good side
and bad side.
Even if you marry Lei Yuzheng,
will you be happy?
Sometimes, for something,
you have to learn to take them easy,
and don't be too serious.
Understand?
Keep your elbow in.
Elbow.
Buddy, say it.
What do you want?
Not just ask me to play this with you?
I wasn't planning to talk about it.
But now that you mentioned it,
I will just tell you.
I want to restart
the Entertainment Center project.
Just...
Jiang Jin and Lin Xiangyuan
do not agree?
No, it's not.
Then what?
You know that
to restart this project,
money is the priority.
Such a large amount of money,
even if they do not disagree,
other directors will probably disagree.
So...
You want to put a "killing spree" on me?
Right?
I've never said that.
You, yourself said that.
Think about it.
To get the approval of the board,
I must have some external funding.
If outsiders want to
take a slice as well,
it means
this project is doable.
Just put up the appearance
to give them some faith.
Let me speak frankly.
You should help me.
Of course, buddy.
For all things of yours,
I have never flinched.
As soon as I get to my office tomorrow,
I'll ask them to prepare the money.
Get ready for you.
As long as you tell me to go,
I'll take the money
directly to Yutian.
Thanks, my buddy.
According to the financial statement
of the past months,
the profits from traditional businesses
are increasing,
but the growth rate is getting smaller.
Now, every industry
conducts restructuring.
I think Yutian
should have a new breakthrough.
What is your opinion?
New Energy Automobile.
(New Energy Automobile Report)
According to our research,
many big cities
are trying to promote
new energy automobile.
More importantly,
among our consumers
in our researches,
since this year,
our consumers' interests in
new energy automobile
are increasing.
That means, the market
is slowly forming.
If we join in the market at this time,
we can grab the original stock.
But we don't have the technicians,
or research and development
institutions for this.
Cooperation.
Nowadays,
it is impossible
to create an industrial chain
all by ourselves.
We have to seek for cooperation.
That is to say, we put in the money
and the institutions
go for the technology.
Every decision
should be approved by the board.
In my opinion,
it can be discussed
at the board meeting first.
So,
we need your support.
Dad,
I have promised
both you and Lei Yuzheng,
I will take Yutian to a new stage.
You have to support me this time.
Shareholders need to see a profit,
and you need to
show that to shareholders.
We must make sure that
nothing goes wrong in this matter.
Don't worry. They are all buddies.
Yutian is planning for something big.
What's going on?
Lin Xiangyuan decided
to hold a board meeting.
He wants to initiate cooperation
with Green Investment,
an emerging company.
Green Investment?
Right.
I read about it
on Economics the other day.
This is an emerging company.
Last week, it invested
a large amount of money
to buy the most famous
new energy research institute in China,
Green Energy.
Yes.
It should be this dubious company.
This dubious company
bought this institute,
and then
Lin Xiangyuan proposed
to cooperate with this company.
What they're asking for is
Yutian should be
the majority shareholder.
This is unbelievable.
Green Investment cannot
afford to lose out in this investment.
It is willing to act as
a "money transfer station" for Yutian?
I heard that
the boss of Green Investment
made a bad decision.
After buying this institute,
they found that investing in new energy
industry needs huge amount of money.
That's why they are
looking for help from Yutian.
Our Yutian's shareholders
definitely want to take this advantage.
It sounds
like pennies from the heaven?
Let's make an assumption.
Of course, that would be
the worst situation.
We assume that the investment company
is to help Lin Xiangyuan.
They took the risk
and bought a research institute
that cost large amount of money.
Then they want to
take advantage of the market's
attention to new energy automobile
to whet the appetite of shareholders,
so as to make the shareholders
eager to make this investment.
That means,
Yutian's money
will be transferred to Green Investment.
Though it is Yutian's
property nominally,
it's actually helping Green Investment
to make money.
If...
If there are
some illegal practices involved,
Green Investment
can be in the name of
new energy research to
perform money laundering.
The money of Yutian!
You're right.
This kind of irrational investment
will feed Green Investment full
in a short time.
That is to say,
Green Investment actually
holds a huge amount of money of Yutian.
If it were me,
when Yutian runs out of money,
I would definitely
invest money back to Yutian
to exchange for shares.
In this way, Green Investment
will naturally become
a shareholder of Yutian.
Even a majority shareholder.
At that time, the legal representative
will be changed
to Lin Xiangyuan.
Hs is so smart!
I said just now that
this is only an assumption.
Yuzheng,
now that we anticipate the risks,
I suggest you exercise a veto.
After all, you are
the majority shareholder.
No.
Before the bad guys come out,
how can we pull the "net"?
I'm going to set the "big fish" free.
Is that what you're waiting for?
Stay close.
OK.
(Securities Law)
Come in.
Mr. Lei,
long time no see.
Reading a book?
Just take a look.
I don't know who
put these two books here.
Maybe
someone is trying to remind me
of something I cannot do.
If I don't read it,
I may let down his "kindness".
I had my staff
to send you the briefing.
I didn't expect
to send you these two books.
You come to me not for these two books?
Of course not.
I'm here to discuss with you
on the Entertainment Center project.
I just want to know
if this project is to be restarted,
what is Mr. Lin's opinion?
Mr. Jiang has talked to me,
and let me fully cooperate with you
to restart the project.
But
some time ago,
our company is going to
invest in a new energy project
which requires
a large amount of capital.
If you want to restart
the Entertainment Center project,
for the company's cash flow,
it's a little difficult.
It is a pity that
I can do nothing about it.
So I'm here to explain to you.
I can understand.
But as you know,
I'm a person
who is not easy to give up.
Don't worry.
About money, it is not a problem.
Anything else?
Forgot to tell you.
According to
the proposal of the chairman,
the board has approved
your position as
the special assistant to the chairman.
Restarting
the Entertainment Center project
is in your charge now.
Mr. Lin, if you have nothing else,
please help yourself.
As a special assistant,
I have a lot of work to do.
Mr. Lin,
the books.
This Lei Yuzheng.
He came back to Yutian
in such a high profile.
He also proposed to restart
the Entertainment Center project.
What on earth is he up to?
What are you worried about?
At least within a few years,
Lei Yuzheng is not able to be in
the top management of Yutian.
The ball is in our court,
and all he can do
is to find the money.
Would anyone help him?
With Lei Yuzheng's strength,
he can just go out there for money,
and it is not a problem for him
to get it.
You are followed?
Is it a mistake?
I took a detour today,
and I found that
someone was following me.
There should be more than one.
Did they find out
you are investigating them?
Should be.
So,
we must now find another way
to cover our tracks.
What do you want to do?
Shangguan always wants to hold
a party for me, for my return to Yutian.
I thought it was too high profile.
Now, I think
the party comes at a good time.
Just let the opponent think that
I have no will to fight now.
On the Entertainment Center project,
after two setbacks,
I have given up completely.
So I need to have fun and relax.
What I'm most worried about now
is my father-in-law.
You mean Mr. Jiang?
In case Mr. Jiang is bamboozled
by Lei Yuzheng,
in a moment of aberration,
he may support his proposal
and become his supporter.
He may divert our project funds to his.
Then we'll be in trouble.
After all, Mr. Jiang,
is a member of the board,
and he can join the decision-making.
So what do we do?
Oh,
there's an antique
appreciation tomorrow.
But I have to go to a party,
and I have no time to go with him.
Make an arrangement for that.
OK, got it.
Do what he wants to please Mr. Jiang.
It can distract his attention.
So he will not always focus on
the Entertainment Center project.
Dad.
Sit.
I'm being stupid again.
Please forgive me
for making Fanlv so angry.
What did you do to Fanlv?
Dad.
Don't ask him.
He worries about me and cares about me.
He doesn't want me to go out
for drinking tonight.
We had a fight.
Fanlv,
I'm so sorry.
I know what you mean.
Shangguan will hold a party
for Lei Yuzheng,
and you don't want me to go.
You're afraid that my friends
bad-mouthed you in front of me, right?
That's a good thing.
For this party,
I think that you should both go.
Dad, only I am invited.
There is no "you" or "I".
In my opinion, this is also
a good chance for you and Xiangyuan
to have better communication
with your friends.
Take Xiangyuan to meet them.
In the future,
there may be cooperation opportunities.
Forget it, dad.
I'd rather not go.
You must go.
You help me take care of Fanlv.
Don't let her drink too much.
Welcome, Miss.
What can I do for you?
I'm good, thanks.
Excuse me, are you...
I am invited by Shangguan.
What should I call you?
Du Xiaosu.
Miss Du, this way please.
Excuse me.
Designer Du.
Come.
Welcome.
I get it.
It must be for my buddy, right?
I really envy him.
Can I open it?
Of course.
Wow,
it means to tie up my buddy.
I wouldn't dare to accept it.
Shall I give you some space?
I'll just leave.
I like the gift very much.
Thank you.
Good.
How are you?
I'm good.
How about you?
I'm good, too.
The gift is delivered.
I gotta go.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪