[English subtitles are available]
[Plot Love]
[Episode 9]
[Nan Xi Shi Hospital Outpatient]
Su Bei...
Brother!
- Brother, you're awake?
- Nan Nan!
Nan Nan, you're awake!
Grandma's here!
Don't go...
I'm not going.
Grandma's not going.
Su Su.
It's clear that Lu Fei'er
went behind our backs.
Why didn't you say anything?
Lu Nan's grandma is getting old.
I was afraid she wouldn't be able to handle it if I told her.
But why did she do that?
She likes her brother?
But she doesn't have to split you up.
She was adopted from an orphanage
by the Lu family.
So does she...
Holy shit.
Did Lu Nan know about this?
When women get tough,
we're no match for them at all.
You didn't see how
Su Bei trounced Su Manni.
She's confident, accurate and tough.
Brilliant!
Of course.
She's my girl!
Now you're proud of her?!
At the beginning, I didn't know it was who
tried to kick her out of the family.
But
seriously,
I was really happy for you
when I saw Su Bei
taking all the responsibilites of the whole company for you.
I know better than anyone
how much pressure you've been under in the past two years
since you woke up.
I was always worried about what would happen
if you couldn't handle the stress.
Fortunately,
you have Su Bei now,
and you don't have to work so hard anymore.
It's really nice
to have her.
Ewwwww.
You talk a lot today, huh?
Fine.
I talk too much.
Ungrateful bastard.
What's wrong, sweetie?
Bei Bei.
Let's go to see daddy.
He's very sick.
Are you worried about him?
Don't worry.
Daddy will be fine.
Even though he's sick,
you can't
be with someone else.
Otherwise,
you'll break my heart.
Humph!
You...
Call Su Bei.
I have something to tell her.
Just say it if you miss her.
Um...
You can
hint about
the headache.
But be natural.
Hello?
Ms. Su.
Mr. Lu has some work
for you to do.
Do you think
you can come to the hospital?
I'm in the middel of something.
Nan!
Nan, what's wrong?
Doctor! Doctor!
Nan! Nan!
Hang on!
Is this some sequela of the accident?
I'll be right there.
Alright!
OK.
Well done.
A bit overacting though.
Am I entitled to a bonus at the end of the year?
Sure.
Your bonus will be to continue working for Eminence next year.
Scrooge!
Seriously,
about Su Manni,
you just let it go?
Do you think
I'm a pushover?
On the face of it, they tried to get me.
But in fact,
Gu's Group was plotting against Eminence.
Without Gu Chengze,
do you think Su Manni would dare to do this?
So
what are you going to do?
You go and check what Gu Chengze has been doing lately.
I don't think he will
keep a low profile.
Alright.
That's what I want to do!
Why hasn't she come yet?
Come on!
[Ward]
It hurts.
How are you?
Are you okay?
He just had a fever.
But he's better now.
Su Bei,
I've got work to do at the office. I'll be off.
OK.
How are you?
Do you want me to get you a doctor?
No no no.
The doctor said
it won't get better soon.
So let's not bother them.
I...
I want water. Water.
Here.
I'm weak.
I'm weak all over. Wipe it for me.
I thought
you had just fallen on you head,
but you can't move your hands either.
So will you be unable to move your legs in a few days?
Very likely.
If that's the case,
will you support me for the rest of my life?
Don't be ridiculous.
What are you? An actor?
I'm a bit tired.
I'm off.
Fine. I'll be good.
If you're tired,
why don't you take a rest here?
Thank you
for everything.
Don't you blame me for taking over as president
without asking your permission?
You've done a good job.
But
you shouldn't have
turned the wheel to the left.
It's very dangerous.
Then you shouldn't have unfastened your seatbelt
to protect me when it's so dangerous.
You shouldn't have gotten hurt.
I'm afraid I would regret it
if I hadn't protected you.
[Coconut Village Ocean Science Park]
[Chris Star of the Universe]
Yeah!
Very good!
Great! Another one!
Right!
One more turn.
Look at the camera.
Good! Another one!
Well done!
Great! Look to the left.
Very good.
OK. OK. Just like that.
Well done!
Alright. It's a wrap!
Thank you, guys.
Good job, Chris.
Thanks!
Chriser, you're wonderful today! So cool!
Auntie Yang,
it's a pleasure to work with you today.
Here you are.
This is for me?
Yes.
Thank you, Chriser.
Auntie, I'm not Chriser.
I'm Chris.
Chriser.
Chris.
Chr...
Forget it.
Just call me Mr. Su.
All right. Whatever you say.
Then
take me to my dad.
OK.
Let's go!
If you don't wake up, dad,
someone else will take Bei Bei away from you.
You've got my money, so you must do as I say.
Take care of yourself.
Dad, you're awake.
Here you are.
This is ugly!
Dad!
I'm not your dad.
Daddy!
I'm not your dad
and I'm not your daddy either.
Then I'll call you Nan Nan,
just like Bei Bei.
Nan Nan, do you play football?
No.
Do you have friends who play football?
Can you
lift me up?
No.
Then what can you do?
Make money.
What's the point of just making money
if you can't play football
and you don't have any friends who play football
and you can't lift me up?
What's the use of making money?
Do you know what money is?
Of course I do.
Where did you get this money?
You don't have to know that.
Just be good
and I'll take care of you.
You'll take care of me?
Do you know who am I?
And you want to take care of me?
You're Nan Nan.
Bei Bei!
How dare you!
I'll teach you a lesson when we're home.
Mr. Lu, sorry.
Brat!
I was so worried!
Thank you.
We're off. You take care.
Let's go.
Let them go home first.
You, come here.
Beibei,
he said something bad about you.
Let's go. I don't want to talk to him.
I...I've got a huge headache.
You go home first.
I'll see you later.
Be good.
Massage my temples for me.
My head hurts so much.
I don't know if there will be a sequela.
I...
go home today.
Why didn't you come home with me?
Don't worry. I'm with you.
Find all that women's stuff
in this house
and throw them away!
Yes, grandma.
What are you doing?
Grandma asked us...
Just do your job.
Leave now.
Nan Nan.
Nan Nan,
why did you get out of the hospital so early?
I told you to get some rest.
Did he do that
because you want to come back?!
She had nothing to do with it.
I want to bring her back.
No.
I told you that
this woman is not allowed to enter our house.
Get out!
Grandma.
She's my wife.
So
this is her home.
If you want to get rid of her,
then I'll have to move too.
Grandma!
Grandma.
What's wrong?
You're having a headache again?
I'm fine.
I'm just upset.
Dizzy.
What upset you?
Stay home and rest.
I told you to stay in the hospital for a few more days,
but you didn't listen.
I want to spend more time with you.
With me?
What a sweet talker! I don't think I'm the one you want to spend time with.
Grandma, I was just faking it.
I'm old
but I‘m not stupid.
I saw how you treated her.
There's no way you were faking it.
Grandma,
there's nothing more important to me
than you and Eminence.
Su Bei is only with me for now.
I'll kick her out
as soon as I acquire Sia.
No.
She must leave now.
Fine.
Since grandma insists,
I respect your decision.
I'll get rid of Subei now
and pay a visit to Sia myself.
Their cooperation with Gu's Group
should be finalised in a couple of days.
There's only one day left.
So I'll go immediately.
Don't worry.
Come on, sit down.
Be good.
It's okay, grandma.
I won't come back until I get Sia.
The doctor said
I should be able to hold on like this for a while.
No, no, no.
You can't go.
My lovely Nan Nan.
I listen to you.
We're not going.
Let that woman go.
Grandma has made it so clear
that you should leave here.
You'd better do.
You're not faking it anymore, are you?
It's not worth it to waste my time
on a loser.
Since you used to be
my sister-in-law,
I'd like to remind you that
my brother loved you before,
so your pestering was a sign of love
for him.
But now he's forgotten about you and he doesn't love you anymore.
So your pestering is a nuisance.
I hope you'll behave yourself.
You find it annoying,
but I think your brother enjoys it a lot.
Now I see
why Lu Nan
had to move out of the house seven years ago
despite grandma's objection.
It's because
someone didn't put herself in the right position.
Besides,
I didn't tell Lu Nan and grandma
about your phone call
seven years ago.
I didn't do it out of repsect
or fear towards you.
I just didn't want to upset grandma
and put Lu Nan
in a dilemma.
That's why you lied to grandma
and told her that Sia was one day away
from finalising the contract with Gu.
Su Bei is expected to turn things around in one day.
The person in charge of Sia
isn't even in China.
So who will Su Bei talk to?
When grandma asks about this,
how will you explain?
But it's an urgent situation.
So I understand why you said that.
Here are the documents for your review.
I've already commented on problematic parts.
Take a look at them.
Thanks.
By the way,
there's good news from Amy.
There're a lot of people at Sia's headquarters
would love to work with us.
If we can have breakthrough of thorough dyeing at this point,
we'll have a better chance
even if Gu agrees to a concession.
Well done.
So...
So we must find the fragrance brocade!
This is weird.
You had an accident
and the fragrance brocade was lost.
Then look for it right now!
Su Bei, I...
We want to celebrate tonight.
So...
Hello?
[Gu's Group Gu Yan Manager]
If you're free tonight,
could you make good on your promise?
Ms. Su, you're not going to break your word, are you?
Let's do it tonight. You decide where and when.
Okay, see you tonight.
What were you going to tell me?
Never mind. It's fine.
It doesn't matter what I say
since you've got an appointment.
Fine.
By the way,
take calcium supplement.
After all,
you're not getting any younger.
Thanks.
Enjoy it.
You're really a good friend, huh?
You've ruined my business
and my dad gave me a dressing-down for it.
It's all right.
I'll treat you to a nice dinner to make it up to you
when I secure the deal.
I'll keep that in mind.
But I didn't expect Eminence
to know so much about thorough dyeing.
Are you trying to
get some information from me?
If so,
will you tell me?
But I don't know about it!
You think I'm the Monkey King who
can do anything?
No no no.
You're much better looking than that monkey.
Be careful.
Mr. Gu,
do you mind if I share the table with you?
If I say yes,
will you use another table?
No.
Why do you have to share the table with us?
There are so many tables available over there. Are you blind?
But I like this table.
I'll cut it for you.
Let me do it.
Here.
It's done.
Eat mine.
The meat looks good,
but
it's a bit overcooked.
By the way, Mr. Gu,
you're not a young lad anymore.
When are you getting married?
I may let you down.
After all, not every woman is as wonderful
as Su Bei.
Exactly.
You must try harder.
After all, only a wonderful man
deserves a wonderful woman.
Mr. Lu is right.
You'd better be nice to Su Bei.
She's very popular.
But she only loves me,
right?
Bei Bei.
Here.
Eat this.
Mr. Lu, why didn't you go to bed?
Can't you see that I'm jealous?
Yes I can.
You were so jealous to the point that
you did public display of affection.
I'm not blind.
Then don't you have anything to say to me?
Yes I have.
Don't you ever
say things so childish.
People will make fun of you.
Mrs. Lu,
we need to talk.
What do you want to talk about?
You can't have any contact with Gu Yan from now on.
I don't like it.
You're jealous.
And you're sweet.
Stop faking it.
Look at your happy face.
I can see that from miles away.
These are the investment information
for Gu Chengze's project.
No wonder Gu Chengze is so generous.
He's desperate.
The projects he invested in
are loss-making.
Tell me.
What are you up to?
Doesn't he have a younger brother?
You want them to fight over each other?
How's the board of directors?
They're convinced now,
thanks to
Su Bei's crisis management.
And our reputation is getting better.
Good!
Love is in the air!
I've been working for you so many years,
and you never praise me.
You don't have work to do, huh?
That expression on your face just now
looks so familiar.
It's exactly the same as
when you talked about Su Bei seven years ago.
How did I look like
seven years ago?
I'm going to marry you today!
Are you happy? Are you happy?
[Seven years ago]
My wife is so beautiful, isn't she?
[Double Blessings]
They'll be jealous!
So jealous!
Look!
Alright.
Let me do it.
I'll do it.
Come on.
What are you doing?
- We're getting married.
- Sit down.
Sit here, you two.
[REC]
Kiss!
Don't look at us.
I won't.
[REC]
Kiss!
Su Bei,
I've given you all my heart.
There's no room for anybody else.
So you can't leave me.
One more kiss!
Come on!
What's wrong?
You're having a headache again?
Come here. Sit down.
Sit here.
I think I remembered something
about Su Bei.
She was so happy and came over to me.
We were smiling
happily together.
You...
You remember that?!
It turned out that
we were really in love before.
But I forgot
about such an important thing.
Don't say that.
It's not your fault about amnesia.
Don't blame yourself.
Besides,
even if you remember everything,
it's all past.
What's the point?
Since you're in love with her again,
just get her back.
Right?
Forget about
your goddamn pride.
If you like her, then go for her.
As simple as that.
Don't be a coward.
To be honest,
I had to bite my tongue not to tell you this before.
I wouldn't bother to say this
if you were not
my best friend.
Alright.
Then make me a proposal
before you get off work.
What?
A proposal?
Why don't you ask me to write a paper?
Fine, fine, fine.
Don't look at me like that. I'll do it.
But
this is not my job,
so I can't do it for free, right?
A luxurious 10-day trip to Europe.
15 days, plus double bonuses.
Good!
Forget about the proposal.
That won't work.
Let me tell you.
All women have one thing in common.
They're softhearted.
Remember that
and you'll make it.
First, you have to...
And then...
Then you come this way
and that's pretty much it.
Got it?
What are you going to do?
Practice!
What about my European tour?
Do it yourself!
You...
Phone!
[Yun Fan]
A tip for you.
I've tried my best to help you.
Remember, you're invincible when you're shameless.
What's wrong?
I'm cold.
Cold?
Aren't you supposed to feel hot?
It's so hot!
You need to go to the hospital.
I'm fine.
Just help me to my room.
Don't go.
Let go of me. I'll get you some medicine.
Let me hold you for a while.
Shouldn't you be weak
when you have a cold?
But you look
as strong as a bull.
I'm dizzy.
I can't hear anything.
Let me hold you for a while.
Let's eat the egg.
Give it a try.
How is it? Is it good?