[English subtitles are available]
You know what that scent is?
Premium floral water for females.
Impossible!
It...
This place it can only be
hair sebum.
How is it floral water?
Staff officer Chen.
Yes sir.
According to the rules,
give him -3 scores.
Please don't!
Chief Song.
How can you be sure it's floral water?
A-a-and
for female?
The service agency my wife work at
sells this floral water.
She uses it herself.
Nobody knows it
better than me.
Enough.
Quit denying
and find out
which female soldier
was in this dorm,
and what happened
on top of that bed.
You know it better than me
how big the trouble is.
Chief Song.
Soldiers are all here.
Don't make things over-complicated.
I'm gonna find out right now.
- Go find it out.
- Right away.
Go.
Niu Mancang!
Yes sir.
Spit it out! Which female soldier was on this bed?
I'm innocent, commander!
It's impossible!
Gu yiye laid on my bed
for a while this afternoon,
and that's it!
Gu Yiye,
You used floral water?
Sir,
I have not.
Then where's the smell from?
Why are you so nervous?
You were not this nervous
when you were at the division HQ.
Are you hiding something?
I, I am not.
Then why are you so nervous?
Sir.
Here's the thing.
- This afternoon.
- Report.
Here's the thing.
The floral water thing...
it was me.
You?
Yes.
Niu Mancang's feet stink so much
that we can't sleep at night.
We don't want it to
affect the hygiene competition.
and I bought some floral water,
dropped some in his shoes,
and tried to cover the odor.
Where did you get the floral water?
Sargent sent me to the service agency this afternoon,
and I bought it there.
Where is it?
It's...
in his cabinet.
Get it.
Yes sir.
Smell it please.
I wasn't expecting
you being so tasteful.
Here's a quote I loved:
It's nothing
to thrive into a big tree in the forest,
but it's pride
in a desert.
Let's do it together.
Be quick washing up after the morning exercise.
There's a formation contest today.
[Who's the hero and who's the brave man? Let's match in the training ground.]
Formation contest is now on
by the unit of company.
Each company
[Training for the outstanding soldiers.]
will choose a squad
representing the whole company.
They will be scored immediately after.
First Company, start!
Right turn!
Double march!
Left, right, left.
Halt!
Goose step, march!
- Not bad.
- Turn left!
Goose step, march!
Halt!
Left turn!
Third Company, start!
Comrade examiner,
Third Company reporting for duty!
Please give order!
Which squad do you choose?
Third Company will ALL participate!
Good.
Start!
Goose step, march!
Left, right, left.
- One, two, one.
- Third Company go! Third Company Prevail!
Third Company go! Third Company Prevail!
Brother.
Under the cheers of female comrades-in-arm,
we won the first prize.
Our comrades-in arms
are like freshly maintained shells,
all ready up.
Time in the new recruit company is intense, but short.
I'm about to join the company,
[Proud of a peaceful motherland, happy for a wealthy society.]
and I feel hard to let go.
♫ Unity is strength ♫
♫ This power is iron ♫
♫ This force is steel ♫
♫ One two three four ♫
♫ Fire upon Fascism ♫
♫ To the sun, and to the freedom ♫
♫ To the new country ♫
Company Commander Zhao.
Thanks for today.
If not for the cheers
of your female soldiers,
We couldn't have won.
You're welcome, Company Commander Qin.
But a victory won by hormones,
is not a true one.
It's not gonna work on the battlefield.
Do you know
what's the advantage of Lu Pingfan?
It's us who won today.
You won for your momentum and unity.
And the shock to the examiners.
But do not be fooled
by such illusion.
Thanks for the advice.
I'm glad you can think in my shoe like this.
We are all training new recruits and learning from each other.
It's our duty.
But you haven't told me
the advantage of Lu Pingfan.
Their pace.
They have a better pace than you.
Their formation
has a trace-less rhythm.
It's cultivated.
Are you saying that
I'm uncultivated?
I did not.
I have something to tell you.
What about we
make a celebration before we join companies.
We're neighbours for 3 months.
Let's say our farewell.
Okay.
Maybe my soldiers will tell yours
about pace and rhythm.
Good.
Go have lunch.
[New recruits company, comrades friendship. Go hand in hand for a bright future.]
♫ The sun is like a golden shuttle ♫
♫ and the moon is like a silver shuttle♫
♫ One for you ♫
♫ and one for me ♫
♫ Weaving a beautiful life together ♫
The whole company is celebrating.
And here I am, cooking for the chiefs.
That Qin the Cannon
must be retaliating good soldiers.
What, now you're bragging
just because they took you seriously?
I'm telling you,
If you didn't tell the company commander
that you've learned from a chef,
he's not gonna drag you here.
Well, I didn't brag about it.
I really did learn from a chef.
In fancy terms,
I'm competent for both military and civilian services.
What, now you mimic my accent?
Keep bragging.
I'm gonna see
what you got here.
So?
Gotta admit, not bad.
That's for sure.
I'm telling you,
our company won the first prize this time
so that
the company commander recommended you.
Don't waste this chance.
I'm just gonna
leave this chance to you guys.
I'm out.
Alright.
Let's bring out the dishes.
All right.
[Never shed tears even for bloody sweat. Never be left behind even being peeled of the meat.]
♫ Always on our minds ♫
♫ It's an ordinary wish ♫
[New recruits company, comrades friendship. Go hand in hand for a bright future.]
♫ May my hometown be beautiful ♫
♫ May the motherland live forever ♫
♫ Listen to the snow and wind ♫
♫ Watch the meteor flying ♫
♫ My heart calls to me ♫
♫ Rush to the turbulent distance ♫
♫ Even if there is disaster after disaster ♫
♫ It can't make us decadent ♫
♫ Let's be friends ♫
♫ We will always have strength ♫
♫ Listen to the snow and wind ♫
♫ Watch the meteor flying ♫
♫ My heart calls to me ♫
♫ Rush to the turbulent distance ♫
The Third Company of new recruits
won the first place
in the queue training evaluation.
This is good.
I'm telling you,
the next time you do this,
I'll count you as cheating.
Even using female soldiers as a shield.
I know.
There were
a couple of other judges
who gave us sympathy points this time.
On the worse side,
we are not strong enough to win.
On the bright side,
we call it
uniting all forces that can be united.
I praised you a few words.
Why are you so proud?
If I hadn't
scored an extra 0.05 points for your squad,
you would never have won the first place.
You are absolutely right.
Wait, wait a minute.
Drinking in the company has a bad influence.
Well, next time, then.
A small amount of wine is fine.
Just a small amount.
That's right! We're not on duty anyway.
A small amount.
All right.
To be honest,
I have always been a little nervous about
male and female recruits being so close.
They are all young and hot-blooded.
I'm afraid something will happen.
When something goes wrong, it's a big deal.
Chief Song,
what do you mean?
In the military,
discipline must be a priority.
But the good news is,
it's almost over.
The new recruits will join the company soon.
Cheers.
Okay, that's it for today.
Leave the heavy stuff to tomorrow.
[Diligent and thrifty, against waste.]
- Mancang, stop it. Go back to sleep. - Yes sir.
Get him!
Turn off the lights.
Where is Gao?
Where did Gao go?
[New recruits company, comrades friendship. Go hand in hand for a bright future.]
The comrades of new recruit company,
how are you doing.
Next,
the new recruit company
to present a song
called the Song of Comrades
Let's welcome.
♫ We are comrades, as close as brothers ♫
♫ The revolution has called us together ♫
♫ You are from the frontier and he is from the mainland ♫
♫ We are all sons of the people ♫
♫ Comrades, we're comrades ♫
♫ We're comrades and we have the same goal ♫
♫ The revolution unites us ♫
♫ We train and study together ♫
♫ We work and rest together ♫
♫ We eat the same rice and raise the same flag ♫
♫ Comrades, we're comrades ♫
♫ For the honor of the motherland ♫
♫ For the benefit of the people ♫
♫ We will fight together to win the victory ♫
♫ To win the victory ♫
♫ We're comrades and we have the same goal ♫
♫ The revolution unites us ♫
♫ We train and study together ♫
♫ We work and rest together ♫
♫ We eat the same rice and raise the same flag ♫
♫ Comrades, we're comrades ♫
♫ For the honor of the motherland ♫
♫ For the benefit of the people ♫
♫ We will fight together to win the victory ♫
♫ To win the victory ♫
By the way,
there's one thing I wonder.
Zhao Hongying's father
is the former chief of
our division commander.
You don't know about this?
Lu Pingfan is chasing her.
You don't know either, right?
Seriously?
Listen to me.
Qin the Cannon.
Don't be such a brute.
You can't just focus on the company.
How can you progress
and win battles
if you don't know anything?
However,
Company Commander Zhao
is helping you today.
I can see that.
You think I'm vulgar, right?
But
that's the way it is.
A little more information wouldn't hurt.
This is not a dish made by old Pickle.
Is there a new chef?
Here's the thing.
Gao Liang always boasted to me that
he could cook big meals,
so today I gave him a chance
to show his cooking skills.
Is it not tasty?
Next time,
I'll let old Pickle make it up to you.
It was Gao Liang.
You wear out iron shoes in hunting round,
must come all not to time-consuming.
A few days ago, Deputy Minister You of
the Logistics Department
asked me
if there were any cooks with better skills.
They intend to transfer two new recruits
to the military authorities.
Well, that's great.
When the new recruits join the company,
I'll take Gao Liang with me.
No, no, no.
You can't do that, Chief Song.
Why?
Gao Liang is not the cooking soldier.
He was temporarily assigned to
make this meal.
Can't he be changed into a cooking soldier?
Gao Liang does not want to be
a cooking soldier.
Revolutionary soldiers are bricks
that should be moved
wherever they are needed.
No.
Chief Song.
Gao Liang's military qualities stand out,
making him a good fighter and
a promising candidate.
You mean,
there's no future as a cooking soldier?
Have you ever asked him
if he wanted to go to military authorities or
the company?
Come on.
Please pick someone else, anyone you want.
Just leave him with me, okay?
Well.
Fine.
I'm not gonna pressure you
with higher authority.
However,
I also hope that you will not
use your thoughts
to crush your soldiers.
It's late,
I'm gotta go.
[No. 1]
Hey, it's me.
Gu Yiye.
Did you ask for leave?
Of course.
That kick you just kicked,
it was powerful
and responsive.
Looks like the three-month-training in the new recruit company
is not wasted.
It's just you're getting less bold.
Why didn't you move at all,
and didn't even hide,
like a rock.
I,
I have something
to say to you.
You were assigned to division headquarters,
and it's harder for us comrades
to meet.
We are both soldiers,
if you don't have any special things,
we don't have to meet.
We won't always be soldiers.
I'll look for chances
to go to the division headquarters to see you.
Becoming a giant tree in the forest
does not mean anything.
Becoming a giant tree in the desert
is something worth being proud of.
That's what you told me,
and I've always kept it in my heart.
It's my goal and motivation.
We'll fight together.
Follow him.
Comrade Jiang Nanzheng.
This is for you as a souvenir.
What is this?
A poem collection I copied.
Just let our friendship
be tested by time,
and let the military
test ourselves.
Yangtze River, Yangtze River, this is Yellow River.
Nanzheng Nanzheng (Conquer South), this is Beizhan (fight North).
It's Gao Liang.
You should go now.
He's edgy, don't let him see you.
Go, go!
- This lummox again.
- Hurry back.
Go go go, he'll be here soon.
Hurry, hurry!
Hurry, he's coming!
Jiang Nanzheng,
I see you.
Did you ask for leave when you came out?
Of course I did.
Why are you here alone?
Watching the stars again?
Aren't you afraid of wild boars?
You're more terrifying than them.
You can read in this darkness?
What book is it?
You won't understand.
I won't understand?
I'm telling you I'm well educated.
Let me see.
You give it back!
Can you reach it?
You can't.
Give me back!
Stop it, Gao Liang.
Give me back.
You're so nervous.
There must be something about it.
Gao Liang I'm telling this again,
we are just common comrades in arms.
Alright.
Do you have a brother?
Why not let me be your brother?
You don't have to hate me so much.
Here's a mango for you.
Keep it.
It's so big.
Smells great.
But...
No but! I'm begging you.
Just take me as your brother,
as a relative of yours.
Whenever I see something delicious, I think about you,
and I want to take it to you.
I was afraid
that this kind of things of bad taste would happen,
and now it happens.
Right under my nose!
Right on you Qin Hanyong's turf.
New recruits in romantic relations.
Oh my goodness.
Why don't you just raise hell?
Do you realize how serious this is?
You know what kind of punishment
you'll be receiving?
Sir,
we are not in a relationship.
Yes, we are not.
I was hoping, you can ask if she agrees.
No.
See, she's not willing to.
What is this? What's this about?
Who are you trying to conceive?
Acting for me?
Sir,
I'm just trying to explain the situation.
I'm not asking you.
I'll get back to you later.
Completely out of line!
[For comrade Jiang Nanzheng. Comrade G.]
To comrade Jiang Nanzheng.
Comrade
[For comrade Jiang Nanzheng. Comrade G.]
G
Gao.
Bad taste.
You wrote all these?
I did.
Chief Song, don't you look down on me.
I'm actually really well-educated.
This is what I wrote to Jiang Nanzheng.
And she won't take it.
I forced her to keep it.
Then she just wouldn't receive it.
I did this all by myself.
She has nothing to do with it.
Gao Liang, you
you shut up. I'll come to you later.
You wrote this?
Fine, come here.
I'll just turn to one random page,
you read it for me.
Yes, sir.
Loafe with me on the grass,
Lose the stop from your throat,
[We're lying on the grassland lazily...]
Not words,
not music or rhyme I want,
Only the lull I like,
the hum of your
valved voice.
Come in.
Chief Song.
Company Commander Zhao.
You are just in time.
Let's admire
what your subordinate did together.
Come on, read.
I mind how once we lay
such a transparent summer morning,
[Remember another brisk morning...]
How you settled your head athwart my hips and gently turn'd over upon me,
And parted the shirt from my bosom-bone...
Oh my god.
The severeness of the situation
is completely beyond my imagination.
Alright, stop it.
Chief Song,
this is Song of Myself
written by Walt Whitman.
It's really classic.
It's from Leaves of Grass.
They are too young,
so they can't express that sense.
You have to forgive them.
Whitman, right?
Whitman!
Even Whitman
can't unbutton other's buttons everywhere.
Right.
Even I flashed!
Em,
Chief Song,
you're familiar with military affairs.
You're experienced in disciplines.
Rest assured,
I and Company Commander Zhao
will investigate the real situation
as soon as possible
and report to you.
If it's really like what you said,
we'll take care of it seriously.
Qin Hanyong,
I trust provosts' eyes.
It's not about your investigation
or reports right now.
Discipline comes first.
This
must be investigated
and dealt with
by colonel office directly.
Jiang Nanzheng, follow me and return to the company.
What are you doing standing still?
Talk to me.
What really happened?
Company commander,
I promise you,
what happened today
has nothing to do with this mango.
The mango is innocent!
No.
[Improve awareness for the assessment which develops abilities.]
You're free to go.
You've got morning exercises tomorrow.
Company commander,
why don't you ask me something?
Ask you about what?
Ask if you are violating discipline,
if you are in a relationship with Gao Liang?
I don't ask you because I believe in you.
[Struck root in the camp]
And,
that soldier named Gao Liang,
he wouldn't have known about Whitman's poems.
So he couldn't have copied it down and gave it to you.
You don't have to tell me who wrote it.
I'm not curious.
But I've got an advice for you,
as a friend.
Boys who like Whitman's poetry
are usually arrogant,
they are outstanding and sharp.
You need to protect yourself
from getting hurt.
The recruit company is about to end.
Military district communications station
has already learned about your recruits.
I recommended you.
So I don't want you
to be affected by this.
Understand?
Go back then.
[Struck root in the camp]
Gao will be miserable this time.
So the training model is a waste.
We don't even know where
we'll be assigned to feed the pigs.
If he goes to feed the pigs, it is the pigs who are tormented.
How can you guys do this?
We are a team.
We've been three months together.
How can you be so cold-hearted?
Who can he blame for?
He can only blame for himself.
Having a relationship with a girl,
and wrote her a love letter.
Being caught with a solid proof.
Not only was he found out,
but he also got Jiang Nanzheng involved.
We are in a military.
A girl
who leaves such a reputation
will have a bad impact on her future.
Do you guys think
Jiang Nanzheng is
really into Gao Liang?
Great.
I can even hear you guys outside the door.
Why are you guys so quiet when the provosts were here?
Now you are talking quite lively.
I'm telling you guys,
all opportunities to go out this weekend are cancelled.
You will be in the dormitory to organize the housekeeping.
You, too.
Gao.
- What?
- Nothing.
What are you guys doing?
Lights out soon. Time to wash up.
Wash up, wash up, hurry up!
- Go to sleep.
What are you looking at?
You know how to start,
but you didn't know how to end it, did you?
How was she?
What the company commander said?
You're the one who caused the trouble, ask them yourself.
Isn't it time for washing up? Where are you going?
Sergeant.
The company commander told him to go to the company headquarter.
Run!
I'm asking you,
how far has your relationship progressed?
Holding hands?
Hug?
Or kissing?
Reporting to the company commander,
you, as a company commander,
you can't insult me.
I confessed it to you
out of trust.
Please respect our relationship.
Our relationship is about mutual appreciation,
mutual encouragement,
and common progress.
Am I insulting you?
And what relationship was that?
Sit down,
did she say she is fond of you?
No.
No?
And dare you say what,
"our relationship"?
Who do you think you are?
Few poems can make you feel awesome?
Sending a book will make you two be in love for a life?
Gu Yiye,
Do you know what the biggest
problem in you is?
Self-righteousness, self-inflation,
Self-interest, pretentiousness.
Company commander,
I think
your eloquence has improved.
I...
Don't be mad.
Go on, go on.
Take your foot bath.
I'm warning you.
This is a serious breach of discipline.
You have to keep your feelings
buried in your heart.
Keep it to you.
Don't go to her.
Expressly forbidden.
This is discipline.
Then I'll ask the chief to explain the situation.
Do you want to torment yourself
or do you want to torment others?
This is a high-pressure line, people who touch it die.
Do you know that?
Does it affect our distribution?
Gu Yiye,
you're so naive.
Distribution is nothing
compared to being out of the military.
I'm telling you,
that girl can say she has no idea of it,
but that poetry,
it wasn't coming out of nowhere.
Think about it,
it's you be the one who take the responsibility,
or Gao Liang.
Where are you going?
I don't want to get discharged,
and I don't want to avoid responsibility either.
Just stay in the army
if you don't want to get discharged.
Be well disciplined in the army.
You so-called intellectual youths,
are so stubborn.
What you gonna do now,
is to take a deep think of it,
ask yourself,
what exactly do you want?
Do you want to be a
good soldier in the army,
or you want that so-called relationship,
vowed romantic relationship?
Or what free-spirited personality?
My dream
it's not just about being a good soldier.
Many people come to the army
to make themselves better,
more tenacious and braver,
more masculine.
But what I'm after is
I was able to make
the army wiser,
stronger, and more powerful through my own efforts.
I will fight for this dream for the rest of my life.
And I know,
what sounds to you
might be really crazy,
I shou'dn't tell you these.
Bu' I'm afraid that you might be worried about me
if I keep it to myself.
Now you had spit it out to me,
I'm even more worried.
[Who knows the dishes food, each grain is hard.]
I have a stomachache.
Give you potatoes.
Sergeant, I have a stomachache.
Let me finish this.
Hurry up.
When you're done eating,
someone comes into the kitchen to help.
Okay.
Let go.
Let go of me!
I have something to say to Jiang.
I have something to say to her too. I'll pass it on for you.
If you dare to go, I will call the class monitor.
How can you be so shameless?
Thank you for the compliment.
Let go.
Sergeant.
Eat some potatoes.
[Saving water is everyone's responsibility]
[Who knows the dishes food, each grain is hard.]
Well,
you stay here to help for ten minutes.
What happened?
Nothing, I'm gonna eat it.
Jiang,
I came to apologize to you.
Why apologize to me?
The people you should really apologize to
are Gao Liang and Company Commander Qin.
I've apologized to company commander.
As to Gao Liang,
I have plenty of time and opportunity to talk to him.
Jiang,
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
I didn't step up and
take responsibility
in the first place.
You don't have to say sorry to me.
You didn't affect me.
And,
We don't have to say sorry to each other.