[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode 19]
Li Qingfeng.
Meeting you
was the best thing that's ever happened to me.
When I first met you,
I thought you were like a piece of wood,
boring and unromantic.
But later I noticed that during every construction project
you seemed to be so gifted in it.
You can always get the best parts of those constructions
fully presented.
You seem aloof and arrogant in usual,
but actually you're a very warm man.
You are different from
any architect I've ever met.
It's lucky for Lin’an to have you.
Only with you here
[Be of Justice, Integrity and Incorruption]
can Lin'an become more and more beautiful.
It's luckier for Xiao to have you.
In this way, the buildings of the Xiao Dynasty
will be recorded in history.
Yet the luckiest thing for me is
having met you.
In every building project,
I could saw a better you.
And that was also lucky for me.
Although
I may not be qualified to be the prince consort,
and His Majesty may not like me,
but I swear
I’m the one
who loves you most in the world.
I will prove it to everyone.
I, Li Qingfeng,
definitely will deserve Princess Zhaohe.
Okay. Get on the boat.
Maybe you should just wait here?
Are you worried about the quality of this boat?
Of course not.
You are the princess.
Just leave it to us.
I am the princess.
It's the reason why I should get on the boat.
Let's go.
Be careful.
In order to test whether this method is feasible,
more people are needed on the boat to increase the total weight.
Can it stand up to the weight?
It definitely can.
You coward!
Let me do it.
Come, Chief Xu.
I'm not afraid of it.
-Be careful. -Okay.
Okay.
Take care.
I'll get on it as well.
Your Excellency, come.
Let's go.
We did it!
Bravo!
We did it! We did it!
Great!
Good job!
Nice!
Come on.
Enjoy your meal.
Enjoy yourselves,
and get drunk.
Good. Come on.
Come on.
Cheers.
Cheers!
Let's get drunk.
Have another drink with me!
Let's get hammered.
Here's to you.
Come.
I...
Qingfeng, here's to you.
Your Highness.
Have some more food.
You're welcome. Come on.
Eat.
It's delicious.
Come, ma'am.
One more.
Taste the dishes.
Come on, bro.
Come.
Your Highness,
I’m here to welcome you back to the palace.
What's the rush?
I'll return to Lin'an tomorrow along with other members of the Wood Feather House.
Then I'll go back to the palace.
Issues in Jinnan are over.
You don't belong to the Wood Feather House anymore.
Come.
Drink.
Don't drink too much.
Brother,
please just give me one more hour.
Just one hour.
Get in.
Then let me go find Luo.
Architect Li,
where's my lady?
She went out with Wang Sheng
and hasn't come back.
That's kinda strange...
I shall thank you.
Take everyone back first.
Where is Langyue?
[Jinnan County Government Office]
Mr. Wang,
why on earth would you bring us here?
Boss Luo is already drunk.
Everyone,
I'm Commander in charge of the Palace Division.
I'm here to inform you that
her Highness
has returned to the palace.
What?
Master has gone back to the palace?
Why didn't she wait for us?
And she will never come back to the Wood Feather House.
Everyone,
your friendship will still remain the same as before.
Take care.
Let’s go.
Wang Sheng, are you kidding me?
Who dares to take Luo away?
I don’t believe it.
She has promised me,
"this time,
neither of us is allowed to escape".
Architect Li,
I know how you feel.
But the princess is the princess!
Sometimes,
she really has no choice.
-Luo. -Luo.
Star.
Moon.
His Majesty wants to get me married to the Northern Zhou.
But I promise you,
I will stay.
I will stay in the Xiao,
stay in the Wood Feather House,
and stay with you.
I will be your deputy architect,
and be
your wife.
Qingfeng.
You can talk with us.
Don't hold it alone.
How about going out for a walk with Niaoniao and I?
Or just you and me.
We can go to Yi Mu Restaurant
to drink and chat?
He won’t do stupid things, will he?
Li Qingfeng!
Li Qingfeng, come out!
If you don’t come out, I’ll kick the door!
I mean it!
Step back.
Each of the door costs 20 tael.
Li Qingfeng,
your skill of coming and going silently
is almost as good as Wang Sheng.
I just went out for a walk.
Why are you doing this?
I'm just worried about you.
Miss Zhao,
did Qingfeng go to you?
I came across him on the street.
He seemed to have lost his soul.
Qingfeng, are you alright?
Now in this yard,
there are only the four of us, right?
Qingfeng.
About Miss Chen going back to the palace,
don't keep it inside.
Just say it out.
I just don't understand
why she left without saying goodbye.
She has already told me everything.
Miss Chen has her reasons.
Everyone can see her affection for you.
So she wouldn't do so without a reason.
Miss Zhao is right.
How about this?
We can turn to Official Meng for help.
Maybe he can get some information from inside the palace.
Qingfeng.
Qingfeng, you...
I wonder how her Highness is now.
[Zhaohe Palace]
Your Highness, I beg you.
Have some food please.
It has been three days since you returned to the palace,
but you have not eaten nothing.
If this goes on...
I won't eat it. Take it away.
Your Highness!
We're begging of you.
We dare not take the food
back to the imperial kitchen.
Please spare us.
Then go feed the dogs and cats.
This...
Enough!
Go tell his Majesty,
it's better for me to stay hungry.
Please spare us.
Slow down, Your Highness.
Or you're gonna choke on it.
Told you so!
Your Highness,
do you think it is really going to work?
I don't know if it will work or not.
But
I must make His Majesty understand my attitude.
I don't believe
he would watch me starve to death.
But His Majesty hasn’t come yet.
Maybe he saw you when you went out to buy the drumsticks?
Mr. Meng bought it from outside the palace
and asked Lord Wang to bring it back.
I don’t think His Majesty noticed me.
Maybe Wang Sheng betrayed me.
I don’t think so.
How about this time
looking for a strip of white cloth for me?
Your Highness, it's not gonna work I think.
Then what else can I do?
If this continues,
Li Qingfeng will think I have given up on our relationship.
Luo,
figure something out
to bring Li Qingfeng to me.
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
Since Princess Zhaohe returned to the palace,
Wang Sheng and Luo have also left.
Now even Official Meng has left.
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
It's now so quiet in the yard.
I'm really afraid that Qingfeng will be broken by this.
Miss Zhao,
I'm afraid this time
you may have to stand a loss.
But I can pay it for you.
No matter what,
I will find a way to pay you back.
What are you talking about?
Although they've left, we can hire new people in.
As for Li Qingfeng,
it can really be tough for him.
Maybe only as time goes by
can Architect Li gradually cheer up.
How have you been recently?
Official?
You came at the right time.
We were just going to you.
I knew it.
You can't live
without me.
What is it?
Tell me.
Of course it's about Her Highness.
Yeah, it should be.
Actually, I also came here for this.
How's Li Qingfeng?
He's not good.
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
My master said...
She said...
My master asked me
to see how everyone is doing.
We are doing well.
How is Her Highness?
You can wait for Li Qingfeng to tell you about it.
Li Qingfeng, I’m here to take you to the palace.
Then I shall go change my clothes.
No need.
I have brought one for you.
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
Wear it.
What?
You think his Majesty summoned you?
Go get changed.
I'm a man.
How can I be humiliated like this?
She can come to the Wood Feather House if she wants to see me.
I will never wear this.
Are you sure?
I feel something is wrong.
Yes.
He still looks handsome in this,
but something is weird about this.
Li Qingfeng, belly in
and bend down.
Yes.
If the eunuchs in the palace
stand so straight like you, they will get beheaded.
Qingfeng, it's no need to be so restrained now.
I...
Remember to make it clear when seeing Her Highness.
Tell her we are all waiting for Luo and her
to come back to Wood Feather House and work.
Why are you humming?
Come on. Practice it.
Go.
Watch your manner.
Let's go.
-Take care, Eunuch. -Take care, Eunuch.
Take care, Eunuch.
The one who solves the problem must be the one who caused it.
I hope everything will be alright.
[Map]
[The Northern Zhou, Kaifeng Prefecture]
Your Highness.
Only you?
Don't worry.
Architect Li's on his way here.
Stinky wood,
He must be angry with me, and wouldn't come.
Yes, I am angry with you.
[Zhaohe Palace]
-I... -You...
Did you encounter any trouble when entering the palace?
Official Meng sent me somewhere outside the palace.
Then Wang Sheng took me in.
No one noticed me.
I called you here
to tell you something very important.
I need you
to face it
together with me.
On the way here,
Official Meng has told me everything.
I've thought about it.
There's only one way.
Which way?
Let's elope.
I can understand if you don't want to.
No.
It's not that I don't want to.
I'm just worried about you.
Have you ever thought
what will happen
if we fail in it?
For my head...
if His Majesty wants it,
then I'm willing to get beheaded by him.
But I can't allow anyone
to take my Langyue away from me.
A marriage for political connection?
The guy's called He Zhigu.
And his real name is Yelü Zhigu.
He's the damn 13th Prince of the Northern Zhou.
Prince of the Northern Zhou?
I know.
On the night of the Zhongyuan Festival,
the last riddle for Li Qingfeng was came up with by him,
"which two characters consist of two persons, three ears and a pen held in a hand?"
And the characters refered to “Ye" and "Lü".
"Yelü" is the royal surname of the Northern Zhou.
So
he did reveal his identity.
But we didn't realize it.
I didn't expect
there was such an episode
on the night of the Zhongyuan Festival.
It was just a coincidence.
Not long after you left,
Li Qingfeng and I
met Miss Chen and him at a lantern shop.
At that time, Li Qingfeng obviously
misunderstood their relationship.
What does the He...
What on earth does this Prince of the Northern Zhou
want to do?
Obviously, he intends to force Langyue to marry him.
This barbarian of the Northern Zhou
claimed to have fallen in love with Master at first sight.
But in fact, he's just greedy for Master's beauty.
He's shamelessly threatening his Majesty to marry my Master to him
with the Northern Zhou's strong military power.
I'm so pissed off.
If I had known it,
I should have instigated Li Qingfeng
to kill him together with me.
We can't do whatever he asks us to do.
Her Highness hasn't said yes to it, has she?
Master has no choice.
Otherwise, how could she leave without saying goodbye in Jinnan?
It must be that his Majesty personally took her away that day.
But...
Can't we just turn him down?
According to my father,
our country made a lot of efforts
into making this marriage a success.
If the marriage fails,
the Northern Zhou will have the reason to invade us.
You have no idea.
The Northern Zhou has been
challenging us near the border these years,
and repeatedly crossed the border line to provoke us.
Its purpose is to invade us.
So his Majesty chose to make peace with them by marriage
because he didn't want the people in the border
suffer from wars,
nor did he want the Xiao thus to get destroyed.
Is the state power of the Northern Zhou
much stronger than ours?
I'm not sure.
You can ask Wang Sheng about it later.
Anyway, now it seems
Master really has no choice.
Wait.
There are so many princesses in the Xiao Dynasty.
Why must it be Princess Zhaohe?
Speaking of this, I'm even more angry.
The damn King of the Northern Zhou
specifically asked for Princess Zhaohe.
Think about it.
It's really an insult for marrying our emperor's younger sister
to his son, isn't it?
I’m so pissed off!
Do you remember the Miss Liu from the Huan Cai House?
You mean Her Highness and Architect Li will also...
No way.
According to Li Qingfeng’s personality, I think he's very likely to...
God, bless us.
It's alright if they elope.
But don't let them die for each other.
[Zhaohe Palace]
Luo, don’t worry.
After I settle down,
I’ll try my best to inform you.
But I still don't want to leave you.
Do you want me to go to the Northern Zhou?
Even if you're married to the Northern Zhou,
I can still stay by your side every day.
But now,
I don’t know when I can see you again.
Silly girl.
In a year or so, if His Majesty still can't find me,
then the marriage will have to be renounced.
Then I'll return back to the palace.
You think he'll really kill me for it?
Of course not.
That's right.
So listen to me.
After I leave the palace,
take the sleeping pill on the table
to sleep for a while,
then I will be free.
By then,
you can just wait for me to come back,
okay?
Luo,
I’m leaving.
Do wait for me.
If you feel bored,
you can go to play Pai Gow [a Chinese gambling game] with Meng Yuanxu.
Anyway,
don't cry.
Don't worry about me.
Okay?
I'm leaving.
Your Highness.
I don't know when I'll return.
But with you by my side,
I can feel at ease.
Do you know where we are now?
No.
Great.
Even you don't know,
then let alone others.
Where are you taking me to?
Somewhere deep in the woods.
Then I'll build a Zhaohe Palace for you there.
I don't want to live in a Zhaohe Palace.
I prefer a Langyue Palace.
Then how about I build you a Qingfeng Lanyue Palace?
Qingfeng Langyue Palace!
Actually, we can keep pressing ahead.
It's cold at night.
Let's rest here.
I don't think they'll catch up so soon.
Please bless us.
Bless Qingfeng and I can be together forever.
Even if having to wander around the world,
I will never regret.
Langyue!
♫The wind stopped in the story of flowers♫
What's wrong?
♫Waiting for people to listen♫
I can't sleep.
Qingfeng.
Do you remember
♫The moon hid in the boundless night sky♫
the first time we met at Miss Zhao's house?
♫Looking for its dreamboat to find♫
Here.
♫I'm trapped in an endless universe♫
Let me dance again for you.
♫You are the starry night sky♫
♫Every single word♫
♫Is never heard but familiar♫
♫Like we have been in chemistry since we were born♫
♫The wind chased the moon for a thousand miles♫
♫Write the most romantic poem of my life♫
♫You are my unexpected scenery♫
♫It's the first time I feel my heart flip♫
♫Not knowing why♫
♫Just let it pass by♫
♫The moon has seen my hair get lifted by the wind♫
♫It also knows what I hope most for the lengthy life♫
♫I have no courage to guess our ending♫
♫From dark night to dawn♫
♫Stars have sunk into the sea♫
♫And I only want to belong to you♫
Brother!
Li Qingfeng, do you admit your crime?
Brother,
it’s not his fault.
It was I who instigated Li Qingfeng...
Langyue.
Li Qingfeng.
I’m asking you,
do you admit your crime?
What did I do wrong?
Princess is about to get married,
how dare you make her escape from the palace with you?
Do you respect the court?
Do you know the Law of the Xiao Dynasty?
May I ask you a question?
Today it's Princess Zhaohe to be married for peace.
Then which princess will be the next one?
Does it mean only by marrying princesses to other states
can the Xiao Dynasty get peace?
Guards.
Yes.
Get Li Qingfeng arrested.
Brother!
Get him executed at noon tomorrow.
along with his entire family.
-Brother! -Yes.
Brother, don't!
You're the princess of the Xiao Dynasty.
How dare you elope with such a rebellious guy?
How inappropriate!
I just don't want to marry Yelü Zhigu.
I've made up my mind.
Stop messing around!
Brother!
Do I have to die in front of you
so that you'll let me go?
Langyue!
Fine!
Tomorrow at noon,
I shall get you, together with Li Qingfeng,
Li Jie's entire family,
your maid [Luo],
Meng Zhongshan’s son,
and that traitor Wang Sheng
all executed!
Go back to the palace.
Your Majesty.
If I agree to get married to the Northern Zhou,
will you spare them?
Langyue!
After marrying you there, wars between the two states will be stopped.
Then there naturally will be a general amnesty.
Okay.
I accept the marriage.
Li Qingfeng.
From now on,
you and me
are done.
Langyue!
[To my Deceased Mother, Madam Ru of Li Jie's Family]
Mom, was I wrong?
I really don't know what to do.
Please tell me.
Qingfeng!
[Memorial to the throne]
Take a look.
If you were me, what would you do?
[Memorial to the throne]
The Northern Zhou has long coveted the wealth of us.
So they've repeatedly provoked us around the border .
People there have been suffering a lot.
If we fight with them,
we can't ignore the Northern Zhou's military force is much stronger than ours.
If we make peace with them, then marriage is the only choice.
And what the Northern Zhou required
was to marry the eldest princess to them.
It's also a humiliation for me.
But I have no choice.
It's not that I don't want to let you go, Chen Langyue.
It's that I can't let go
of thousands of people in the Xiao.
Brother,
I see.
Li Qingfeng is right.
The peace of the Xiao Dynasty
can't always be won by groveling.
So I have decided
the Fengjiang Tower will be rebuilt to revitalize the Three Armies.
Langyue.
I trust you.
So till now,
I have no intention to restrict your freedom.
I even...
hope you can participate in this.
You can just consider it as
my last gift for you.
[To my Deceased Mother, Madam Ru of Li Jie's Family]
When coming to visit my mother before,
I could often find someone had been here.
In this world,
only you and me
still remember to come here.
I'm going back to the Wood Feather House.
So what?
The marriage of Her Highness has been settled.
You...
know everything?
It's spread all over the court.
How can I not know?
Qingfeng,
for the Li family,
don't hold fantasy about Her Highness anymore.
Do you only care about the Li family?
Aren't you a member of the Li family?
I am only myself.
I know
you've always thought
your mother's death was caused by me.
Back then, your mother and I secretly got married.
But in the end, Xu became my wife.
So I could only take your mother as my concubine.
But I had my reasons.
Everything in this world happens for its own reasons.
But I've had enough of your reasons.
[To my Deceased Mother, Madam Ru of Li Jie's Family]
[Ministry of Works]
[Office]
Appointed Emperor, I hold admiration to the former emperor.
Now worrying about the future of the Xiao's military affairs,
and the morale of the Three Armies,
I'm to rebuild the Fengjiang Tower.
Thus this message is sent
to appoint the Minister of Works, Situ Qing as General Architect.
Within seven days since this imperial edict is received,
[Imperial Edict]
the repairing, expanding and building projects
[Office]
shall be completed.
No delay is allowed. That's all!
I, Situ Qing, accept the order and thank His Majesty.
The Fengjiang Tower?
What's it for?
Ask Wang Sheng about this. He knows it.
The soldiers of the Xiao who are going to war
will be examined by the Emperor at the tower.
When they return in triumph,
they will be rewarded at the tower.
So the tower
means a lot to every soldier.
So,
His Majesty is going to fight against the Northern Zhou?
Then Her Highness doesn't have to get married there?
The war will not start for the time being.
Even if the Tower is built,
we still need to train soldiers for a long time,
but Her Highness's marriage can't be delayed for so long.
But since His Majesty has made up his mind,
I believe in the future
we'll have a stronger military force.
Nothing else.
It's just for not being so passive when again meeting this kind of thing.
Wang Sheng, I still don’t understand.
The Xiao has been prosperous under His Majesty's reign.
It's even better than before.
Is the Northern Zhou's military strength
really much better than us?
Since our former emperor passed away,
we've put focus on developing culture and economy.
And military affairs have thus been ignored.
But the Northern Zhou is a country of martial arts,
having built powerful military strength.
Even during the reign of the former emperor, they wouldn't give in.
And our military strength
has indeed been greatly exceeded.
If the Northern Zhou invades us now,
I'm afraid it will be hard for us to defeat them.
It seems that Her Highness
does have no choice this time.
His Majesty ordered the Ministry of Works to rebuild the tower
and get it expanded.
In order to leave no regret,
Her Highness asked to participate in the construction.
This is also her last wish
before she gets married to the Northern Zhou.
Since it's construction work,
can Her Highness do it together with the Wood Feather House?
You still think about making money at this time?
You misunderstood me.
Luo,
can you take me to Her Highness?
But Her Highness said
she didn't want to see Architect Li again.
Luo.
Although she said that,
she didn't really mean that.
There must be some untold words
and unexpressed feelings
between them.
You said Her Highness wanted no regrets.
I think this is the last chance.
I have an idea. Follow me.
I don't know if this is right or wrong.
It's said that the royal family is ruthless.
Now I've witnessed it.
Official!
You have to be careful about what you said.
What am I afraid of?
After Master and Luo left,
my life has been without any hope.
Your affection for Her Highness
is so touching
that heaven and earth can witness it.
Although I have deep affection for Master,
but that's not the kind of affection between lovers.
I couldn't see it clearly before,
but now I can.
Yes.
The person I like is Luo.
I don’t want to lie to myself anymore.
I've lied enough to myself before.
The person I like is Luo.
Not only that,
I’ll also marry Luo in the future.
Good! Official,
I admire you.
Luo is a very good girl.
You must treat Luo well in the future.
Don’t worry.
Even if the ocean goes dry, the rock crumbles, and the whole world falls apart,
I will never let Luo down.
Official!
Love is a matter between two people.
You haven’t asked about Luo's opinion.
Luo,
do you like Official Meng?
I...
-Luo Ye, what do you mean? -Yes.
I like Mr. Meng.
Luo, what did you say?
Say it again.
Official?
You're not deaf.
Why did you ask Luo to say it again?
She will get shy.
Last time...
Stop talking.
Let’s talk about it later.
Okay. I shall listen to you.
Miss Zhao came here
for Li Qingfeng again?
This time, it’s really not for him,
but for all of us.
Miss Chen, think about it.
We've been together for so long.
It's true that your suffering
can't be escaped,
but since we've known each other,
we shouldn't leave any regret.
Just consider it as a perfect ending
for our friendship.
What do you think?
Thanks for your kindness.
On this thing,
you have my words.
Wood Feather House will participate in the construction of the Fengjiang Tower.
Really?
But
there's one condition.
In the future,
please take care of Li Qingfeng.
What do you mean?
You know I like Li Qingfeng.
I also know you like him.
Since I'll soon be married to the Northern Zhou far away from here,
I hope I can help you two get together.