I followed Gordon Ramsay's recipe
for the perfect scrambled eggs.
Oh, thank you. This looks amazing.
Except I cut the tomatoes in half.
The recipe says to saute them whole,
but I once had a patient
who almost choked to death on a...
Oh, my God.
These are perfect.
I'm glad you like your breakfast.
I read that if I made you feel
loved and cared for,
it could help us work out
your insecurity.
Over my friendship with Lea.
Aww, Shaun.
You don't have to do any more research.
I am fine with you and Lea being friends.
But you can keep making
me eggs anytime you want.
♪
DR. REZNICK: You're late.
I made Carly a special
breakfast this morning.
And then she wanted to have sex.
So we did.
That's great, Shaun.
Next time, feel free just
to say you missed the bus.
Women don't like it
when you kiss and tell.
Even though they do it all the time.
Not at work.
Apparently, you've never been
in the nurses' break room.
What were you doing in there?
Delivering the donuts.
Best lesson I learned as a cop,
better to feed down than kiss up.
Oh, it's my fault we
haven't started our rounds.
I missed the bus.
DR. MELENDEZ: It's all right.
I'm glad you're all here.
Because I want to apologize.
Dr. Lim told me she received a complaint
about me playing favorites.
She obviously didn't reveal any names,
but I want to assure you all
that I don't have any favorites.
And if I did anything
to give that impression,
it's my mistake.
It won't happen again.
We're a team.
And we need to be able to communicate
and trust each other
in order to be our best.
So in the future,
if you have any concerns,
you can come to me directly.
Absolutely.
NURSE VILLANUEVA: She got
blindsided, never saw it coming.
Thank God a woman driving by
had pepper spray in her purse,
or the dog would've killed her.
- Brave woman.
- CLAIRE: Loosen the tourniquet.
Oh. Okay.
We need an OR stat. Page Dr. Melendez.
Right away, Doctor.
DR. PARK: And start empiric antibiotics.
I'm gonna guess this dog
wasn't big on flossing.
(CHUCKLES)
On it.
Wasn't that funny.
Donuts. Best 10 bucks you'll ever spend.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Cory's upper trachea never
fully developed in the womb.
His upper airway is totally blocked,
and he has no larynx at all.
The trach tube he needs to breathe
continues to cause reoccurring
infections and pneumonias.
He says it tickles
when you touch his neck.
(CHUCKLES) Sorry.
Not much I can do about that,
but I'll try to make it quick.
Why are you signing?
He's mute, but he's not deaf.
It helps us stay mindful
of what he's going through.
What did he say?
He says when we get mad,
we don't sign... We yell.
And when we play soccer together.
(CHUCKLES)
So keep your room clean
and pass your dad the ball
every once in a while,
and then they won't have to yell.
The good news is his lungs are clear
and I don't see any sign of infection.
Thank God. The better news is
he's a good candidate
for the surgery we discussed.
Yes, it seems a bit experimental.
It's shown great results.
If we can excise the scar
tissue and open up the airway,
he still won't be able to talk,
but he'll finally be able
to breathe normally.
It's a complicated procedure,
but given the severity
of the infections he's been dealing with,
I think it's definitely the best option.
♪
He says he'll do anything
to get rid of the tube
sticking out of his neck.
And you two?
♪
Okay, now you're the one yelling.
We hear you.
What do you think?
Let's do it.
(PARENTS CHUCKLE)
DR. MELENDEZ: Fran?
(EXHALES DEEPLY) Fran, I'm Dr. Melendez.
This is Doctors Park and Browne.
You were attacked by a dog,
almost bled to death.
You remember?
Yes.
We had to repair a severed
artery in your arm.
So, am I okay now?
The surgery went well.
Dr. Park.
We were able to stop the bleeding,
which had caused you to go into shock.
But we still need to go back in,
stabilize the shattered bone,
repair nerve damage,
and do skin and tissue grafts.
But after that?
I'm a firefighter.
I need my full strength.
With plenty of physical therapy,
we should be able
to get you pretty close.
♪
(MRI MACHINE PULSING)
It must be hard for him to communicate.
My friend's 12-year-old daughter
took a signing class at summer camp.
She picked it up pretty fast.
Non-verbal communication
is definitely more confusing.
That's why Carly and I
always talk out our problems.
Sorry to break it to you, Murphy,
but it doesn't matter
how explicitly Carly speaks.
She's saying a lot more silently.
And it's often the opposite
of what she said out loud.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
Why would Carly lie?
It's not lying.
It's communicating indirectly.
Everyone does it,
but women way more than men.
Most of the time, we don't realize it.
That sounds sexist.
You gonna report me to HR
or listen and learn?
Has she ever told you that
she didn't want to have sex
because she had a headache?
No.
And I thought you didn't want
to hear about my sex life.
Fine.
But if you ever get the feeling
she's upset about something
and she insists nothing's wrong,
something's wrong.
♪
Humerus isn't broken.
It's... pulverized.
Who do you think complained to Lim?
No idea.
And we're gonna need internal fixation
with locked intramedullary nailing
to stabilize the fractured pieces.
It must be Morgan.
She's always looking for
a competitive advantage.
Let's focus on the patient.
You can start your
whistleblower investigation
as soon as we're done.
How does she expect us to trust her
if whenever something doesn't go her way,
she just goes to the boss...
It wasn't Morgan.
It was me.
Why?
(SCOFFS)
You're the least
competitive of all of us.
That's not true,
and I didn't do it to help me,
I did it to help you.
If people see you're getting
special treatment,
even if it's not your fault,
they'll resent you.
I'm not getting special treatment.
And I don't need your protection.
Fine. My mistake.
So you can yell at me
or we can get back to work.
♪
Just what the doctor ordered.
- W-W-What?
- You.
I need a double dose of Shaunie, stat.
Glassy is driving me crazy.
What is it with old
people and technology?
Hmm.
Don't worry. I just need
to vent for a minute.
And I'll scram if Carly comes.
It's okay.
I think Carly's not insecure
about you anymore.
Really? That's awesome.
I added the "I think"
because Morgan thinks
women sometimes say the
opposite of what they think.
But I don't think Carly
would hide what she thinks.
What do you think?
Nobody always says what they think.
So...
Morgan's right?
Except for the sexist part?
No.
I think Carly is very in tune
to how you communicate.
If she was unhappy,
I'm sure she wouldn't hide it.
Yes. I agree.
Lunch is over. We have a surgery to do.
Hey, Morgan. Love your boots.
Thanks. Love your sweater.
Thanks.
♪
(WHIRRING)
- (WHIRRING STOPS)
- DR. MELENDEZ: Nice work.
Look at that. On the bone.
Teeth marks.
Must've been a huge dog.
During "no knock" searches,
I was more afraid of dogs than guns.
Gangsters have horrible aim,
but their dogs never miss the target...
Which was our crotches.
Damn. How many times
they get ahold of you?
Never. Another benefit
of martial arts training.
You kicked the dogs?
Like I needed a 60-yard field
goal to win the Super Bowl.
That's awful.
It's self-defense.
Totally.
DR. MELENDEZ: I need
9-oh nylon microsutures.
Next step is to suture in
the interposition graft.
Dr. Park's doing great.
Might as well continue.
I... I wouldn't mind
getting my hands dirty.
Let's see how Park does with this first.
Make sure your stay sutures
are at six and twelve o'clock.
♪
(BELL DINGS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(INDISTINCT TALKING ON P.A.)
You are very efficient.
And you're very clever,
introing your insult with a compliment.
Your "helping me out"
appears to have conveniently
helped you out.
Eh, I was expecting worse.
Melendez is bending over backwards
to avoid anything that might convey
the slightest bit of
appreciation for my work.
Because it couldn't possibly be
that I was actually doing
a better job than you.
Right. You're probably
buying him donuts, too.
I did what I thought needed to be done,
and you're accomplishing nothing
by continuing to badger me about it.
Thanks, Dad.
You're welcome, child.
(MONITORS BEEPING)
SHAUN: The boy's obstructed
cricotracheal segment
looks bigger than what we saw on imaging.
I chose to be aggressive with resection.
Murphy, flex the neck
to mobilize the ends
and reduce tension on the anastomosis.
Are you sure we're gonna
be able to cinch it closed?
Not "we." You.
Step on up.
Four-oh vicryl sutures
on a needle driver.
Place lateral traction sutures
at the proximal and distal airway.
♪
- You all right?
- Yeah, it's just,
I... I hit my finger
with a hammer last night.
I was trying to hang a painting.
Murphy, take over.
It's all right. I can...
Move. You're a surgeon,
not a hockey player.
We don't play through our injuries.
Next time, hire a handyman.
Those fingers are your livelihood.
Got it.
♪
I know Carly says
she's not jealous anymore,
but based on what I saw at lunch,
I'm thinking maybe she should be.
I think Murphy's old enough
to handle his own girlfriend trouble.
I don't have any girlfriend trouble.
That "eating off the plate" move
is the oldest trick in the book.
♪
Lea was hungry.
It looked more like she was claiming
territory than satisfying hunger.
She might as well have peed on your leg.
You, shut up.
And you, keep a smaller gap
between the sutures.
We're gonna need a solid anchor
to get the anastomosis airtight.
That's better. Good job.
♪
- Good work today.
- Thanks.
See you tomorrow at the track.
I, uh...
I... I wanted to talk to you about that.
We can't do this anymore.
It's just a run on a public track.
It's not like we're meeting at a hotel.
(CHUCKLES)
I just shouldn't be socializing
with residents outside of work.
Any of you.
Neil.
I've been going through a tough time.
Our friendship,
having someone I can talk to,
it helps.
I'm not abandoning you.
I'll be there to support you at work.
You've got your therapist.
You're gonna be fine.
This is exactly why women have
such a hard time finding mentors.
No one questions when guys hang out,
but anytime a woman wants to build
a totally appropriate relationship
with a male colleague,
the stupid rumors start.
I agree.
But the rumors have started.
♪
DR. LIM: I'm gonna plug the trach tube,
and I want you to try to take a breath.
Nice and easy.
(INHALES)
♪
(EXHALES)
(CHUCKLES) He says it hurts,
but it's the best feeling he's ever had.
♪
CARLY: What's wrong?
You don't like it?
It's delicious.
I hear delicious, but I see disappointed.
It's not the chicken.
It's my patient.
We fixed his airway,
and he can breathe without the trach now.
That's fantastic.
But he still can't talk.
He can talk.
He just does it with his hands.
Mm, but only with people
who can also sign,
and they have to be
looking at him, and...
Well, could you do
a cadaveric larynx transplant?
No.
I've heard that's worked for
some throat cancer patients.
No, Dr. Lim ruled that out years ago.
The risk of tissue rejection
is too great in a child his age.
Well, could you wait till he's older?
No!
If he doesn't learn to speak soon,
he'll never be able to.
Okay.
I need to do some reading.
Oh, come on, Shaun.
You should at least eat something first.
No. I'm hungry,
but I will do the reading first.
♪
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
You're in early.
(SIGHS)
What's the haps?
Are you serious?
I didn't even know
Michelle Obama was in SEAL Team Six.
Have you ever noticed
how Glassy grinds his teeth
when he's listening to someone talk?
It's like a cow chewing on...
You never used to do that.
Do what?
Eat food off my plate.
I used to work full time
at a place with private chefs.
Now I work part time in a place
with hard-boiled eggs
in a vending machine.
She said it's like
you're peeing on my leg.
You're gonna have to expand on that.
Morgan thinks your body language says
you're trying to assert
your dominance over Carly.
Morgan is one twisted biatch.
Is she right?
No.
Not even close.
I promise you my voice and body language
are communicating the same thing,
which is pure, non-threatening,
platonic friendship.
Shaun?
He also snores.
Really loud.
- Glassman?
- Oh!
I have to go!
♪
(SIGHING) Okay.
(INDISTINCT TALKING ON P.A.)
CLAIRE: Incision sites look good.
And skin and tissue grafts
appear to be taking hold nicely.
We were able to reattach
your bicep muscle and tendon.
That's good to hear.
Can you lift your arm?
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
No. I... I can't.
Because it hurts too much?
It doesn't hurt at all.
I figured that was
because of the pain meds.
♪
You feel that?
No.
♪
Vocal cords aren't the only way
a person can create sounds
with their mouth.
You want the kid to learn
to burp his way through his conversation?
Mm, I don't think it would be possible
to sustain enough air output to...
It was a joke, Murphy.
Oh.
Snoring is a better model anyway.
Soft palate tissue is what vibrates,
making the sound when people snore,
but it's not stiff enough
to replace the vocal cords.
But we could use his own costal cartilage
to act as vocal cords.
The larynx is a complicated
piece of anatomy.
Basically, a tiny musical instrument.
We can remove two of his ribs
to create the anterior
and posterior larynx frame
and then stretch the cartilage across it.
And then cut open a trachea
we worked so hard to close?
We could destroy
everything we just fixed.
Yes.
I think it's worth the risk.
Because you're thinking
the kid's like you,
that he needs to speak
out loud to be understood.
She's right.
The larynx is like a musical instrument.
But if Bo Diddley can make
a guitar out of a cigar box,
I'm pretty sure I can make a larynx
from bone and cartilage.
♪
(SIGHS)
Absolutely not. He's finally healthy.
There's no need to take any more risks.
You're right. There are definitely risks.
But I wouldn't present the option
if I didn't think we could manage them.
Couldn't we just wait
until he's a few years older?
I assume the stronger he
is, the safer it is.
Most verbal language development happens
within the first eight years
of a child's life.
Cory's already 10.
It we wait any longer, he may not be able
to learn to speak, even with a larynx.
He can communicate without speaking.
You're making a big mistake.
(SIGHS) Murphy.
He'll always be... Limited.
It'll be difficult to make friends,
to interact with strangers.
DR. LIM: Murphy. That's enough.
They're aware of their options,
and they've made their decision.
♪
The suture repair looks fine.
Which makes me think
the nerve here got compressed
between the bone and the dog's teeth.
It's too wide a span
to repair with a graft.
What if we built a nerve conduit
out of silicone and polyglycolide?
We could use it to guide
the severed nerve ends
to grow toward each other,
create a pathway for them
to connect and heal.
I'm not sure the nerves
can grow across that distance.
It's definitely worth a try.
We can't just experiment on
her, like a lab rat.
(CHUCKLES) And we can't
just sit back and do nothing.
I'm not saying we should do nothing.
I'm just saying we can't
experiment on her blindly.
Maybe we could use donor
tissue to bridge the gap.
Well, that means putting the
patient on a transplant list.
Who knows how long it would take
before she gets a viable donation?
The firehouse won't hold
her position until she heals.
She'd lose her job.
Well, first, you want to
treat her like a guinea pig,
and now you're deeply concerned
about her life experience.
- You just want to be right.
- And you don't?
Are you gonna step in at any point?
I think Park's idea has
the best chance of success.
Get her prepped.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
Did you really think his idea is better,
or do you just not want to look like
you're biased toward me?
I'm not happy
about this situation either,
but I think you're overreacting.
You better get it under control,
or you're gonna find yourself
watching from the gallery.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
- Hi.
- Hey.
(ELEVATOR DOORS CLOSE)
(ELEVATOR WHIRRING)
Do you have a problem with me
staying friends with Shaun?
I know you've told him
you're fine with it,
but are you?
Yes.
Really?
I mean, I'm totally glad you are.
It's great.
But I'm not sure I would be
if I were in your shoes.
(CHUCKLES)
If it was any other guy,
I probably wouldn't be.
But Shaun, he always tells the truth.
So when he told me that
he's not interested in you,
I believe him.
Okay.
You told the residents not to come to me?
No. That's not at all what I said.
You didn't tell them,
"Next time you have a problem,
come to me directly"?
I was encouraging open communication
and trust on my team.
What I have is a group
of ambitious young residents
who are struggling to figure out
how to be cooperative
as well as competitive.
You're not helping them figure it out
by suggesting they
resist taking complaints
up the chain of command.
I'm sorry you've had to waste
your time dealing with this,
but there really isn't...
Neil, I am not wasting my time.
You do have an issue.
And you've got to stop
pretending you don't.
DR. REZNICK: The incision
is healing nicely.
We should be able to discharge you today.
Are you happy to be going home?
Do you have any questions for us?
Are you sure?
Because you don't really seem
all that happy to be going home.
What is he saying?
He said Dr. Murphy was right.
He does have a hard time
talking to kids at school.
And making friends.
He doesn't want people to ignore him
or act like he's stupid anymore.
Honey, I'm so sorry.
♪
Okay.
♪ May the good Lord shine a light on you
♪ Make every song your favorite tune
♪ Warm like the evening sun
That's two segments from the seventh rib.
Let's close his chest.
♪
(HIGH-PITCHED WHIRRING)
♪ Angels beating all their wings in time
♪ Hah ♪
♪ With smiles on their faces ♪
♪ And a gleam right in their eyes ♪
♪ Whoa, thought I heard one
sigh for you ♪
♪ Come on up, come on up ♪
♪ Come on up now ♪
♪ May the good Lord
shine a light on you ♪
♪ Shine a light on you ♪
♪ Make every song you sing
your favorite tune ♪
♪ May the good Lord
shine a light on you ♪
♪ Shine a light on you ♪
♪ Warm like the evening sun ♪
Reznick, I need you to
secure the posterior surface
while I place PDS four-oh sutures.
Murphy, be ready to suture the graft
into the anterior section.
Morgan realized our patient wasn't happy,
even though he said he was.
If she hadn't been there,
we wouldn't be doing this surgery.
It wouldn't have mattered
what I was able to realize
if you hadn't been so obsessed
about finding a new surgery
to help the patient.
(MONITOR ALARM)
Blood pressure's plummeting.
The field is filling with blood.
I can't see the source.
Murphy, expose the external carotid
and find the superior thyroid.
BP still dropping.
SHAUN: Heart rate is up.
Place a temporary clamp on it, Reznick.
(ALARM CONTINUES)
It's not working. This is venous.
10 blade.
♪
I see what happened.
Left and right jugular veins
are connected by a venous arc
we injured during retraction.
Dr. Murphy, just double ligate
with two-oh silk ties on both ends.
SHAUN: Silk ties.
♪
(ALARM STOPS)
He's stabilizing.
Good job.
Both of you.
♪
Congratulations.
It's not every day you get to
build a kid a brand-new larynx.
It was very exciting.
♪ Was I on your mind? ♪
Those two are getting pregnant tonight.
♪
Yeah.
They should get a room.
So they can make out in private.
(LAUGHS)
♪
Oh, my God. It's Lea.
(CHUCKLES)
♪
She's not getting pregnant.
She definitely uses protection.
Every time one of her
boyfriends would come over,
- she... She would...
- That's okay.
I don't need the details.
♪
Would you ever be comfortable
making out in public like that?
Hmm.
I... don't know.
As a board-certified pathologist,
I think we need to conduct an experiment.
Okay. (SIGHS)
♪ You were in my dream last night ♪
♪ Creepin' in again ♪
♪ When I least expect ♪
Shaunie!
I can't believe you're here!
(CHUCKLES)
♪ Is this what 22 feels like? ♪
♪ Do you feel... ♪
DR. MELENDEZ: 10 blade.
Transverse incision approach
to the brachial plexus.
Adson forceps.
I can assist with ligating
the traversing external jugular branches.
I could divide the omohyoid muscle.
It's all right.
Probably best for me to handle this.
Retracting to the side.
♪
♪ Sister, won't you listen? ♪
♪ I don't wanna love the one who lies ♪
♪
♪ And I can hear him whisper ♪
♪ 'Bout the things you did
in days gone by ♪
I'm sorry. I think we killed the mood.
No!
Mm.
You did manage to wound it pretty bad.
(CHUCKLES)
It's bleeding out.
(LAUGHTER)
Yes.
It's a joke, Shaun.
See, what Carly did was...
I get it.
She anthropomorphized the word "mood"
to make it seem like you hurt it
and it's now hemorrhaging.
It's very clever.
(LAUGHTER)
♪ Can't you hear
that boom, badoom, boom ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom, bass? ♪
♪ He got that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ Yeah, that's that super bass ♪
♪ This one's for the boys in the polos ♪
♪ All your Marcos and the moguls ♪
♪ He could ball with the crew,
he could solo ♪
♪ But I think I like him
better when he dolo ♪
♪ And I think I like him
better with the fitted cap on ♪
♪ He ain't even gotta try
to put the mack on ♪
♪ He just gotta give me that look ♪
♪ When he give me that look ♪
♪ Then the panties comin' off, off, oh ♪
♪ Excuse me, you're a hell of a guy ♪
♪ I... I... Mean, sigh, sickening eyes ♪
♪ I can tell you're in touch
with your feminine side ♪
♪ Oh, yes, I did, yes, I did ♪
♪ Please, someone, who the heck I is ♪
♪ I am Nicki Minaj, I mack dudes up ♪
♪ Back coupes up
and chuck the deuce up! ♪
♪ Boy, you got my heartbeat
running away ♪
♪ Beating like a drum,
and it's coming your way ♪
♪ Can't you hear
that boom, badoom, boom ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom, bass? ♪
♪ He got that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ Yeah, that's that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ He got that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ Yeah, that's that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, boom, boom, badoom,
boom, boom, boom, boom ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ He got that super bass ♪
♪ Boom, badoom, boom,
boom, badoom, boom, bass ♪
♪ Yeah, that's that super bass ♪
SHAUN: It was fun last night.
I'm glad you and Lea are friends.
CARLY: Yeah.
What was your favorite song?
Mine was Whip It.
I have to go.
I have an early morning.
Okay.
I will see you at work.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
You're at 60 meters per second.
Normal electrical signal
velocity of the nerve is 50-65.
That's... good?
Very. The surgery worked.
Your strength might go down a bit,
but you definitely
should get function back.
(SIGHS)
How can I thank you? Seriously.
Well, actually, uh,
it's Dr. Melendez you should thank.
He did the surgery.
We didn't really do anything.
Well, you obviously did something.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay. You're welcome.
Get some rest.
How are you feeling?
Any pain or discomfort?
Good.
If you're feeling up to it,
we'd like you to try to make a sound.
Now, start down here
and just push the air up.
Be gentle.
We don't need you breaking
any wine glasses just yet.
♪
(EXHALES)
(GROANING)
(CHUCKLES)
That's the most beautiful
voice I've ever heard.
It's just a primitive sound.
With speech therapy,
he'll be able to fully speak.
♪
Cory says thank you, Dr. Murphy,
for pushing for the surgery.
This is the best day of his life.
You are very welcome.
♪
(LIGHT PIANO MUSIC PLAYS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
This is not you.
And it's not right.
We can be friends
and have it not be weird.
It's already weird.
I'm not gonna stay.
Well, you don't have to run
away just because I'm here.
I'm not running. I'm being professional.
You're overcompensating.
Trying to play it safe.
And it's... It's hurting things.
It got Park and I in an argument.
That's not how I want to be mentored.
That's not who you are.
At least, it's not
who I thought you were.
Enjoy your dinner.
♪
I'm confused.
One day, you're filing
a complaint about your boss.
The next, you're being incredibly nice
and supportive to your fellow resident.
I told you,
I just felt like Dr. Melendez's
treatment of Browne
was starting to cause
dissension on the team.
I have no doubt that's part of the truth.
I'm guessing the other part was...
Preemptive.
You thought it would inoculate you.
We'd never be able to fire someone
who filed a formal complaint
against their attending.
Which is why I'm so confused.
Why would you feel like
your job could be in jeopardy?
I don't.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Okay.
Just so you're clear...
I won't hesitate
to let you or anyone else go
if I feel it's deserved.
No matter whether they've
filed a complaint or not.
Of course.
I understand that.
Good.
Have a good night.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
♪
Thanks.
Two menus.
♪
(SIGHS)
I'm going to make you
a surprise dinner tonight.
It's a special grilled cheese sandwich.
It's special because it uses
four kinds of cheeses...
Gruyere, Parmesan, yellow...
I don't think that we
should be together anymore.
Hmm?
I can't be your girlfriend anymore.
Did...
Did I do something wrong?
No, Shaun. It's not...
Last night at karaoke,
when you and Lea were singing together,
there was something between you two.
♪
You love her, not me.
(CHUCKLES) No.
N-No.
No.
I don't.
It's obvious.
You're wrong.
You say that.
And maybe you even believe it.
But...
I saw what I saw, Shaun,
and I am telling you,
it doesn't matter what you say.
It's true.
And I think she loves you, too.
♪
♪ This one goes out... ♪
You should tell her how you feel.
♪
♪ A simple prop ♪
♪ To occupy my time ♪
♪ This one goes out to the one I love ♪
♪ Fire ♪