Previously on "The Good Doctor"...
We had the clinic at the hospital.
Come back as President, and...
and we'll re-open it.
We need to go to HR and break up.
I have accepted
your explanation and report.
Thank you.
But I don't believe it.
♪
Traditionally, you don't get to
lead surgeries until fourth year.
That will be changing.
When the right surgery
comes along, it'll be yours.
I want you to meet our new attending,
Dr. Marcus Andrews.
Pleasure to meet you.
You had a date last night, didn't you?
It was hard, uncomfortable, unpleasant,
and I have no idea if she was happy,
and I know I wasn't happy.
♪
[THUD]
I don't like when you do that.
I know.
But I did it anyway
because you need to snap out of it.
The moping... it accomplishes nothing.
I'm not moping. I'm eating.
Which is the only thing
you're doing outside your room now.
You didn't even come out to tell me
to turn down the Talking Heads.
It... didn't bother me.
The walls were shaking.
I'm surprised the cops didn't show up.
You like Carly.
You need to get back in the saddle.
And luckily, you have
a totally awesome roomie
who's here to help you.
I'm not going on any more dates.
Shaun... everyone gets it.
Dating is stressful.
But being alone is worse.
I'm not alone.
I have you. I have Dr. Glassman.
Yeah, friends are great,
but everyone needs a special friend.
I don't.
Shaun...
I'm not like everyone!
♪
No one is like everyone.
We're all unique.
But we're also the same.
♪
[KEYS JINGLE]
I had rent control.
The only way for them to jack the rent
is to get me out,
so they just make up a reason.
Said that I was
playing my music too loud.
And the all-night parties,
the fighting with the neighbors,
the wandering around the parking
lot without any clothes on?
I had a robe on!
And I wasn't wandering.
I was trying to take the trash out,
but they moved the damn bins.
It was windy.
Mom, you were clearly
off your meds and drinking.
Okay.
"Was."
It was a temporary setback.
Okay, nobody's perfect,
but it is all under control now.
People with things under control
don't show up at
their daughter's at 1:00 a.m.
looking for a place to stay.
I will be out of your hair
before you even know.
Two weeks.
Three... tops.
One!
I don't have time
to babysit a grown woman.
Well, it's three weeks
until the end of the month.
You at least owe me that.
No, I don't, actually.
One week.
[SIREN WAILING]
We need some help over here!
Male, 30s, gaping 10-centimeter
laceration to his left cheek.
Probable fractured
temporal bone, maxilla,
- definitely shattered mandible.
- What happened?
He tried to stop some creeper
from groping a woman on the subway.
Maniac ended up bashing his skull
in with some kid's skateboard.
Wheels broke off, and the metal axle...
did that.
Okay, we need to secure his airway.
His mouth is filling up with blood.
Intubation cart.
He has a through-and-through oral defect,
- [SUCTION]
- and the mandible is crushed.
We need hemostats.
The woman?
She's fine.
Cops arrived, tased the dude,
took him away in cuffs.
Everybody's fine except for the hero.
We're gonna need to intubate
through the neck.
Betadine, scalpel,
6-0 tube to place surgical cric.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
♪
[INDISTINCT TALKING OVER P.A.]
Could you do me a huge favor and
take this up to Lim's office?
- Sure.
- I'm running late.
No problem.
Melendez is waiting.
Sorry, I had to help Kellan
with a biology project this morning.
What's in the box?
Ducati throw pillow.
You really think you can
bribe Lim with a pillow?
I'm not bribing her. I'm being nice.
She's starting a new job in a new office.
Where she'll decide who gets
the first lead surgery.
I'm not stupid enough to think
I can influence her decision with a gift.
But it never hurts to have a
good relationship with your boss.
And it's a damn cool pillow.
[COOS]
MELENDEZ: Hey.
No signs of any post-op infection.
There's also no sign
your surgery did any good.
Tom.
How often is he vomiting?
After every feeding.
Okay.
Shh.
This is obviously not
the outcome we had hoped for,
but a pyloric stenosis
requires a cautious approach.
If we're too aggressive...
- [BABY VOMITS, CRIES]
- [GASPS]
It's okay, buddy. I got you.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
[CRYING]
Our baby is in pain. He can't eat.
And you don't seem to have any clue why.
I would be upset, too,
if I were in your position.
But you're wrong.
We need to conduct some tests
to confirm, but I am confident
it's just a matter of going back in
and making a tiny adjustment.
Your son's in good hands.
Thank you.
I'm sorry. I'm just...
A father who loves his son.
You've got nothing to apologize for.
♪
That was impressive.
Get an abdominal ultrasound to confirm
it's just an incomplete pyloromyotomy.
You're wasting your ass-kissing.
First surgery isn't his decision.
No. He's just the one sleeping
with the one making that decision.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
Pupils are equal and reactive.
Do you know where you are?
And do you know how you ended up here?
Josh, you have multiple fractures
in your cheek and jaw,
and a large piece
of your cheek tissue, skin,
and underlying muscle was torn off.
You're going to need
extensive reconstructive surgery
to save your jaw function.
You need to read these consent forms.
And if you have any questions,
write them on this pad.
Was the woman on the subway
a friend of yours?
ANDREWS: He's a fool.
Trying to prove how macho
you are can get you killed.
Clamp the branch
of the inferior alveolar.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
So, you would just stand by?
Let a woman get groped?
Apply manual compression.
Try and close the fracture gap.
You help every homeless drug addict
you see on the subway?
I don't.
And neither does Browne,
which is why she ought not
get so self-righteous.
Yes.
I help my patients
to the best of my ability
because it's meaningful,
and to me, the downside
is purely financial.
For friends, I'll risk a little bit more,
but the only people
I'm risking life and limb for
are my family.
Someone gropes my wife on the subway,
they're gonna get whupped.
This isn't gonna work.
The mandibular ramus
is just too shattered,
and I can't get adequate stabilization.
We can't do any skin or muscle grafts
if we can't fix the skeletal structures.
Alloplastic augmentation
to bridge the gap?
The span is too wide.
♪
We're gonna have to wire him shut.
Wake him up.
He should know he's never gonna talk
or eat solid food again.
♪
_
Forever.
♪
Do you have any questions?
I'm sorry.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
♪
_
[CHUCKLES LIGHTLY]
♪
The Cantrells want a new surgeon.
What can you tell me
about the first surgery?
Is this an M&M review?
Not yet.
Is it possible...
you may have been
a little too aggressive?
Cut too deeply?
Are you really asking me that?
I need to know.
[PEN CLICKS]
I definitely didn't go too deep.
Great.
We'll talk to the Cantrells.
Audrey.
Is this weird for you?
♪
A little. You?
I'm trying not to let it be.
Good.
Me too.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
Hello.
I'm here to pick up artificial
dermal regeneration templates.
Let me get it.
Hey, Shaun.
I heard what happened to the guy.
Sounds horrible.
Is he gonna be okay?
He won't be able to eat
or speak normally ever again.
Thank you.
Shaun.
You seem a bit uncomfortable.
If it has anything to do with our date,
I just want you to know,
I had a really good time...
and hope we can do it again.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
I had... a horrible time...
and... don't want to do that ever again.
♪
Extensive swelling.
But within the acceptable range
of post-op edema.
The very top of the range.
I think maybe Melendez did go too deep,
injured the pylorus.
Well?
The swelling is within
the acceptable range
for a post-op edema.
Got your muffins. Delicious.
I'm glad you liked them.
I did.
Just kinda surprised
you thought I could be bought
with baked goods.
We're not trying to buy you off
with muffins or a pillow.
Someone got me a pillow?
No. I wanted to show you my
support for your promotion.
You're all gonna lead
surgeries... hundreds of them.
So it doesn't matter
who does anything first.
The only thing that matters
is that you do it right.
So, what was in the box?
Sample marketing pamphlets.
My buddy owns a print shop,
asked me to give Lim some samples.
Well played.
But it's all moot anyway.
It doesn't matter who goes first.
Right.
Just so I'm clear,
that "right" was sarcastic, right?
Right.
[SIRENS WAIL IN DISTANCE]
Hey.
Since when does the President
need to stock his own shelves?
When it's a free clinic
and you want it done right.
Thank you.
[WHISPERING] Have you ever
had sex in the office?
I'm not gonna answer that.
First of all,
it's embarrassing if I say yes,
and it's even more embarrassing
if I say no.
I take the fifth.
If we're gonna get married,
I need to know all your naughty...
SHAUN: I brought us lunch.
I know what you each like.
[CHUCKLES LIGHTLY]
Dr. Melendez is not
just our best surgeon.
He's one of the tops
in the entire country,
with the expertise to know
that the best way
to avoid a truly bad outcome
in this procedure
is to err on the side of caution.
- W-We hear all that.
- We do.
And we really appreciate you
taking the time
to explain everything.
But we would just... be more comfortable
having someone else take over from here.
You do understand?
Of course.
I assume you'd be okay
if I perform Braden's second surgery?
Eh... the Chief of the department?
Eh...
Absolutely.
Thank you, Doctor.
Of course.
♪
Nobody likes dating.
It's awkward and uncomfortable.
It's expensive.
Ah. That's why you proposed
after two dates?
To save money?
I proposed after two dates
because after one date,
I realized how much
I loved being around you
and how much fun we'd have together.
He's right, Shaun,
'cause the fun can be so fun.
That didn't happen to me.
[CELLPHONE BUZZES]
I have to go to surgery.
Shaun.
Whenever you're ready, you'll try again.
- What?
- Whenever he's ready?
He's got to go at his own pace.
He needs to be pushed.
I'm not gonna push him.
A man doesn't push another man
into a date.
He pushed you.
Shaun doesn't know any better.
If you want him to find love,
he literally needs to be pushed into it.
Literally?
Shaun's not like other men.
Oh, he easily admits he's wrong?
He easily changes course?
If you don't talk to him,
is anything gonna change?
CLAIRE: No good deed goes unpunished.
Why does it always work out that way?
It doesn't.
Most good deeds get rewarded.
And what do you base that on, Murphy?
Certainly not the news or the Forbes 500.
CLAIRE: Or the Bible.
I base it on neuroscience.
Bad outcomes just implant deeper
in our cerebral cortex.
So, evolution agrees with me.
Our brains encourage us to be selfish.
Yes.
Which makes it strange
that people keep being unselfish.
You were.
You saved my job.
And now you're an attending
instead of the President.
Screws and wire ligature.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
We're not doing this.
We can do better.
There is no other procedure.
♪
We'll invent one.
Truce during surgery.
Fair. What about procedures?
Imaging is fair game.
Anything invasive, we go to our corners.
Crap. I left my keys in my locker.
- Losing my mind. I'll see you tomorrow.
- Night.
[INDISTINCT TALKING OVER P.A.]
CLAIRE: What about a muscle
graft from the temporalis?
That wouldn't address
deep mucosa or bone.
Unless we took
an osseocutaneous free flap
from the radial forearm.
We'd need approximately 2 inches
and could use the natural concavity of...
And he could lose the use of his hand.
That seems like a reasonable trade-off.
I'm not telling this guy
that we can restore his speech
and all it'll cost is his hand.
Because he's a hero?
What he did has nothing to do with it.
It's what we can do that matters.
What we can do is what we were doing.
That's the protocol.
Aren't we risking more damage
by leaving him in an ICU bed
while we try to invent a new treatment?
How about attaching two free flaps
on vessels on either side of his neck?
Heard from Claire you're having
an all-hands-on-deck sesh.
Happy to join.
Good. How about Park?
He left.
Said he had a thing with his son.
Thankfully, I don't have kids,
so extra hours... not a problem.
Have you considered an
allograft augmentation or a...
Heard y'all were working late,
so I got some coffee.
♪
Any way I can help?
[CLEARS THROAT]
MELENDEZ: I want to talk about
our meeting with the Cantrells.
On date night?
Can it wait... 10 1/2 hours?
I guess.
Thank you.
Have you ever been to The French Laundry?
No.
We should do a weekend in Napa.
I know this great little B&B
just south of St. Helena...
It's not about the Cantrells.
It's about what you said to them.
Has it been 10 1/2 hours already?
I "erred on the side of caution."
Caution is a good thing.
Err isn't.
I didn't err... not at all.
I was going to bat for you.
I think that maybe you're so afraid
of appearing to favor your boyfriend
that you're overcompensating.
Given I think you may have erred,
I'd say I was incredibly supportive.
In which case, you went against
your better professional judgment
to favor your boyfriend.
So, I'm too supportive
or not supportive enough?
Should I change the reservation
to two tables for one?
♪
I've had plenty of first dates
that were actual disasters.
Took one woman to a Coyotes game,
saw four minutes of it,
spent the rest of the night in the ER
while she got 17 stitches
after being hit by a puck.
We got married eight months later.
Then you divorced her.
It was worth it.
♪
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
We don't have a choice.
Evolution needs us to propagate,
so it gives us a shot of happiness
every now and again
to suck us in like idiots.
[SCOFFS]
To keep us in a game
that we know we're gonna lose
almost every time.
Because the upside's like...
nothing else.
Love.
But if Shaun really
doesn't need to play, then...
good for him.
We've officially turned into
an episode of "The Bachelor."
Everyone go home.
I'm not tired.
I am.
No.
There are still
a number of possibilities.
Murphy, you are smart
and you're creative,
but there are things you can't do.
You can't do miracles.
You can't fix the unfixable.
♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS DEPART]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[LOCK CLICKS]
[KEYS JINGLE]
[SIGHS]
Hey, baby.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
You work way too hard.
Yes, I do.
Uh... let me get you something to eat,
'cause I made some pulled pork
and some peanut coleslaw.
No, thanks, Mom.
Did you find a place?
I saw one, but it was nasty.
Y-You must be hungry.
You saw one,
and then you came home and cooked?
Yes.
I came home and cooked dinner
for my daughter.
I'm trying, Claire.
Okay, I'm taking my meds.
I'm seeing Dr. Donovan.
I am doing my best.
♪
I've heard that before.
You got six days.
♪
[SIGHS]
Shaun, you need sleep.
Your neurons will be sparkier
in the morning.
There are 640 muscles
and 206 bones in the body,
but only 284 and 72 of those
are of sufficient size for our grafts,
but that still leaves
20,448 possible permutations.
It's not unfixable
until I rule out every...
So, some anatomy problem,
you won't give up on,
but after one date,
you think you've explored
all the possible permutations?
Stop distracting me.
I'm distracting you?
By talking about you?
By talking about love?
Yes.
I... I need to concentrate.
Okay.
I'll shut up.
You're still talking.
Good night, Shaun.
You're still...
We only have 206 bones?
- Still talking.
- Oh...
[SIGHS] Yes.
♪
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[LOUD KNOCK ON DOOR]
CARLY: Shaun?
I think we should talk.
So did Lea.
But I have to find a solution
for an oromandibular defect
that doesn't involve titanium plates,
356 of our muscles, or 134 of our bones.
I don't think you never want
to see me again.
I have to find a solution
for an oromandibular...
We have to talk.
You owe me that much.
Why do I owe you that much?
Because I thought we had a nice time.
And I thought you were a nice guy...
an honest guy...
and I still think you are,
and I'm confused about how you feel
and about how I feel about how you feel,
and I just need to talk about it.
So, if you have any feelings
for me at all,
you'll help me understand.
♪
[SIGHS SHAKILY]
Okay.
My little sister, Andie, has autism.
We're not all the same.
I know.
I think growing up with Andie
helps me understand you.
But it also makes me wonder about myself.
And did I date you to prove something?
Did I date you to...
somehow make things better for Andie?
I don't think I did, but...
♪
My point is...
I have questions, too, Shaun.
♪
Trying to figure out what we want
and why we want it and is it good for us
are good questions.
And they can't all be answered
over one dinner.
♪
I have to go.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
♪
Murphy...
I've... I've got it!
I've got it!
We take a vascularized free flap
and suture it
to the facial artery and vein,
then flip up the pectoralis.
♪
It's a great idea.
We're not doing it.
It's never been tried before.
Risk 1... graft failure brings infection
and he loses the other half of his face.
Risk 2... sepsis and he dies.
Risk 3...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, risk whatever.
We do the standard procedure,
the guy never speaks or eats again.
Dr. Murphy, could you please
give us a minute?
Why do you want to do this?
You've been my boss for a few hours,
and you're already
questioning my motivations?
You fell on your sword for Shaun,
and your reward for your act of heroism
was getting fired.
And now you're back here,
answerable to me.
I imagine you've been asking yourself
if it was worth it.
[EXHALES SLOWLY]
♪
Your issues with the procedure are valid,
but at least let me put them
before the patient.
He'll say yes.
I won't sugarcoat the risks.
He'll say yes anyway.
He wants to believe things will work out.
That's why he's a hero.
Sometimes the hero loses.
Which is why he's got to learn
when to stand back
when there's nothing he can do to help.
♪
Are you going to order me to stand back?
No.
♪
[INDISTINCT TALKING OVER P.A.]
Hey, Shaun?
You got a minute?
Okay.
[SIGHS] Debbie wanted me to talk to you.
To tell you...
not to give up on love.
Don't give up on love.
Okay.
Do you want me to let her know
you told me?
Yes, please.
[SIGHS]
Hey, Shaun?
I know this, uh, dating thing
can be scary.
You're good at dating.
Well, before Debbie,
the last time I went on a date,
"Wake Me Up Before You Go-Go"
was the big hit.
'Cause a-a-after Maddie and the divorce,
I kind of shut down for a while.
Yeah, I... and it felt better
to be in a place
where I couldn't get hurt.
But then, last year, I got my diagnosis,
I thought I was gonna die,
and Debbie came into my life,
and I said to myself,
"I-I-I don't want to be safe anymore."
You know?
I want to... I want to...
I want to feel alive.
And... And if I get hurt, I get hurt.
That's part of the deal.
Morgan says it's biological,
that it doesn't make sense.
Morgan's right.
So I'm right?
No. No.
Look, i...
it's wonderful, this love thing.
Why should it make any sense?
When I think about the reasons
I-I'm in love with Debbie,
okay, she's... she's kind, she's funny,
she's... she's loving.
But that's not it. Not really.
[CHUCKLES] Don't tell her this,
but there are other people in the world
that are kinder, that are funnier,
that are more loving than she is,
but she makes me happy...
just being around her.
It makes absolutely no sense,
but I wouldn't trade it for anything.
♪
Okay.
I have an ethical dilemma.
I was going through state regulations
for medical staff...
specifically, residents...
and their new guidelines
have raised an issue for me.
The state caps residents
at 80 hours a week,
but I don't think that's nearly enough.
I work over 100, and I don't
plan on cutting back,
so I'm wondering how I should be
reporting my hours.
Park offered to co-write a paper with me.
[SIGHS] What a suck-up.
I said yes.
It's an interesting case.
It should be written up.
So he's...
Gonna do a lot of work for nothing.
Except for the good
of the medical community.
And I'm gonna tell you what I told him...
if you come to me with one more favor,
one more humblebrag,
if I suspect either of you
have your lips puckered,
you're going to the bottom of the list.
Yes, ma'am.
[WATER RUNNING]
[WATER STOPS]
Dr. Lim?
Do you ever think about what it means,
me doing all this?
Means you've underestimated me.
Maybe.
But it also means that I care.
That getting the first surgery
means something to me...
enough for me to go out
and really overspend on designer desserts
and then to spend even more time
trying to make them look homemade.
If I'm putting that much effort
into muffins,
imagine how hard I'll work
to make the most of this opportunity
if it's given to me.
♪
[DOOR OPENS]
With considerable
physio and speech therapy,
this graft would allow you to not
only chew and swallow whole foods,
but it would enable you to talk again.
_
It's an untested procedure
with not-insignificant risks.
CLAIRE: If the graft doesn't take,
more skin and bone could become infected,
possibly necrotic.
[STYLUS TAPPING]
_
We need to know you understand.
It's an experimental procedure.
In addition to all of
the usual surgical risks,
there are all of the unknowns...
bleeding out, permanent graft loss,
stroke...
death.
♪
_
Good for you, Josh.
Get him prepped.
♪
Okay.
LIM: Infuse carbon dioxide.
♪
Grasping duodenum
just distal of the pylorus.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
♪
Huh. Look at that.
That's not good.
Page Dr. Melendez.
An intussusception.
The telescoped bowel
is causing a blockage.
The baby had two unrelated
conditions causing the same symptom.
We only know about the second condition
because of the first surgery.
Treatment protocol is a barium enema,
but not for someone Braden's age.
An air enema might work.
Unless the intestine's torn.
- [BEEP]
- Morgan, reposition the scope
to get a better look
at the intestinal wall
around the intussusception site.
There's too much swelling
and edema to be sure.
With the risk of infection,
we don't have time to find out.
You're gonna have to open him up.
You should.
The Cantrells made their wishes clear.
Well, that's when I made them
think you'd erred,
which you did not...
not on the side of caution...
not at all.
We do the surgery together.
Who's the lead?
I think you know.
Pulling rank?
Absolutely.
As Chief of Surgery, I designate you.
ANDREWS: It's like a puzzle.
You secure to the artery,
then the vessel just won't quite
stretch to the vein.
CLAIRE: You could mobilize
the recipient vessel.
Repeat that, Dr. Browne.
Mobilize the recipient vessel
to create more slack.
You saw Carly again.
How was it?
Inconvenient.
But despite her intrusion,
I was still able
to concentrate on medicine.
That wasn't an intrusion.
That was a date.
It was walking.
Walking with someone you like
who likes you, too,
is a non-date date.
Some of the best dates that I have had
did not involve flowers
and restaurant reservations.
Just...
sharing a bag of chips
and sitting on a couch.
ANDREWS: Secured.
Remove clamps.
Blood flow to and from graft.
Let's move on to the pectoralis flap.
- [MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY]
- Blood pressure's dropping.
Okay. Heart rate is up.
Push IV fluids,
give epinephrine 1 milligram,
then start a drip.
There's intestinal wall perforation.
Repairable?
[SIGHS] There's too much tissue damage.
Infection?
No sign of peritonitis,
but we'll need to remove
this section of bowel.
[ALARM BEEPING]
- He's tachy.
- Hypotensive.
Push vasopressors and antibiotics.
- [MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY]
- Check an iSTAT hematocrit, ABG.
Give two units PRBCs.
I don't see any major bleeding.
Push more fluids, start an inotrope.
Check all vessels we worked on
for clots with the Doppler.
Okay.
♪
Large clot in the carotid.
Clamps back on,
performing carotid arteriotomy.
Will try to aspirate out the clot.
Stand by with heparin.
[BEEPING CONTINUES]
♪
Carotid clot removed.
[BEEPING CONTINUES]
♪
[BEEPING SLOWS]
EEG looking good.
[SIGHS]
Resuming pectoralis flap dissection.
Good work, everybody.
♪
ANDREWS: Go ahead... say something.
Yeah, you can talk.
Maybe not too much at first...
give the jaw a chance to heal.
♪
[HOARSELY] Thank you.
[CHUCKLES LIGHTLY]
♪
On behalf of all of us,
you're very welcome.
The woman who was being accosted
when you intervened is here.
Is she all right?
CLAIRE: She's not here as a patient.
She's been... waiting to see you.
Okay?
Hello.
Hey.
I am so sorry this happened.
Me too.
You look...
When the swelling goes down,
he'll look a lot better.
It's okay.
My face was never my fortune.
What made you do it?
Why did you step in?
♪
I don't know.
You needed help.
♪
Olivia, by the way.
Josh.
We'll let you two get acquainted.
♪
It didn't matter who got
the first lead surgery... to me.
But it's recently
been brought to my attention
how much it might mean to some of you.
Seems I'd forgotten
how important this decision is
when you've been
dreaming about it for years.
You're all excellent candidates,
each deserving,
and will all get your turn.
Starting with Dr. Browne.
Yes!
Thank you.
[DOOR OPENS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- Congratulations.
- CLAIRE: Thanks.
What the hell was that?
I was happy for a colleague.
You weren't campaigning for you to win.
You were campaigning for me to lose.
Do you dislike me that much?
I just wouldn't want you supervising me
as Chief Resident.
You'd be a nightmare of a boss.
Shaun.
Dr. Lim thought my motives
for fighting this hard
for this patient were miscalculated.
She was right.
We shouldn't have saved his face?
We have limited resources,
and we're even more limited
in our personal capacity
to determine who is deserving,
so we make a choice
to treat everyone the same.
So why did you treat
this patient differently?
Because I was angry.
I made a sacrifice to save you.
I lost my job,
I took a substantial demotion.
And I thought I was a fool.
The cost was way too high.
I resented you, and I...
kind of resented the universe.
But today...
...you made me proud of my sacrifice.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Very few things
that are worthwhile in life
come without a cost, Shaun.
♪
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
This is tricky.
I feel like we were just tested
and both of us failed.
♪
But...
we'll get better at this.
♪
BREEZE: Hey, honey.
I'll make you a plate, and you
can take it to your room.
Thanks.
I saw three more apartments today.
One was kind of nice,
but it's not ready
until a week from this Tuesday,
which puts me over your deadline
by three days.
No.
Three days? Come on.
You can stay here.
For a little while,
until you're a bit better.
But you have to stay on your meds.
And keep away from other drugs
and alcohol.
I'm testing your urine every two days.
Don't miss any appointments
with Dr. Donovan.
Can you live with that?
[SQUEALS, LAUGHS]
♪
Do you have a couch?
♪ You held the balance of the time ♪
♪ That only blindly I could read you ♪
♪ But I could read you ♪
♪ It's like you told me ♪
♪ Go forward slowly ♪
♪ It's not a race to the end ♪
♪ Well, you look like yourself ♪
♪ But you're somebody else ♪
♪ Only, it ain't on the surface ♪
♪ Well, you talk like yourself ♪
♪ No, I hear someone else, though ♪
♪ Now you're making me nervous ♪