- Okay.
- [LAUGHS]
Okay.
[SCREAMS]
[TRACK CLACKING]
Okay.
[SCREAMS]
[BOTH SCREAMING]
[SHOUTING]
[PANTING]
- [LAUGHING]
This is terrifying!
[BOTH SCREAMING]
[LAUGHS]
- Oh! Oh!
- And very fun!
- [SCREAMS]
♪
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
[SMOOCHING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Are you ready
to try lying down?
Because I am ready, Shaun.
I am very ready.
Carly...
Mm.
600 thread count
microfiber sheets.
A shredded
memory foam pillow.
A 40-watt A19
incandescent bulb.
[SWITCH CLICKS]
♪
[CLEARS THROAT]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[SIGHS]
♪
I'm sorry.
You didn't return
my calls this weekend.
After a ride
up Skyline Boulevard,
60 minutes of Muay Thai,
and a 15-year
reserve Scotch,
I had a moment
of clarity.
What you said about my
objectivity in the Fields case
wasn't about me.
You were in pain.
I was taking
responsibility.
And asking you
to take your share.
It was a good
surgical plan.
You need to accept that,
despite being
a gifted surgeon,
you are fallible.
I think I should run my
procedures by Glassman
from now on.
Audrey, we need
some checks and balances.
I am checked
and balanced.
♪
And I'm the chief
of this department.
You will continue to run your
medical decisions past me.
♪
ANDREWS: Browne,
you're with Melendez today.
Murphy and Park, meet me in
the E.R. observation unit in 20.
I thought I was on E.R. consults
with Park today.
If I'm being bumped because
I took off the other day,
Dr. Browne
was every bit of...
First lead surgery.
Thank you.
Scheduled for tomorrow.
Study the images
and prep your patient.
[DOOR OPENS]
Yes! [LAUGHS]
I rock, I rock!
The surgery gods know it,
I know it,
and apparently,
so does Andrews.
Boasting doesn't have
the same impact
when you're picked last.
He was obviously waiting for
the right case to come along.
No.
You're kidding me.
This is much better
than my first surgery.
Damn right. A med student
could do an appy.
The carotid endarterectomy
takes serious finesse.
Fair to say it's really
a 5th-year procedure,
but I don't have time to sit
around debating semantics.
I have the Holy Grail of
resident surgeries to prep for.
♪
[DOOR OPENS]
The tumor was found
on my left lung
at my medical fitness exam.
Tricky spot.
Curable,
but tough to remove without
taking the entire lung.
That's what they said.
And you didn't like
that answer?
I need my lung.
I'm going to the moon.
♪
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
ANDREWS: When did
the chest pain start?
Around 9:00 this morning.
Okay, I'm gonna look
at your heart.
This gel may be
a little cold.
You see a cardiologist.
Did you use
the nitro he prescribed?
It usually relieves the
angina, but not this time.
Are... you
the same Rosalind Elion
who just published a study
on IDH2 Inhibitors
in Myeloid Leukemia
in the Journal
of Pediatric Oncology?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
You're famous.
W... I-I used an IDH2
on a kid with AML.
- I mean, he's doing great.
- Oh.
Your studies revolutionized
leukemia treatment.
It's an honor
to meet you.
That's kind of you to say.
Noticing anteroapical wall
motion abnormalities.
Is your chest pain
worsening?
Yes. How did you...
[INHALES SHARPLY]
She's having
a heart attack.
Contact her family,
then meet us in surgery.
She needs
a triple bypass.
♪
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
- [MOUSE CLICKS]
- The moon?
The moon.
In 2020.
It's a private venture
partnership with NASA.
Floating in an expanse
of uninhabitable emptiness
200,000 miles
from the nearest Starbucks...
- Mm.
- ...not for me.
You never wanted to be an
astronaut when you were a kid?
Had enough challenges
here on Earth.
Did you?
- I was a Trekker.
- [LAUGHS]
All my friends
had Spock ears.
I was all about McCoy.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
There's our tumor.
It's embedded
in the hilum.
NASA doctor was right.
We'd have to take the entire
lung to get it out.
Not necessarily.
The tumor's grown
into the upper lobe.
If we can remove it
from the main bronchus,
we can get
a clean margin.
The rest of the lung
can stay.
No-go.
You'd have 80% of your...
If treatment reduces
my lung volume at all,
I'll be unfit
for space travel.
The mass is too deep.
Major blood vessels,
your airway, esophagus,
and heart
are right there.
The next opinion you get
will be the same.
Or worse.
Thank you
for your time.
♪
[GASPS, SIGHS]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
♪
[PILLS RATTLE]
What do you see
at the apex?
I see perfusion
abnormalities.
Her LAD and PD
are completely occluded.
She listed her husband
as her medical proxy.
You'll need to update him
as soon as he gets here.
The entire left side of her
heart is compromised.
He's not coming.
They've been divorced
for two years.
He hasn't spoken to her
in almost that long.
Murphy, anastomose the internal
mammary to the LAD.
Let's see if we can give
her heart a blood supply.
I tracked down her sister
in Santa Cruz.
She hasn't seen Rosalind
in years, either.
That's a lot of legwork
for a surgeon...
no social worker
available?
It's good that
you didn't find anyone.
Family members are the least
qualified people in the room
to make
medical decisions.
Judging by the state
of her myocardium,
there's only one choice,
anyway.
She needs a new heart.
♪
I think it's possible
to spare her upper lobe
using
a surgical robot.
Wren Braxton
came to see me.
You're her second opinion?
Or fourth
or whatever she's up to?
I'm surprised you didn't offer
the robotic option.
It's the type of surgery
I usually send your way.
I didn't offer it
because with the robot,
if I nicked
her pulmonary artery,
she'd likely bleed out
before I have a chance to
open her up to control it.
She's just
gonna keep looking
until someone gives her
the answer she wants.
And then what?
What do you think her odds
of survival are
if some hack tries
to cut the tumor out,
leaving the lungs intact?
Roughly zero.
I agree.
And with you?
With the robot?
Still lousy.
You can do this.
You're overestimating the risk,
and I know why.
And you're doing exactly
what you did last time.
Assuming that
I can do anything.
So everyone else is biased
except for you?
The one who just had
a patient die on him?
If it's had any effect,
it's to make my judgment
more acute.
I won't risk
having Wren leave here
the same way
that Patty Fields did.
People risk things
to make their dreams come true.
If you don't want to help her,
I'll do it myself.
♪
PARK: The intra-aortic
balloon pump
will support your heart
until we find a donor.
And when might that be?
SHAUN: A heart is the most
difficult organ to procure.
But since yours
is so badly damaged,
you are very high
on the list.
I suppose that's a good thing.
Not really.
The...
We're doing
everything we can.
Thank you.
PARK: Is there anyone
you want us to call?
Yes.
[BREATHES SHALLOWLY]
My lab assistant.
The next few days
are crucial
to my monoclonal
antibody study.
Hannah needs to stay with
the cultures around the clock.
[GROANS LIGHTLY]
I don't want five years of work
to go to waste.
Can I ask why you listed
your ex-husband
as your medical proxy?
I had to name someone.
Leo is the only person
I ever discussed
my medical issues with.
Now, if you don't mind,
I have a lot of work to do,
which, as you've indicated,
I may not have
a lot of time to do it.
♪
[PEN CLICKS]
[PENCIL SCRIBBLES]
How are you, Shaun?
These are
STAT cardiac labs.
I have to go.
I hope you're not embarrassed
about last night.
I want to have sex
with you.
That's nice.
I think about it
very often.
Even when I'm supposed to focus
on more pressing matters.
Like 15 minutes ago
when I was filling out
that lab requisition,
I almost forgot to add
a BNP.
That's good.
No, it's not.
We need a BNP
to monitor her cardiac function
on the balloon pump.
I've been thinking
about you, too.
Sometimes
when I shouldn't.
- That's bad.
- Not really.
I've been doing
some research.
I came across this therapy
psychologists use
to treat phobias.
Apparently, it works
in people with autism, too.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
If you're game,
we could try tonight.
I'm game.
♪
MORGAN: I need
a different first surgery.
There a problem
with your patient?
The plaque dissection
is too advanced
for a third-year resident.
I was nervous as hell
for my first surgery.
And it was only
a tonsillectomy.
I could take out a pair
of tonsils blindfolded.
It's not nerves.
This is more like
a fifth-year procedure.
You're setting me up
to fail.
This is why I picked you.
You come to me scared,
and you couch it in arrogance.
It's rare that a resident
has what you have...
the aggressiveness,
the work ethic,
and talent
to be a leader.
I'm not setting you up
to fail.
I'm setting you up
to shine.
Or am I wrong
about you?
No, sir.
[CHUCKLES]
♪
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[EXHALING SHARPLY]
I want you
to do my surgery.
The one
Dr. Lim suggested.
It was Dr. Lim's idea.
She's an excellent surgeon
and my superior.
And you think
I'm an idiot.
I am afraid
of this surgery.
And I'm afraid
of going to the moon.
It's not about
the moon.
It's about the fear.
It's about
getting beyond that.
That's how
great things happen...
how they've always
happened...
because someone
took a chance.
From what I've read
about you,
you're exactly the kind of
person I need in my corner.
Exactly the kind
of person
I would've thought
would understand.
Fear is also
what keeps us alive.
[SIGHS]
What do you think
the odds are
of you not coming back
from the moon?
The reason it's heroic,
the reason it's exciting
is because you don't know
what to expect.
You can't anticipate
everything.
1%, 2%, maybe 5%.
60%.
This surgery,
if I were doing it,
there is a 60% chance
that you die
on the table.
It's called
exposure therapy.
We'll lie down on the bed
side-by-side,
fully clothed and not touching
for 15 seconds.
When this timer goes off,
you'll go into the other room
for a three-minute break,
and then we'll go again
for 20 seconds.
Over time, we will progress
to longer intervals
and start to
lie closer together.
This seems like
a good approach.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Whenever you're ready.
[TIMER BEEPS]
♪
[HEARTBEAT]
[EXHALES]
♪
[TIMER CHIMES]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Are you okay?
What...
What are you feeling?
I... I... I don't know.
I don't...
I don't know.
I don't know why
it didn't work!
It's okay, Shaun.
We'll try again.
No! No.
No... No, I can't.
W-We'll try for less time.
I can't do this!
♪
Go.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
What?
Go.
Get outta here.
We can watch
the end...
I got the sheets,
[SNIFFLES]
The pillow,
the damn lightbulb.
I read
18 psych journals.
And you give up
after eight seconds?
You're right.
This isn't going to work.
♪
Go home.
[FOOTSTEPS FADE]
How are things with Carly?
I lasted eight seconds.
She kicked me out
of her house.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
First time is difficult.
I'm sure she didn't...
We tried timed exposure therapy
to get physically closer,
but I...
couldn't do it.
[CHUCKLES]
So try something else.
When I lie close to her,
I feel diaphoretic,
my heart rate is elevated,
and mouth gets dry.
I don't know how to
not feel that way.
You want this, Shaun?
Yes.
Very much.
Then rely
on your strengths.
Treat it like
a surgical problem.
Do your research.
Carly came up with
a solution, it didn't work,
but that doesn't mean
the next one won't.
[DOOR OPENS]
Give me some good news.
I had a potential donor
in San Diego,
but the heart
was just too damaged.
I'm at
the GE junction now.
Now she has complete
right-sided failure, too.
It's time to discuss a DNR.
She's got one day left
in this world.
Let's keep her comfortable.
♪
60%?
That number
is grossly exaggerated.
I spent an hour
convincing my patient
I'm not trying
to kill her.
She came to me.
I gave her my surgical opinion.
I... I could fire you
for this.
Because I contradicted
your opinion
after you contradicted
my opinion?
I gave her an option
you were too afraid to present.
No, you proposed
a potentially deadly surgery
to a woman
who was desperate
for any option,
no matter how crazy.
- You don't have the authority...
- Authority?
I thought we were talking
about the patient...
It was unprofessional,
disrespectful...
- I don't...
- If anyone showed a lack of respect...
Doctors.
My office.
♪
[MONITOR BEEPING]
I wouldn't want to be
kept alive on life support.
Not if there was no hope
for a recovery.
There wouldn't be.
As your heart failure
worsens,
you may get short of breath
from fluid build-up.
We can use diuretics
and vasodilators
to help control that.
I recommend
both of those.
Of course.
Yes.
If that doesn't help,
we could insert
a catheter in your chest
to drain the fluid.
The procedure does risk
a lung puncture,
which would worsen
your symptoms.
You should give us every option
to keep you breathing easy.
And we'll be on call
all night
to make sure you're
as comfortable as possible.
Thank you.
I went through this
with my mom
when she was dying
of leukemia.
I'm so sorry.
Was that recent?
I was 10.
I remember feeling
so helpless...
You should reach out
to Leo.
[SCOFFS]
It's too late.
I don't believe that.
♪
There were, uh,
things between
my wife and I
that I thought
we could never get past.
But last Christmas...
...we almost lost
our son.
And when I reached out,
Mia was there.
Leo...
always made me feel
pressured to choose
between my research
and him.
Eventually,
I realized he was right.
So I chose to go
- where I was needed the most.
To call him now would be
hypocritical and...
unfair.
It took a lot of time
and dedication to push
our understanding of leukemia
as far as you did.
I'm glad I have treatment
options for my patients.
You made a good choice.
♪
[SIGHS]
Sorry to keep you
waiting.
I assume that some of this
is professional,
the other 90%
is personal.
Am I right?
Well, it's a very
difficult case.
We're both
just overly invested.
Actually, I'd love for you
to weigh in on this one.
Dr. Lim, are you confident
in the surgical plan?
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
You didn't even look
at the case.
- The pulmonary...
- Dr. Lim is my Chief of Surgery.
I trust her judgment.
I'm sorry things
got out of hand.
It won't happen again.
It better not
happen again.
If you two can't control your
interpersonal squabblings,
I'm gonna have to lose
one of you...
at least.
♪
We need an endoscopy suite
to fetch the spoon
out of this guy's stomach.
Cool.
How's the intimacy research
going?
Dr. Elion has had
a very successful life
without a relationship.
So can I.
Success and happiness
aren't the same thing.
You need to decide what will
make you happy in... the end.
I don't know if it's being
a great surgeon
or being close to Carly.
But I'm better at surgery
than I am with her.
Dr. Elion is wrong.
You don't have to choose.
I fly to Phoenix
every other weekend
to spend time
with Mia and Kellan.
Then you won't be great
at either.
I think Dr. Elion
is afraid.
I think it was never
about the journals
and the lives
she could save.
I think she's always
been afraid...
afraid she might
lose Leo
just like she lost
her mother.
And you,
you lost the person
you loved the most
when your brother died.
Your elevated heart rate,
sweaty palms...
they're not about
your sensory issues, Shaun.
It's what we all feel...
fear.
W-Why would anyone
want to feel afraid?
Because the thought
of ending up alone is scarier.
♪
I don't think Dr. Elion
refuses to call Leo
because it's hypocritical.
I think she's afraid
he won't come.
Can you handle the spoon?
Yes.
Okay.
- Good morning, Dr. Glassman.
- Morning.
Which shoulder
would you like to hurt
for the next 24 hours?
I'm not here
for a vaccine.
Okay.
Wrist and thumb joint pain.
I need cortisone shots.
Surgery's in two hours.
Can I ask you something?
If a patient...
say, a violinist
who concertized
three or four times a week...
were to come to you
with achy joints,
would you give
them a cortisone shot
or tell them
to lay off for a while?
[CHUCKLES]
Better question...
if he or she came to you
with achy joints
and pretended they needed
a vaccination,
what would you do then?
It's...
[INHALES DEEPLY]
It's because
I wanted you to know
and no one else.
[DOOR CLOSES]
I saw a rheumatologist
last month.
I have
rheumatoid arthritis.
Wow.
I'm sorry to hear that.
My... My mom had it, too.
It... It destroyed
her wrist and finger joints.
LIM: Maybe I should leave
St. Bonaventure.
Berkeley's chief
is retiring this year.
I could apply
to replace him.
We're entitled to have
differing opinions.
We can argue...
Apparently we can't.
♪
I love you.
I want our relationship
to work.
And I want to be chief.
If we can't find a way
to work together
with me as your boss,
then something
has to change.
Looks like
you caught it early,
without any noticeable
erosion of the joints.
That's good.
What's your D-MARD dose?
20 milligrams,
but Dr. Baxter
just [INHALES SHARPLY]
started it.
Okay.
You're gonna
have to postpone
your first lead surgery
for a while,
see how you respond.
I-I'd have to explain why
to Andrews and Lim.
As you should.
A cortisone shot
is just a temporary fix.
Do you know what
the chances are the D-MARD
can maintain
the dexterity you need
to perform an operation
in the long run?
45%.
I-It'll change
the way they see me.
Yeah,
you have a condition...
a medical condition.
They'll expect less from me.
They'll be looking
for me to fail.
Th... That's why I'm confiding
in you instead of them.
You advocated for Shaun
when everybody else thought
he couldn't be a surgeon.
I'm sorry, you're comparing
arthritis to autism?
I'm comparing
people's assumptions,
people's prejudices.
I'm asking for a chance
to prove myself.
In this surgery today,
you're gonna have to create
a plane as thin as paper
between two delicate
layers of tissue
without disrupting the major
blood flow to the brain.
If you miss by 1/10th...
1/10th of a millimeter,
the patient will suffer
permanent brain damage or worse.
♪
Right now,
it's a matter of pain,
not function.
You think I would put
a patient's life at risk?
That's insulting.
I'm sorry.
Without the pain,
I can do this.
You believed in Shaun.
I need someone
to believe in me, too.
♪
Okay.
Leo Adan?
That's me.
I'm Alex Park.
I'm Rosalind's doctor.
She's dying.
She wants to see you.
Then why didn't she call me?
Why'd she send you?
She doesn't know I'm here.
Even when we were married,
I never topped her to-do list.
She wasn't
cheating on you.
She wasn't doing anything
except saving lives.
She deserves
to be cut a little slack.
Yeah.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
She was saving
the whole damn world.
She's a saint.
I made partner, she wasn't
there, everybody understood.
My mother died, she wasn't
Well, I didn't.
[SIGHS]
Look, maybe I was a selfish jerk
for wanting my wife to be around,
but I did.
She didn't send you.
Good for her.
She's not a hypocrite.
At least that hasn't changed.
♪
Assistant port
is secured.
Load the forceps
and electrocautery.
[MACHINE WHIRS]
♪
My chief's doing
a difficult surgery.
I'm here to help
in any way I can.
♪
Instruments are ready.
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
♪
[MONITORS BEEPING STEADILY]
Time of initial incision,
11:32.
♪
- How is she?
- She's really short of breath.
I gave her vasodilators
and diuretics,
but she's not settling.
[GASPING]
[MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY]
She has bilateral
pulmonary edema.
She needs 40 milligrams
of furosemide.
I'll push two
lorazepam, too.
[WEAKLY] I can't...
c-catch... my breath...
You've got fluid
in your chest.
This medication should help
ease your breathing.
She should be improving,
but she's not.
Maybe we should insert
a drain.
[BEEPING CONTINUES]
Shaun, this isn't about
the fluid.
She's scared.
Rosalind,
I know
this is frightening,
but you are not alone.
I'm here, and I am not
going anywhere.
As long as you need me.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[BEEPING CONTINUES]
♪
Leo.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
♪
[BEEPING SLOWS]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
♪
I see the base
of the tumor.
There's a lot of bleeding
teasing off the pulmonary vein.
Put a bipolar electrocautery
instrument on the right arm.
It's way more friable
than it looks.
The tumor's invaded
the vessel wall.
I need to load
more hemostatic matrix.
If I keep going, I'll end up
with a bleed I can't control.
♪
I need to take the lung.
Prep her
for an open thoracotomy.
♪
I need
a prostatectomy kit.
Now.
Prostate cancers tend to grow
along the surrounding nerves.
The equipment's designed
to dissect the tumor
without injuring
the nerves.
Substitute arteries
for nerves,
and you've got
our situation.
♪
Load the hot shears.
Unclamp the proximal
and distal end.
You have good shunt flow.
Loupes.
[MONITORS BEEPING]
Forceps and dissector.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
♪
Is there a problem,
Dr. Reznick?
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
♪
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Nice work, Dr. Reznick.
[SIGHS]
♪
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Did you...?
We got it all.
And you'll still need
that flight suit.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Thanks, Doc.
He might've helped out
a little, too.
The tumor was more entangled in
your arteries than it appeared,
but Dr. Melendez pulled off
a remarkable win for us.
This is the reason you still
have two complete lungs.
♪
Sign it.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Both of you.
I'm gonna leave it
on the moon.
♪
NURSE PETRINGA:
She's very close.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
♪
[BEEPING SLOWS]
[FLATLINE]
♪
I'll pronounce her.
I'd like to do it.
[FLATLINE CONTINUES]
♪
[VOICE BREAKING]
Thank you.
♪
I hope it's not too late.
It's fine.
Come in.
You were right.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
That was a crazy surgery.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
But not as crazy
as I thought.
It wouldn't have even happened
if it wasn't for you.
You were right, too.
I'm not objective
when it comes to you.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
I blew off your
concerns about the risks
'cause I thought
you'd lost your mojo.
Great.
We're both right.
And we found a way
to work together.
And our patient's
better off for it.
Today.
What about
the next time?
We won't make
the same mistakes.
I'm not sure
they were mistakes.
I think they might have
just been our nature.
♪
I don't think
I can give you
the unconditional support
you deserve from a partner
and the objectivity
you need from a chief.
And...
I don't want
to give up on my dream.
I love you.
But it's not enough.
Goodnight, Neil.
♪
[RAIN FALLING]
Dr. Reznick.
Dr. Glassman.
Thank you
for your support.
My pain is 90% better
than it was.
The shots helped.
Well, you did
a remarkable job.
♪
I'm fine.
Congratulations.
♪
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[LOCK DISENGAGES]
I did extensive
further research
on intimacy treatment
for autism.
And?
And...
I found nothing.
You were right.
Exposure therapy
is the most effective option.
You're very smart
and thorough.
Thank you.
I'd like to try again.
♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TIMER BEEPING SOFTLY]
[TIMER CHIRPS]
♪
It's time to
take a break.
I know.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
This is terrifying.
♪
And...
very nice.
♪