My Dear Brothers
EP11
You haven't eaten for 200 years,
and you ate stinky tofu for the first time.
Are you okay?
Hou Chi
It's spicy, right?
Have some water.
He ate such spicy food,
and you give him hot water.
Doesn't it work?
Of course.
Go get some ice. Hurry up.
Come on.
Okay.
Listen to me, you two.
It's okay to be in the same room.
But there are some rules.
Firstly,
no sharing a bed.
Secondly,
no physical contact.
Thirdly,
sleeping with the window open.
Open the window?
Why?
I noticed that
the window of your room
is facing the window of my room.
Keep the window open.
And if this guy is up to something,
you shout aloud and I'll hear you.
What?
Loser.
Do you want to fight again?
I think I need to say it again,
Shi Xia's brother is me.
How we get along
is none of your business.
What can he do
since you've made such spicy food for him?
I should warn him,
what if he wants to...
what if he has unkind thoughts to you?
Bro
What are you looking at?
I'll look at it with you.
Time flies.
What can we do?
I think Miss Shi Xia
is very nice.
What do you mean?
Do you think I have a crush on her?
There's no shame in that.
Even if Shi Xia is the disciple of Yuhua Sect,
but what does it matter?
We're from Devil Sect.
There's no need to follow the pedantic rules.
Me,
the great Devil Lord.
Yeah.
You are the Devil Lord.
Are you not worthy of a disciple
of Yuhua Sect?
No, No.
Now, it's Hou Chi and her.
Do you forget?
You've already beaten Hou Chi.
Why are you worried about him?
If Hou Chi had any sense,
he wouldn't have stopped his sister
from dating you.
I can't explain it to you.
It doesn't matter if you can't explain.
Our old rules.
Scrambling.
We Devil Sect have so many ways to do.
Even ten more girls,
let alone Shi Xia,
are a piece of cake.
Scrambling.
They are coming.
You are up?
Did you have a sound sleep?
Did you?
What are you going to do now?
Yesterday I was rude.
I apologize to you both today.
Hosted by the Devil Sect,
we would like to invite you
to visit the Otherworld Town.
Food, drink and fun are all on us.
No need.
Listen, if you don't want to go,
it doesn't mean Miss Shi Xia doesn't want to.
Yeah.
Miss Shi Xia
I have been sniffing around.
There are so many delicious food
and fun things in the Otherworld Town.
Husppy
Do a good introduction.
Okay.
As is known to all,
the Otherworld Town has a history
of more than 2000 years.
But this year the Otherworld Town is particularly bustling.
Look.
And listen.
Shouting.
Why?
Because of His Majesty.
For 2000 years, we Devil Sect never take
the test for the head of the Immortals Alliance.
It's the first time ever.
The first time?
Here comes the Devil Lord.
He is gorgeous, elegant, rich...
Rich but young.
Get to the point.
There is a restaurant named the Great Hotel.
They launched a blessing feast
specially for the test of the head of the Alliance.
Therefore,
I wonder if you would
do me the honor of tasting it?
There are 108 dishes,
bringing together the featured food of Immortals Alliance.
Hou Chi
You don't have to eat,
but you can't starve your sister.
I don't want a blessing feast.
Now I get it.
Sister shows duplicity again.
Okay. Let's go to the Great Hotel.
-Let's go.  -Very good.
Come on.
One small step forward,
one giant leap in life.
Come on.
Let me lead the way.
Come on, sister.
It hurts so much.
Sister
Sister, don't cry.
Do not cry.
I'm holding your hand.
You won't get lost.
Let's go.
No, what are you doing?
It's safer to hold sister's hand.
Wait a minute.
You two have such a touching relationship.
Count me in.
Come on, let's go our separate ways.
Welcome, Devil Lord.
I booked the whole place today.
Help yourself please.
Just be my guest.
Come on, come on in, come on in, please.
Here we are.
Husppy
I'm here.
Go ahead and make the arrangements.
No problem.
The Great Hotel is famous for its featured food.
I heard the food here is very strange,
including man-eating plants that can swallow a sheep,
and flying thorn melons.
I want to check it out, too.
What is the purpose
of the Devil Lord's invitation today?
Well, you can tell.
An old saying goes,
It's often your opponents who know you best.
Tell you honestly,
I have one lifelong regret.
A year ago,
I lost my sister.
I looked around,
I've been all over the world,
but I still couldn't find my sister.
Shi Xia
I mean Shi Xia and my sister look alike.
I almost thought she was my sister.
Do you understand?
No wonder you hit it off with Shi Xia.
(Of course.)
(Shi Xia has been my sister for 19 years.)
But Shi Xia is my sister.
You lost your sister
and you should focus on your sister, not mine.
(Shi Xia is clearly my sister.)
(You're the one who focused on my sister.)
You're right.
Your sister's back.
My sister's gone.
You should know
what it's like to lose my sister,
right?
Even if it's only half a day away from my sister,
I'm tortured inside.
(Don't say that in front of her real brother.)
The Otherworld Town is my last hope.
If I can't
find my sister here,
I might as well give up.
You can't just give up.
If you want to find her,
I will do everything in my power to help you.
Thank you.
Sir
I need you to find me some girls later.
The best kind of girls.
What? Find some girls?
Yeah.
We don't do that at the Great Hotel.
You're looking in the wrong place.
Get out.
You got me wrong.
I want to find a girl as a sister.
Understand?
Not really.
Fine.
I want you to know this for sure today.
Do you understand?
Sure, sure.
Hou Chi of Yuhua Sect is as good-looking as Pan An.
He is tall, gentle, and handsome.
Devil Lord Qiu Ping is as good-looking as
Song Yu.
He is young and rich.
This is good.
No.
Everybody
Hou Chi of Yuhua Sect and Devil Lord Qiu Ping
are eating at our restaurant today.
Any girls who want to see them?
Here, here.
Once every ten immortal coins.
Only ten immortal coins.
Even 20 immortal coins are acceptable.
Aren't we here for a big meal?
What is this?
Contest for sister selecting.
Contest for sister selecting?
It is.
What sister selecting?
For whom?
Come on, sit down, please.
It's about to start.
I'm helping you test your step-brother.
Don't worry. It's fine.
The first one.
She is beautiful with fair skin and long legs.
Is she beautiful?
What do you think of her?
She is pretty,
and as elegant as hibiscus.
I think she is good.
Shi Xia, what do you think?
She is plain looking without charm.
Score.
You are out.
The second one.
She looks like a flower.
Actually, she's got more on her mind
than you do.
She's both dignified and graceful,
like a bright peony.
I think she's good.
Peony?
You compare her to a peony
with a face like that?
Hou Chi
You don't have a good taste in selecting sister.
Score.
The third one.
The third, the third.
God.
Although the lady is not very beautiful,
she has a good figure.
All right, time's up.
You may be excused.
Gosh.
I'll give you 20 more immortal coins.
I'll watch them a little longer.
Come on. Watch me. Come on.
You?
Go away.
Watch me.
Next...
My turn?
As for this girl,
do you also think she's good?
This girl has a round face
and big eyes.
I think she is worth considering.
So in your opinion
anyone with a round face and big eyes
can be your sister, right?
What's wrong with that?
Of course.
There were 153 girls today,
and you approved 153 times.
Did the Devil Lord think
that none of the 153 girls
could be a sister?
Of course not.
Do you think it is a joke?
As long as it's a girl, you think she's good.
I gotta go.
It's not done yet.
Distinguished guests, here's your food.
The dish is called Birds Pay Homage to the Phoenix.
It's is the specialty of our restaurant.
It looks like
superficially,
the phoenix accepts the worship of the birds.
But in fact,
the birds are for the phoenix's selection .
Cut it out.
Get rid of this dish. It's not good.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
This is a good dish.
We just have to choose one out of a hundred.
Hou Chi, what do you think?
Exactly.
You.
Here comes the dish.
This dish is called Two Dragons Playing with a Pearl.
The pearl
is a dragon's favorite.
Two dragons like the pearl at the same time,
and fight for it.
It's a good dish.
The script is very realistic.
It shows the heart of the dragons.
Fight for what?
Did the two dragons ask the opinion of the pearl?
Another dish.
This dish is called the Leaping Carp.
Thousands of carp
tried to leap and survive.
But only one succeeded.
This dish is the grand finale dish
of the blessing feast,
which has a special meaning.
All right, you're hopeless.
There is only one who can leap over and survive,
and that must be me.
Enjoy your meal.
But don't give up.
Wait for another 200 years,
and I will not fight with you for the next head of the Alliance.
I have made an agreement with my sister
that I must be the head of the Alliance.
On the field, I never give in.
Give in?
I want you to be clear.
Did you give it to me last time?
I did it on my own merits,
the halo of the hero,
and the belief of the Chosen One.
It's different this time.
I have the Heart of Guardian.
Didn't you just get a sister?
Can you promise that your sister won't leave?
Come out with me.
She means you.
You.
I need to talk to you.
Go ahead.
What?
It's not your first day being my brother.
You've been so secretive all day.
What's wrong with you?
You've really wronged me this time.
Did I?
Have I ever wronged you?
You did it more than once.
Since my childhood,
you've driven away every male in my life.
I'm your real brother.
I have an obligation to protect my innocent sister.
I'm not innocent.
I have acute eyesight.
I saw clearly.
It was safer to hold sister's hand.
I signed a brother-sister contract with Hou Chi.
You think I want to be
the sister of that idiot.
Good. You don't want to be his sister.
And you are not the must for your idiot step-brother, either.
What did you say?
You can't tell
after the whole day?
I can tell.
I can tell you are not with kindness.
You are really stupid.
It totally proved that
Hou Chi is a bad brother.
Anyone can be his sister.
Think back today's contest.
Hou Chi gave every girl a pass.
What does that mean?
It means that in his mind
any woman can be his sister.
He grew up in the Yuhua Sect.
He is very simple.
He probably didn't want to
hurt the self-esteem of girls.
Simple.
You really hit the nail on the head.
Hou Chi lives in the mountains all his life
and never sees the world.
He never meets other women
except you.
Suddenly he has come into the real world,
and seen all kinds of
attractive girls.
He has plenty of choices.
Yeah.
He recognized a sister for practicing and being the head of the Alliance.
It's the same with anyone.
There is no condition
for an elder brother to be nice to his sister,
regardless of her figure or temper.
What we care about
is unbreakable blood ties.
Believe it or not,
I'm more reliable than your step-brother.
You'll see.
Nature.
Master, take your time.
How beautiful.
Hurry up.
I can't hold on.
Sit down and take a break.
Sit down and have a rest.
Are you stalling for time?
I'm not.
If you don't believe me,
you can just go.
Anyway, if Hou Chi doesn't listen to you,
don't come to me.
The umbrella has gone for so long.
I don't know if Hou Chi is ready.
Master
You all sit down and rest for a while.
Have a rest.
It hurts.
-Who are you?  -It hurts.
Qing Feng, pick that one for me.
Okay.
You...
You wanna die?
What are you doing?
My elder brother Zhen Shanhu...
W... What are you doing?
What did you give me to eat?
What did you...
Amazing.
It stops hurting.
What a skillful doctor.
A highly skilled doctor.
Guys
Throw a banquet in the base
to thank our skillful doctor
and his friends.
It's fine.
It's a piece of cake for me.
But Zhen Shanhu,
you and your brothers are supposed
to be bandits?
You...
What do you mean?
You should stay where bandits are supposed to be.
I...
Send them to court.
Don't you really want to take a detour and send them to court?
It is the duty of a fairy family to punish the evil and promote the good. Master.
I don't care.
I'll go first later.
Master Lord, please do not worry too much.
After all,
Yi Yaogua is always with him.
Yaogua follows
the lead of him.
Nothing serious will happen.
Sir, I'm sorry.
I just missed a dish.
This dish is called Hang by a Thread.
It is a collection of eggs laid by 21 kinds of birds
from the nearby Sacred Mountain.
Hang by A Thread.
I need to help Devil Lord choose his sister quickly,
before he sets his sights on Shi Xia again.
Let's start.
Sister was right.
This should be done quickly.
Yeah, we do it quickly.
Don't call me sister from now on.
It's fine.
Just pick a sister.
Hang by a thread.
Sister seems to be angry again.
As a real brother, I can't recognize my sister aboveboard,
I won't let the step-brother off.
Husppy
Please welcome contestant No. 154.
This sister is a master.
Although the girl does not show her real face,
her dancing is better than anything.
She is as quiet as a shy flower,
as dynamic as the weak willow in the wind,
as beautiful as a peach in spring,
as clear as a chrysanthemum in autumn.
I think she's great.
Don't you just want a new sister?
Let me help you.
Brother.
Brother?!