Senior brother
Why are you here
It's a good thing I caught up with you
Going to the shrine is such a fun thing
Can you still not call a senior brother
Senior brother
You'd better go back the same way
In case something bad happens to you
That's what I did
I won't feel at ease in this life and the next
You can still remember me in the next life
It's worth it
Senior brother
I know your name is Yi Yao. Take the test
Is also trying to help me
Or do you know me best
It seems that I didn't recognize you as a bosom friend for nothing
It's a brother who is beautiful and kind-hearted
Otherwise, I won't become friends with Houchi
What a good friend
Senior brother
Actually, I've been curious about one thing
You and Houchi are so different in character
How did you become friends
Remember that time
I just learned that I have no spiritual roots
Bi Hong
You have no spiritual roots
You can't learn
Chi Er
Bi Hong, is this your instrument
Head Childe
What a big shelf
Don't be too cruel
Show me your instruments
We'll let you go
Show and show
Bi Hong
Bi Hong, he really jumped
Bi Hong Bi Hong Bi Hong
Bi Hong
Go and tell the master quickly
Good
Brother, brother, where are you
Posterior cistern
I'm here
If you see the fairy umbrella hold your breath
Convey your heart to it
I-I can't
Don't go
Back pool, I'm under the cliff of the back mountain
Brother, brother
Did you arraign me with a fairy umbrella
I can also control the fairy umbrella
It's really the back pool. He told me
There is a difference between having spiritual roots and not having spiritual roots
He also told me
It seems that there is no spiritual root
It's not that bad
I can't think of this wood in the back pool
I was a warm man when I was a child
But
The fairy umbrella he gave me
I lost it a few days ago
It hasn't been found yet
Lost
Yeah, I lost it in Xianmo Town
How come you've seen it
No
I
Senior brother
Time and summer
Don't be afraid in summer
Stay where you are, brother. Come to see you
I can't find the entrance now
How did you take the way
Report to your Majesty
The dark forest seems to have an enchantment
Subordinates have not cracked
I'll go by myself
Brother
Dark forests are dangerous
You can't go alone
Brother
You wait for me
Your Majesty, pay attention to safety
Senior brother
Time and summer
Posterior cistern
Why are you here
When did you come
Are you awake from the wine
Sister, I'm fine
You still think of me as a sister
Of course
It was you from beginning to end
Actually
I said that the other day for a reason. I
Sister
No need to explain
But my words hurt so much
You must have broken your heart
It doesn't hurt. I'm not sad
Really
That's good
Let's go and find the senior brother together
Don't
Why
I just want to be with you
We have to find the brother quickly
Just walk out of the dark forest together
Why rush for a while
Why is there no hurry
We still have to talk to the Lord God
I'll give you the qualification for re-examination
You don't even know
Your master is going to eat me alive
Master is also good at exams
It's not as important as you
I just want to be with you
Every minute and every second
There is no outside interference
There is no dispute between immortals and demons
Just the two of us
It's a spirit tree
The spirit tree has come back to life again
Sister
I want to be with you
Be with you forever
But we shouldn't do this
Why shouldn't things in the world be
Come with me in summer
What about the leader exam
Do not participate
What about the brother-sister contract
It was agreed that you would take the leader exam
And take me home
Cancellation of contract
Don't leave me
Time and summer
You're not the back pool
Houchi can't ignore the brother-sister contract
No desire, no error
If there is nothing wrong, there is no intention
I see
The dark forest stirs up people's delusions
You can't get out of the dark forest if you can't get out of your delusions
Senior brother
You wake up
You don't care what you see
That's all your delusion
We're in a dark forest
Brother, let's go over there and have a look
Good or not
Good
Brother, we will live here
I don't care about other people's fingers anymore
Isn't it good
Brother, you are going to fall off the cliff
Senior brother
You wake up
You're about to fall off a cliff
Man lives all his life
Why pursue those things that you can't ask for
Isn't it enough to have me by your side
Go
Brother, brother
Seek such happiness
I am willing to die
Senior brother
I'm tired
I know I have no spiritual roots
But I never gave up
My father has been pushing me for 200 years
Let me be a mortal
Go to the days of ordinary people
But I just stubborn don't want to give up cultivation
But I just found out today
You can only be happy if you accept your fate
Senior brother
Do you remember
My life is up to me, not up to heaven
Yeah
We are going to see the Lord God now
I don't just have to ask Houchi for a make-up exam qualification
I also want to ask for one for brother
No
I don't have a spiritual root
So what
Dreams are still necessary
Senior brother
Summer I
What happened to me just now
You just lost your mind
I know now
The horrors of the dark forest
It will trap people in their own delusions
The so-called mind magic is hard to get rid of
People will be tortured to death like this
Delusion
My delusions
Time and summer
Chi, how are you feeling now
What's wrong with me
You passed out on the first floor
All Dharma Immortals can't wake you up
What the hell happened to you
Wan Xian Meng exam
Stop
You have missed the leader's choice
Two hundred years of cultivation were all in vain
Disciples are guilty of their teachers
Ask Master to punish
This is the end of the matter
It is useless to say more for teachers
Let's take a long-term view of everything
You can't watch me
How come it's three people
I don't know who is the God official
I don't think any of these three are alike
Lord God should not be
The immortal leader of the seventies and eighties
How can you be so young
Go
I'll type this
I won
You win again, you cheat
Forget it, forget it
Willing to admit defeat
The outcome has been divided
It's up to me today
Turns out the three of them
They are all the doppelganger's adult
You guys come up
See Lord God
You came to see me for the sake of the leader
Yes
We want to be Yuhua Houchi
Seek a make-up exam qualification
Lord God
Disciple Yuhua Bi Hong
Please give Houchi a chance to make up the exam
Time and summer
I heard that the magic statue also lost the exam qualification
Yes
All right
We promise to make up the qualification of magic statue
What about the back pool
He can run for the next leader
If there is another one
It is unfair
Time and summer
What is fair or not
Make-up qualification
Who do we like
Give it to whom
Time and summer
Can you be so willful when you are a God official
Of course
This is the power of the divine officer
But if you have so much power,
Why don't you just give the magic statue and the back pool
One person, one make-up exam qualification is good
Posterior cistern posterior cistern
You're not tired of talking, and we're tired of listening
How about this
You go and help us send the order first
I want to summon the magic statue
Tell you
Lord God has never been out of the shrine
You want to summon the magic statue
Then go and see yourself
Why bother others
If it is inconvenient for God's Lord to get out of the palace,
I am willing to do it for you
But in our hometown
It takes some errands to ask for help
You know what I mean
Dare to talk about conditions when you see our seat
Little girl has a lot of courage
Time and summer
Lord God
Hour
I guess for thousands of years
No one has ever entered the Palace of Innocence
Lord God can't get out at all
Right
My sister can only play by herself even pushing Pai Jiu
It must be lonely
I underestimated you
Don't you just want to help Houchi
Strive for the make-up exam qualification
If we promise you, it will be
The sister
I want to ask for one for brother Bi Hong, too
Time and summer
Greed
I finally met my fairy sister once
I may have made a little more wishes
I'm sorry
Good
We promise you
Thank you, Lord God
Brother
Do you have to go in alone
Qiu Li will go with you
Lacquer Ling Ling
In
Keep an eye on the holy aunt
Erha
Let's go find Shi Xia
Good
Go
Brother
It's really you
Isn't that true
This
Are you all right
It's okay
Sister Shixia, you're not hurt, are you
Am I not good here
They say to go to the dark forest
You will lose one important thing
Brother Bi Hong and I have lost nothing
You see
What did I say
It's still my big man's halo
Big male master
You have another aura
Lord God wants to see you by name
I
Really
You wanted to see me
You
Is the magic statue
I never expected it
The big male script also has benefits in this direction
Lord God, you have something to say
You can't take advantage of your status as a divine officer
Those who use their hands and feet on candidates
Shut up
Continue
You didn't
I do
Have everything you should have
You have no spiritual roots
Spiritual root
That doesn't
You summoned me for Linggen
Spirit should be passed down by blood
Why does the magic statue have no spiritual root
The holy garment still has induction
Five senior brothers' blood is not broken
The real magic statue should still hide in the magic school
Lord God
You can't keep your word
Right
What did she say
Go ahead
Pass the word of this seat
Two thousand years ago
The fairy magic array has been laid out
Tomorrow, six of our brothers and sisters will launch an array together
You can stabilize the world and do it firmly
In this world, the stars and the moon will never be reversed again
Vanity disorder
Shi Ji
Tomorrow, after the brothers join the battle,
You have to guard the battle for three days and three nights
Never leave
Yes
I will definitely wait until the brothers come back
To be a brother means to say
Whether we come out or not
You must keep a good array of immortals and demons
It's not good
Five senior brothers left a letter and went down the mountain
The fifth teacher brother ran away
Master Brother, what should I do
I'm going down the mountain now
Go and get Qiu Baiyan back
It's too late
I really ran out of money for the deployment
There are only three days left
Master Elder Martial Brother
The hour has come
Enter the array
Five senior brothers
Your magic pie finally showed up
This time
I will definitely find the spiritual root of heaven
Completely stabilize the fairy magic array
Two thousand years
I have been guarding the fairy magic array for two thousand years
This day is finally coming