My Dear Brothers
EP03
I have something to ask you.
Oh God, is he gonna tell me how he feels?
Can I be your...
Guru
I know you're great,
and I respect you.
But I don't want a relationship yet.
... be your brother!
Brother?
There's such an intimate atmosphere,
but he just wanna be my brother?
What do you think?
No.
Why?
I have a brother.
What your brother did or not,
I've done for you.
Well, I have to thank you for that?
Thank you for not killing me
when you amuse yourself these days?
Why do you say that?
First you made me some awful food,
then you told ghost stories to scare me.
Just now you acted like going Bungee Jumping on the ferris wheel,
letting loose buckles.
I'm lucky to be alive for now.
Well,
how can I be a good brother to you?
Why do you want a sister?
In order to improve my force.
You...
I thought Yuhua Sect
is noble and decent.
How can there be such nonsense?
You just need to know that
brother will protect sister.
Oh great,
I can't learn enchantments here,
but you intend to use me to enhance your force.
You want a sister? Ok.
But you have to promise me one thing.
What?
Send me to the academy to learn Enchantments.
No.
Then there's no need to discuss.
Each one minds his own business.
Bye.
You look so upset.
Let me guess,
did you have a quarrel with sister?
No fight,
and no sister.
Let me tell you.
I have a friend,
who hasn't had a sister for many, many years.
Recently, he met one,
and he asked me for advice on many things.
It goes well now.
Senior, let me ask you.
If the younger sister doesn't want an elder brother,
what to do?
You were rejected?
Then you would be in the resurrection.
The most important thing in resurrection
is to find what she needs.
If she needs money,
give her money.
If she needs enthusiasm,
be enthusiastic.
If she needs tenderness,
be tender.
What does this sister need?
Senior
I recently encounter a talented man,
and I want to recommend him to the academy.
I wonder if you can help me.
Hello,
how do I look?
Thank you.
By the way,
Why didn't you recommend me in person?
Senior often goes outside the mountain.
It makes sense for you to know him.
What's this?
My smell is on this instrument,
and it can cover up your feminine scent.
Keep it with you.
It looks exactly the same as you!
Even the expression!
What's its name?
Instrument is instrument,
it has no name.
I'll give it one.
How about "the doll pin"?
Remember, don't...
Don't be found that I'm a girl.
Otherwise, I'll be whipped.
Got it.
How can I use it?
If you are in danger,
it'll inform me.
You are the pretty... boy
who met my Junior
by chance?
You really look so pretty.
Uncle Master
Am I that old?
Since you are a peer of my junior,
how about call me Senior?
Senior
The hierarchy is wrong.
We feel like old friends at the first meeting,
with our mutual agreement,
why not?
Let's go, take the kid to school.
I'm not a kid.
My junior and I are 200 years old.
In our eyes,
you're a kid.
Let's go.
Master Uncle
Here he is.
Is he the talented man recommended by Bi Hong?
I'm Shi Xia,
live in Lotus Village down the mountain.
Please allow me to enter
Yuhua Sect.
Lotus Village?
Never heard of any talented man
with immortal perception there.
Right.
He has no immortal perception.
Nonsense!
How can one cultivate without immortal perceptions.
When is there a rule in Yuhua Sect that
one can't cultivate without immortal perceptions?
Even there isn't a rule,
you should know it.
If one has no immortal perception but forcibly do that,
it's like a drop in the ocean,
comparing eternity with sun and moon.
Every man has his destiny. Don't delay him.
Yeah,
I've been doing nothing all day,
just fool around with birds and flowers.
More importantly,
I have no immortal perception, too.
What a pity,
I live for 200 years.
Interesting, isn't it?
Even if you live for a thousand years,
you're not equal to one
with immortal perception.
Don't get angry.
You finally tell the truth.
Anyway, in your eyes,
I'm nothing.
Stop talking,
take him back.
May I say something?
The Immortal Venerable said, every man has his destiny.
Then if a creature was
born to be evil,
he is doomed to be evil,
and there's no need to change him?
In my hometown,
there's a saying,
I am the master of my own fate.
Why bother?
Let him audit for a month as usual,
and he can become a full member if he gets the signatures of all the elders.
Otherwise, stop pestering.
I agree.
Do as you say.
Yes!
In such a big place,
he just sits in the corner,
maybe he is a study slacker who sleeps in the class.
Excuse me,
hello, I'm new here.
You must be the bold external student
who has no immortal perception and not from any famous family
and want to cultivate.
I have to ask, the one who
gangs others up,
and with pompous manners,
and puts cultivation secondary,
gossip first,
who are you?
The owner of this seat.
So, it's you who messed with me!
There's no seating chart,
why do you say it's yours?
Go and ask around.
Our big brother, Yi Yaogua,
the only son of the Baling Yi family.
The instruments made by his family
are the most sophisticated and powerful in the whole immortal world.
All the sects scramble for that.
Every instrument is hard to get.
It turns out you are a son of immortals.
You!
Qing Feng
Nice dress today.
Take it off!
What are you doing?
He is wearing the same style as Uncle Master,
and he's not qualified to wear it.
Aren't all blue clothes the same?
So are you.
Yeah.
I say he can't, then he can't.
Let me go!
Now you beg for mercy,
too late!
You just can't wear the same style!
Big brother, now it's not the same.
Why is it so abnormally quiet today?
Not even a bird or a worm chirping.
I heard that it's a nice room for two.
Except for a new roommate,
it's just like being with Guru.
Hello? Anyone here?
Who's there?
Sorry,
I don't know someone was here.
Don't come over!
Ok, I'll go.
We're all men, what are you afraid of?
I...
I warn you,
I'll teach you a lesson if you come closer.
I found your secret.
What secret do I have?
If you come closer,
I'll be unkind.
You?
The skin,
the body,
and the chest wrap,
do you think I'm blind that I can't tell you're a girl?
What do you want?
What do I want?
It depends on you.
If you make public, don't blame me for being rude.
Let me go,
I'm kidding.
I'm not kidding.
The doll pin is not with sister?
What a coincidence!
It's like
Hua Mulan meets Zhu Yingtai.
It's really a coincidence.
But yours is a very advanced instrument.
No wonder your smell
was covered up so completely.
What about you?
How do you cover up yours?
This is Black-Sun Elixir,
which can replenish the male smell
to cover up female one.
But I have to take it
every four hours.
This is great!
If I lose the doll pin someday,
I can borrow yours.
You'd better not.
As a girl,
taking it will damage your body.
You can't stand it.
You come to Yuhua Sect for study
despite the harm to your body.
You don't
come for idol
as Yi Yaogua does, do you?
Of course not.
I want to practice the enchantments well, it's useful for me.
Tell me about you.
Why do you come here?
I...
... want to learn the enchantment of breaking the virtual space.
I've never heard of that before.
Is there anyone who might know?
Master Yuan Ye.
He's very knowledgeable.
If you can get on his good side,
I think you can get some clues.
How?
How is your painting skill?
After a fashion.
That's what I drew.
What, people...
It's not important, go on.
Master Yuan Ye
probably will test History of Immortals tomorrow.
I heard that there was a senior student
who drew an illustration during the exam.
The picture and its accompanying essay were both excellent.
Master Yuan Ye was very satisfied.
History of Immortals...
Where's my textbook?
Junior Master
Please bless me to be like you,
to be the most famous star in the immoral world,
to be a great hope of a sect.
It was your fame that brought me to Yuhua Sect.
Hopefully in the near future,
I can see you again.
We have a test today,
and the content is
the science of holy beast.
Wasn't it History of Immortals?
Yeah, why changed?
Each one draws a holy beast,
not limited to textbook.
You can start.
It's over.
I forgot bringing the textbook.
I don't even have things to copy.
Shi Xia
Where did you get your school supplies?
A friend gave them to me.
This is a sketch pen,
you can speed up
100 times by using it.
This is the erasure paper,
it can be reused 100,000 times.
You have a very thoughtful friend.
So amazing.
Master Yuan Ye, excuse me.
I met Junior Master when patrolling the mountain,
he said he was looking for a student
called Shi...
Yes, it's me, it's me, it's me!
It's me, it's me!
You...
Others go on.
Junior Master
Junior Master, Junior Master
Why are you here?
I'm Yi Yaogua,
the most excellent student of this year.
What can I do for you?
Junior Master truly deserves his reputation,
handsome and charming,
graceful and gentle.
What classes are you taking these days?
It's no more than the Histories of Immortals,
an introduction to noble families,
a general history of fairy arts,
the science of charms, instruments and holy beasts,
and spirit maintenance.
Some practicing experience of mine.
God, it's, it's, it's
Junior Master's note!
Take it back and study with your classmates.
Junior Master is really a prodigy.
If you could teach us for a few days,
I'd die without regret.
Even if you do as Master Yuan Ye,
who said test the History of Immortals,
but changed to the science of holy beast,
I'm willing to take your class!
Change the subject at the last minute?
Don't worry,
I'm knowledgeable,
and I have your note.
It doesn't matter.
I only pity those study slackers.
Study slackers...
Cobras?
Alligators?
Zombies?
May I come in?
Have a seat.
The test is over.
Any volunteer can
show his painting to us?
Master Yuan Ye, I'll go first.
What I drew is called Yong.
It's a bird with a human face,
four eyes
and ears.
Your stroke is exquisite.
The four eyes are just in the right size and arrangement.
So it can...
It can scatter cloud.
So where it is,
there is a great drought.
Great, it's not in the textbook.
Your knowledge is very good.
Others,
You all have to learn from Yi Yaogua,
not limited to the textbook.
Next,
everyone show the holy beast you have drawn in turn.
I drew a phoenix bird.
Good.
Baize.
Not bad.
The one who is new here,
what did you draw?
This is a human baby?
This kind of holy beast
is also called "Four-legged gold-spending beast" in my hometown.
It's the most powerful beast in my hometown.
You don't have to take this class anymore.
Please don't, Master!
I need the approval of the elders,
could you give me another chance?
If you can draw one,
I'll eat it.
That's what you said.
Master Yuan Ye temporarily changed test.
I'm afraid sister that has not prepared for it.
Master
You want to go outside?
I have something that I don't understand
to ask you.
Go ahead.
As the old saying goes,
it is better to travel ten thousand miles than to read ten thousand books.
Whether it's time for me
to travel outside?
I appreciate that
you can think so.
But it is not the right time to go outside.
When you are the Lord of Immortals Alliance,
you'll have many chances to experience the world.
I see.
The new student,
how is your painting?
Big brother, what's that?
This beast is called Sun Wukong.
It is not what you paint carelessly, is it?
Nonsense!
This is a very rare ancient beast.
Master must know it.
The ancient beast is...
Master Yuan Ye
I have been reading extensively since childhood.
Why haven't I seen such a holy beast?
Yi Yaogua
You read extensively?
For Master, that's teaching fish to swim.
There is one or not, Master will make decision on his own.
Well...
Let me help you recall.
Sun Wukong is different from ordinary holy beasts.
It's intelligent but stubborn and obstreperous.
First it got Golden cudgel at the dragon's palace.
Then it drew on the death book in the hell.
After that, the heaven assigned it to be an official.
Then it made havoc in heaven,
fighting with 100 thousand of soldiers.
But it was still defeated by the Tathagata,
and was pressed under five fingers mountain for 500 years.
Yeah, right, I remember.
In the early years,
I used to have it,
which was particular about food and very hard to feed.
It's just a holy beast from unofficial history.
No wonder you didn't obey the basic drawing method
of holy beasts.
I didn't
because it's presented differently.
Master, please wait.
Qing Feng
Please hand me my pen and notebook.
I've never seen painting moving before!
Awesome!
Great! Great!
Shi Xia, you really took me by surprise.
Good, very good!
Go ahead, eat it.
The whole book is yours.
This new student is really good.
Yeah, I've never seen
this drawing method before.
Little one
Which book did you know Sun Wukong from?
Give it to me!
Give it to you? Ok.
Maybe your big brother didn't have enough to eat.
You!
Don't put shame on your face!
Come on,
face is given by others,
but shame is caused by himself.
Let's go.
Stop!
You made a fool of me
in front of so many people.
I won't just let you go!
My instrument!
Master Yuan Ye
Master Yuan...
We've been tricked. Go for them!
Run!
There they are! Go!
Big brother
What?
Isn't this Black-Sun Elixir?
Someone dressed as men!
There's actually something so crazy in Yuhua Sect.
This is a butterfly instrument,
which loves to follow women's scent.
Let's go!
What about Little One?
Are you stupid?
Little One
is not crazier than dressing as men!
Butterfly, go!
What's wrong?
God, I lost my Black-Sun Elixir!
It's too late. Let run away first.
Qing Feng, are you all right?
Shi Xia, go.
The potency of medicine is about to wear off.
They'll catch me soon enough.
No, you're hurt.
I can't leave you!
I'll get you in trouble,
go!
You can use this.
Shi Xia
Master won't agree with
me going outside now.
What are you doing?
-Get out of my way!  -Go!
See where she can go!
Go away! Stop chasing me!
Go away!
Go!