My Dear Brothers
EP10
Hou Chi, surprise
It seems no one lives here.
It seems Hou Chi is slower than me.
I arrived earlier.
Do you think it's appropriate for me to come to him?
It's troublesome enough to have one brother.
Now I have two.
And they're enemies.
Shi Xia is my sister!
She's my sister!
First come, first served!
There's no need to argue.
So the negotiation is off the table.
No! No!
I won't let this happen!
Stop fighting!
If I interfere, it is nothing more than suicide!
What should I do?
No matter how,
I should find Hou Chi first.
When Shi Dong is not around, I'll explain it to him.
I don't belong to Devil Sect.
Then it works!
But what if he doesn't trust me?
He would hate me if I do that!
Nope.
Why should I care if he hates me or not?
Tell me, should I look for Hou Chi or not?
If you point towards the north,
I'll go out to look for Hou Chi right now.
Good!
You're indeed pointing towards the north.
I accept your advice!
Good news! Good news!
I've fished for the information.
There's no one reporting for duty in Yuhua Sect.
So she lives alone!
She lives alone!
Then I'm relieved.
Pass my order.
Ask guardians to guard the room of Yuhua Sect more strictly.
Did you hear him?
Keep an eye on it!
Yes!
If there's any man who tries to get in, beat him!
Beat him to death. Cripple him.
Wait.
Do you want us to cripple him or beat him to death?
Depending on my mood.
Hou Chi, right?
How dare you share one room with Shi Xia?
Devil Lord rescued her himself.
It seems that Shi Xia is not an ordinary person.
Shi Xia even has no Holy Root.
How come she is not ordinary?
I think there must be a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
Can it explain why she broke into the ward of Mount Yuhua?
Can it explain why she approached Hou Chi on purpose?
Can it explain why Devil Lord rescued her himself?
What I worry most is that
Devil Lord did so to prevent Hou Chi from election.
For the Immortals Alliance election,
there must be a plan made by Devil Sect.
No need to talk.
I'll go downhill now.
I'll kill the devil girl to assist Hou Chi!
The fact hasn't been figured out yet.
Is Yuhua Sect killing the innocent?
Even though we cannot kill the innocent,
I won't allow Hou Chi to take the risk by himself.
I'm willing to follow him to the Fairy-demon Town.
I'm also willing to go.
Me too.
He's willing to give up the exam
to protect Shi Xia from danger.
In the world, I'm afraid that only I'm able to
be a good friend with Shi Xia,
talk for both sides,
and mediate between them
at the same time.
You can go.
But don't expect that you can protect Shi Xia.
In your journey,
remember the purpose of going downhill.
Hou Chi
must be in the election.
Yes!
It's high quality!
Miss, Miss. Come here.
Did you see a handsome Immortal with a poker face?
No.
Hello. Did you see a tall,
slim, and handsome Immortal with a poker face?
No. No.
Dolls! Adorable dolls!
Handmade dolls!
Of high quality!
Sir. Would you like a doll?
I never expect dolls can be so pretty.
How's that, Sir?
You really have a good taste!
This one is the bestseller.
Buy one.
Did you see a
handsome Immortal with a poker face?
No.
Sir.
See you next time, Sir.
Dolls! Adorable dolls!
Miss, Miss.
Look at dolls and see if there's anything you like.
I don't buy dolls.
Did you see a
handsome Immortal with a poker face?
He's about that height.
His eyes are just like these.
Are you looking for that Immortal?
Miss!
Miss! Your Majesty is looking for you.
Where have you been early this morning?
Your Majesty cannot find you!
Let me go!
No, I won't!
You're the only one whom Your Majesty likes.
Be good.
Go back.
Let me go.
I'll ask Your Majesty to order you to commit suicide!
No wonder you're chosen by Your Majesty.
You have the same temper as him does!
Devil Lord Qiu Ping versus Hou Chi from Yuhua Sect.
Do not miss out on this!
Bravo!
Hou Chi. I've won already.
Just quit.
How come?
I, Hou Chi, as the best potential
successor of the leader of alliance in the celestial,
can never lose to you, who is
such a handsome, talented,
extraordinary, and well-known Devil Lord!
Sister
The Immortal Venerable. Look for others at other places.
Don't interrupt me to watch the show!
Are you watching the show?
Of course! Or are we watching you?
Go, go, go! Leave here!
My sister also likes to watch a show.
Where is my sister?
Where are you pointing at?
If you cannot find her, why would we use you?
Sorry I didn't finish the task.
You... you just order me to commit suicide!
That's it. That's it!
Forget it. Forget it!
She has the same temper as me.
I didn't expect you to deal with it.
Hou Chi! Hou Chi!
Why... why don't you act according to the script?
Hou Chi! Hou Chi! Hou Chi!
The one who plays Hou Chi acts really well.
What crap are you talking about?
Hou Chi! Hou Chi!
Beat him, Hou Chi! Hou Chi!
What an idiot you are!
It's you!
Who is he?
Oh lord! He is Hou Chi for real!
Tell me.
Where is my sister?
How dare you ask me?
You caused my sister to be locked in the dark room.
How did you protect my sister?
The real Devil Lord
versus Hou Chi from Yuhua Sect!
It's coming!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Beat him!
Your Majesty
Good legs!
Give me a hand!
Beat him!
Get down!
Beat him! Beat him!
Hold on!
I'm not come here to fight you.
I come here to look for my sister.
Looking for your sister? Bah!
I must give you a warning today.
Never meddle with others' belonging!
What did I meddle with?
You know what you have done!
Young man, you have no martial ethics.
You raid.
Come on.
Look how precisely I shoot!
Brother!
Who is she?
Sister
He knows her.
Why did they stop fighting?
What are they doing?
Thinking for a long time,
I still can't avoid the worst situation.
I hope the heaven
will bless me with wisdom and eloquence.
Didn't Devil Lord just say
never mess up with others' belonging?
Well,
Devil Lord is not vicious.
If he didn't bring me to the Fairy-demon Town,
I wouldn't find you.
You...
I know you must feel strange and wonder
why did Devil Lord rescue me
from Yuhua Sect?
I didn't expect it myself.
But I'm not a spy from Devil Sect.
I have nothing to do with Devil Sect.
Do you believe me?
Of course I believe what you said.
I started to doubt myself.
But don't you doubt me at all?
You're my sister.
Wait me for a while.
The most difficult task for me
is finished in this way!
Pay attention to your standpoint!
I know.
Blood is thicker than water.
The Immortal Venerable acted so well!
This is your reward.
Follow me.
So rude!
The doll is handmade.
Have a look.
Sir, I want this one.
I kept it for you.
I knew the Immortal Venerable would come and buy it.
Here you are.
The Immortal Venerable bought the doll
to send this lady as a gift.
The person that she was looking for is the Immortal Venerable.
What a coincidence!
Why did you take my doll?
It's just a doll.
So annoying!
Immortal coins.
Sir
I'll buy all the dolls you have.
For my...
For myself.
Devil Lord needs so many dolls.
Are you victimized by severe insomnia?
Has the ward of your bedroom been canceled?
Not yet.
It's said that the ward is set by Shang Feng.
Shang Feng has been cultivating for more than 2,000 years.
How can I cancel his ward?
Since you came here to take part in the exam,
you should adhere to the rules.
Why do you make the owner in a pickle?
Stupid!
If I didn't make him in a pickle, you will share...
the same room with your sister.
Sister and I
have been living together in Yuhua Sect.
Any problem?
No. No.
Usually, my brother practices mediation outside,
and I sleep in my room. Right?
Right.
My sister is sleepless and afraid of dark.
I tell stories for her every night
to comfort her to sleep and then I leave.
Waiter! Come out!
I'll meet your boss.
Do you think it's easy for you
to see Shen Guan?
Devil Lord. May I have a word with you?
Let's go.
Hou Chi is as dumb as a piece of wood.
I share the same room with him.
It's you who takes the advantage.
What's your logic?
I...
Getting along with him in Yuhua Sect for such a long time,
I am also a spy around him.
I can help you to inquire information from him.
After all, blood is thicker than water.
Why do I think you are hoaxing me?
Why don't you believe your own sister?
Okay.
It's not a big deal to deny our relationship.
Tell everyone that we're siblings.
To let the world know that you're not Devil Lord Qiu Ping.
Erha
Send Devil Lord to the room.
Take him away!
You wanna repel?
Hands...
Hands off me!
Or I'll order you to commit suicide!
If you miss the exam,
Immortal Aunt will also order us to commit suicide.
Let go of me! How dare you!
Didn't I ask you to keep an eye on the room of Yuhua Sect?
Why does Hou Chi show himself in front of me
safe and sound?
I did intercept
an apprentice of Yuhua Sect,
and according to your order,
I crippled him.
Yes.
At first, one of his hands was crippled,
and then we broke one of his legs.
See?
Did I accidentally injure others?
I'll go to the Fairy-demon Inn.
No! No!
You should rest for over three months if your bones are broken.
You should at least rest for one month for your injured legs.
Just live here as long as you can.
Junior Master is so young.
If you go outside alone,
what should you do if you're hoaxed by bad guys?
I've found Shi Xia.
Everything's okay. Don't worry.
Master Yuan Gui is ready to bring me downhill.
I'm afraid it's not good for Shi Xia. Deal with it soon.
How long will it take for Master to pack up?
It's been almost six hours!
Bi Hong. Hurry up! We should go now.
Let's go.
Master
We went downhill to perform a task.
But you're dressed like this.
That's a little bit too ostentatious.
I don't think so.
Doesn't my outfit fit
the style of our Immortal, which is the first Sect of all?
Lin Kui
You're right. Let's go!
Master
Wait for me.
Hurry up!
Okay.
Well, the room is a little bit tiny.
Is it?
It's the same size as my cottage.
You should look at the area for per person.
I live alone in your cottage.
But now we share one.
Look how tiny the room is.
When I yawn, I almost hit you.
Sister has never practiced Kung Fu.
You cannot hit me.
I...
I mean,
it's so inconvenient!
Please feel free to tell me why you feel inconvenient.
How dumb he is!
He knows nothing about the taboo between men and women.
Here you are.
My new doll.
I have always been wanting it.
What...
are you going to do?
This doll is ugly. Dump it.
Why are you so cruel?
The doll is made by yourself.
It has been accompanied with me for so long.
It's not its fault to be ugly.
It's innocent!
You two
should get along well with each other.
You're right.
I should be responsible for it.
Calm down, Shi Xia.
We just share one room. No need to panic!
What are you doing?
The clothes are worn out.
Right.
You really had a fierce fight with Devil Lord today.
Nope.
Even though they share one room,
I won't allow Hou Chi to be so comfortable.
Hot-chilly pot.
Hot chilly crayfish.
Does it smell good?
Good. So good!
So good!
Sister
Why do you look so strange today?
Do I?
Maybe I'm like you,
who is used to staying uphill for so long.
I'm not used to seeing so many people after going downhill.
Sister is lack of experience in the society.
Experience in the society?
Then tell me about it.
Rule number one:
Ask less, observe more.
Rule number two:
A golden key can open any door.
Is it also realistic for the celestial?
Where did you learn all of these from?
I'm on the way looking for the entrance of Devil Sect.
Looking for the entrance of Devil Sect?
Didn't you come to the Fairy-demon Town to take the exam?
Why do you look for the entrance of Devil Sect?
I heard that Devil Lord took you way.
I wanted to rescue you.
It's a misunderstanding.
Devil Lord is also kind.
When he found that I missed you,
he brought me to the Fairy-demon Town.
You missed me?
What does miss mean?
Missing...
Missing means when you're separated with someone,
you're always thinking about the one.
You will feel time passes so slowly,
and every day you wish to meet him soon.
Just like when I missed my brother before.
Sister
I miss you too.
It's midnight snack time.
Rabbit heads. Hot-spicy pot.
Hot and spicy crayfish.
Don't miss the delicacies!
What... what are you doing?
I thought you would like to eat some marshmallow.
I... I want to eat stinky tofu!
This one. This one.
Delicious!
Have more of it.
The hot-spicy pot is so good!
So yummy!
It's not spicy enough.
Remember to add more peppers in it.
It's so easy to get yeet hay if it's so spicy.
I asked the cook to add less peppers in it.
Or you would shout again if you get pimples tomorrow.
It's been a long time since last time I ate spicy food.
If you don't allow me to eat what I want,
I'll shout at you right now!
Sorry for keeping you waiting for so long.
This is my specialty.
Stinky tofu.
It smells so stinky.
It must be poisonous.
I think you're the one who is poisonous.
You're poisonous!
It's called stinky tofu.
It smells stinky, but tastes good.
I'll taste it for you.
How's that?
The stinky tofu is amazing!
Erha. Good for you!
Why... why are you in a daze?
Here. Have one.
Help yourself!