My Dear Brothers
EP09
Seriously?
It's quite dark.
Why do you bring me here?
To get home quickly.
So you come the farthest way round?
It's so weird.
Ouch, I've got a tummy ache.
Just wait for me here.
Again?
Three minutes.
Hey, you liar.
Why do you leave me...
Shi Dong
Shi Xia
Where are you?
Shi Dong
Sorry,
I couldn't be with you on your birthday.
That's okay.
I'm used to the fact that
you are unreliable.
So, Shi Dong didn't leave me on purpose.
He's also here.
Your Majesty
Here to visit your Majesty.
Your Majesty?
How dare you!
Why not kneel down
at the sight of the Devil Lord?
Kneel!
Devil Lord Qiu Ping?
How dare she address the Lord by name?
Deserve a beating.
How dare you?
Stay away from her, or you will die miserably.
From now on,
you should call Shi Xia your Devil Lady.
You should respect her
as you respect me.
Got it?
Wait, your Majesty.
Just order me as you like, Devil Lady.
Gosh, Shi Dong is the Devil Lord.
Now I'm a spy of Devil Sect in their eyes.
Are you sick? Why take so many medicines?
Are you looking me down?
Don't you know Dragon Ball?
Today I'll widen your horizon.
This is the Ark,
a means of transport invented by me.
Do you like it?
Come on.
Follow me, Husppy.
Do you like it?
Have a look.
Look at this,
it's the driver's cab.
Look at that horse.
Great, right?
Come here.
Come on.
Bubble tea.
I've never expected I could drink it in this world.
You've scared me!
Remember to shake it before drinking,
or you'll miss its essence.
There wasn't such thing before,
but I invented it.
I remember that Bubble tea is your favorite drink.
Just a sip.
You've drunk so much!
You didn't say how much a sip could be.
You can drink like I do.
Shi Dong
Come on.
Do you like it?
Just so so.
I haven't had milk tea for long
so I can bear this now.
What?
Leave here.
You heard that? Leave here.
Don't stand in the way.
I mean you.
Devil Lady, huh?
The days that Immortal Aunt isn't here...
Get out!
are numbered!
Don't hinder us from
talking about the old days.
The Yuhua Sect is so mean.
The dress is too plain.
When we return to Devil Sect,
I will make you a set of advanced custom clothing.
I'm here for you now.
It's on my schedule.
Here for me?
Stop boasting.
Now I know
you were enjoying life here the year you disappeared.
You don't understand.
Thanks to the past year,
I could grow into
the hero in an adventure novel.
What do you mean?
I've jumped into the sea, jumped off the cliff
and been struck by the lightning.
But I can't go back to our world no matter what I've done.
Then I figured out a question,
why I can't die as I wish.
Have you read time travel novels?
Why the hero in an adventure novel
be able to achieve in unfavorable circumstances?
Look at me,
I've been the Devil Lord within one year.
This only shows
I am destined to be the hero in an adventure novel.
You've lost your mind.
Don't believe me?
I'll show you.
Junior Master has never gone downhill and is unfamiliar with the road.
This trip is a good opportunity
to get closer to him.
Hope to discuss
the practice experience with him within three days.
This way, Master.
I've arranged everything for you,
the inn, restaurant,
tea house, and rest place along the way.
Just rest assured to follow me on the road.
Shi Xia has been captured by Devil Lord Qiu Ping.
Please rescue her quickly.
There are many bandits
in these places circled by red.
There are some liars who sell fake medicines
in the places circled by green.
So I suspect that
there are strongholds of Devil Sect
near these circled places.
Master, the Otherworld Town isn't in that direction.
Junior Master, where are you going?
Devil Sect.
The owner asked you to go to the Otherworld Town
to participate in the preliminary contest of the alliance election,
but you are going to the Demon Sect.
Just because of Shi Xia?
Shi Xia was captured by the Devil Lord.
She is the Devil Lord's friend.
He didn't capture her, but rescued her.
You can rest assured.
Shi Xia isn't a spy.
Do you know how to go to the Devil Sect?
Devil Sect has stayed away from the world for a long time.
For more than two thousand years,
no one has got the entrance.
How can I know it?
Junior Master is really obsessed.
If he continues like this,
he will only go further on a wrong path.
No, I can't
allow him to do this.
I should help him find the witch
and question her to make him give up completely.
Wait for me in the Otherworld Town.
I will meet you again
when I rescue her.
No, I have to go with you.
You see, you've never gone downhill
and you don't know the dark side of the world,
but I am different.
Let's welcome the Devil Lady.
Long live the Devil Lord!
How about this?
Okay.
Long live the Devil Lord!
Husppy
Hey,
is this the slogan I asked you to chant this morning?
Don't you remember?
Listen to my direction, okay?
Morning, friends in Devil Sect.
Morning, your Majesty.
Our slogan is...
The road to become immortal is long,
and milk tea will always be with you.
Sugar, milk and ice,
Devil Sect will help you go ahead.
Yeah, help you go ahead.
I can sell 600 more immortal coins of holy power.
Can holy power be bought and sold here?
In my place,
as long as you are diligent and wise,
you can win immortal coins.
Holy power can be bought by immortal coins,
and immortal coins can be bought by holy power.
In this way,
you can live a decent life
as a person with Immortal perception.
Besides,
those holy power will be of great use someday.
Good job.
See,
you can't deny that I'm capable.
I'll be the head of Immortals Alliance.
You also want to run for the leader of Immortals Alliance?
What does it mean?
I'm destined to be the leader of Immortals Alliance.
The ending of my hero's script is,
I'll become the leader
and lead Devil Sect to the top.
You, go here and search.
Yes, boss.
You two,
go there and search.
Yes, sir.
Master, I've sent out the mission.
We just need to wait for the result.
What is this?
This is immortal coin, or money.
Why do they take it and work for you?
This is the first experience you have to learn.
Money makes the mare go.
We need money for everything
after going downhill.
Good, you have a lot of money.
Master
I will make you the symbol of
Yuhua Sect again.
You will definitely not be able to accept
such a large amount of information at once,
or take a sip of milk tea to recollect your thoughts.
Come on, take a sip.
How do you become the Devil Lord?
Where is the original one?
The last Devil Lord Qiu Ping is tyrannical.
Nobody can find him now.
Only I can take on
this important task at present.
So you are
an impostor?
Not so serious.
Just borrow his identity temporarily.
What's more, no one knows Qiu Ping's face.
What if you are found out
that you are not the real Devil Lord Qiu Ping
one day?
Don't worry.
This kind of small probability event
is unlikely to happen to the hero.
All right.
Up to you.
Take me to the preliminary contest of the alliance election.
Why?
Is it because of Hou Chi?
That's not true.
How can I miss
the glorious moment
when my brother
is elected as the leader?
What if we meet Hou Chi?
Come on,
I'm his little sister now.
No way, since you've found your true brother,
you have to sever ties with him.
Got it?
Don't be childish.
We can't let others know our relationship.
We both need an identity in this world.
You are Devil Lord Qiu Ping,
and I'm Hou Chi's sister.
I don't agree.
As your brother, I can't admit it.
Somebody help!
Okay, I'll take you there.
That's a deal.
Go and change your clothes first.
Master
Where did you get this map?
The drawing is twisted and hard to read.
This is certainly not from a professional.
Most important of all,
all the places circled by purple
have been searched,
and none of them is true.
I should have known that Senior is unreliable.
I guess Master Bi Hong just believe the hearsay.
After all, in the past two thousand years,
no one has ever found the entrance of Devil Sect.
Who are you?
How stupid you are!
You're robbed.
How dare you!
Don't you know who we are?
Listen, I'm Yi Yaogua,
from Yuhua Sect.
-Yi Yaogua. -And this one is...
We are looking for you.
I've heard you are generous
and you are looking for the entrance of Devil Sect.
Hurry up.
I have a method to
find the entrance of Devil Sect.
Listen,
Devil Lord has gone to the Otherworld Town.
Do you have the guts to go to him and ask?
Please wait for me, Master.
How dare this group of villains look down on our Yuhua Sect.
I'll teach them a lesson.
Boss!
Good for you.
But no matter how good you are,
you are alone.
You're not our rival.
Master, well done.
You've got the second experience of the world,
escape if you can't beat others,
before I tell you.
Hit him!
Arrogant.
Can you be arrogant now?
Look, what is that?
What's that?
Louder applause.
It can be much louder.
Isn't the Otherworld Inn designated by
Immortals Alliance?
Why are the candidates?
I guess everyone knows that your Majesty is here,
so they returned home.
You're right.
If this is the truth,
the blessing from gods is too much.
Come on, take a look of the inside.
Okay.
Okay, come on.
Let's go.
Devil Sect hasn't shown in the selection for many years,
but we can still be placed in the center.
Yeah.
Husppy
Good public relation. You'll get awards.
Don't flatter me.
What's public relation?
It means to be a big spender.
Why do you call me a pig?
I mean this.
Oh, this.
Waiter
Candidates from Devil Sect arrive.
A candidate from Yuhua Sect arrives.
Fantastic, this inn is fully automatic.
Well, we are all from Devil Sect.
Yeah.
Where is the apprentice of Yuhua Sect?
Where is he?
Are you the betrayal?
How dare I do that?
Though I want to be.
Not me nor you.
Who would he be?
How can you be an apprentice of Yuhua Sect?
You're my...
follower.
You can be an apprentice of Yuhua Sect,
but you must live with us.
Right.
Let's go.
Okay, go.
Here we are.
Devil Sect.
Wow, that's awesome.
Good.
What's wrong?
What happened?
All candidates must stay in their own rooms,
and those who break into the room of other sects
will be disqualified from this competition.
Who set this rule?
Husppy
Break the ward.
Okay.
It doesn't work.
Vandals will be disqualified from this competition.
Who is it?
Come out!
Your Majesty, don't make your own future
ruined because of me.
Just a trifle.
It's not worthy.
Come in.
I'm Shi Xia, an apprentice of Yuhua Sect.
I'll go back to my room.
Your Majesty, calm down.
Don't make troubles, okay?
Vandals will be disqualified
from the competition.
We should make great achievements,
right?
Husppy
I order you to find
the person who spoke before it's dark.
I must beat him up.
No need for your order.
I want to beat him up, too.
Have you ever thought of this, Hou Chi?