My Dear Brothers
EP13
Hou Chi, I feel so hot.
Hou Chi
Hold me.
Hou Chi, open the door.
Don't touch Shi Xia.
Or I'll kill you.
You hear me?
Open the door.
Husppy
Tear down the door.
Ok.
Don't destroy public facilities.
Don't break into others' rooms.
Or you'll be disqualified.
Brother
If you dismantle the door,
your bright future will be ruined.
Dad, mom, where are you?
Dad
My younger sister is the most important person in my life.
I'll protect her even at the risk of my life.
If Shi Xia's hurt,
my future won't matter.
Gun.
Ok.
Here you are.
Brother
You told me that you would
protect me
and Devil Sect.
Are these lies?
Get out of the way.
I...
You will abandon me because of Shi Xia.
Stupid Bai Li.
It was you who drugged Shi Xia.
Yes,
I'll ruin her.
You can't like her.
No, no.
I feel so hot.
Draw Immortal Aunt away.
I dare not.
Hurry up.
You...
Devil Lord is unqualified for destroying public facilities.
Devil Lord
Where are you gonna take my sister?
Immortal Aunt
Why didn't you
drug Shi Xia with the real Desire Poison?
I saw you become Bai Li again
and forgot all the plans.
I was afraid that you would drink the liquor,
so I changed it temporarily.
Stupid Bai Li.
Now Devil Lord and Hou Chi
are both infatuated with Shi Xia.
I have to come up with an idea
to reveal who she really is.
Brother
Shi Xia, you're awake.
You're sober?
Recall everything?
Sober?
Miss
You're a light weight. Don't get drunk again.
It's harmful to your health.
Thank you.
It turned out that I wasn't drugged with Desire Poison.
Thank you, Immortal Venerable.
I'll pay you back later.
No need.
I want to talk to my sister.
Do you mind?
No, she's my sister.
It doesn't matter. Get out.
No.
Devil Lord is a good man.
Could you please wait for me in the Otherworld Inn?
Shi Xia
Come with me now, right now.
Did you drug me?
Am I
a bad guy in your view?
-Did you do that?  -Don't talk nonsense.
From now on,
you must stay with me.
Although I'm not reliable,
I'll protect you well.
Indeed, the Little One has something to do with Devil Lord.
She cheated Master Hou Chi.
I'll reveal who she really is.
Who is it?
So luxurious.
I heard he is Bi Hong from Yuhua Sect,
who cured Prince Regent.
He's now an honoured guest of Prince Regent.
Stop.
Down.
Oh, it's you.
My friend from Yuhua Sect.
What's up?
You came to find your sister with your whole family?
Is this what the Lingxiu Sect taught you?
Your owner broke the rule 200 years ago,
brought back this b*stard without immortal perception,
and raised him.
Now
you did the same thing again.
You must break the rule very early.
Bullsh*t.
Hou Chi, Devil Lord, and the demon girl from the Devil Sect
drugged my junior sister with Desire Poison.
Hou Chi?
With Desire Poison,
he must do something disgusting.
Where are they? Show me the way.
Junior Hou Chi
Hou Chi
Why are you here?
Shi Xia isn't with you, is she?
No, she is.
I sent you so many messages by my fairy umbrella.
You received none?
Hou Chi, it's hard to find you.
Master
Master Lord
Shi Xia and Devil Lord are in the hospital.
We can't let them go.
You can't decide
my thoughts.
This is Devil Lord.
Demon girl
How dare you hurt my junior sister.
I'll kill you.
You are not qualified to do this.
She's from the Yuhua Sect.
I'll teach her a lesson myself.
Master
Wait.
Master Lord
There's the Shen Guan ward in the Otherworld Town.
You can't use your holy power here.
What?
Master has promised me
that as long as I run for the head of the Alliance,
he would let go of Shi Xia.
You...
Master Hou Chi
Don't be cheated by the Little One again.
She is a wh*re.
Yi Yaogua
Stop making things worse.
I'm not talking nonsense.
I heard it in the hospital.
What did you hear? Tell me.
Is she a spy from the Devil Sect?
Worse.
Shi Xia
She is Devil Lord's lover.
What? Lover?
Hou Chi
Hou Chi, did you hear it?
The Devil took her
from the Yuhua Sect to the Otherworld Town
to disturb your election.
No,
she won't hurt me.
You don't need to worry about this.
I'm bringing Shi Xia back to the Devil Sect.
She won't disturb you, Hou Chi.
No, Shi Xia is from the Yuhua Sect.
You can't take her away.
She was almost killed
by you and Yuhua Sect.
Don't you feel shameful?
Let's go.
Shi Xia
It's up to you.
If you stay,
I assure you
that no one will hurt you.
What are you thinking about?
Why are you hesitating?
Do you know he...
Stop.
No.
I must tell you the truth.
Do you know Devil Lord became disqualified
because of you?
Really?
He thought you were drugged,
so he broke the ward in the inn.
It's how he is.
Shut up.
Devil Lord sacrificed so much for Shi Xia.
There is something between them.
Really?
Sorry,
I want to talk to him.
What are you doing?
Feel guilty
because I'm disqualified?
Listen.
Do you want to go home?
Yes, I do.
Sorry, I can't leave with you.
I have to be with Hou Chi.
He promised me that
he would send us home as long as he becomes the head of the Alliance.
No way,
you have to go back to the Devil Sect with me.
What about going home?
I'll figure a way out.
It's settled.
What can you do?
I've investigated it.
Only if becoming the head of the Alliance to break the void...
You don't trust me, right?
I want to be the head of the Alliance.
Do you think it's a joke?
I said it was like a male script.
You think it's a joke?
In your opinion,
I'm always a useless brother,
right?
Shi Xia, listen.
No matter how I am,
there's one thing for sure.
I'll protect you well.
(It turns out that he knows everything.)
(I hurt him.)
As long as you follow my order,
go back to the Devil Sect and stay with me,
I won't regret it.
I chose to leave with Devil Lord.
Shi Xia
You said he wasn't Devil Lord.
I can't explain it,
but...
Stop.
Let's go.
Ok, thanks for watching.
That's it for today.
Shi Xia
Hou Chi
Don't you say something?
You allow him to leave like this?
The Devil Sect quitted election.
Of course, they can leave
as soon as possible.
Wait.
We are not over yet.
Sir
It's just Desire Poison.
It's called Wan Du
that could detoxify the poison.
Wan Du is highly poisonous.
How could it detoxify?
Yes, it is highly poisonous,
but if you want to make it an antidote,
you need a human being.
As long as he takes it,
various drugs
will collide and harmonize in his body.
Six hours later,
his blood
will be the antidote to Desire Poison.
But
within the six hours,
he'll suffer from
overwhelming pain.
Later
it'll become an antidote.
It's not good
to publicize
her suffering, right?
Since it was Immortal Aunt from the Devil Sect who drugged her,
we need Immortal Aunt to detoxicate it.
No need.
I'll be the man.
Shi Dong
I'm Devil Lord.
So I'm in charge of the Devil Sect.
Ok,
since you took the responsibility,
we'll come tomorrow morning.
Let's go.
Hou Chi
Tell me what had happened.
Why is Shi Xia with Devil Lord?
Senior Bi Hong
What is lover?
Lover
is who you have a crush on.
Devil Lord has a crush on Shi Xia.
I see.
No wonder that he always tried to approach us
in the Otherworld Town.
It turned out that he liked my sister.
But he has his sister.
Why is he so greedy?
What?
(It seems that)
(he doesn't know love yet.)
(He takes love as family affection.)
(Love someone so sillily)
(and lose his lover so sillily too.)
(He wouldn't feel too sad.)
(There's no need for me to enlighten him.)
Hou Chi
Love
is like bubbles.
What's more, you owned it.
(He's better than me.)
It's my fault.
Devil Lord abandoned his qualification to the exam
for Shi Xia.
Compared with him,
I lost.
No wonder that she chose him.
Hou Chi, you need to forget it.
Forget?
How?
How is he?
Hou Chi is upset.
What a silly boy.
He's going to take the exam the day after tomorrow.
Let me go in there and tell him off.
No, Master,
you need to know
that he isn't in a good mood.
And if you break into his room,
maybe he'll be more upset.
It's my fault.
I failed to protect Master Hou Chi.
So Shi Xia could get a chance to approach him.
If you can let her do that again,
maybe he won't feel so upset.
Bi Hong
Don't talk nonsense.
Qing Feng, Lin Kui, Yi Yaogua
Guard at the door of him
these days.
Don't offer any chance for the demon girl to approach him again.
Roger that.
Brother
I'm sorry.
Immortal Aunt
F*ck off.
Keep away from me.
It's the prohibited skill of the Devil Sect
that will hurt your immortal perception.
Please stop hurting yourself.
The blood pill cultivated by holy power
will only ease Demon Lord's pain for moments.
I'll be satisfied.
From that day,
he is the only person I care about.
Your Majesty
Stop.
I'm Immortal Aunt from the Devil Sect.
Stay away from me.
For seven days and nights in succession,
only those who survived
in the hunting
have the right to live.
Qiu Ping
Please
don't.
You should beg your traitor mother.
Qiu... Qiu Ping
Enjoy the game.
Qiu Li
Go.
Good. It thundered.
I heard that Immortal Aunt was afraid of thunder the best.
When hearing thunder,
she couldn't use her holy power.
Search for her.
Don't be afraid.
You're the only one
who is nice to me in the world.
I'm willing to do anything
for you.
Qi Lingling
Brother
Are you ok?
Qi Lingling
What's wrong with him?
Is he ill?
He's ok.
Take good care of him.
Senior Bi Hong
How is it?
It can ease Wan Du's poisonousness.
After Devil Lord takes it,
he'll feel better.
Thank you.
I heard that you've attracted a lot of attention along the way.
Many businessmen
wanted to marry their daughters to you.
You didn't like them?
There was one.
I thought she had a loved one,
so I hid my love from her.
Then I missed her.
Now
she chooses another man.
Who is she?
It's her loss.
Senior, tell me her name.
I'll help you.
You are willing to help me?
Of course,
we're bosom friends.
So I'll help you.
Yes,
we're bosom friends.
The medicine is almost done.
Send it to Devil Lord later.
Shi Xia
Unexpectedly, when we meet again,
you fall in love with Devil Lord.
But it's no use for me to regret it.