Brother
What happened
Are you all right
It's too dangerous
My deity almost can't come back
I didn't expect these gentle scum
How can you use such a lousy trick
What the hell is going on
It was a dark and windy night
Can't see one's fingers
Weren't you tied up during the day
Render the atmosphere
It is said that I was left alone
Suddenly black at the moment
A linen cloth covered my face
There it goes
I found myself dragged into a cave
A masked man is extremely vicious
Little rabbit
Grandpa told you today
Sooner or later, you have to pay it back when you come out to mix
I don't go to hell, who goes to hell
Right
In our line of work
Will always leave the last bullet
Or you die
Or I die
Are you acting with me here
The lines are set by set
I'm not afraid of scaring you
Do you want to process art
You are insane
Can you be serious
This is your life.
Only one finger is lost
What if next time I
Actually, I
I'm not trying to take a breath
Are you coming back to see your sister
Otherwise, I would have fought hard with him. I
Brother, you just got back
The injury is not healed either
You, you, you, you, sit down and have a rest
It hurts so much
Do you really want to cheat Shi Xia like this
It's not so good, is it
Is it worse than this one time
Isn't it bad
Difference
You can go back on your word
It's no accident to lose to Houchi anyway
Bullshit
I'm afraid of being timid in summer
When the time comes, shout
Make everyone know that this deity has been kidnapped
Isn't it very disgraceful
Do you want face
Don't I want to lose face
Why are you proud? People don't want to save you at all
Totally nonsense
Can she not save me if I'm really tied up
Hold back
She must have tried her best to save me
Did you sit down
Sit down
Your Majesty
You have taken another good move now
I
Good chess
Summer girl is the one that deals with Houchi
Chess pieces
Erha
Let me teach you a lesson
What's the reason
I am a generation of famous demons
How is it possible to do something to use women
I did this purely to let my aunt
Recognize the situation clearly
Change evil spirits and return to righteousness
Right
Use a little force
Posterior cistern
No matter what happens,
I will definitely send you into the examination room
Now we have a deal
You will enter the examination room tomorrow
And I will follow the winter back to the magic school
This difference
I don't know when I'll see you again
If I can watch you enter the examination room,
I have fulfilled my final agreement
Candidates of various schools
Admission now
After a wick of incense
The exam officially started
I'm all set
Why hasn't the back pool come yet
Shit
What about the back pool
Two guests walk slowly
Good
Work quickly
There is a man lying at the boss's
Xianchang Houchi Xianchang
Go and find Chief Bi Hongxian
Yes
What about the back pool
There is only half a time left for incense
Houchi didn't return all night
Why didn't anyone report it
Uncle Tai
Little Martial Uncle should be in town
Let's split up and look for it
Is it related to the witch girl in summer again
No, did you
No, you say no
Martial uncle
Don't call me Martial Uncle
Don't punish Qingfeng
I know the whereabouts of the back pool
Our Yuhua School
I will never believe half a sentence of your witch again
Tai Shi Shu Shi Xia said it was true
Yesterday, I was in the town with Yi Yao
Seeing Houchi with one's own eyes and meeting time and summer
You
You guys
There is also Yi Yao
Where is he
When I find the back pool,
I'll settle accounts with you two again
Where is he
First floor
Mortal
Bi Hongxian, you can come
Something big has happened
Come on, come on, go upstairs
Fairy Chang, take a look at it quickly
Posterior cistern
Time is running out
I can't wake up when I tie it so hard
Such a strong smell of wine
You can't be drunk, can you
Fairy long, this can't be delayed
The first test will begin soon
Never let Houchi delay the exam
Where is it
Demon Girl
Don't you dare play games with the old man
It must be because the magic statue was disqualified
You just came to hurt our back pool, didn't you
I must save you today
Yuhua Houchi entered the examination room
Excuse me, Yuhua Houchi has entered
Just went in with Yuhua token
Okay, I see
Fortunately, there was no mistake
Otherwise, the leader will come
I will never spare you
The hour is up
Wan Xian Gate is closed
The initial test of Wanxianmeng leader officially started
Senior brother
Houchi has successfully entered the examination room
Very good
It's not like this. It's not like this
Yi Yao
Yuhua sent candidates to Houchi
Fail to arrive in time
Disqualify from an examination
In addition, Yuhua Yi Yao cheated for the exam
Yuhua School canceled the qualification for three times
Three sessions
Six hundred years
What the hell happened
It was all the idea of Master Bi Hong
Have you answered this letter
If it weren't for how I couldn't wake him up
I can't let Yi Yao take his place
The back pool doesn't go
At best, it is disqualified from the exam
You can still run in the next term
How about this
Three sessions, six hundred years
It's all over
Drink
Be late
Also take the test
You are working together to destroy the back pool here
Others are still fine
As for that summer
We will not tolerate it
Newspaper
It's bad. Something big has happened
What
Houchi was disqualified from the exam
Ban the exam for three times
What
My aunt was detained because of this
I really didn't mean to
You listen to me
I didn't do it on purpose
It's really not me
Boy
Why did you come here to take the test
You must listen to me
I really didn't mean to
Here's what happened
Yao Yi
Your little Martial Uncle has been practicing hard for 200 years
For today
Are you just watching
To watch him lose his qualification for the exam
Don't
What if you can help your little Martial Uncle pass this level
You are his great benefactor
He's sure to look at you differently
Maybe you can be a disciple in the room
With your present cultivation,
It's a piece of cake to try it first
What if you don't want to
I can find someone else now
Leave it to me
I'm just out of a good heart
I didn't expect to cause a big disaster
Isn't that a pity
It's too much
Time and summer
What have you done to little Martial Uncle
I
Are you really a demon
Do you know how badly you've done little Martial Uncle
Yi Yao
Two Master
How is the back pool now
Can I see him
You came just in time
Demon Girl
You missed the exam in Houchi
My whole Yuhua School's painstaking efforts were all in vain
How dare you ask
Head
Don't let go of this demon girl today
Bearer
Take away
Yes
Master
Let go of that girl
Who is it
This is not a demon
What are you doing here
What about you, old man
Go
Devil
You're just in time
You have repeatedly let this demon girl
Harm our Yuhua School
Today
Let's settle the new account and the old account together
Left and right guardians
In
Protect Your Majesty
Yes
The feud between Yuhua School and Magic School
Finish it today
Don't blame me for being unjust
Don't
Wait a minute
Isn't there an enchantment in Xianmo Town
Enchantment is used to protect candidates
Now the selection test has officially started
The enchantment is naturally eliminated
The immortal school and the magic school are sworn
Kill all the demons of the magic school
I count one, two, three, hold me tight
Come with me
Kill all the demons of the magic school
II
III
Go
Time and summer
Ladies and gentlemen of the fairy school and the magic school
Listen to me, everybody
The feud between the fairy school and the magic school has a long history
Solving by force will only avenge each other's grievances
Today's events started because of me
I will definitely give Yuhua an explanation
I want to see the divine officer
Strive for make-up exam qualification for Houchi
I don't know how big it is
For eighteen hundred years
No one has ever seen a divine official
What's more, the dark forest
You can't get through at all
Dark Forest
The dark forest is the only way to the shrine
I heard that everyone who has been there
Will lose one of the most important things
Someone broke his hand and foot
Some people are crazy
Someone's temperament has changed greatly
Even so
I'll have a try, too
Time and summer
Is there something wrong with your mind
Sacrifice yourself for the back pool make-up exam
He's doing this because of me
I must do my best to make up for it
No
I didn't expect Tiny to be such a person
Affectionate and righteous
What am I talking about
It's all her fault, little Martial Uncle
If you can really be the back pool
Win the qualification for the make-up exam
Your feud with our Yuhua School
It can be written off in one pen
Head
It's a deal
Help me hold off the magic statue
I'll be right back
Time and summer
This is it
Lord God lives in
In the shrine on the top of the mountain
If you want to see the divine officer, you must enter from this
Through the dark forest
Isn't it just a small cave
It's no big deal
You come out alive before you talk big, you
The Lord God
Is it male or female tall, short, fat and thin? What are your preferences
Can you provide some information
Tell you
Lord God has never been out of the shrine
Isn't this the same as not saying it
I won't waste time with you
I'll see you out
Wait a minute
Before going in
Is there anything you want to say
If I can't get out
Talk to the magic statue for me
I'm sorry
And
Tell Houchi for me
Just say I went home
I will definitely bring your words to you
Finally, I will send you a free message
Legend has it that the Palace of God is named after
A word from the Lord of God
If you have no desire, you will have no intention.
Thank you very much
Till we meet again
Loosen me
Let me count three
Don't let go and turn your face again
II
Brother, don't say anything
I know my brother cares about Sister Shisha
After these decent people leave,
Let's sneak into the dark forest
Go meet her
How is it
Do you really think so
Then I will feel at ease
Rest assured to the dark forest
There is this deity
Nothing is a problem
Loosen it
The back pool is slow to wake up
You can't be countered, can you
He was not countered
I gave him an injection a long time ago
Is to drink too much
I haven't touched a drop of wine in Bigu for two hundred years
I can't believe I was drunk before such an important exam
Before going down the mountain
What have you promised me
Such a small thing is screwed up
This, this
You have to blame the God official
Have to make an enchantment in Xianmo Town
I can't kill that witch if I want to
Just
Since it's summer to break into the dark forest,
Then look at the back pool
His own fortune
Dark Forest
Don't be afraid
Don't be afraid of the summer
You can even have a moment
Really regard me as my brother
Never
I lied to you
I'm a demon
We're the enemy
I don't care
All I know is that I recognize you as my sister
I will be like this contract symbol
Always shelter my sister from the wind and rain
He's doing this because of me
I must do my best to make up for it
I made it