My Dear Brothers
EP02
I allow you to stay with me.
(Is he acting a domineering president?)
Immortal,
I think you may misunderstand,
I'm here by accident.
I don't want to stay here.
I want to go home.
Go home?
What for?
A lot of things.
Go to school, do part-time job,
take exams, do internship,
play games, play with mobile phones,
eat snacks, and watch variety shows.
Don't you visit your brother?
He...
He's disappeared.
It doesn't matter.
Anyway, he's disappeared,
and I feel more free.
There is no one in this world
who will stay with another forever.
Isn't a brother supposed to protect his sister?
It used to be.
Stay here. I'll protect you.
Junior
Is there another immortal?
Hide yourself.
You can't be seen by him.
(Hide?)
(What a good chance for me to escape!)
(I won't just hide.)
Senior, what do you want me to do?
I haven't seen you for just one day,
your yard has got a wall.
And beautiful flowers.
It's a new method of practicing.
You yard
hasn't changed for about 200 years.
Today's change
is interesting.
Senior, if you have something to tell me, just say it here.
No.
I'm talking business with you today.
I am here today
to deworm for you.
There is no worm here.
It used to be none.
But now there are flowers and grass,
they will cause worms.
I remember you were afraid of worms most
when you were young.
Senior
Senior, I can do it myself.
I can help.
This brother looks very kind.
(It seems that his secret)
(is behind him.)
Sprinkle some in the room.
Senior
Wait.
Bro
What is that?
Dude
Can't you see me?
This is illegal imprison.
You are such a j*rk knowing enchantments.
J*rk?
What is j*rk?
The change of the clouds.
The spirit of the flowers and grass.
The rug of the mountains
and the waves of the sea.
They are all the same
with the journey to immortality.
This is what I learned from my recent practice.
It seems that you were concentrating on practicing.
But you're not experienced.
In your flowers,
most of them are female,
which are easy to attract insects.
Are the flowers divided into male and female?
Of course.
Everything in this world has yin and yang.
Do you know
why there's no female in Yuhua Sect?
The Master said
it's for calmness.
Females are like the female flowers in your yard.
There is
a strange breath all around her.
But in our Yuhua Sect,
we pursue the calmness.
The feminine breath is regarded as
the biggest culprit that disrupts practice.
What kind of absurd rules are these?
100 years ago,
there was a female who wanted to study from a master,
so she came to the ward at the foot of Mount Yuhua.
As a result, she was found by The owner,
and was sentenced to ten firewhips.
Okay, it's getting late.
I'll go back first.
It seems that
it is impossible for me to go back on my own.
But I can't be stuck here either.
I have to take the exams, do the internship,
and elect for the chairman of the Student Union.
And I also have to find my brother.
If my brother goes home but can't find me,
how anxious he would be!
(This Immortal is a super scholar,)
(he can send me back with the spells.)
(But, will he do that?)
Stay here. I'll protect you.
(That man,)
(he's weird with a bit of sincerity.)
(It's unfathomable.)
(How can I persuade him to send me back?)
I have a stomachache.
I must be poisoned.
Maybe I ate insecticide accidentally.
Help!
Take me down the mountain.
Take me to the hospital.
It doesn't matter.
Here is a detoxification pill made
by my Senior.
It's so bitter.
Immortal, you've been lived alone for so long,
you must feel bored.
Let's play a game.
Okay.
You promised?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
The winner can make a request,
and the one who lose is not allowed to refuse.
Okay.
(This is my strong point.)
(Shi Dong never beat me once.)
The rules are like this.
Let's start.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Best two out of three.
Best three out of five.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Paper, paper, paper.
Best 53 out of 53.
You win.
My request is...
No excessive request.
No embarrassed request.
No request of violating the law or discipline.
No request for infringement of privacy.
I just want to know
how your brother protects you.
(Is it a request?)
(He's so different.)
My brother,
he was an unlearned liar.
He could do nothing except playing games.
And he was good at fighting and getting into troubles.
He often spent all of our pocket money.
Then he asked me to pretend
I'm poor in front of the shop owner,
saying that I was an orphan,
and asked them to free of charge.
Before he dropped out of school,
every time he failed the exams,
he made me to ask our uncle and aunt to sign for him.
And,
he violently beat all the boys around me
who treated me nice.
He blocked all my love affairs.
He often went to Internet bars all night.
If it weren't for
that he would cook a few dishes,
he could tell a few bedtime stories,
and the baby doll
who accompanied me from childhood to adulthood,
I wouldn't bother to care about him.
I have said so much,
do you understand?
Cook,
bedtime stories,
and the doll.
There must be
a lot of ingredients left
by your Senior in that basket.
Junior, I'm so sorry.
I left the food container at your place accidentally.
You can handle it for me.
Friendly reminder,
there is the best pork belly in it,
and it is suitable to be made into
Braised Pork in Brown Sauce.
Hold on, Shi Xia.
I can do it.
I'm not hungry.
What is this smell?
It is on fire!
Awful cuisine?
Have a try.
It doesn't matter.
My master said
practice makes perfect.
Immortal, I believe you will be successful
if you practice repeatedly.
But I may not be able to live until that day.
Put out the fire by yourself.
Fortunately, there are two packs of instant noodles,
they really saved my life.
(The stupid guy.)
(I guess I can't count on him.)
(If the enchantments can bring me home,)
(then I can learn it.)
(I failed in cooking.)
(Is it because)
(I didn't get the method about how to use a sister?)
Senior
Please come to my place.
Junior
About girls,
it is complicated.
I must teach you in person.
Let me in and talk to you.
No need, Senior.
Just teach me here.
Do you want to know
how to make girls adore you?
Listen to you?
You are asking the right person.
I have some experience in this area.
To get a girl,
it takes three steps.
First,
establish your own glorious image.
Describe yourself
as outstanding as you can.
Girls have a mentality to worship the strong.
They can't resist the strong.
Second, showing your weakness.
Shape yourself a man
lonely and lack of love.
Girls have motherhood,
so they can't help caring about you.
Third, response to her every request.
Let every aspect of her life
has your traces.
Clear?
I'm survived.
Immortal
Have a try.
No, thanks.
I don't need to eat since I was born.
200 years?
Haven't you eaten a bite?
Your life has lost a lot of fun.
My master said
that was a lack of troubles.
Making you practice all day and not letting you eat,
did your master treat you as a human?
Don't speak ill of my master.
Immortal, if...
I mean, if
I want to learn some enchantments
of the Yuhua Sect,
like something that can open the ward.
Is it possible?
Maybe there's a chance,
but it will be difficult.
To get a girl,
you have to establish your own glorious image.
Let her worship you.
The Yuhua Sect has been established
for more than 2,000 years.
With the purpose of eliminating demons
and defending the way and supporting justice,
it has stood proudly in the world.
Five leaders of the Immortals Alliance
were from here,
and it was known as the leader
of all the Sects.
The enchantments of our Sect is broad and profound,
and it is difficult for ordinary people
to get its essence.
(Just a recitation of the school motto,)
(do you need to act like that?)
Do you have anything that can't be understood?
Immortal
I'm also a straight A student in my hometown,
can you try to teach me a little?
Eh...
What I practice is the superior enchantments
participating in the election of the leader
of the Immortals Alliance.
It doesn't suitable for you.
The head of the Immortals Alliance,
terrific.
It is true.
The head of the Immortals Alliance
is the supreme honor of the Sects.
A general election is held about every 200 years,
and the selected person
can enter the Otherworld Array,
to become a real immortal.
The latest general election is in this year.
If there's no accident,
the selected person will be
in Yuhua Sect again.
It will be
me.
Immortal,
you are really not humble.
What is humble?
Humble is
like what you do.
Speak out your excellence
without reservation.
(She also thinks I am excellent.)
(She admires me.)
Immortal
Do you have some textbooks here?
Books.
There's a lot in the attic.
Okay, I'll learn by myself.
What? Hou Chi suddenly stopped inedia?
He caught the cold and took medicine?
According to our observation in the past few days,
it seems like this.
I will ask him personally.
The owner is out.
Junior
Greetings, The owner.
Greetings!
What happened to Hou Chi?
Don't worry.
Hou Chi is your direct apprentice,
he had been outstanding since childhood.
It doesn't matter to have some changes.
Besides, it's less than a month
before the primary election
of the head of the Immortals Alliance,
we can't mess ourselves up.
It matters to the election,
it's better to find out what happened.
We can ask Bi Hong about that. They are close.
Ask Bi Hong to come to the hall.
I'm Bi Hong, the disciple of Yuhua,
pay my respect to Masters,
and The owner.
Bi Hong, do you see anything strange about Hou Chi lately?
Junior told me that he is trying
a new practice method recently.
A new practice method?
Did you ask him what the practice method is?
Junior is the hope of our entire Yuhua Sect.
What qualifications do I have
to intervene him?
According to your understanding about him,
you should be clear.
He has been practicing hard for 200 years,
and has never stepped out of the yard.
He only wanted to be the head
of the Immortals Alliance,
and did not think about other things.
I don't think it's necessary for you
to worry about him.
That's it.
The Yuhua Nine Layers of Hou Chi
has already cultivated to the eighth layers.
If he practices intensively,
he is very likely to break through to the ninth level
before the election.
What Yuan Gui said is right.
Then I understand.
Hou Chi chose the new practice method just
for making the breakthrough.
Junior, let him do that.
You may be excused now.
Take care of Hou Chi these days.
If you see anything strange,
report it immediately.
What else do you want to say?
Every time you called me in the past 200 years,
you just ask about Hou Chi.
Don't you have anything to ask about me?
Junior, that is your fault.
You should care more about Bi Hong.
After all, you two are father and son.
If you talk to him more,
he won't run down the mountain too much
to dispel loneliness.
A person without the immortal perception,
let him do whatever he wants.
Why should I bother in vain?
Masters
I don't know if I should say it or not.
Say it.
We heard that the Devil Sect
was spreading around,
saying that the Junior Master
was defeated by the Devil Lord.
And the head of the Immortals Alliance
this year must be the Devil Lord.
How could it be?
Hou Chi hasn't even been out of his yard,
how could he be defeated by the Devil Lord?
You descend the mountain quickly to find out
the truth of what the Devil Sect said.
Okay.
Senior Yuan Ye
Strengthen all the wards in Mount Yuhua.
Yes.
Yes, Master.
The enchantment about how to
speed across the sky.
The enchantment about how to drive the sword.
The enchantment about space-time reversal.
After learning this,
I could be able to open the ward.
I want to read.
I want this book.
(I made a breakthrough today.)
(Could it be that the sister played a role?)
(I still need to work harder.)
Step forward with your right foot,
bend your knees into a right lunge.
Make a fist with your right hand
and raise it to the upper front.
Isn't this just military physical boxing?
It's already the ninth layers. Why...
The enchantment of breaking the virtual space.
After you learned this enchantment,
you can walk freely between time and space.
It wouldn't be limited by the past and the future.
This enchantment is exquisite and profound,
it is the highest secret enchantment,
and it can not be recorded here.
It's already a quarter to ten.
You have to go to bed.
Got it.
It really is the healthiest daily schedule.
Immortal
Don't be too stingy.
I can't sleep with the light off.
What do you want to do?
Stay away from me.
Stay there.
Didn't you say that
your brother told you the bedtime stories?
I can also do it.
On the coast of the East Sea,
there is an eighth-layer Yulin beast.
It is huge and 32 feet tall.
The passing friars were all killed by it.
And then?
It died.
How?
My master led it to this yard,
and a righteous cultivator with the same name as me
killed it.
That's all?
What do you think?
The ending is a little hasty.
I know you haven't heard enough.
I'll tell you one more.
There was a devil cultivator in Yulin City.
He specialized in grasping the souls
of living people,
practicing thousands ghost flags
to improve his cultivation.
There were countless ghosts
died in his hands.
And then?
My master led him to this yard,
and a righteous cultivator with the same name as me
killed him.
You want to listen more?
I'll tell you one more.
There was once a traitor in Jiyue Sect.
He practiced sorcery, fell into the devil way,
and killed his masters.
And my master...
Led him into this yard,
and a righteous cultivator with the same name as you
killed him.
How did you know?
After all,
they were all killed by you.
These are trifles, not worth mentioning.
Just one day, I have made great progress.
Sister, is really extraordinary.
What kind of protection do you need?
Protection?
Don't be silly.
Do you know what protection is?
It's really not easy to protect one person.
I just want to get a good sleep.
Please don't bother me.
(Although she has no requirements,)
(I still need to work hard.)
The owner
I went down the mountain these days and found
that the Devil Sect was spreading rumors
about the Devil Lord defeated the Junior Master.
They also printed the process of battle
on the booklet.
There are also the picture version
for the people who don't know words.
I heard
that the Devil Lord is rehearsing a show.
And it will be touring around before
the selection of the leader of the Immortals Alliance.
What do people under the mountain say?
Be honest.
They said that
this is the first time that the Devil Sect
has joined in the selection
in the 2,000 years.
And they defeated the Junior Master
who is well-expected.
They thought that
it's fate.
Leave me alone.
Alright.
It is not so great to use the enchantments
to make it.
Here you are.
What kind of ghost is it?
Have you seen the ghosts?
Didn't I see him every day these two days?
Don't worry. This doll will accompany you from now on.
This doll?
I will have nightmares with it.
I don't like it.
Why does she get angry?
Junior Master, The owner is coming.
The Leading Master
Is it the man
who whips others?
Hide yourself.
Okay, I will hide well.
Don't let your master come in.
Master
I wanted to see you
as soon as I stopped the closed-door practice.
What do you do recently?
Everything is fine.
Such a big problem, how long are you
going to hide about it?
(Oh, no. Master found the girl.)
Master, please listen to me.
It's the fact.
You don't need to explain.
I broke the rules,
and I should be punished without any complaint.
But, she's not a bad guy.
The Devil Lord secretly attacked you
without moral,
and you still thought that he is a good guy?
The Devil Lord?
It scared me.
I heard that
you are not doing inedia recently,
and got a cold.
Were you hurt badly by him?
I'm fine.
It was because I distracted for a while,
and then got into the Devil Lord's trap.
Go into the house,
let me see your injury.
(What? He wants to come in?)
Master, let's go to the Holy tree.
(The expression of his Master)
(is like a roller coaster.)
( My heart nearly stopped beating.)
It's just a little injury, don't need to bother you.
Concentrate and calm your mind, put your heart and power together.
Master
You lost
a lot of Holy Power to heal me.
It doesn't matter.
Your heart was hurt by the Devil Lord,
so the wound would not heal for a long time.
I am worried that this
will affect the election.
Chi
You are the only hope of our Yuhua Sect.
You must be careful.
I won't slight it.
These vines
were made for you by Bi Hong, right?
What a fool!
He just loves to care for these flowers and plants,
and attracts the attention of women.
It's not my Senior.
You don't have to speak for him.
Chi
When I was in the closed-door practice,
I got something new.
Let's swap our ideas about it.
Listening to the conversation
between him and his master,
he is like a pure
and unpretentious practicing machine.
Did I really misunderstand him?
Why should I care so much?
Get me out of here.
Get me out of here!
Brother!
Sorry.
I had a nightmare.
It doesn't matter.
Did your master punish you because of me?
That's me disappointed them.
You are pitiful.
200 years,
you just know about the practice.
You're like a machine.
The sorrow of a super scholar.
Quality education has a long way to go.
Wait me for a while.
This is for you.
For me?
The second place in the exam can also be rewarded.
Let me tell you.
Squeeze it when you feel stressed.
It can help you release your pressure.
And you can also eat it.
So perfect.
This object is not recorded in the books.
This is my gift for you.
Isn't it the first time
you have received a gift from someone else?
Can I give you a gift, too?
What do you want to give to me?
Is there anything you want to do,
but your brother never did it for you?
Yes.
What is that?
The Ferris wheel.
The Ferris wheel?
The Ferris wheel can lift people
from the ground to a very high altitude,
and you can overlook the panoramic view
of the entire scenic spot.
So easy.
Let's go.
Why do you bring me here?
Immortal
What is that for?
It might be the Yuhua College.
It might be?
Haven't you been there before?
My master said
that is a training place for ordinary cultivators.
It's not suitable for me.
What I practice is different from theirs.
What are the differences?
We should go back.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
Miss
I have something to ask you.
Is he going to confess?
Can I be...