[English subtitles are available]
[Forever and Ever]
[Episode 23]
It's almost time.
We should go back.
Give me some more time.
There's no hurry.
I don't know if I'll get to see
this beautiful scenery in the future.
Don't be silly.
You're going to Shanghai for treatment.
When you recover,
you'll come back.
You should stay in your room.
What are you doing out here?
I wanted to enjoy the sun.
Have you packed her things?
Yes.
I've put them in the car.
It's a long walk from here to the car.
Being in a wheelchair looks sad,
let me carry you.
All right.
Here.
Hold me tight.
Hold tight now.
Are you not going with me?
No.
Silly, of course I'll go with you.
I've asked them to make a stew,
so you can have it on the way.
I'll go get it. Wait for me.
What's wrong?
Wenxing's illness has suddenly deteriorated.
She transferred to a hospital in Shanghai today.
Which hospital is she in?
The one you were admitted to last time.
Will she undergo surgery?
She still have to wait for a compatible donor
for a heart transplant.
The earliest time would be next month.
Should we
postpone our wedding?
She has been asking me
and my mother every day
if she can see us getting married
before her surgery.
Actually I think
our wedding is just at the right time.
You don't have to
give yourself too much pressure.
Let's go visit her tomorrow.
Long time no see, bride-to-be.
Please sit down, Mrs. Wang.
Okay.
I heard you became ill.
How are you now?
I'm fine.
Young Master Zhou
is a bit impatient.
Your wedding is too soon,
which doesn't leave me
enough time to work.
That's why
I only have six gowns here,
and they are still initial samples.
I think
I will have to come back another 3 to 4 times.
Have a look, maybe you'll like one of them.
Next time when you finish the dress,
just tell us in advance,
we'll go over to your place.
No need for that.
You just recovered and should take care.
And since Wenxing
is in a hospital in Shanghai,
I get to see you both
when I come here.
Did Wang Man come today?
She's in Shanghai,
but
she's pregnant and needs to rest.
Mrs. Wang, have a cup of water.
Thank you.
You two newly-weds must have a lot to talk about
when she tries out the gowns.
I'll give you guys some space then.
Let me help you.
All right.
Have a look at them.
Wang Man is pregnant.
Who's the father?
Zhou Wenchuan.
I don't know much about
what happened
between Tong Jiaren and Zhou Wenchuan.
Try on the dresses first.
Grandmother.
Have some water.
Thank you.
Mr. Wang.
You'll feel sad
staying in the room all day.
You should go out more often.
OK, Grandmother.
I'll go downstairs and take a walk after meal.
Good.
Wenxing,
I brought something for you.
Sweet green rice balls.
I've been craving for them these days.
Have a taste.
How is it?
It's good!
That person you spoke about,
when is his birthday?
Are you almost done?
I've kept my regular customers waiting
to make yours first.
He was born in November, a Scorpio.
November.
Doctor Lin said we still have to wait.
I didn't see you just now,
I thought you didn't come today.
I went to meet the doctor.
Wenxing said she wanted to walk Mrs. Wang out
and catch some sunshine.
That should be fine, right?
That's fine.
You guys don't come often,
go spend time with her.
There are still a few reports not out yet.
I'll go ask.
All right.
Let's go.
Yeah.
My birthday is in lunar September.
That's soon.
I hope I can have my surgery done
before that.
Even better if I can make it home before that.
You will.
Lunar September
is the month of chrysanthemum, right?
The alternative names of September and December
are the easiest to remember.
One is when chrysanthemums bloom,
called the month of chrysanthemum.
The other is when everything is covered in ice and snow,
called the month of ice.
When I was little,
I was forced to remember these.
But now I've forgot all of them.
You don't have to use them,
it doesn't matter.
But Mei Xing likes these things.
The sentence you wrote about his secondary name,
he remembers it even until now.
When willow drops its leaves and the lotus fades, the plum is still blossoming.
He's in his thirties already,
but still single,
would he be single
for the rest of his life?
Chen,
how many girlfriends do you think he's had?
I've never asked him about that,
how should I know?
Liar.
Your wedding
has to be big.
I will definitely attend it.
Definitely.
Take care of yourself first.
When your test report is good,
take the surgery immediately.
It's all right to take the surgery later.
What if my favorite guy
is not you any more
after I get a
new heart?
I don't care about that.
All I care about is your health.
Shi Yi,
how do you stand him?
He's abnormally rational.
What can I do? I have to accept that.
Wenxing likes Mei Xing?
I can tell.
You can tell?
It's actually the most difficult
to hide your feelings for someone.
You can easily tell
who a girl has feelings for.
Through her
gaze, behavior,
and the way she speaks.
So in the past, when a girl likes you,
you just ignored them?
I rejected all of them.
Every single one.
Does Mei Xing like Wenxing?
I don't know.
You don't know?
We've
never talked about this.
Wenxing is your sister,
you should care for her at least.
The most difficult thing in life
is when both party have feelings for each other.
That wasn't like something
you would say.
Mei Xing said that.
All right. Try it again.
Is it still crooked?
No.
Then
what shall we do next?
What do you want to do?
I want...
I'm hungry.
Then let's go out and eat.
Go out?
The weather report said
it would rain this evening.
The rain and us having food does not oppose each other.
Yes, my hubby is always right.
Let's tidy this up.
You scared me.
Why aren't you asleep?
I couldn't sleep, so I'm watching a movie.
Horror movies are not for you.
Have you taken your medicine?
Try to sleep then.
You stink of alcohol.
Wait.
It's cold outside.
Don't you feel cold wearing that?
No.
It's be around ten degrees these couple of days.
This will be just right.
I don't wear suits to the institute.
Why?
It's too formal.
But I think
you look good in suits.
[Stay Simple and Humble]
Oh yes, my mother asked me
the exact date of our wedding.
She wanted to inform our relatives.
I told her we hadn't decided yet.
But we have.
I thought about it all night,
and I still think that
we should postpone our wedding until Wenxing's surgery has been done.
Before that
you will be
worried about Wenxing,
and so will I.
It just doesn't feel right.
I'm also not in the mood
to decide on the wedding dishes
or send out invitations.
Come on, listen to your wife.
Okay.
Uncle Lin is picking you up?
He's already downstairs.
Off you go.
Bye.
See you.
I really want to get married to him.
With Du Feng?
Who else?
How far have you two gone?
Isn't it too early to talk about marriage?
Well, someone here got engaged
before she kissed him.
I'm different.
At least we've chated via email for half a year.
What made you
want to marry him?
What is it...?
He has good personality.
I'm sure it's not superficial.
I can feel that.
Unlike your scientist.
Your scientist
seems rather unworldly.
He feels too distant.
Really?
Using the term "unworldly"
to describe a man,
seems kind of weird.
Anyway, it's like
he doesn't really care about
anything.
Are you guys
a good fit for each other?
Very good?
Or not at all?
Let's talk about something else.
Why avoid this?
A few days apart
and you aren't telling me anything.
You don't understand.
To me,
even he's just there at home
or in the study,
I'm happy
just looking at him
by his side.
No, I don't even have to look at him,
just thinking that he's mine
makes me happy.
Fine.
Is it good?
Enjoy your meal.
I need to head out.
Where are you going?
A business meal.
You said you were here in Shanghai to accompany me,
actually you are here for my brother,
to help him with his great manufacturing industry dream.
I'll come back as early as I can,
okay?
How early will that be?
Eleven.
Before eleven.
Wait,
this is for you.
What is it?
Poison.
Poison? You want to poison me?
Hangover medicine.
So you won't feel that bad
after drinking.
Half past ten.
Give me a second.
I'll give you something else.
All right, all right.
I'll be back by ten.
I'll be back ten sharp.
I'm heading off.
Hurry up and finish your meal.
Mr. Mei.
Mr. Mei treats you
differently now.
He treats me as his own sister.
Of course it'll be different.
Actually family relationship is better.
You can never give up on your family.
But love is way weaker.
I've always been eating alone
since I got admitted.
Will you eat with me today?
The food was prepared for you,
I shouldn't eat it.
You dislike me.
You little heartless brat,
I'm doing what's best for you.
Fine, I'll eat with you.
Wait for me,
I'll go get a pair of chopsticks from the nurses.
You guys came.
What's Wenxing doing?
She's having dinner.
I want to talk to her alone.
Go find somewhere to sit with Song.
She's pregnant, so she can't stand for a long time.
All right.
She hasn't eat much.
Try to get her to eat
when you talk to her.
These are ice cream moon cakes.
Remember to put them in a fridge.
Thanks.
How are you? Any better today?
Yes, I feel better.
I brought your favorite
claypot rice.
I was just saying
that I had been eating alone.
Now you're here.
Here.
Here you go.
Has Shi Yi moved out?
She's watching TV.
Yanyan.
You had the strings changed?
Let me take a look.
Thank you.
The strings are a bit too loose.
I'll change them tomorrow.
You spoiled brat.
Remember the brand
you're used to
and keep using that.
Leave the Guzheng here.
I'll find some time to tune it for you tonight.
Great.
What's his name?
Zhousheng Chen.
Are you guys
in a relationship?
Yes.
I'll give you some wedding candies when we get married.
Thank you, honey.
I didn't expect
you could play so well.
Was it good?
Very.
Very good?
Very good.
Next time I'll bring my Guzheng from home
and play something for you.
Okay.
Hello?
Chen.
Wenchuan.
We're at a hospital,
calm down.
You better pray
nothing bad happens to Wenxing!
Why did you hit him?
You should ask him that question!
Let's go.
Here are the true results.
Data which have not been altered.
If not for this,
she could have had her surgery the night before.
Also,
your younger brother came in the evening
and had a big fight with Wenxing
in her room!
He must have lost his mind!
How can he disregard
the patient's welfare!
Doctor Lin.
How's Wenxing?
Not good.
Something happened just now.
I've already called the police.
The police?
What happened?
You should ask Wenchuan that.
Madam, the police are here
to take Wenchuan's statement.
Chen, you should go check.
He's ill-tempered,
he can't handle it.
He should handle this himself.
He's your younger brother.
I only have one sister.
And she's in there
fighting for her life!
Let's go.
What had happened?
Wenxing's pre-op tests were not good enough
because Zhou Wenchuan altered the data.
Who told you that?
Doctor Lin.
He's Wenxing's
primary doctor,
so he knows Wenxing's condition
better than anyone else.
He had a feeling that there was something wrong.
So he redid the tests,
and found out
that the data was altered.
Why?
Doesn't Wenchuan know that
she needs the surgery as soon as possible?
He wanted everyone
to focus on
Wenxing's surgery,
so that he could cover up
the problems in his accounts.
Regarding the mismatch
in these company accounts,
go back and check again.
You can go now.
Okay.
[Zhousheng Chen]
Coming.
Come in.
You guys talk.
I'll leave you guys alone.
What happened?
I'm sorry.
I got a little bit emotional.
It's late.
You two should rest.
I need a bath.
I'll put your clothes here.
Let me wash your hair, okay?
I know you are sad.
I just don't know
how to comfort you.
Shi Yi,
will you give me a hug?
Sure.
Wenxing will be fine.
She'll be all right.
Don't be too worried.
It breaks my heart
to see you like this.
Zhousheng Chen,
I love you.
I love you, too.
You're here.
You didn't sleep last night?
Wenxing
is not doing well.
You should see her.
Sorry for what happened last night.
I broke your tea cup.
It's okay. It's just a tea cup.
Mei Xing,
I don't know
if I should say this
now.
Wenxing...
Don't worry.
After her surgery,
I'll take her away
from the Zhou family
and take good care of her.
She will get well quicker
if she knows you said that.
But I have to help Zhousheng Chen
accomplish what he wants to do.
Maybe I had
owed him something in the previous life.
That's why I need to follow him
no matter what.
The previous life...
There were a lot who owed him in the previous life.
Everyone around him
would give their hearts to him.
Shi Yi,
about the tune names before...
I know.
Don't get me wrong,
I just want to say that
I've already
let it go.