[English subtitles are available]
[Forever and Ever]
[Episode 27]
[Abide by Morality and Benevolence]
Who brought you here?
My brother, Anyun.
I'm grounded here
and can't go out to see you.
Sorry you had to travel
a long way here.
Wang Anyun may be a good tailor,
but not a caring brother.
It's getting cold, yet he failed
to remind you to put on more clothes.
We came here by car. It's not cold on the way.
[Abide by Morality and Benevolence]
Do you have everything you need
while staying here?
Though I'm not allowed to get out,
I'm still my second uncle's
favorite nephew.
Don't worry.
The hundreds of households here all belong
to the Zhou clan.
No one will give me a hard time.
Have you eaten yet?
No.
I'll take you to pot cover noodles.
[Abide by Morality and Benevolence]
Let's go.
You should have some.
I've eaten. I just wanna keep you company.
Go on.
I'm not hungry.
Are you on a diet?
You need to get more nutrition.
Don't try to lose weight.
No. I'm not on a diet.
Get your passport ready.
It'll be the Mid-Autumn Festival in two days.
That's when we'll leave.
My grandma will have her birthday celebration during the Mid-Autumn Festival.
All the relatives will come visit.
The Wang family,
the Qin family, and the Mei family
will come as well.
That'd be the best opportunity for us.
I know you don't want
to leave your grandma and your brothers.
But this could be
the last chance we have.
It's okay if you can't get your passport.
I'll figure something out.
What's this?
Take a look.
I made them.
They look good,
but the taste is average.
Is there something on your mind?
Have a taste first.
Try one.
Ever since we were little,
you've always been nice and good to me.
When we argued,
I never gave in
until you apologized first.
You've never
done me wrong.
As for the breakup and marriage,
it was my mistake as much as yours.
But living in this world,
we can't think only of ourselves.
We need to consider our family,
our friends,
the rights and wrongs,
and good and evil.
I guess you know where I'm going with this.
The noodles are getting soggy.
I can't convince myself to do that.
For the sake of Wenxing
and my family,
I cannot see you anymore!
Wang Man.
Come back!
[Family of Books and Rituals]
Shi Yi.
Look!
The moon is so bright and shiny tonight.
It's so pleasant
to look at it!
You don't have to keep me company.
Go ahead
and tuck my great grandson
in.
Grandma, he's asleep already.
Kids go to bed early.
It is his bedtime.
My great grandson... Um...
Um...
What's his name again?
Talk about my bad memory!
I... I forgot his name again!
His name is...
Mushi, Zhou Mushi.
Mushi!
Lovely name!
I remember now!
Grandma,
it's cold at night.
Let's go inside and rest.
All right! Okay!
Careful.
Hello? Mom.
It's thundering.
Don't put the crabs next to the window.
They'll be scared.
Thundering?
It's not thundering here.
I know.
Don't worry.
Even if it's thundering,
your crabs will be safe.
Where's Dad?
He's blowing air towards the crabs
with a fan.
He said they are
sea crabs,
so mimicking sea wind would be good for them.
By the way, do you
want me to walk
the crabs, too?
I mean, they stay
in the glass tank all day long.
Will they develop
depression over time?
Other people worry that they'd escape.
You, however, want to walk them!
Alright, I'm hanging up now.
Have a good night's sleep!
Bye-bye!
You had a long chat today, didn't you?
I also went to the opera.
You did?
I had to.
My mother and second uncle had something to discuss.
I couldn't just leave the guests alone
at the theater,
so I stayed
and kept them company.
Oh, I forgot to ask you.
Why the name Zhou Mushi?
I think Zhousheng Mushi
sounds a little awkward.
Zhou Mushi is catchier.
Changing the family name for the given name.
What if your mom despises you for that?
It'll be fine.
I have the final say on that.
Do you want a child?
Yeah.
How many do you want?
Do you want a boy
or a girl?
I'm fine with both.
It'd be great if it's a twin.
Two at a time. How convenient!
♫In the memory♫
One looks like you, and the other looks like me.
♫The snow-covered city tower♫
That's exactly my thought!
♫When your name rings out♫
I think tonight is perfect
for making babies,
♫Finally blooming again♫
right?
♫Like a flower of the soul♫
♫The dreams that have accompanied me through the light years♫
♫I know that with just one glance♫
♫I can be sure that is the destination♫
♫Not afraid to fall for you♫
♫Running to the world with you♫
I'm ready.
♫In the poem to be continued to write in the rest of my life♫
♫With your name in each line♫
♫If it started all over again♫
♫I'd still remember our love♫
♫It took♫
♫Hundreds of centuries♫
♫For our love to begin♫
Then, let's do it.
♫There's no way it'd end♫
♫May there be a right time and a right place♫
♫For the ones in love to hug each other♫
♫How can I let go♫
♫When all my expectations are lost♫
♫If the fate had been kind to me♫
♫If I'd had enough time♫
♫Would I have been able♫
♫To hold on to my love♫
♫How am I supposed to live without you♫
♫How can I fall in love again after the farewell♫
Wenchuan,
what are you doing staying up this late?
♫The impulse and courage we once had have gone with wind♫
I'm not sleepy.
Fourth Great-uncle, please go to sleep first.
I'll go to bed soon.
♫The smile I remember♫
♫Has become a pain that never goes away♫
These are all the keys
to the Zhou's mansion.
Give them to Shi Yi.
I have only one request.
Treat your younger brother well.
I want
to have a talk with you tonight.
Grandma is asleep?
I want to ask for an official
wedding gift from you.
What gift?
The library.
To be specific,
it's a wall in the library.
Could you ask them
to prepare an ink brush and some ink for me?
I don't need Xuan Paper.
Great-uncle...
Liansui.
Please ask Lin Fei to prepare ink brush and ink
and take them to the library.
The library?
Are you going there to admire the moon?
I'll prepare some snacks for you!
It's not necessary.
Then what's the point of making that many?
I'll prepare some for you guys, anyway!
Lin,
I've had them
mow the lawn.
It looks much nicer, doesn't it?
You've been of great help
to the Zhous since you came.
I'm flattered.
Are you two taking a walk after your meal?
We are.
Where are you going?
What's this for?
Take a guess.
What's that?
Ink.
Ink?
What do you need that for?
It will be hard to clean
if it stains the floor.
Someone asked us
to prepare it
so that he could please his wife.
Just leave it be.
The entire residence will be theirs in the future.
It's not our business even if they want
to tear the house down.
See you!
Be careful.
Okay.
Careful. Don't spill it.
Young people
don't listen to us, anyway.
Yeah.
Cook a few more dishes
for dinner tonight.
Let's have a drink.
Why do I
have to cook?
I don't know how to cook.
I would do it if I knew.
So, all you can do is eat, huh?
Fine. Let's go.
You've had an idea about what to write?
The library is over 100 years old.
You are the first person who's ever
wanted to write something on the wall.
Will you sit there and keep me company?
Sure.
[Fu]
[Fu on the]
[Fu on the Imperial Park]
Are you tired?
Do you want some water?
No. I'm good.
[Fu on the Imperial Park]
You don't remember the next line?
The next line is "Beauty and soul are given,"
"the heart is overturned."
Seriously. That is the next line.
I know.
Then why don't you write it?
My hand is sore.
Is this the reason why you once asked me
at the Azure Dragon Temple
if I've seen an old-fashioned library?
Of course not.
Back then,
I thought you were just a researcher.
You were right.
I am just a researcher.
Writing on the wall
is so different
from writing on the paper.
I can't afford to make any mistakes.
With paper, at least I can change it and rewrite it.
With a piece of wall, though,
I can't just rebuild a wall.
I was even sweating.
So, you are going to stop for today?
I'll finish it some other time.
Would you like me
to walk you back?
I still have something
to discuss with my mother.
Let's go.
[Fu on the Imperial Park]
Uncle Mei, I'll go in first.
We've got many important guests.
It'll be improper if you and Shi Yi
don't go and greet them.
You can take care of it all by yourself.
I've faced them for over 20 years.
Of course I can handle it well.
But are you going
to hide Shi Yi forever?
Sure, I can still do it for a few more years.
But one day I'll be too old to do it.
What are you
gonna do then?
You must
have something important
to talk to me.
The police
went to Mei Xing today and asked him
to assist with investigating Zhou Wenchuan.
About what happened to Wenxing?
It's not about the hospital.
It's about Zhou Wenchuan's
illegal fundraising and smuggling.
Uncle Mei is outside right now.
He wants to see you.
He said he had been
a close friend to you and my father
for years.
Considering this friendship,
he's willing to represent
Zhou Wenchuan.
However,
on one condition.
Mother,
you need to convince Zhou Wenchuan to turn himself in.
Let me think about this.
Well?
She needs time to think about it.
From the suspicion of Wenchuan and Wenxing's births,
to your father's death
and the death of Ren's mother,
she managed to go
through every major incident.
This isn't something an ordinary person can do.
You go back.
You shouldn't get involved
in something like this.
I'll stay here.
I will talk to her
after she calms down.
Thank you, Uncle Mei.
Second uncle.
Song, what did she say?
She said
she wouldn't meet anybody.
Are Mr. Mei and Zhousheng Xing
still there?
They never left.
They are still downstairs.
Every time I see you,
I wanna have a chat with you.
But then I realize
that we really have nothing to talk about.
Then forget about it.
We are not young anymore.
Why bother?
Song, how is she doing?
She didn't sleep
or eat last night.
I'm really worried about her health.
Uncle Mei,
second uncle,
the two of you have been waiting for a whole night.
Please go back and rest.
Go bring Wenchuan back.
Zhousheng Xing.
Let Song go with you.
He'll get suspicious
if you go alone.
[Profound Reasoning Requires Great Knowledge]
Lin,
how did you sleep
last night?
I slept
pretty well.
I didn't!
How come?
You didn't cook for me!
And you didn't drink, right?
Then, tonight,
let's have a drink together.
How long has this theater been closed?
When was the last time it was open?
Do you remember, Lin?
Stop nagging!
Open the door.
They are waiting to clean it.
Hurry!
All right.
Let me sing something for you.
Sing something? Good!
Here it goes.
♫I hereby present you this kasaya♫
Come in.
[Profound Reasoning Requires Great Knowledge]
♫Which emits glowing rays♫
♫Guiding your way to the West♫
Fourth great-uncle.
What brings you here?
I'm here to check on my uncle.
Uncle.
You are eating?
Have you visited the Wang family?
Yes.
But...
Uncle,
I think you should just let it go.
They wouldn't meet anyone
from the Zhou family.
I managed to trick her
to come out yesterday,
but she went back right away
when she saw it was me.
By the way, Uncle,
cars with license plates
that they are unfamiliar with
can't get in the town at all.
We've tried many times,
but we were stopped at the entrance every time.
I think you may
have to find another way
to get out of this town.
I'm not leaving.
But...
didn't you say we'd leave on the Mid-Autumn Festival?
Again, I'm not leaving!
Uncle, just because of a woman
who dumped you,
are you really...
All right. I'll zip it.
Then enjoy your meal. I'm leaving.
Fourth great-uncle, I'm leaving.
Is this your lunch
or dinner?
As one who has nothing to do,
does it matter when I eat?
Your mother wants you to go back today.
Stop eating.
We are having a birthday banquet.
There's plenty of good food.
Save your appetite for later.
Second uncle.
You won't go back?
No.
I'll be at the ancestral temple tonight.
[Family of Books and Rituals]
Grandma, careful!
Grandma.
How is Man doing?
Let's go, Grandma.
[Family of Books and Rituals]
Mother.
Kneel!
I asked them to bring you back
because I have a few questions for you.
In Germany,
your brother and Shi Yi...
I did it.
Are you involved in illegal fundraising?
I planned it.
Why do you need that much money?
Why didn't you tell me
if you were in trouble?
I've had some problems
with the business these years.
I was going
to remedy the situation
with the family's savings
by saying it was for overseas investment.
But you know what happened after that.
My brother made it impossible for me to do so.
I thought
after marrying Tong Jiaren,
I'd get your support.
But you didn't do anything wrong.
You just protected
the entire Zhou family at my cost.
As for my second uncle,
I can't rely on him at all.
Knowing you as well as I do,
I'm sure you didn't
bring me back just for
my grandma's birthday banquet.
You wanna send me to prison.
Right?
Mr. Mei
is willing to represent you.
But he hopes
you can turn yourself in.
Fine.
I will do so.
I'm done. It's all yours.
Okay.
[Invitation]
The short life is like a dream.
How often can one enjoy himself?
Only my love, Shi Yi,
deserves my lifelong pursuit.
[The short life is like a dream. How often can one enjoy himself? Only my love, Shi Yi, deserves my lifelong pursuit.]
♫Maybe it's the snow falling without a sound♫
What is it?
I miss you.
♫Maybe it's the flower in the mirror without a trace♫
That's out of the blue!
Is there a rule about when I can miss you?
♫I've seen all the scenes of the passing years♫
You are acting weird.
♫They're not as good as you, not as good as you♫
Not really!
I want to talk to you
about my working plan.
♫I look at a ripple♫
Okay, go ahead. I'm all ears.
♫It's like there's no wind and no sunshine♫
Originally I was going to open
a studio in Xi'an in two years.
But now I've changed my mind.
♫The more silent my love becomes♫
The dubbing industry
has been developing rapidly in recent years,
online or offline.
♫The more my heart turns to rain♫
Since I love Xi'an so much, I should
go there early and get a head start.
♫There is grace in your eyebrows♫
I'll work in both Shanghai and Xi'an.
The old studio can help the new one to grow.
♫I'll spend my whole life looking for it♫
Miss Shi,
you really can't wait
to mark your territory, can you?
♫Don't blame me for the sporadic sweet talk♫
Mark my territory? You think I'm a bandit?
♫I wake up from my dreams and I'm even colder♫
If I were a bandit,
I'd make you my wife!
♫My heart that can't stand being away from love♫
I don't mind.
As long as you build
♫Hides nothing from you♫
a lab on the mountain for me.
♫The scene I look down for♫
♫Gets clear after saying goodbye♫
♫Every glimpse means missing you♫
♫Even if to be a stranger to you♫
What are you doing?
I'm taking advantage of you.
Today you really...
Love you even more!