I need a batch of clams from Liaodong
tyranny of women's blood discord
you find out
Arrive in Beijing in August and September
Yes
Free at kisskh.me
Your Highness
This herbal remedy for qi and blood
Physician Sheng told you
How do they know how to distinguish medicinal materials
what brought you here
don't help
Yes
If shipped to Beijing in September
Probably sun-dried
drying
This
This is locked
should be this
help people over
Yes
Thank you Your Highness
Jin Yiwei is really Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon
Wait another half an hour before leaving
Your Highness Your Highness
humiliation is wrong
I follow you to protect your highness
take away
Free at kisskh.me
Your Highness
Your Highness, come back
no
Does this help or not?
what are you two looking at?
come help me
wait half an hour
Okay
queen
Concubines see the emperor
more revealing
poor health
What do you want to see me
ask your majesty's permission
Quansheng Imperial Physician
Continue to diagnose illnesses for your concubine
He had given the queen a prescription before
nearly lead to life
Fortunately, the dragon is safe
I leave him alive
It's already gracious
How could the queen believe him?
The concubine believes that Imperial Physician Sheng
Imperial Physician Sheng did not deceive His Majesty.
is pregnant or sick
Concubine, don't you understand?
ask your majesty's permission
Imperial Physician Sheng continued to treat me
queen concubine
Dai Yuan sentenced him to be proficient in women's prescriptions
How can a mere ximai be misdiagnosed?
If you believe that quack
In case of injury to Long Si
Then who is to blame?
There is no His Majesty the Dragon
It's a big deal
nature cannot be ignored
queen concubine
You go back and rest in peace
Then announce how the imperial physician asks for the Ping An pulse for you
Safety
within three days
I'll be pissed at this
where is peace
queen
stand up
Happiness is a great thing
How can you be full of nonsense
father emperor
The queen is upset
will speak ominously
please forgive me
Help your mother back to the palace
His Majesty
I married into the royal family when I was fifteen
Served His Majesty for over twenty years
gave birth to three sons and a daughter
i don't ask for anything else
Just ask your majesty
look at me
Dedicate your life to serving you
allow me to be willful once
just once
I want to see Imperial Physician Sheng
i want to live
beg your majesty
I ordered the Tai Hospital to consult for you
isn't it just saving your life?
All women in the world have to give birth
I've never seen you so crazy
queen
have you given birth
Can you tolerate a quack doctor misdiagnosing
let us lose one
hard-earned child?
all consequences
I will do my best
beg your majesty
The Empress Empress is the Lord of the Six Houses
Mother in the world
How can you say something so bizarre
Birth of an heir to the royal family
It is the primary responsibility of the concubines of the harem
If you change your concubine
The concubine is willing to risk her life to save the dragon's womb
How could the queen concubine
can't stand the pain
His Majesty
Moonlit night cold
You can no longer tolerate the empress
so sloppy
If it really hurts Long Si
How is that good?
Help the Queen back to Kunning Palace
retransmission
Calling all imperial physicians for consultation
His Majesty
beg your majesty
i hurt
please help me
His Majesty
go
this hour
go quickly
Yes
queen
Come
The concubine lost her temper today
beg your majesty's forgiveness
Concubine resigns
before the imperial examination
Always praise the queen for being obedient and wise
I also use her as my helper everywhere
How did the queen become today
like another person
in this way
so arbitrary
irresponsible
His Majesty
Wu Cairen
The Empress is not here today
please come back
I won't go in and disturb
I'm standing here
Wait for the queen to get better
I'll go in and say hello
come in with me
go down first
Your Highness
What's in that sack?
Will it still move?
come back
come back now
I'm not a doctor
what a hindrance here
Then you just let the female officer Mei
No matter how persuaded he refused to leave
Don't let His Highness see it with your own eyes
I serve here
how do i go
So that the princess is beautiful in front of her
Now is the critical moment
you can't leave
in this deep palace
Pampering must be less but not more
no less than me
let's go
Mother
Your Highness
Free at kisskh.me
Zhanyong Zhanchang and Jiaxing
crying to see you
they are worried about you
But I have had them sent back first
until you feel better
let them come over to greet you
Okay
Mother
This time I brought Sheng Yin here
Take your own pulse
His Royal Highness
Your Majesty has decreed
Sheng Yin is not allowed to enter the palace again
Your Highness
it's illegal
rules are important
or mother's life is important
Sheng Yin
Yes
I
how
Your Highness
Thank you for being decisive
If three more days
Hua Tuo can't be cured
Sheng imperial doctor
The lady's condition is really serious
The Empress's pulse is tight
lethargy
neither slippery vein nor pregnancy
But the meridian is blocked
poor blood
Dang Yi Tao Ren Cheng Qi Soup
Hedidang decoction for promoting blood circulation and removing blood stasis
Of course
They have been taking drugs to soothe their minds
Warm menstrual bleeding
Naturally, the more you make up, the more severe the disease will be
Closed in April
abdominal pain
what is not pregnancy
As for the slippery veins
That's the weak girl
Ximai just now does not show
Your Highness
Peach Kernel Chengqi Soup with Peach Kernel Rhubarb
There are leeches in the soup
Both are anti-stasis medicines
Pregnant women are taboo
Sheng Yin
you are famous for a moment
Lost the dragon's life
It's a death penalty
His Royal Highness
Never listen to what a quack doctor says
He takes this medicine
Don't say dragon fetus
The phoenix body is also in danger
Your Highness
Slave's Previous Diagnosis
Slippery vein indeed
Your Highness, please think again
A lot of money
Destroy the bones
There are too many idiots in the world
Your Highness
no need to say more
Hope Your Highness decides
Your Highness
Physicians can prescribe medicines to patients
But you can't make decisions for the patient.
Mother
you told me when you were young
There is a decision in the way of life
indecision is bad
So the son's behavior
All learn from mothers
Even if you go the wrong way
Overcoming thorns
also to walk a bloody road
But now it's a matter of life
It's up to the mother to decide
If you think Sheng Yin is right
your son supports you
Your Highness
In case the emperor blames
The son is guarding outside
no one will disturb
do not worry
Son is always with you
Please Sheng Yin
Medicine
Yes
His Majesty
You can be the master
what happened
His Majesty
You must stop the crown prince
He insisted on letting Sheng Yin heal the queen's concubine
I'm afraid
I'm afraid that this time Long Si really can't keep it.
arrogance
His Majesty
Qi Kai Niang Niang just took the medicine
Zhu Zhanji
Where is that quack doctor
Your Majesty is here
Doctor Sheng, you are
Back to the words of the imperial concubine
The minister has issued a military order in front of His Highness
If you can't cure the queen concubine
willing to die
Sheng Yin you
You you made a big mistake
Dai Court sentence
Dare to learn from me and swear in public
you
Free at kisskh.me
If the Empress cannot be cured within ten days
take your head
His Majesty
two
dare
His Majesty
The imperial physician's diagnosis is based on medical skills
not ignorant
Hastily threatened with a knife and axe
The imperial doctor is frightened
How to diagnose and treat with peace of mind
Sheng Yin
you don't swear
If you hurt Long Si
What is the compensation for taking your head?
Zhu Zhanji
Is this a trick you did?
teach them
father emperor
Please respect your mother's decision
I don't respect your mother
if i don't respect her
How to convene a doctor's consultation
Why come to visit late at night
Zhu Zhanji
do you know
Maybe because of one of your mistakes
will cost your mother's life
And the unborn child
you you laugh
laugh laugh laugh what laugh
father emperor
When you were in the East Palace
Don't hesitate to offend the grandfather, but also stick to your heart
Brave advice
as your wife
Mother is always by your side
undiminished love
Did she ever ask you about the consequences of doing so
Did she ever have a trace of fear and retreat
she never
what you do
She doesn't ask if you want to do it
resolutely support
but you
Why don't you want to trust her
If you can't heal the queen
I don't want your head
I'm going to destroy your whole door
His Majesty
After the Queen Mother took the medicine
Sure enough, a lot of bruises fell.
The spirit is also good
Ziping
I come
You worked here all night last night
only when cooking
my heart is peaceful
last night
The queen concubine used blood medicine
except for bruises
Fear of lack of blood
Today, it is appropriate to use medicinal diets that nourish qi and nourish blood
I want to prepare in advance
live you alone
All credit goes to others
why?
The more you practice, the better your skills
Until no one can replace
is unique
Suffering is a blessing
It's not all bullshit
Row
to please the queen
Just to please His Royal Highness
Ziping
There's something in my heart
about my past
I want to tell you today
Yao Zijin
Invite your mother to eat
This longan wolfberry pigeon egg soup
Nourishes qi, nourishes blood, nourishes yin and moistens the lungs
should be taken first
Are there bergamot petals on this?
Back to the Queen's Concubine
This meal is called bergamot chicken
The entrance has a peculiar taste
fermented bean curd
Do not
lingering on the tongue
like wine
Back to the mother's words
This meal contains
Tofu milk and glutinous rice wine
Warm glutinous rice wine
It was specially selected by the slaves for you
you have a heart
empress
you slow down
you are recovering
Do not overeat
Crispy outside, juicy inside
It tastes really good
It's a pity
for many, many years
I don't smell this anymore
Empress Zhang is from Yongcheng
Love to use Hu spicy soup with fried dumplings for breakfast
You are proficient in local delicacies
How can you not even know this
Just some street food
How can such crude food be offered
There are more than twenty Chinese herbal ingredients in the soup
Adjust with the changing seasons
Queen asks for recipe
you are speechless
so that
Niang Niang knew someone else who made the meal
What a waste of the chance I gave you
empress
Your phoenix body is just recovering
Otherwise, after a while
Do you know the origin of this spinning wheel
slaves heard
This was given to you by Empress Renxiao back then
Yes
When my mother gave it to me, she said
No farming
or starving
one woman does not weave
or suffer from cold
Men's tillage and women's weaving
husband and wife
The truth is the rule of the world
Yes
empress
What a pity the spinning wheel was broken
Niangniang sent it to Shangshi Bureau
when the firewood burns
Yes
father emperor
How did you come
I heard that the father emperor dragon is not in good health
Erchen specially came to plead guilty
father emperor
Take your medicine first
Wei Chen is late
please forgive me
Guangzong County, Shunde Prefecture has a lot of rain this year
Local reporting is late
Disaster relief was delayed
I already ordered
any natural disaster
Be sure to open the warehouse first
But so
There must be officials who are greedy
you want
father emperor
If you are concerned about local officials
Taking advantage of disaster relief to enrich one's own pockets
Can be dispatched to inspect the imperial censor
Whenever the censors go to investigate with great fanfare
within sight
But other people want to see
young
What do you know
father emperor
Now Jinyiwei is out of Beijing to get people
Frequent arrests without permission
One can imagine
How arrogant he is
If you order them to visit secretly
I'm afraid there will be more wrongdoing
When the grandfather was there
They will also shrink
now
it's me
Let Jin Yiwei act cheaply
father emperor
go out
Sonny's words clash
Please take care of the dragon body
If it weren't for your mother and son joining forces to anger me
I am in good health
why don't you go
Erchen resigns
Free at kisskh.me
Breech birth
I read the memorial you presented
Fairly fair
But those things have the ministers of various ministries to worry about
don't get your head around this
a cruel loyalist
The butcher who killed countless people
Even a scholar who has read enough to give advice to the emperor
Why is there water transportation in the capital to relieve the distressed households?
nowhere
just nonsense
Don't dare to speak out loud
People only need a few
Talk to the guests and friends at Lord Liu's banquet yesterday
write down
Tomorrow your brain is in danger
Don't contaminate my eyes with this pickled stuff
This is
His Majesty
relapse
The Dai Court ruled that the dragon body must be conditioned according to the recipe
I can't be vegetarian anymore
help
move in
move things in together
come over
Come
be careful
you bring it
This is what the concubine of Yongning Palace wanted
you can't take it
Do you have eyes?
Dare to occupy the things of the queen and the master
you let go
Give me
don't take my
What are you making a fuss about?
Jade sister
Obviously it is the black wolfberry from Kunning Gongding
She insisted that the imperial concubine should be used
Gotta take it all
We ordered three days ago
Just a momentary mismatch
There's always a first comer
let go
you all took it
What am I going to tell you?
stop
Kuai
It doesn't matter if the little palace maids do wrong and scold a few words
who let you do it
say more
The imperial concubine prepares black wolfberry
It's to cure the emperor's heart disease
who can surpass the emperor
Goji berries for me
I
Give me
This is set by the imperial concubine
mine
OK
This black wolfberry is born in the mountains
hard-won
You dare to knock over such a precious medicinal material
Obviously you let go first
Why did you frame me? You knocked it over
you
Wen Dianshan, take a look
Parsley is in trouble
I
heartless thing
dare to spoil anything
Everyone makes mistakes, let's just say
so loud
What did the outsiders hear?
pack up
I have no one behind me
dare not be arrogant
Which is better than sister above
Catching up with the same family
It looks like it's about to climb the tall branch
you
deceiving too much
face has changed
This is a sore foot, right?
I let you fall
Xuelu, you take it
open
don't take
can't take
really can't take it
don't waste it
can't take it
stop fighting
Hidden set
don't take it
you
come over
wait
stop
let you hit
Ziping
Yin Ziping
don't take it
stop fighting
Ziping
stop
Master Shang Shi is here
still not stop
kneel down kneel down
kneel for an hour
meditate on oneself
I
kneel down
pretend
what about you
what to fight
Emperor Chrysostom's words
Reinstated Meng's position
I'm not good at refuting His Majesty's wishes.
lover of man
for profit
If you want to become the head of the Shang Food Bureau
Everyone must be convinced
otherwise
Even if I make a will
You are also hard to convince
empress
slaves have confidence
On seniority
Mengshi is far above you
I'm going to give you a fair shot
queen concubine
go down
Your Majesty has just decreed
Guo Guifei's elder brother Guo Xuan attacked the Marquis of Wuding
Grandmother Yan's over-qualification as Mrs. Yingguo
Mother Xu was named Mrs.
and
Huang Yan, a close attendant of the late emperor, had illicit affairs with foreign ministers
After Huang Yan was executed
All the funds under his name have also belonged to the Marquis of Wuding.
Everything is planned and then acted
impatient
no big deal
Yes
Granddaughter Guo's Duansu is at the knee of grandmother's book
self-deprecating
Over the summer and through the autumn
I recently heard that my grandmother was at peace
The special envoy will lead the imperial doctor
ask if
Yujing
you must take this letter
Hand over to grandmother
and bring me a few words
Friends and relatives
So Fu Dian
Respectful and modest
so self-defense
Ask your grandmother to take care of the brothers, sons and nephews in the clan
Only then can we protect our Guo family
long-term peace and prosperity
empress
Now your own brother is the marquis
It can be seen that His Majesty treats the Guo family with favor
Even the queen's maiden home is far from
you should be happy
Why are you still so worried?
I'm happy
someone will be unhappy
If you can't stay safe
disaster
not far
Yes
wait
here
It is a thousand-year-old wild ginseng and a thousand-year-old ganoderma
This is medicine from the hospital
old age
Infirm and susceptible to cold
This is specially reserved by the imperial doctor.
you take it
You have to observe the maid next to the old grandmother.
In case of poor care
dismiss it immediately
Yes
be careful on the road
let's go
Your Highness is back
How did you come
Didn't Your Highness love this Duyou the most?
Just because the string is broken
What a pity
now i have found
Strings matching the original piano
Replaced for His Highness
you listen
The sound is as clear and smooth as before.
Why don't I play a song for His Highness
Relieve Your Highness
no need
Someone will sort it out
Your Highness, if you have any troubles
Can I tell my concubine?
I am stupid
may not be able to relieve His Highness
But if you speak your mind
No one will complain
Your Highness Qin, please stay
Thank you for your trouble
if nothing else
I'll see you another day
Your Highness
what else
The study is simple
no place to live forever
Mother fears that people will lose care
sent me here to discuss with His Royal Highness
go back to live
People come and go in the palace every day
very noisy
compared to here
lack of taste
i live here
where is your majesty
where should i be
Since you refuse to move
that from tomorrow
I always come to be my partner
Your Highness is busy
I grind ink and pour tea
If you are free
Talk to you again to relieve boredom
nice
I already said
You don't have to serve day and night
When the former mother was the concubine of the East Palace
The diet and daily life of the emperor
will take care of themselves
This is the duty of a wife
In the past, because of His Highness's tolerance
I'm so lazy
Seriously changed now
I said no, no, no
Yuan Qi
send the princess back
Yes
princess
you please
I will come again tomorrow
no need to send
Take good care of Your Highness
Your Highness
did you see
how do i feel
Today the princess
different than usual
What time is this
Why haven't you delivered food yet?
sent sent
already delivered
Miss Yao has put the food box
put it outside
Wasn't the Crown Princess here just now?
I can't even send it.
you go tell her
I don't like today's meal
make her redo
redo
Yes