[English subtitles are available]
[Plot Love]
[Episode 19]
[Clothes sketches]
[Tseng Guofan's Home Letters]
[Su Bei]
[Clothes sketches]
[Dear Mr. Lu, my lover]
[Seven years ago]
Yun Fan,
book a ticket to Italy for Su Bei
as soon as possible.
Don't you need her consent?
I'm in charge.
Sending her away
is our best solution
at the moment.
[Clothes sketches]
[Dear Mr. Lu, my lover]
You're sending me away?
You should stay abroad to lay low first
and come back when things are settled.
I didn't plagiarise.
My original sketches are all here.
How can you send me abroad?
The person's dead.
How can you prove you didn't plagiarise?
If you stay, you can only get insults.
Because of you,
the whole Eminence is at risk.
You don't believe me.
It doesn't matter whether I believe you or not.
What matters is if the public and media believe you.
After you left,
I'll solve the problem soon.
To you,
to Eminence,
this is the best solution.
Then can I still become
a designer in the future?
Are you planning to blame me
for everything when I'm gone?
Whatever you say.
You must go abroad.
I'm not going.
I'm staying to find out the truth.
There's no time for you to find out the truth.
If you wait any longer,
it won't bode well for Eminence.
You blame me for dragging Eminence into it.
Since things turned out this way,
we should get a divorce.
I can give up being your wife
but you can't force me to go abroad.
It's ridiculous.
What's the point of getting a divorce?
Even if we divorce,
you have to stay in the other country.
You must not come back until I say so.
How could you not believe in me?
If they don't believe in me,
I can take it.
You are the one I trust the most.
Don't think that you're the only victim.
If you had been more cautious,
things wouldn't have ended up like this.
Rather than making a scene here,
you should learn your lesson
and reflect on yourself when you're abroad.
Fine.
I'll go.
I won't bother you.
But I tell you.
I didn't do it.
I will leave.
But I'll leave with honesty.
[Divorce Agreement]
[The woman gets a divorce without taking away anything]
[Woman (Signature): Su Bei]
We were really
young and stupid at that time.
[Youth]
[Blooming youth]
[Clothes sketches]
Are you still busy?
Have some coffee.
I must find out who leaked the design
and made my dear
so busy that she can't spend quality time with me.
You can leave it to me.
Our most important task now
is to settle the matter tomorrow.
Any ideas?
Seeking your pure self.
What do you think of
the idea of pure self?
Tell me.
How does the designer I miss so much
find your pure self?
The idea is inspired by
who I was seven years ago.
She wanted to have a pure relationship.
To express her feelings to her loved one,
she designed a collection of clothes.
Her loved one had a crisis after seven years.
She decided to use the clothes
to preserve the love.
Do you feel my heart?
Bei Bei,
you don't need to say much.
I get it.
We've been through so much together.
Everything we have
is rooted in our mind.
Although I completely
forgot about you
after the car accident,
these numbers
were in my memory.
I didn't know
what it stood for.
But there was a voice
in my mind that told me
it was very important.
Not long after,
I found out
it was our wedding anniversary date.
It was my forever love for you.
You were my missing piece of memory,
but
you have always been in my heart.
I can't.
I have to go to work tomorrow.
You're such a buzzkill.
I'll make up to you after finishing work.
And this side.
Cook me some noodle.
Hurry.
[Eminence]
I sent you the email.
Okay. I'll revise it and give it back to you.
Ms. Su. Mr. Lu.
- Ms. Su. Mr. Lu.
The live streaming will start tomorrow afternoon.
Let's work hard for it!
Tell the sales department to start the pre-selling.
Okay.
I'll notify the sales.
And
contact the factory for fabrics.
Whatever the price is,
we have to get the fabric
as soon as possible.
If they‘re on leave,
you have to call them.
Got it.
Yu Jia,
go through all the data
for every piece of clothes.
Calculate the cost first.
Okay.
Ms. Su,
for the pattern on the clothes,
shall we use screen or heat press printing?
If I let you decide,
which one would you choose?
Screen printing is cost effective and efficient.
Heat press printing costs more
but cannot endure multiple washing.
But
either way
will cause damage
to the clothes to some degree.
So
I'll use embroidery printing.
In that case,
our profit could...
Remember
cheap price will ruin our design
and make the consumers question Eminence.
We can lose the deal
but we cannot go wrong.
Ms. Su,
I really admire people like you
who view quality as the first priority.
So cool.
Work harder and no ass-licking
Mr. Lu, your takeaway is here.
Come on everybody!
Have some late night snacks!
You've been working so hard.
- Thank you Mr. Lu.
Thank you.
Ms. Su and Mr. Lu, you should also join us.
- Thank you.
- Here you go.
Let's go
there to eat.
It smells so good.
[Xiangyang Bakery]
It's for you.
It's really delicious.
Try it.
Is it good?
It tastes better when you took a bite.
It's PDA at middle of the night.
Mr. Lu,
please stop.
Do you want some?
[Eminence Group]
You'll definitely win.
[Pure Collection]
Three, two, one. All set.
Hello everybody
- Today, the Eminence Group
- Good luck!
collaborated with the famous international brand
Sia to introduce the new Pure collection.
[Eminence Group and Sia]
[New Collaboration Launch]
It's finally launched today.
Because it's the first day of the launch,
to show our sincerity,
Eminence has invited
our model,
Liu Qianying.
Hello everyone!
[Stream live]
I am Liu Qianying.
Nice to meet you all.
I joined the live streaming with the Pure collection.
Not only do I have tasks,
I also bring some wonderful gifts for you.
Everybody please wait patiently.
Thank you Qianying.
Today our live streaming
invited another important guest.
That is the designer of the Pure collection.
The beautiful and talented
Mrs. CEO of Eminence,
Ms. Su Bei.
Ms. Su, welcome!
Hello everybody, I'm Su Bei.
Thank you for your support for Pure.
Thank you for following Mr. Lu and I.
As soon as Ms. Su joined us,
our live streaming
is filled with audience.
Can you
share with us today
about the concept of designing Pure?
I think people want to know more about
what gifts I bring.
So Pure
has launched eight new outfits
For every outfit,
it will be sent out to five lucky customers.
So generous of Ms. Su.
The audience of the live streaming
came at the right time.
I believe
whether you have fallen in love or not,
[Gu Yan|CEO]
you will find
the love of your life sooner or later.
[Live streaming]
Seven years ago,
when I was young,
I was in a pure relationship.
I was his favourite girl.
He was the one I trusted the most.
We had
a wonderful time together.
To preserve the love
and find the love.
this time,
I give you Pure that
has environmental protection as its theme.
I wish every girl who has love
will find their pure self with courage.
Ms. Su really has
great resilience.
She's capable and talented.
Any major things can
be solved on her watch.
After spending time with her for a while,
any men would fall for her.
People can be
so different, right?
Some people
copy others' ideas
to win again.
Who would have thought
that
things turn out to be good.
The result is even better than the copied idea.
She's just being opportunistic.
She's winning empathy by striking a chord.
We didn't get her this time,
but she won't be
lucky next time.
A person with love.
In front of all the people online,
she dared to express her love.
In order to have the courage
and be able tou se the opportunity,
there has to be someone who loves you.
[Pure collection]
[Explore anywhere]
My dear colleagues,
I have great news.
Sia reported that
our sales
doubled as much as we have expected.
But we can't relax now.
We still have a big challenge,
which is shipping on time to our fans.
Don't worry, Ms. Su.
We'll make sure we can finish
the follow up work.
Fighting!
Thank you for your hard work.
Great!
I know you're excited
but no need to hug.
Mr. Lu,
I'm a lady.
The same is for the lady.
Fine.
- Mr. Lu, we'll be back to work.
- Back to work.
You've worked hard.
Why didn't you compliment me?
I always think you're excellent.
I'm not complimenting you
because compared with the value
you bring to the company,
I'm more concerned about your hard work.
It's good to have you.
I have explained
everything very clearly.
Who should take the responsibility
is our internal issue.
You don't need to interfere.
Although
the loss has been compensated,
you should still find out who is to blame.
We can stay out of this.
But if this person stays
in Eminence for the long term,
who shall be responsible for further losses?
So
I hope Mr. Lu
can give us
a satisfactory reply.
Or else
we'd like to ask Mr. Lu
to take some time off work.
You're threatening me.
Lu Nan,
you can't say that.
You're the president.
After the incident,
you should give an explanation to us.
If you have the competence,
you should show us what you found
to prove yourself.
Yun Fan, Maggie.
This is the document I've found
and notes from the surveillance camera.
People who saw the sketches
are those in the design department
and Ms. Su's assistant, Ye Ting.
The design department has worked overtime.
So the only person who can get in contact
with those out of the company  is Ye Ting.
[RMB: Five hundred thousand yuan]
Ms. Su's assistant.
How did her personal account
suddenly receive this large sum
of money at this point?
Ye Ting, explain yourself.
I don't know.
How can you not know about your account?
I really don't know.
Nobody has ever transferred money to me.
No need to investigate anymore.
All the evidence is here.
No way!
Ye Ting would never do that.
Think about it.
How did you get the money?
I believe you are innocent.
I really don't know.
Although this account is under my name,
I've never seen it before.
No need to explain anymore.
Since you're Ms. Su's assistant,
this thing must have
something to do with Ms. Su.
Since the sketch was leaked out,
Ms. Su tried to turn the tide on her own
and solved the problem successfully.
She even managed to double the sales.
Because of this,
I can guarantee that
Ms. Su couldn't be involved.
It seems that Eminence
has become a couple company.
We shareholders
don't matter anymore.
Fine.
Since I owe you an explanation,
I'll hand Ye Ting over
to the police.
You really suspect Ye Ting?
Whether it's true or not
will be revealed by the police.
She's just assisting the investigation.
You have to believe in law.
Suspecting her
means you're suspecting me.
I said
we'll leave it to the police.
What's the difference between
investigating her and suspecting me?
Don't be ridiculous.
Somebody has to be blamed.
I'm so disappointed in you.
Ye Ting is in my team.
Before there's any concrete evidence,
nobody can fire her.
Let's go.
[Eminence Group and Sia]
[New Collaboration Launch]
Ms. Lu, what happened?
What happened?
We've been worried to death.
Don't worry everyone.
Yeah.
I'll be responsible for everything.
Just focus on your work.
Hi Mr. Lu.
- Hi Mr. Lu.
You can leave now.
Okay.
[Eminence Group and Sia]
[New Collaboration Launch]
Can you stop being so selfish?
I'm not only your husband.
I'm also the chairman of the board.
You made me lose face
in front of all the other directors.
What do you mean?
Are you sending Ye Ting to the police?
For an outsider,
you want to hurt our relationship?
Outsider. You're saying she's an outsider.
Isn't she?
Lu Nan,
when I was criticized seven years ago,
what were you doing?
When I was giving birth
and the baby was sick,
what were you doing?
When I was making a living
and drinking a lot for work,
where were you?
It was Ye Ting
who supported me through
the most difficult time of my life.
She isn't an outsider.
You have no right to judge her.
Fine.
I admit she went through with you during
the most difficult seven years of your life.
But that is past tense.
People change.
You can't say that
there's no problem with Ye Ting now.
If you think there's a problem with Ye Ting,
there's a problem with me.
You're being ridiculous.
Lu Nan. I tell you
in my heart, Ye Ting
was never an outsider.
On the contrary, you
are so selfish.
You hurt people around you for yourself.
Seven years ago,
you didn't try to find out the truth
and sent me abroad directly.
Seven years later,
you don't try to find out the truth
and send Ye Ting to the police.
Lu Nan,
in my heart,
you can't be compared with Ye Ting.
In your view,
am I that terrible?
I find what you did
very disgusting.
Lu Nan,
I want a divorce.
Fine.
Let's do it. I don't care.
Sister,
you can't suddenly bring up divorce.
You have to think straight.
You and Ye Ting are the most important people to me.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
You're drinking.
Why are you here?
We're
colleagues.
I came to comfort you.
Go away.
This is not nice.
You'll feel lonely drinking alone.
I came with sincerity.
Enough.
You better stay away from me.
I'm a corporate espionage.
What are you talking about?
Am I that kind of person?
Aren't you?
Come here.
Sit properly.
Although you're a tomboy,
I'm willing to swear
in the name of my future generation
that you would never do anything like that.
I trust you.
Are you afraid?
Close your eyes.
[Eminence Group]
What is it?
It's a transfer from the director of boards.
They decided that
from now on you'll be removed from
the collaboration project with Sia.
Eminence Starlight will be handed to others.
It's just a temporary suspension.
After the investigation of the design sketch,
Mr. Lu will resume your position.
Is this what the director of board wants
or what he wants?
It certainly isn't what I want.
I'll go ask him.
I'll go too.
When immortals fight,
moral will injure.
If you don't want to die,
then stay away from them.
Can't you see I didn't even go?
Ms. Su,
can't you knock?
It's not at home.
You have no respect.
Lu Nan, what do you mean?
Getting rid of me after I finished the job?
You were so sincere just then
and now you turn yourself against me.
Lu Nan,
what kind of person are you?
What kind of person am I?
Don't you know?
All right.
Enough.
Compared with the company,
I need you to return to family.
Our family needs you.
Mr. Lu,
you want me to take the blame again?
What are you thinking?
I want the best for you and for our child.
You've been working so hard
and suffering a lot.
I care about you.
Chris also needs your company.
When I was settling the sketch matter,
why didn't you say I worked too much?
Now the board is holding me accountable.
You ask me to return home.
I'm not stupid.
I'm serious.
You can't settle the matter now.
Leave it to me.
You can take a good rest at home.
I want one more baby.
For the Lu family business,
one child is not enough.
Let me tell you.
In your dreams.
I'll never have children with you.
Why are you arguing?
Don't be ungrateful.
There's a cap to my tolerence.
If you can't tolerate, then don't.
I can't tolerate you anyway.
I must be blind
to have feelings for
someone selfish like you.
My lawyer will prepare for divorce agreement tomorrow.
Fine.
Get a divorce.
Even if we divorced,
you won't get a penny
nor Chris's custody.
Let's go.
That can't be true.
What's happening with the CEO?
Ms. Su
- Ms. Su.
I decide to leave Eminence
and create my own brand.
Does anyone
want to join me and leave?
I do.
Don't leave me here.
You have to think carefully.
Yu Jia,
do you want to leave with me?
Anybody want to leave with me?
I do.
Ms. Su,
we'll go anywhere you go.
I do.
Great.
From now on,
I won't let you down.
Su Bei,
what's going on?
Why are you leaving in a sudden?
What are you doing? You can't go.
How can you leave in a sudden?
Grandma, I don't want to,
but I have no choice.
Nan Nan,
Nan Nan
come on.
Can we stay, mom?
Chris, good boy.
If we miss great grandma,
we'll come back to visit her.
Don't go.
Stay with great grandma.
What's going on, Nan Nan?
Nan Nan, you have to talk to Bei Bei.
She's leaving.
You can stay if you don't want to go.
No.
When you two argue,
don't let my great grandson suffer.
Grandma, just let her leave.
Don't come back after leaving.
Chris, let's go.
Grandma.
Grandma,
What's wrong, great grandma?
You're leaving at will.
Whatever I say,
you won't care about me.
Just go.
I don't know when we'll meet again.
Great grandma, I won't go.
Bei Bei, don't go..
Good boy.
Chris you stay with great grandma first,
okay?
Bei Bei.
Good boy. I'll pick you up after some time.
I used to
wish playing golf like this.
The feeling of dominating the whole field.
Back then,
I always came with Gu Chengze, that jerk.
I was his aid.
I could only stand beside him
like a slave.
Now I finally achieved it
but there's nothing more.
I actually miss
the feeling of being marginal.
Try it.
Mr. Gu is starting to
miss the feeling of being marginal.
I'd rather not try.
So I can still dream about
dominating the field.
[Yu Jia]
Hello.
Okay. Got it.
Nice play.
[MISS Studio]
[Opening Ceremony]
Thank you all for coming
to attend the opening of MISS Studio.
It's not only a milestone in my life,
but also grand for all the MISS members.
From now on,
dreams will come true.
We will work together
for the development of MISS.
Everything's hard in the beginning.
But I believe
as long as there is
joint effort and mutual trust among us,
we can definitely succeed.
Great! Great!
Ms. Su.
We have faith in you.
As long as you guide us,
we can stick through any difficulties.
This way please.
And this way.
Thank you.
[Gu Yan]
[Zijin Mining]
[Tianyuan]
Congratulations on the opening.
Thank you.
What did you want to
talk about collaboration?
Before that,
I want to apologize to you.
I didn't think the decision of the Gu's Group
could affect your marital relationship
and cause some conflicts.
It has nothing to do with Gu's Group.
It's our own issue.
You've came a long way
to get together.
Why are you divorcing again?
Actually there has been
a big problem in our marriage.
I used to think that
as long as we love
and tolerate each other,
we can solve all problems.
But now it seems that
I was just cheating myself.
There's nothing bad about divorce.
It's a relief for the both of us.
It's nice to be on my own.
I have my career and my child.
As long as you're thinking straight.
Speaking of important matters,
the environmental-friendly organization
is going to hold a conference in Nanxi.
The Gu's Group
is the clothing sponsor for the conference.
We plan to,
other than providing daily outfit,
sponsor the formal dress
and advertising outfit with Chinese characteristic.
Every member will get three sets.
So we're
looking for
a design group
that can produce together.
If you can participate in the design,
it will be a great publicity
for your  company.
The Gu's Group has professional design team.
Why do you want me?
Because it's like the steak.
If the steak is good,
there's more people
willing to spend their money.
I have confidence in your talent.
Thank you.
But
if I
proposed a divorce to Lu Nan
and decided to work with you,
it'll bring the blame of others.
For me and for you,
I need to think about it.
No hurry.
You can tell me after you thought about it.
[Lu Nan]
Nan Nan,
did you regret?
You look like
a defeated jet.
Do you know what mom is doing now?
I don't know.
Judging by your look,
she must be with another man.
That man is no good.
If your mom left for him,
you'll have no mom anymore.
You're just jealous
and talk too much.
If you want me to win your wife back,
then say it directly.
Let's go.
Let's wait for her at her home.
Bei Bei,
Bei Bei.
Mr. Gu,
we meet again, Chris.
Su Bei,
even if we divorce,
Chris is still your child.
As a good mother,
how could you
neglect your son?
Sorry. Chris.
I've been too busy lately
to take care of you.
Bei Bei,
I know you've been working hard.
I'm not mad.
You know what.
It's Nan Nan
who's jealous of Mr. Gu.
Chris,
Chris.
Good boy. Come here.
I'll play football with you during the weekend.
All right?
Yes.
No.
I can spend time with my own kid.
No need to bother you.
Listen to me.
Su Bei is still my wife
so Mr. Gu
please respect the border.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lu.
If you didn't mention,
I almost forgot that
Su Bei has a husband.
Please be assured that
I'll wait for Su Bei to get the divorce.
You are really in a hurry
to find another man.
Isn't it too early?
Let's go, Chris.
How can you do such thing as
finding a second-line?
Aren't you afraid that
I'll use it as an evidence of affair against you?
About the divorce,
I already handed it to my lawyer.
Before it's settled,
I don't want to see you anymore.