At the age of 29,
you're still shining.
But I'm not...
by your side.
My life of eternity...
has finally come to an end.
Times after my death,
you are still here.
You've forgotten me...
and your life is perfectly
complete with me gone.
I have to disappear.
To make you smile.
This is the decision I have to make.
I have to end my life.
In the end,
that's the decision I made.
Mister.
What?
I can't tell who's the one in a rush.
Do you see me now?
Yes.
Are you mad at me?
- Why would I be?
- Then why are you mad?
How far back are you going?
I feel like I'm collecting
all the accrued miles.
I did not.
See? You're mad now, too.
Who do you think you are?
Who are you to keep calling me?
You're so noisy.
Why do you get me flustered?
Why do you get me confused?
Who do you think you are?
You should've removed the
sword when I asked you to...
since that's your worth.
I was just...
That's why...
I said I'd remove the sword.
You're the one who wouldn't talk to me.
I thought you were waiting
for the first snowfall...
since that was the promise.
Forget it.
You may have time to kill
since you live forever,
but I'm an average human being...
so time is gold and money.
How long must I be on standby?
I'm busy with school and my part-time job.
- Tomorrow.
- Why not today?
I'm free today.
Not today. Tomorrow.
It's too nice out today.
I want to take a walk with you.
Tomorrow.
Again? Why?
Let me do it before I go to school.
The weather stinks today.
I'll need to pick you up later.
Tomorrow.
One more day.
Why not today?
Just one more day.
No way.
It's snowing.
It's the first snowfall.
Why is it snowing already?
That's crazy.
I like it because it's pretty,
but the flowers must be cold.
Right?
We're seeing the earliest snowfall ever.
This is you, right?
You wanted me to pull out
the sword when it snowed.
I'm sorry for being selfish,
but I wanted something to remember by.
How long are you going to enjoy this?
You better hurry up and get pretty.
Okay, now.
All right. It's time to make you pretty.
Any last words?
Every moment I spent with you...
shined.
Because the weather was good,
because the weather was bad,
and because the weather was good enough...
I loved every moment of it.
Also,
no matter what happens,
it's not your fault.
Are you...
really going to turn into a broom?
That won't happen.
I'm glad.
Here I go.
Why can't I grab it?
I can see it, but I can't pull it out.
Did you put enough pressure?
Here, let me try again.
You said earlier that it's not my fault...
no matter what happens,
- so don't take it back.
- Hey.
- How can the goblin's bride...
- I said, don't take it back.
Just stand still.
I'm more surprised than you.
I'm standing still. How can
I get more still than this?
Give me that agreement.
I'm going to burn it.
Wait.
I know what it is. This must be it.
I get it now.
- What is it?
- The cursed prince.
You know, the ones in fairy tales?
What about them?
A kiss.
[GOBLIN: THE LONELY AND GREAT GOD]
Synced, ripped & added missing lines by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
Why? Are you in pain?
By any chance, is it because of the sword?
Ajusshi.
I can grab the sword.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, I'll pull it out for you.
It is moving.
The oracle was true.
The future I envisioned was true.
Through this child, I will be able
to end this immortal existence
and return to nothingness.
A human life is a hundred
years at best. That I
wish to turn around and
look back once more,
is that just a life of an immortal?
Or is it your face?
Ah.
I think it's your face.
Episode 8
Ajusshi, are you okay?
I think I should be the one asking that.
Is that right?
Oh, what an ordeal.
I'm sorry. You were startled a lot, right?
Ajusshi didn't know that
it would hurt like this.
Since no-one has ever grabbed it before.
By the way, you can really fly.
I wasn't asking you to show me this way.
That's a piece of gum
(CAKE, HOMONYM FOR SWORD).
We should toughen up our hearts.
I see now that this is not
something to be taken lightly.
But to be honest, I was more surprised
that I could move the sword.
Aren't you really relieved?
With that, it has been proven that I
am really the Goblin's bride, right?
I'm glad.
Are you not glad?
See... I am really the bride.
This was fate.
Fate.
It's cool.
Why is this Uncle not home yet? I can't
get my allowance until I fulfill my task.
Let's see what commotion there was today.
It is him.
Uncle, you were on the second floor?
I was waiting all this time.
Uncle, hurry up and look at this.
By any chance, was this you, uncle?
So how can you sit around like this?
Take care of it.
- Was this really you?
- I don't have any energy to explain, so don't ask.
We don't have any time. Hurry.
What on earth did you do?
Grandfather, listen to what I'm
going to say now, carefully.
Uncle... no, not me. Uncle!
Mr Kim, listen to what I'm
going to say now, carefully.
From this very moment,
by gathering up the
entire secretary's office
at Cheon Oh Group...
No, not me.
It's not about me!
Uncle down the hall, we
have to go somewhere.
Where?
Since uncle lacks social
skills, he shattered society.
From this moment, you are
to request all the sites
which have links to the video
remove them immediately.
Before it spreads, you are to
block it quickly and precisely.
You may utilize big data
and if you do make contact
with the person in charge, it might
be easier and more effective if
you tell them that Cheon Oh Group
will remove all its sponsoring ads.
Now... let's start.
Yes.
Now, everyone.
Okay, firstly, those whose car or
property got damaged, please stand here.
Those who saw something disturbing
and got mentally disturbed.
Please line up over there.
The car was mangled due to a
sudden gust of wind. That's all.
The money was just luck that
fell out of the sky. That is it.
Also, you did not see me today.
Okay, next.
I'm next. By the way, isn't
it really dark out here?
I wasn't feeling too good.
Could you please look into
my eyes for a moment?
The car was mangled due
to a sudden gust of wind.
The money fell down from the sky,
that is it. Today you did not see me.
Okay... next, next!
Yes, hurry, come this way.
Eyes, look at my eyes. Look.
Yes, next person.
What's your car type?
It'll be done here once
we delete these files.
Can you look into my eyes for a moment?
I mean, what kind of couple fights
like that to demolish 30 cars?
Do you know how much Uncle down
the hall and I went through?
You did a good job. Thanks.
Don't be thankful. I just don't have
the energy to fight, that's all.
Let's postpone this fight. It's
disturbing enough as it is.
No matter how disturbed you
are, it's worse for me.
How do you know whether it's
not as bad or worse for me?
Hey, for me, this thing...
this much, like this...
Nevermind. Forget it.
Did you come back from
nearly dying or something?
What's wrong with you guys, again?
Buckwheat, we don't have to leave anymore.
I'm the real bride. Surely!
Oh, it hurts.
Ajusshi, what's wrong?
Surely, he's not dead, is he?
It's because of the medicine.
Let him sleep.
If he sleeps like that,
he won't get full rest.
You should carry him like this to the room.
Yes, do that. If you can do it that is.
What's wrong? Why did
you take the medicine?
Does it still hurt?
♫ When I look at you ♫
♫ my tears keep falling, as if somehow ♫
Who exactly are you?
That you pierce me like this?
♫ That person I am unable to avoid ♫
♫ I love you, love you, love you ♫
♫ I felt our connection ♫
♫ And I miss you, feel you ♫
Our restaurant's radish is good.
♫ My one love ♫
Thirty seven.
Thirty eight.
Let's go home after fifty people pass by.
I went easy on you.
Synced, ripped & added missing lines by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
He doesn't have a fever...
This grown-up adult passes
out and sleeps anywhere.
Because it hurts.
You're awake?
It smells like a pain relief patch.
I was hurting here and there.
Are you hurting a lot, too?
You said you were fine earlier.
It was a lie.
You're always lying.
Get well soon.
You don't even know where it hurts.
Where does it hurt?
First love hurts a lot.
She must've been really pretty.
I saw you wrote stuff down about it too.
A lot. Every day...
She's pretty.
You're not feeling well at all.
You're gravely ill.
Sleep a lot. So you can get well soon.
Don't do that.
Why? Why should I be nice to someone
who only thinks about his first love?
Is that something to say to your bride?
If you look closely, you
can see the pretty parts.
So don't leave.
Did I or did I not tell you not to
say words that begin with "ch"?
Psh! You're so petty.
Please put in all of the
vegetables and heat the bread.
Yes.
Here's the bribe you ordered.
Fine. The item?
Can you actually interpret this?
It is must for a third generation
Chaebol to finish studying
the Thousand-Character Classic
at the age of three...
- But what is this?
- Your Uncle's background information.
Especially about his first love.
It's our secret.
This little girl. I enjoy digging
up background information.
This is letter means "to hear".
In case you don't know it.
You can't not know what this means
after eating up all the sandwich.
- It's not allowed.
- It's a love letter.
- A love letter?
- Yeah.
It's a sad love confession.
After living for one hundred days, one day,
on an ordinary day...
I had my suspicions. I guess it's just as
I thought. It's fine, I know who it is.
- Who is it?
- I heard all about it.
Well, that can happen.
There can be one woman
you can't ever forget
after 900 years.
- He said there's just one person?
- It's not?
- I wouldn't know about that.
- Oh, I got scared.
Anyway. About Kim Shin...
Who's Kim Shin?
- Your Uncle.
- My uncle's name is Kim Shin?
Our uncle's name is Yoo Shin Jae.
Well. It's a long story.
Anyway, about the sword
in your Uncle's chest.
Our Uncle has a sword in his chest?
- Ah, what do you know about him?
- What's the sword about?!
If you only tell me a
little here and there, I'll
get a gum-plex. (PLAY
ON COMPLEX, GUM=SWORD)
If you keep doing this, I won't tell
you something that only I know of.
What is something that only you know of?
You said he cried after
looking at this painting?
Yeah. He was completely bawling.
I kept telling him he couldn't,
but Uncle down the hall
- kept asking to see...
- He cried? Why?
I don't know. Go tell him off, Uncle.
Let's get angry at him.
Hurry. Huh? Huh? Huh?
Why did you look at my painting?
He said he tried to stop you.
He said you cried. Why would
you cry when I don't even cry?
I was flustered too, so I
thought about it a lot.
Stendhal's syndrome. (strong reaction
to art or something personally
(significant) I'm thinking maybe
it's something like that.
It was really touching, and
I felt really overwhelmed.
But who is it? The girl in the painting?
What are you going to do
with that information?
It seemed like I saw her before.
Who's the girl that you saw? The
girl that I know is my sister.
- You had a older sister, Uncle?
- Have you really seen my younger sister?
Think about it carefully.
Where you saw her.
Ah, younger sister.
I think it's one of
the deceased I was in
charge of, but I'm not
sure about that either.
This girl reincarnated? When?
I told you I'm not sure. Do
you know how many people
I've taken? How could I
remember all their faces?
It just seemed like I saw her before,
so I am making that assumption.
I don't have memories, only feelings exist.
It was just really sad.
My heart ached.
Uncles, I got it. I think I know.
What if Uncle down the hall is a
reincarnation of your younger sister?
Uncle down the hall, try call him
Orabeoni (OLDER BROTHER) once.
- I'll kill you.
O...
Orabeo...
Sunbaenim, have you heard?
About Kim Cha Sae from Jangamdong?
What about Kim Cha Sae from Jangamdong?
He went to get the deceased, but it turned
out to be his wife in his former life.
So he classified her as a miscellaneously
omitted and they ran off together.
- And then what?
- That's all.
I don't know what happened after that.
They probably got caught though.
How did he remember his past life?
I don't know. That's
why everyone is uneasy
these days. I drink every
day these days, too.
You only end up being filled
with thoughts. They say if you
commit a huge crime in your past
life, you become a grim reaper.
What wrongdoing did I commit in my previous
life, and how bad would it have been?
Could it be that my memory was wiped
so that I wouldn't be agonized by it?
That I should repent my past
wrongdoing by doing this kind of work?
It must be a consideration
on the part of God.
If you remember, you do.
If you don't, you don't.
It should be all God's intention. However,
to give back someone's lost memories,
I'm curious to what God's intention is.
In many ways...
Joon Yeong!
Mom!
Was it fun?
What shall we eat?
I'm leaving.
Drink alcohol in moderation.
Work hard.
Mom. Where is this place?
I think it's a tea place.
Ah. What are we going to drink?
What are you going to order, Mom?
Mom ordered Heaven.
To give to Joon Yeong.
Heaven?
The Heaven that you have
ordered has come out.
Thank you.
Mom. Why are you crying?
Synced, ripped & added missing lines by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
- What are you doing?
- You surprised me!!
What are you doing here right now?
I was on my way to the library.
How about you? Do you know this house?
Who are you?
Stay out of my way for a sec.
Open the window, let some fresh
air in, and button up your shirt.
You'll need this.
Let's go.
Daddy!
How did you get here?
I called a taxi and showed
the address to the driver.
It cost $5.20.
I want to go to this place.
I know where it is! Wear your safety belt.
- Daddy, I'm hungry.
- Huh?
Here you go.
Daddy, I missed you.
Me too.
Today too... you were a little cool.
Sometimes the parents, the
children, or the siblings
become the guardian guards for each other.
I merely gave him the sandwich.
It was his daughter who saved him, not me.
That's cool as well.
The price of a sandwich is no joke.
It's a good thing that President
Yoo earns good money.
By the way, about the sword,
why did it suddenly move?
When I wasn't even able
to grab it before? Right?
Shouldn't there be something more
powerful than the sign on the back?
For example, real love?
Hey, don't you have anything to tell me?
- No, I don't.
- I'm sure you do.
- Ohh, that? There is one thing.
- See?
You do have something to say.
Don't hold back and
say it. It's so apparent, so tell me.
It's ok.
Whatever you say, you
know that I'm the kind of
person who will accept
it without judgement.
I know that you're rich,
but are you alright with just
being at home all the time?
That's what you wanted to say?
All you did was serve the country
during the Koryeo Dynasty, right?
Hey, are you done with talking?
I've had jobs, too!
It won't be eternal,
but it'll keep you from being
drunk for a very long time.
It won't be eternal,
but it will be fragrant
for a very long time.
It won't be eternal, but it will
be useful for a very long time.
But why are you speaking very informally?
I'm sorry dear customer.
- Mr. Yoo Jae Shin! - I'm sorry
(SAID IN INFORMALY) - Hey!
I'm sorry about that too. (INFORMALLY)
That's why you've always been home.
Because you got nothing. (EARN MUCH)
Got nothing? What do you mean?
What do you think it means?
It means you're lacking.
It's my first time hearing
that kind of things being
said to me! It's really my first time!
Really!
I guess your first love never
gave you these constructive
criticisms. Seeing how you've
never heard it before.
Are you jealous right now?
What?! Why would I be jealous?
I don't even know if she was from
the Koryeo or the Joseon Dynasty.
When did you meet her?
During the Koryeo Dynasty?
The Joseon Dynasty? In the beginning
of the dynasty? The middle? The end?
She probably very beautiful
in a sophisticated way.
But you see, first love
usually never works out.
Go back home. And don't wait for me
since I'll be late.
Who says it doesn't come true?
I don't like it...
Hey, why would you respond to my
"Hey" by saying "Ho"? (YA-HO=HOORAY)
Don't you find it funny?
All of us found it funny.
It's lame.
By the way...
your birthmark has faded a lot.
Really? Could it because I'm getting older?
But why do you keep spending money to buy
this for me when I can't even drink it?
It's a waste of money.
Who else would take care of
you by getting you coffee?
Did your national exam go well?
Yes, of course.
That's why you should tell
me before it's too late.
Other ghosts
are so enthusiastic about
asking me to listen
to their stories and
remove their sorrow.
But why do you not ask me for anything?
I won't be able to come here
often once I get into college.
Then, can you come here
just once to see me?
With some pretty flowers?
I'm in Paju.
Yes, I'll come.
But... how did you die?
While on my way to the graduation ceremony
from a car accident...
Anyway, I'll be waiting for you!
I wonder what her story is.
Welcome!
How do you keep finding out where I am?
It was me who was more surprised. Why do
have to happen to be here of all places?
I heard that the number of
chicken restaurants in Korea is
greater than the number of
McDonalds in the entire world,
so why does it have to be this place?
Because it's the chicken restaurant
that Mister Goblin found for me.
As always, he's never helpful to my life.
What is it now?
Why do you keep showing up randomly
like this and making my heart drop?
Why do you think I came
to a chicken restaurant?
It's to buy some chickens.
Get me some chickens.
Stop talking nonsense. I
know that you're vegetarian.
Even though you know that,
give me some chicken.
That one! With lots of radishes.
Seriously?
Is this a meeting that
had been pre-arranged?
The scene of that pre-arranged meeting,
did I come upon it? Very coincidentally?
Hey, what are you doing?! You're not
allowed to touch this hat so carelessly!
You're not supposed to be seen
by people so carelessly either!
Go there and remain silent in that corner.
Then, I can give you an extra drumstick.
Welcome!
Have you been well?
Sit wherever you'd like.
Please sit down. What
would you like to eat?
I've been thinking that we could
have some chicken for dinner today?
Don't you feel like you want to have
chicken for dinner for some reason?
There is no other way but to
have chicken for today's dinner.
I'm sorry for being egoistic,
- but today's dinner should be chic...
- Shut up. ("SHUT" SOUNDS LIKE CHICKEN)
Mr Reaper, come see me for a sec.
Go ahead and eat first. I'll be
back before the crusts cool down.
Oh, I'll just go back to noth...
Why do you keep coming to my restaurant?
It wouldn't be because of me.
By any chance, is it because of my boss?
It's nothing like that. Only, I'm
just going there to see her.
As long as you don't reveal my identity,
I think everyone can be at peace.
Just worry about yourself
not saying anything.
The fact that Tae-Hee oppa came to my
part-time work and smiled brightly at me
and that he took two orders when
he left is a secret between us.
Secret?!
He came to see you at your part-time work?
And he smiled brightly at you?
Let's say that smiling brightly at you
is something that should be kept secret.
But why is getting some to go a secret? Be
honest. How many coupons did you give him?
Hey, you be quiet. How many
times did that punk come by?
Let's say that he came by five times. Then
how many coupons should he ideally get?
I told you to be quiet!
Hey, do you know thanks to whom
he's such a great baseball player?
It's all thanks to me who used to be
his guardian god a long time ago.
You don't know anything and what?!
Let's say that's true.
But do you really think
you should take all the
credits for his success?
It's all due to my first
love's strong persistence.
Don't you know about
human persistence?
Look at me! I eventually
managed to grab your sword!
- Let's see if I let you become pretty or not.
- Hey, hey.
Tell me how the untimely
death system works.
I'll try to figure it out somehow if
you just tell me the basic principles.
And I'll resolve the chicken
coupon problem for you.
- Why would I ask for
your help when I know a
- faster way to resolve it? Eun Tak!
- Hey.
- Ji Eun Tak!
- Wow!
I'm tell you, someone put back
the piano without being noticed!
How could someone put
something back so large and
not even be noticed by
any of the neighbors?
It's like a ghost did it. It's so weird.
Hey, Ji Eun Tak.
You have a second, right? There's
something I'm curious about.
Did you do well on your national exam?
You could say that... Why?
I guess you did really well on it.
That's annoying.
You must have done well,
too, since you're smart.
But you don't even take extra lessons
outside of school. That's cool of you.
- Are you being sarcastic?
- I'm actually being sincere.
Which universities did you apply to
as early action? In case we overlap.
Even if it's to the same
universities, we wouldn't
overlap since I'm a social
consideration candidate.
So... are you getting accepted?
What are you talking about?
I heard you can see ghosts. Don't
ghosts tell you things like that?
I'm also curious as to whether
I'm going to be accepted or not.
So that's what you were curious about.
But I like that you're direct
instead of talking behind my back.
I can't help suppressing
my curiosity by nature.
That must why you are good at studying.
I just see them, they
don't tell me anything.
I'll be going now.
For 3 years we were in the same class.
We had a 3-years worth of
conversation all in one day.
You have your interview for Seo-Un
University tomorrow, don't you?
Good luck with it.
Y-you too.
Synced, ripped & added missing lines by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
♫ It's a beautiful life, I
will stay by your side ♫
Why did you come here when you didn't even
pay any attention to whether I left or not?
♫ It's a beautiful life,
I'll stand right behind you ♫
- Are you sure you didn't forget to bring anything?
- Like what?
Ohh, my scarf!
Because you kept ignoring my
greetings, it kept distracting me!
♫ If I'm with you under this sky ♫
♫ Just breathing alone makes me happy ♫
Don't be scared and don't get nervous.
♫ Beautiful life, beautiful day ♫
♫ I live in your memories,
beautiful life ♫
- Would you like me to come with you?
- ♫ Beautiful day ♫
Am I a kid? ♫ Stay by my side ♫
- Why isn't the bus coming?
- Are you still mad at me?
I was going to be, but
it got ruined because
of the scarf. - ♫
Beautiful my love ♫
- So you are jealous.
- So what if I am? Are you
- happy that I'm jealous?
- ♫ Beautiful my heart ♫
Yes. It made me feel good all day.
Then go home now.
I'll do well on my interview.
Thank you for the scarf!
Be careful, there's someone behind you.
I'm sorry.
I was going to avoid bumping into them.
Your eyes are really big and clear,
so everything gets reflected! Really!
Yeah, alright, so get on the bus.
A pickpocket! He's a thief!
Why you? You weren't in that scene...
What did you say?
My mom will kill me this time if I
do badly on my interview again.
I wish there was an accident instead.
Hey, don't say things like that. They
say be careful what you wish for.
Whether I die by my mom's
hands or in an accident,
people all die anyway.
Hah!
Oh, this is so tiring so early morning!
Please have some coffee.
Hey, it's me who said was feeling tired.
Why do you only give him coffee?
I told him not to get one for you.
- Are you still mad at me?
- Who says that I am mad?
Everyone says so that you're still mad.
As long as you know.
There are people that I don't recognize.
Even those from Han-Nam area volunteered.
It seems like it is indeed a huge accident.
I heard that even the volunteering team
each got five sheets. But you have a lot.
It's my jurisdiction.
Hyeon-Jeong Kim, Age 34.
Su-bin Park, Age 2, Accident.
It seems like it's mom and child.
I guess I'll have to
prepare a Heaven again.
Pardon?
Synced, ripped & added missing lines by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
Why don't you close up early and go home?
I haven't even started selling
yet you want me to close up?
I mean, what are you talking about?
It means that I'm going to
buy everything you have.
Why are you so impatient?
Do you even know what these are?
They're socks. So how about it?
Will you agree to it?
...
This crazy bastard!
You're that bastard from the
bus stop the other day, right?
Who are you to keep following me?
Who do you think I might be?
The money you stole is only $23, $32,
$10, and three vouchers.
Do you how many people could have
been dead today because of this?
What are you? A cop?
The owner of this wallet
you just pick-pocketed
from will have to be
hospitalized for three weeks.
He will go to work without even
wearing a cast because he'd be
fired if he missed three weeks of work.
All because of you.
What the hell are you talking about?
Is this wallet yours by any chance?
He'll have to use his salary as his
hospital fee, and his not wearing
a cast will cause him to get a shock
later in life. Because of you.
Shut up if you don't want to die.
I'm asking who you are, you bastard.
I don't like letting someone like you live,
but it would be a side-effect
of my intervening in the
life and death of human
beings, so just go on living.
Don't think that you've received
enough punishment by this encounter.
You're going to be punished
again even after your death.
However, an eye for an eye, a tooth
for a tooth. This is my method.
It will hurt a bit. Bear it.
Ouch, ouch... ouch.
Get ready. Today's task will start soon.
Yes, yes.
The bus in question is approaching now.
Oh, it's Mr. Reaper!
Did that girl just see you?
Is she really seeing us right now?
Some of the people confronting their
imminent death can be like that.
I feel sorry that she's so young.
Why is she there?
Does anyone have Ji Eun Tak on their list?
Who are you talking about?
That's true.
There's an extra person
on the bus who's not
listed. Wasn't everyone
supposed to die?
Wait a sec, what happens
if one is left out?
I don't think any accident will take
place today. We came here for nothing.
What? Why?!
Ohh, the bus is not supposed to
just continue going like that!
It shouldn't be moving normally.
There's supposed to be
an accident happening right now!
It's leaving safely!
What should we do? Don't we
have to cause an accident then?
The bus... just went...
without anyone dying.
This never happened during my 300
year long career of a Reaper.
Seriously. What should we do?
It's my first time witnessing the coming to
existence of Miscellaneous Ommitted People.
This is indeed a miracle!
Miracles do happen...
- Wow.
- "Wow"?
Do you know how much paper
work this miracle entails??
What should I do with this little thing!
I'm sorry, sir. I was just very amazed.
But how did you predict this?
What a scare!
I-I think it's a Goblin.
Why? Don't I look like one?
Let's have a conversation.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Why do you keep on interfering with human lives?
Ji Eun Tak nearly died today.
If that's that child's fate,
it cannot be avoided.
Says who?
The only thing I cannot
grant is my own death.
Do you want to see me interfere with
every human life for that child?
You! In someone else's workplace...
But... the accident was strange,
regardless of how I think about it.
A few days ago, I already saw the accident.
But Eun Tak wasn't there. I also saw
that child's future 10 years from now.
But this was an accident that
would have definitely killed her.
It is because that accident that
you saw wasn't part of her fate.
She only got into that
accident as a variable.
Because you were going to save her.
Oh, thanks to the Miscellaneous Omitted
Person whose boyfriend is a Goblin,
All those who were supposed
to die ended up living.
You made me have to work overtime.
Would you like to eat some
chicken for midnight snack?
Have you really not had any
thoughts of turning into ashes?
It was a joke. Don't
take it that seriously.
I'm wondering what exactly it
means to turn into ashes...
Is it like dispersing
as dust, wind, or rain?
To somewhere in the world?
Why do you even wonder? The Miscellaneously
Omitted can't even grab the sword.
Eun Tak... grabbed the sword.
The sword even moved, so I...
I almost killed that child.
It hurt so much.
It was first time I felt that kind of pain.
Don't you think you should
tell her the truth now?
About what will happen when
the sword is taken out?
No.
If possible I want to hide
it, for about 80 more years.
- Why?
- That's a human lifespan exactly.
That is the maximum years a
19 year old can live to be.
I want to do that.
But will that happen?
Will it not be possible?
[SEOUL UNIVERSITY ADMISSION TICKET]
Did you come to pick me up? I'm surprised!
What I ate for lunch hasn't been
digested yet. That's why I came out.
I know. There's no way that you would come
out just so that I would be comfortable.
Huh? What is all this?
Why socks?
The 20s and 30s of someone
who I managed to save today.
Oh...
In order to save my 20s and 30s,
did you decide to start
selling socks from today on?
Because I asked you why you were jobless?
- Do you want to do it with me?
- All right.
Since all my interviews
have ended, I have
time now. So I'll take
care of Ajusshi better.
In what ways are you going
to take care of me?
What are you doing?
I'm strengthening my arm.
I'm going to make sure I
pull it out in one go next
time without hurting you.
I realized last time that
arm strength is important.
Take it easy.
What is this? A cheer that's
making me feel deflated?
Would you mind giving us some privacy?
- With whom?
- I just need a second. Go in your room.
Come here, huh?
Come down here for a sec. Don't you
think that I've been punished enough?
Are you that against my
receiving a tiny present?
You showed me that in
advance on purpose,
right? To prevent me
from taking any action.
Do you think I'll make that
choice just because of that?
I'm not going to, I'm never going
to, even under the threat of death!
Come down, will you? Come down,
and let's talk face to face!
Hey!
Do you think you'll be scared? Just
come down! Seriously, this fellow...
Is he still sick...?
I didn't see. I'm being honest here.
I really don't like it.
I, who likes you,
can't be this stupid.
What did you just do to me?
Never mind if you didn't here it.
/ I heard it.
That's good then.
So... umm...
He just... confessed to me...?
This guy... omg
forty eight
forty nine
fifty
What?
Wow
Because you never call me, I didn't
even bother to check my phone!
You surprised me!!
I was surprised that you
were the first to call me.
Especially because you called me ten times.
That's because I thought of something I
wanted to tell you when I was working late.
It seems to be a very
important thing to say.
Yes, indeed.
I'm not religious.
Why are you so good at speaking? Do
you have a religion by any chance?
There is something I should have...
yet again...
I'll get in touch with
you when I'm ready
You called me ten times to tell me that?
I thought I should tell
you as soon as possible
How cute.
I'm... cute?
Didn't you know that? Did no
other women tell you that?
I'm not seeing any woman
That's a good thing! That!
Not seeing anyone else!
Don't get ready to see other women.
Everything's perfect right now.
Understood?
I wonder whether this guy is a playboy
Answer me in a really really honest way
I'll tell you too.
What is it that I should answer?
My real name has only one syllable.
Sun Kim.
My parents wanted me to be well off, so
they hired someone to come up with
my name despite their being poor.
Apparently that clairvoyant
said it had to be that name.
But I prefer Sunny
It gives off the impression
that I'm sparkling
I hated that name so much
It feels like it contains a long history.
Sun Kim.
At this time each year,
Mister goes to that place
and puts up a candle.
Mister Woo-Bin Kim, what's your real name?
I know that that's a fake name.
I won't tease you even if your
real name doesn't suit you
so can you please reveal
your real name to me now?
[WANG]
Synced, ripped & added missing lines by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
With anger and wish, I'm
giving you the sword.
Go as far as possible, and
never come back if you can.
By that, you mean... How dare you say that?
Koryeo is your country.
I defended its borders because
you ordered me to do so,
and I destroyed the enemies
because you ordered me to do so.
When my sister is in this country,
and so are the citizens, how can...
Now you're worrying about things
that a king should be worried about.
Let it be known that Ryul Jang is dead.
It will be known soon.
It's a king's order.
Why? What's wrong?
Breast? Towards the middle?
What did you have for dinner?
Are your hands cold? Give me your hands.
Massaging your hands will
allow blood to circulate well
I'm sorry, but can you
look at my eyes please?
What?
Let's say that this meeting
never took place today.
I'm sorry that I couldn't walk you home.
Go back home.
Synced, ripped & added missing lines by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
Where did he go?
In the future,
you will have to take care of Mister Goblin
You should remember this day really well
Why are we going to hang candles?
Who are they for?
They are the people
whom Mister Goblin has been
feeling sorry for a long time
Btw grandpa! Did you know that there
was a sword stuck in my uncle's heart?
How do you know that?
You should not let him know
that you know about it.
Why?
That sword is
an award as well as a
punishment for Mister Goblin
It's the reason for his existence
and the clue for his disappearance
You who are my life as well as
my death
I love you
Therefore, I'm keeping a secret
and asking a higher
power for its permission
For another day
so that you don't know about
it even for another day,
so that yo don't know about
it just for a hundred years
You know me, right? There are some
things that I should let you know.
You have some time, don't you?
Be quick, will you?
I'm not in the right mood to
face a Goddess at the moment
Something went wrong...
Probably
everything started from you.
Where on earth did he go?
That's why I told him to
let me know before leaving
although he could appear without telling me
What are you curious about?
Oh, yes.
I think I already told you once.
You'll have to prepared
for me to leave to a
place that's further away
once the bride appears
There's something that
I'm feeling weird about.
About the sword in Mister Goblin's heart,
What will precisely happen
when the sword gets pulled out?
He kept mentioning that he
was going to go somewhere
So you're not leaving anymore? For now.
I might have to prepare to
leave for a place further away.
Where is that place he referred to?
Get that sword pulled out
of you as soon as you can
Get it pulled out and disappear
You appeared out of nowhere, and the first
thing you're telling me is to die...
You should at least me explain your reasons
You've lived enough.
But that's not the case for that kid.
I was really happy when I found
out her identity. Therefore, just
brings things to an end right now.
It's so enigmatic.
I don't know what decision
you're talking about, and
when I was first born
You marked me.
Aren't I your child?
That's why I'm telling you all this.
For my kid whom I wanted to be happy
It's something you'd want the most.
What do I want? / You
want that kid to live.
If you don't die,
Eun-Tak will die.
What you're saying is that
it's because he wants to die
that he asked me to become his bride
and pull out that sword?
So,
if I pull out that sword,
he will die?
That is,
if I pull out that sword,
he will disappear?
From this world? Forever?
Ever since she was born, she's been
fated to pull out that sword for you.
To be more precise, you caused
her to be born with that fate
If she fails to execute her task as a tool,
the reason for her existence will disappear
because then there won't be any
reason why she should exist
Therefore, if she doesn't
pull the sword out,
she will keep facing death
I'm assuming that she's already
confronted death multiple times
You're thinking right, those accidents.
There will be more in the future.
Those accidents will be take place more
frequently, and they'll be more intense.
Even you almost killed her
with your own hands
It's moving!
One day after living one
hundred years like that,
When the day is good enough,
there came first love.
Please let me be able to confess
I'm seeking
the permission of the sky.
♫ Where are you, who I am ♫
♫ Who I am, Who I am ♫
♫ Prison like loneliness ♫
♫ Loneliness ♫
♫ Many people walked passed me ♫
♫ This place is where
everyone walked passed me ♫
♫ Where I am ♫
♫ Who are you, Who are you ♫
♫ I cannot hide this joy ♫
♫ I flipped the world to find you ♫
♫ You who came into my dreams ♫
♫ Where are you ♫
♫ I will find you ♫
♫ I will recognise you ♫
♫ Despite where you are,
despite who you are ♫
♫ I will recognise you ♫
♫ I will remember ♫
♫ I will look at you ♫
♫ Even when you are not here,
even as many sunsets pass by ♫
♫ I won't forget you ♫
♫ When I tightly hold you like this ♫
♫ I keep forgetting about everything ♫
♫ The place I have to return to ♫
♫ I will find you ♫
♫ I will recognise you ♫
♫ Despite where you are,
despite who you are ♫
♫ I will recognise you, I will remember ♫