Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
♫ How can I get over you? ♫
♫ Why do we have to be ♫
♫ Apart ♫
Mister!
♫ Mysterious discovery ♫
Mass is not directly
proportional to volume.
A girl as small as a violet flower.
A girl who moves like a flower's petal.
Is pulling me towards her with a
stronger force than her mass.
At that moment,
just like Newton's apple,
without stopping, I rolled
towards her until I fell on her
...with a loud thump.
...with a thump, thump.
The red crossing was amazing!
You did that, right?
It's so fascinating!
Mister!
My heart keeps bouncing between
the sky and the ground.
Are you angry?
It was my first love!
- Episode 5 -
I... will walk.
It's okay to stop the car over there.
I memorized the area around the hotel,
- and if I walk I will be there soon...
- Do that then.
Goodbye!
Only the Goblin's bride
can pull out the sword.
When she pulls out the sword, you will
become dust and finally be at peace.
Sometimes in life, a strange
genre suddenly gets into the mix.
What genre was your day?
A romantic comedy? A strange,
but beautiful fantasy?
A sad melodrama?
Can you not do this?
Talk to me like a normal person. You
scare me when you act like this.
I'm sorry for startling you. I
want to ask you for a favor.
I'm really sorry for asking
this, but can you fill up the
refrigerator that's in the
room where I used to live?
The refrigerator?
It hasn't been too long since
I passed away. Mom was
busy with the funeral and
hasn't been to my place yet.
If my mom finds out that
the refrigerator is empty,
she will be heartbroken.
Please help me out!
But... I don't have any money.
Ah... I wasn't able to think that far...
I'm sorry.
Ah! There is a way!
Thanks.
♫ And I'm here ♫
♫ Just, just like I used to be ♫
♫ And we were here ♫
♫ In old days with you ♫
♫ With me ♫
♫ All my fears ♫
♫ Have gone when you whisper to me ♫
♫ No matter how you ♫
♫ Fall apart, apart ♫
♫ When you fear ♫
The tea is getting cold.
You lived well while being in this world.
Have a safe journey to the next life.
♫ When you feel so lonely ♫
♫ I'll be here ♫
♫ Here, for you ♫
What's this? Is it a coincidence?
It's not for me. Why didn't you call me?
I was waiting. You said you would!
I will do it. I'll go and do it right now.
Go where? Are you going
to look for a pay phone?
I have a phone at home. At home...
I'll call soon.
So funny!
When we've bumped into
each other like this?
Ah! It was nice to see you.
It's driving me crazy...
Instead of a phone call, how about coffee?
There are a lot
of coffee shops in Seoul and
I have a lot of free time..
♫ I keep on asking you ♫
♫ I'm always verifying with you ♫
Excuse me...
Are we just going to keep drinking coffee?
When the sun has gone down?
Isn't the daylight too short?
It's not short. You've been
like that for an hour.
Aren't we going to say hello? We're
not going to ask how we've been?
We aren't going to have a conversation?
Hello. Have you been well?
♫ I'm saying she's
pretty, pretty, pretty ♫
Yes. Have you been well, too?
Is my ring well? You still
don't have a phone?
Yes, I've been well.
The ring is fine. I don't have a phone.
♫ Despite the weather ♫
Be honest with me. You
forgot my name, right?
It's Sun Hyo.
It's Sunny, not Sun Hyo.
Seriously...
You are such a funny man!
Are you acting like this on purpose?
♫ I just want to hear it badly ♫
What are you staring at?
I can't help looking... when you smile.
♫ I'm saying she's
pretty, pretty, pretty ♫
♫ Why don't you believe me? ♫
Now that I think about it, I don't
know your name. What's your name?
♫ I'm still, to you ♫
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
She asked my name, but
even I don't know it.
She asked me how I was, too. To ask someone
who's not alive if they are doing well?
That girl's smile
in the sunlight of the brightest
time of the day, Oshi. (11AM-1PM)
That moment during which I am reminded
of the moment my life was shattered.
I made up my mind.
I must disappear.
Before I want to live longer,
before I want to become happier...
For you,
I have made the inevitable decision
to leave this world.
But... I hear your voice.
Are you really going to die?
Yeah.
[$1,540]
By any chance, did you drink?
No way.
Yes, you did. The refrigerator
is completely empty.
Chocolate, peanuts, even beef
jerky, there is nothing left.
Fine, you could eat and drink.
However, why did you throw
away the empty bottles? You
thought I wouldn't notice if
you threw the bottles away?
I had my reasons...
Chairman said that if I need
anything I should say it.
I'm sorry, but can you pay for me?
I don't have money.
I don't have any money either. I don't...
I... don't have any money.
I was about to pay...
Oh, you startled me.
I'm going in.
Mister, why are you here?
Deok Hwa told you everything?
Like what?
The thing is... he told me off.
He isn't someone with such a clear
conscience where he can tell others off.
I emptied out the refrigerator completely.
Couldn't you pay this somehow...?
Once I get my pay from my part-time
job I will repay you diligently.
It's not possible?
To be honest, you're the
one who drank the alcohol.
I used the rest for a good cause.
If you ignore me, I will
blow all these out.
I can make you come in and
out of here all day today.
Don't make wishes anymore.
You don't have to do it anymore, because
I will be by your side from now on.
Let's go home.
Which house...?
The house where I live,
since you are the Goblin's bride.
Mister, do you love me?
If that's needed, I will do that, too.
I love you.
♫ Since I had too many bad memories ♫
♫ I erased you ♫
♫ Because your love hurt ♫
♫ I buried it away ♫
Mister, do you love me?
If that's needed, I will do that, too.
I love you.
Do you dislike me that much?
How much and how do you dislike
me that you are this sad?
The rain just continues to pour.
Well, it's fine.
Even if you dislike me, even if you're sad,
I'm still going to live at your house.
I'm in no position to be picky about
whether I get a cold or warm goblin.
In the end, all I have to do is
to take the sword out, right?
Yes, that's all you have to do.
Please wait. I'm going to pack my things.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
Mister, what's your name?
I'm not asking because I'm so curious.
Regardless of the fact that we
are in a vague relationship
that's closer than cohabiting
but farther than a marriage,
I'm the Goblin's bride.
I should at least know the name of the
Goblin who's going to be my husband.
Us... I guess there's no "us" yet.
I think it started before you were born.
Us.
Sometimes Yoo Jeong Shin;
other times, Yoo Jae Shin.
Currently I'm Yoo Shin Jae.
My real name is... Kim Shin.
We can go...
It's green light.
Today... is the day we put out the trash.
You are refreshing every time I see you.
Give it to me. I will do that from now on.
What's with her? Why is she trying
to impress me all of a sudden?
She will be living with us starting today.
For your sake, the choice
that I have to make...
it's to end my life.
I'm rooting for the path
that's ahead of you
and the things you will do.
Let's go inside.
Yes. Please take care of me.
So, the thing that I will be doing in the
future... there must be a lot of housework.
It must be 4 digits, right?
Probably have to press the
star (*) at the end...
You don't know the passcode? Both of you?
We've never keyed in the
code before going in.
It reminds me of that moment...
Right before you
go in the haunted house
at an amusement park.
You feel scared and nervous, and
you don't know what's inside.
And you wonder if you'll be able
to come out safely once you go in.
Come in.
You... Why here...? Why is she...
When and how is she here?
She's going to be living
with us starting today.
Please take care of me.
Tell her the passcode.
1004 (ANGEL). But why is she
living here? (T/N: "cheon sa"
- (1004 AND ANGEL ARE HOMONYMS
IN THE KOREAN LANGUAGE.)
Why? What about me? About me?
You drink that in one go. Sober up.
We should get a cozy
chair right about there.
Is this a photo studio? It
would be better to have
pastel colored wallpapers
that soothe your emotions.
Is this a kindergarten?
We'll put a 19th-century romanticism art.
And a fireplace here would be good.
Is this a hotel? Over there, we should
have a Scandinavian style wallpaper.
- Is this a model house? She's my guest!
- It's my house!
It's my room.
I'm okay with everything.
We'll put up some 19th-century romantic
art style wallpaper on this side.
And we'll put a pastel-toned
fireplace over here. To be fair.
Then for now, should I sleep
on the living room sofa today?
If you are uncomfortable
having me in the
living room, the flower
garden is okay, too.
I'm not in the position to
discriminate where to sleep.
- So, if you are going
to bring someone in, you
should get a bed fi... -
Sleep in my room tonight.
With you?
No!
Then what about you?
- What does this mean?
- I shall sleep on the bed,
so don't worry about me and
sleep comfortably on the sofa.
Look at how strangely this Goblin talks.
Never. It's my bed. You'll make it unlucky.
I know. I told you not to concern yourself.
- Go and sleep in the sofa in the living room.
- I can't sleep on the sofa.
- She'll probably be going in and out.
- Then go sleep in a hotel!
I can't sleep at a hotel.
She's in that room alone.
Where are you going?
The miscellaneously omitted... I'll
make her sleep in the flower garden.
- Were you always this inconsiderate?
- Yeah.
- Then I will sleep on the sofa.
- Don't talk to me.
Please help her a lot when she's around.
Aigoo. It's so comfortable.
Do I have to sit like this?
My book.
I told him to look at it. Did
I tell him he could have it?
[THE STARS MIGHT TAKE YOUR GRIEF AWAY]
He didn't throw it away.
He's preciously cherishing it.
What book is this?
I don't know Chinese characters.
Even in a foreign land,
the war does not stop.
With swords and arrows, snatching
the land and the grains.
Taking lives.
The god of the foreign land and the
god of Goryeo are all the same.
The child who left Goryeo with me...
I buried him and his
grandchild's grandchild.
I, in a chair in a corner of a room,
I spent days and weeks.
My will is not words that are
left in the face of death.
Dear God,
my last testament is to ask you for death.
Though I have at times
regarded this life as a
reward, in the end my
life was a punishment.
Anyone's death...
I couldn't forget one.
So I...
am to end this life.
However, God is not listening as always.
Have you seen God?
Perhaps, are you looking at him now?
I told you not to talk to me. How
could someone like me see God?
I have seen him before.
- What does he look like?
- Just...
It was a butterfly.
It's always like that.
It makes you not able
to touch a passing
butterfly recklessly.
If he had at least shown me his face,
then I could resent him objectively.
I know.
If God really does only give
you how much you can handle,
I wonder if he didn't overestimate me.
Are you having a hard time?
Don't worry.
God whom humans see that often...
how could we not see him even once?
Right, this is the Goblin's house.
I wonder what they do for breakfast.
I wonder if there's any groceries.
They have everything that's needed,
but it feels lonely somehow...
How beautiful.
I wondered how it would be
since it's a men's household.
It's been such a long time since
I've had a meal prepared by someone.
I didn't say I was going to give you any.
Thank you for the meal.
I will earn my own allowance. And starting
tomorrow, I will take care of my own meals.
- I will also do the laundry myself.
- That's how we usually do it.
A wealthy household like this
usually has helpers that do...
What's this? Did you
practice without me knowing?
You seem to be in top form.
Since you two are like this, I see
why you can't get any helpers.
So I wrote down a few things
in a similar context.
I wish you would abide by them.
My appeals. First, I hope
it doesn't rain often.
Since the citizens would
be uncomfortable, so as
long as I am living here, I
wish you would be happy.
2. If you have any complaints, please
say them. Saying that you'll take me
or you would make things
that could make you
take me, I hope there
would be none of those.
3. If you have something
urgent, please call
first. Don't just suddenly
appear in front of me.
Ji Eun Tak. 010-1234-1234. And you
can't do so during class hours.
Not during work and I turn
it off in the library.
I will be going to school.
Could she be telling us to call her?
Is she looking down on us because
we don't have cellphones?
Really?
I want this one in chic black. I like it.
You have this bluish-blue. You like it?
This punk is over-excited
since it's his first
time seeing something like this.
Explain it.
Now, now. Take your time memorizing your
numbers. This is called a smart phone...
I'm okay, so just explain it to
him who's never seen this before.
What he said is right. You
only need to explain to me.
Uncle, do you know how to use it?
This thing is very smart...
Do you think I didn't use it
because I don't know how?
- It's because I don't have any need...
- When I watch dramas,
they look at each other's
faces when they call.
If you were that desperate, you should
have bought this 300 years ago!
These uncles, seriously. I
will teach you that later.
Now, first. Let's go to the Play store.
- Now?
- What?
W-Why are you getting up?
- You said let's go to the Play store.
- Oh.
Is it far?
What are you doing? Go get dressed.
You said you wanted to call while
seeing each other's faces.
I know. I can't see your face, though.
Are you holding it against your ear?
Move it away.
Move what away?
Your arm! Hold it at arm's length!
Like this.
Arm?
Okay.
Like this?
I can't see.
What should we do about you?
[KIM SHIN]
When they say military officer...
A general?
Oh, public service. A stable job.
But why aren't there any articles?
Were there not many accomplishments?
What is this? I don't know this number.
Hello?
Oh! You also know how to use a smartphone?
5.5 inch QHD display,
Octa-core processor, RAM 4GB,
proud on its strong materials
with a light and slim body.
What did you memorize it?
What do you need? There are a lot
of toothbrushes and towels at home.
Ahjussi, you don't know what this
it, right? Actually, this is you.
The cheeks are pink, so why is it me?
Not that. He's actually a goblin,
but since people are scared of him
he's wearing his favorite buckwheat
hoodie and pretending he's not a goblin.
Isn't he so cute? You
understand what I mean, right?
Ahjussi, this is something that
people use to study at night.
Ahjussi, this!
Do you have anything else that you need?
This is a lot. When I think
about having to carry all
these when I move out,
it's nothing but luggage.
- What do you mean?
- You never know with a
relationship between a man and a woman.
I could leave.
Not that? I'm asking what you mean
by carrying them all when you leave.
Who said I'm going to let you
have them when you leave?
[AGE VERIFICATION]
[GRIM REAPER]
But when I think about it, I don't even
know your name. What is your name?
I mean, did I ask for your annual salary
amount or your assets or your inheritance?
How can you stand up all of a sudden and
leave just because I asked your name?
I'm a bit sensitive about names.
I'm sorry, Sun Hee.
It's not Sun Hee, it's Sunny.
Are we already breaking up?
You said let's get some coffee for a
moment, and we finished drinking it.
So unbelievable.
But, by the way, the receipt that
you borrowed to get a refill,
you haven't returned it...
Why do you think I asked
for a coffee refill?
Do you like coffee a lot?
Please give me the receipt. My
company is strict on the receipts.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
♫ I keep asking about you ♫
♫ I keep wanting to confirm about you ♫
♫ Even if you tell the same thing ♫
♫ Even if you tell me every day ♫
Okay, okay.
♫ The lips come flying again ♫
♫ The cold sweats are coming out again ♫
♫ It's just an answer ♫
♫ But what you want to hear ♫
♫ Those words you want to hear ♫
♫ Those words to test me ♫
♫ You are really pretty, pretty, pretty ♫
♫ Why don't you believe what I say? ♫
♫ Why? ♫
♫ I say it, I say it, and
no matter how I say it ♫
♫ That expression of yours ♫
Go to your room. I made it a bit livable.
Really?
Do you like it?
You were going to come up anyway
but you had me carry all that?
Because I need my hands to rest.
These and these, this hand
spent a lot of money.
Ah! Was it this hand, too?
Could this be heaven? I love it.
Did you do it yourself? With those
fern-like (BABY-LIKE) hands?
I requested for it to be done as
though I was doing it myself.
Then rest up.
Oh. Don't put nails in the
wall, and my room's right
under yours so keep your
heels up when you walk.
Yes, please rest.
She's moving the flowerpot.
It has to face the south...
♫ Only your voice is heard ♫
She put it nicely.
♫ Nothing else is heard ♫
She likes the bed.
♫ As I focus on you more than anything ♫
♫ Or am I just crazy ♫
She opened the door to go out.
It seems I can't focus at all.
♫ It seems there's something
wrong with my head ♫
[ONE LADY IS STUDYING.
BECAUSE SHE IS A SENIOR.]
Na-Name?
Why a name?
By chance, are you talking
about when the grim
reaper calls your name
three times you die?
I'm married now.
I'm not who I used to be.
I have a family now.
I need to follow my husband's name,
so it's not Ji Eun Tak anymore...
It's not Ji Eun Tak.
Not your name. A man's
name that women like.
What?
I don't have a name.
So I want a suggestion. What
name would be like that?
You don't have a name? Mr. Goblin had one.
What is it?
Kim Shin. Isn't it pretty?
Jerk.
Well, do you have a name you thought of?
Hyeok, Joon...
Min?
If it's a name that women like, there
are three that best represents it.
Hyun Bin, Won Bin, Kim Woo Bin.
Bin...
It's not possible that he's really using
Hyun Bin, Won Bin or Kim Woo Bin, right?
But your name is Yoo Deok Hwa, isn't it?
There's a backstory to that
which I've been deeply upset
over. Why did Uncle have to be
so into Lee Deok Hwa in '91?
That's why I haven't even
watched the Moogando
(INTERNAL AFFAIRS) yet.
I'm boycotting.
Even if I become the head of
Cheonho Group, I'll probably still
come up behind that guy in search
rankings who was born in '61.
But then again, I would lose even to you.
What does that mean?
It means that a really important
thing lies in your hands.
- Something important? Like what?
- My card!
That... is more important than my life.
Wow!
What's wow?
I thought I was born with nothing.
But it seems like many things lie
in my hands, so it's fascinating.
Over here.
Can you stop the car in front
of that chicken place?
Perhaps... the chicken place
that you work in is that place?
Yes. Why?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
Please listen as you eat. The matter I
told you before about the chicken place.
I fell into an expected ambush so let's
forget about it. Please cancel it.
You're worrying about all sorts of things.
I didn't start it.
This is what they call this a
"blessing in disguise," right?
That's why I'm saying
this, but could there be
something that Grandpa
told you to give me?
There is.
Ji Eun Tak's college entrance
exams aren't too far away,
so he said she should take
good care of her health.
W-What you have to give me is not a card?
First, don't talk to Ji Eun Tak.
Second, remember that silence
is golden. Third, be silent.
Fourth, keep the mouth shut.
He asked me to relay this
message with the hopes that
you could handle these
difficult tasks very well.
It's not a card?
It's not.
♫ Right now in my dream you are present ♫
♫ We keep running into each
other like coincidence ♫
♫ Even your uncaring speech
is becoming familiar to me ♫
♫ Basically I like you ♫
[IF YOU'RE BORED WHILE
STUDYING, THE SWORD, PLEASE.]
[I KNOW YOU ARE BUSY STUDYING, BUT WHEN
YOU HAVE TIME, THE SWORD, PLEASE.]
[I KNOW IT'S HARD TO STUDY BUT FOR
A MOMENT, THE SWORD, PLEASE.]
♫ What kind of thoughts are you having? ♫
♫ You, you, you are you the same as me ♫
[I know you feel lonely while
studying, but if you get a chance,
[THE SWORD, PLEASE. AND KEEP THIS
A SECRET FROM MY COLLEAGUE.]
You startled me.
What is your dream? What do you want to be?
While eating this much
and not taking out the
sword and just studying,
what is your dream?
A radio PD (PROGRAM DIRECTOR).
For the rolling
admission, I studied
that department as well.
That's not what I'm saying.
How will you get
accepted to college when
lacking such comprehension?
Why would you wish me bad?
Actually I thought about it carefully,
and about you getting pretty,
I put it on hold for now.
On hold? Are you sure you
thought about it carefully?
What if you kick me out after
I lose my effective value?
The thought of that is so
stressful that I can't study.
If you can't even study, then why are
you finishing up the snacks every time?
See! Your true colors are showing.
You begrudge it?
That's why, how nice would it have been
if you gave me the $5000 when I asked?
Hey, still, I am water and fire
and someone who's here but
not, so how can I be so crass
as to bounce it off with cash?
I'd accept it with refinement, of course.
But... why does it have to be $5000?
The amount is too ambiguous. It'll be hard
to even rent a place with that in Seoul.
I don't even dare to dream
about renting a place.
Until I grow up, it's
money to stay at a sauna,
and if ever I do get accepted into
college then I would need tuition.
I came up with that exact
amount after careful
calculation of student loans
and various living costs.
That ambiguous $5000 is like $5,000,000 to
someone like me who has nothing. Happy?
Give her $5000. How could you do that?
So coldhearted.
I have something I am curious about.
I won't give you $5000 (OHBAEK).
That startled me. I heard
it as confess (GOBAEK).
Give her $5000.
Make your pronunciation clear.
I got startled!
He said to give me $5000.
Go and study.
But, then, is your name Kim Shin?
Yeah. Why?
Your name... is really cool.
Seriously, he's not calling. Call.
Boss, are you busy?
I don't even remember when I was last busy.
Then... can I call you Unni for a while?
I have no unni that I can confide in.
Wanting to call me unni...
then there's only one genre.
Are you pregnant?
No!
- Then?
- Just...
What do you think about marrying early?
How old is the guy? 19? 20?
A bit more.
It's not much even if you say so.
What kind of kid is he?
He's always near books, he
has deep taste in music and
art, and he also used to work
for the country back then...
Not that, what does he do to you?
Does he treat you well?
Ahhh...
For now. Since he needs me.
Then what about you? Do you like that punk?
No.
Then what about that
punk, does he like you?
No.
What's that then? Both of you don't
like each other. Why do this marriage?
I know, right.
What's with this marriage?
Continue with your work.
Mister, do you love me?
If that is needed, I will do that, too.
I love you.
I don't need that love.
Make sure you're not the one who needs it.
Just wait and see if I
let him become pretty...
I'm back.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Immortal Team @Viki
Are you folding laundry? I will do it, too.
You were always doing this by
yourself before, right? I can tell.
Thank you for recognizing it.
So all the bathroom towels are washed by
Mr. Grim Reaper. No wonder it felt killer.
Can you please refrain from
the expression "killer".
I'm sorry.
I really like the towels in this house.
They are soft and fluffy.
Thank you.
Netherland's representative painter
of the 17th century royal family.
Rembrand van Rijn's painting
best known as "The Night
Watch" unveiling the spectrum
of light and darkness.
But actually the true name of
the paiting is "The Militia
Company of Captain Frans Banning
Cocq." Where should I hang it?
That scarf, I think I saw that when
you were 9. It's the same one, right?
You're right.
It's a keepsake from my mom.
My mom thought that I could see ghosts
because of the mark on my neck.
So she always placed this around
my neck since I was a child
in hopes that I wouldn't see
ghosts when it's covered.
But it was no use. But it became a habit.
Now this is like my mom.
Give her $5000 (OHBAEK). - Why do keep
on telling me to confess (GOBAEK)?
And also you! You've got a
story to every question.
I'm too scared to even
ask you a question now.
- What's with him?
- I didn't reply to you though.
He has a really bad personality.
You must have had a hard time.
But, have you decided on a name?
Hey, Senior. Aren't you going to study?
You might
not get into college if
you do well (KEEP IT UP).
Why would I not get in if I do well?
If I do well then I would go in.
Nevermind. Go in and study. Would
you be a radio PD if you do that?
Oh, you want to be a radio PD? So cool.
Yes, I liked radios since I was a child.
I was the one who mentioned about
radio but why are you talking to him?
Talking with people that I live with...
People? See if there are any people that
you live with. Look at the sword here!
Mister, perhaps if you
haven't decided on a name,
how about Park Bo Gum?
Park Bo Gum (GUM=SWORD)?
What "gum?" Just because I have been
lenient because you see the sword!
Seriously.
Whose fault is it that I have this
mark and that I can see ghosts?
Have what? It's pretty.
Mister, did you just lift my hair?
Ahh! That's why you got stabbed with a
sword. People get stabbed for a reason.
How could you poke a person where it hurts?
Are you a psychopath?
Mister, do you think you weren't
like that at first? You said I
wasn't the goblin's bride, don't
live in rumors but in reality.
You must think you've never poked where
it hurts and you're all soft and fluffy!
I said that for your sake! For you.
If it's for me, give me a boyfriend!
Part-time work, my aunt's family,
and boyfriend! My wish for a
boyfriend has not come true yet!
- It's here! Your boyfriend!
- Where? Where here?
Here! Right in front of you! Me!
He must be crazy. What boyfriend?
With whose permission? Does he like me?
Give me $5000.
After 900 years...
If we argue about it, it would
be husband not boyfriend.
Should I go and make that minor correction?
It's a mess.
Someone can't even call
because he has no name.
They are just...
Someone can't even call
because he has no name.
They are just...
- It's so dark in here.
- What are you doing?- You're still at that?
Leave. Both of you.
What's wrong with Uncle down the hall?
It a face that's thinking of a woman.
What did I do? Where?
This must be that woman's number.
Put that down while I'm talking.
Uncle, this kiss mark, did you
try kissing it or not? Honestly?
You need to follow me. That
place won't be a good one.
- Uncle.
- It's going.
Hey! Don't!
If you won't call then why get her number?
To appear human. You never
know when I would call.
Now is that time.
Hello?
Like a human. Hurry.
Not Seon Hee, but Sunny
Hello, I am...
No. Should I go roughly?
What are you doing? Don't
you recognize my voice?
Not this, either.
Hello. Oh my! Hello.
- I go for the third.
- You were listening?
Why aren't you getting caught?
Isn't it cool? Fascinating, right?
I could do this, too.
Ding.
Eat, eat.
Freeze.
Hello.
You know how to call.
I thought you didn't or
maybe you broke a finger.
Ah, yes. I learned. My finger is not
broken. Thank you for the concern.
So my number was there.
Yes. Your number is here.
I waited for your call.
Ahh... yes.
"Ahh... yes." Is there nothing after?
Don't you have anything
more you want to say?
- For example?
- Morning, lunch or night? When is the
most comfortable time to
meet or something like that.
Morning, lunch or night? When is
the most comfortable time to meet?
I find it comfortable to meet in the
morning and separately at night.
I must seem human, so I'll walk.
Get in.
A human won't be able to
walk all the way to Incheon.
Ah!
- It's here. Your boyfriend!
- Where? Where here?- Right here! In front of you! Me!
I was startled because
you were in front of me.
I was thirsty... that...
I have to go to work.
Ji Eun Tak...
Yes?
You called me just now.
- I did? - Yes.- Why? - I know. Why?
Because it's awkward.
Me, too.
Then... should I say I'm hungry, naturally?
Will you? Then I will naturally
say, "Do you want to eat beef?"
I will go and get my coat then come out.
Go and wear your coat.
I'm done wearing. Let's go.
Wow! This is my second time here. I
might be a regular at this rate.
We sat there back then.
Welcome to Quebec. Please have a seat.
That's why, I should have
gone abroad to know.
So what, travelling abroad at 29?
When I was 29, I
didn't even go to the supermarket
in front of my house.
- Really?
- I didn't have any appointment?
I've been traveling around just fine, for
someone who's never been abroad before.
I only get lost a little and I don't
skip meals and I can eat a cow.
I'm at a nice restaurant with some man.
It's the man that has to be nice, not the
restaurant. I have to go. I'm sleepy.
Okay. Have a good night.
CEO, over here.
At the age of 29, you're still shining.
But I'm not... by your side.
My life of eternity has
finally come to an end.
In the time after my
death, you are still here.
You've forgotten me and your life
is perfectly complete with me gone.
I have to disappear
to make you smile.
This is the decision I have to make.
I have to end my life.
♫ Where I am, who I am ♫
♫ This loneliness like a prison ♫
In the end,
that's the decision I made.
♫ This place that everyone
just passes by me ♫
♫ Oh, where I am ♫
♫ Who are you? Who are you? ♫
♫ This happiness I cannot hide ♫
♫ Even if I dig around the
world like I am crazy ♫
♫ Dearest, where are you ♫
♫ I will find you ♫
♫ I will recognize you ♫
♫ No matter what you look
like I will recognize you ♫
♫ I will remember it. I
will recognize you. ♫
♫ Even if you are somewhere I am not ♫
♫ I will not forget. Your
speech, expression, everything ♫
- Preview -
He's still handsome and still strange.
I know he's strange but when I
see his face, I forget all that.
You don't press down the head like that.
You're supposed to brush it gently.
Can you make me prettier now?
- Yes.
- You shouldn't get hurt anymore.
You've been hurt many times.
I left the deed of the
property in the room.
This is really your house now.
Have a long and happy life.
And I have a favor to ask.
When I disappear, her
mark will disappear, too.
When that happens, erase her memories.
Don't let her blame herself.