[Lonely and Splendid Goblin]
Wait.
But I'm not done talking.
Did you just come through
that door, following me?
But what's with this place?
What's going on here? Where is this really?
Canada.
Canada? That maple nation?
The aurora nation?
This is really abroad?
Amazing! You had this kind of power?
You do, too. What are you really?
If this really is Canada and if this is what
your powers can do, I've made up my mind.
- On what?
- I'm determined.
- About what?
- I'll marry you, Mister.
No matter how I think about this,
I really think you are a goblin.
I love you.
Look how you're acting like it's
the first time you heard it.
- Don't!
- Oh!
Look how you're not saying no outright.
Okay, let's go that way.
Think of it as our honeymoon.
Hey!
♪ I only hear your voice loudly ♪
♪ I can't hear anything else ♪
♪ I can only see your eyes very well ♪
♪ Maybe I really am crazy ♪
♪ I think of you only all day long ♪
♪ And maybe it's made my head strange ♪
♪ Maybe I've fallen for you ♪
I look really natural, right? I don't
look like an illegal alien, right?
I don't look like someone who's come
abroad for the first time, right?
♪ You shake me up ♪
♪ You appear here and there
and get me all confused ♪
♪ I keep seeing you even in my dreams ♪
Merry Christmas.
♪ It's everywhere ♪
♪ Only I can see ♪
Could you take a picture for me? I want
to have a trace of me in this scenery.
- If you look here, and you push this, and you hear a click...
- I know.
Oh, unexpected. Then, take it
after you go one, two, three.
I don't want to.
Seriously! Where are you going?
Hey, wait for me.
Maple nation, for sure.
Is this the place? The red carpet for me?
You feel honored to be
walking with me, right?
Good. I was nervous you might
say, "honored, my foot."
By the way, what's that sign?
Fairy sighting zone.
This is? Fairies come out?
Awesome. It's romantic.
How great for you.
Why is it great for me?
Fairy sighting. You met a fairy.
Tinkerbell.
I'm a little upset that I got caught.
How did they know I'd come?
They put that stuff there so people
can make romantic memories like this.
What's the name of this neighborhood?
Quebec.
Even the name's dashing.
But did you know this?
If you catch a falling maple leaf...
You caught it? Hurry and throw it away.
Why should I?
If you catch a falling maple leaf, you'll fall
in love with the person you are walking with.
Be honest. You just made that up, right?
I didn't. It's in the same category of a catching a
falling cherry blossom and your first love comes true.
You said you loved me.
- Are you a goblin?
- No.
That's why you should
hurry and throw it away.
Why did you want to catch it then?
I thought I was walking
with that other guy.
Other guy?
I'm going to go close to the
handsome guy and take a closer look.
Ghost. Canadian ghost!
Scary.
I made eye contact with the ghost.
I'm nauseated.
You said you see ghosts often.
What's so scary?
He tried to talk to me in English. When a
ghost talks to me in English, it's scarier.
But this, Mister! Isn't this a hotel?
I know we are abroad, but don't you think this is too much
with a high schooler? You were saying this and that way.
You said you were going to marry me.
Are you a goblin, Mister?
I'm not. Rest here.
- Where are you going?
- I've got something to do.
What thing do you have to do?
Can't I come with you?
It's my first time abroad
so I'm very scared.
A kid who's so scared runs
around everywhere really well.
That's because... you were
by me and I trust you.
Will it take long? Who are you meeting?
Oh, you're meeting a woman then.
Right? To come all the way to Canada
must be because of some promise.
You must have had your reason to
say I wasn't the goblin bride.
I got it. See you later.
I have no money and no
passport and nobody I know.
My breathing's unstable, too, but
I'll just have to wait alone.
You know what I'm saying, right?
I don't.
It means, could you lend me $10?
You could abandon me. Well, intentionally or accidentally.
In that case, I'll need to call the embassy.
If I abandon you, summon me. That'll
be faster than the embassy.
It's not even $100 but just $10 but he reasons
it like that. Yeah, don't give me any.
Okay! Yeah? You're not.
You can't give it to me.
Give me a break!
Your change and receipt.
I'll enjoy it.
This is the miscellaneous omitted
person document you asked for.
They said it must be hand-written.
Okay.
But how does a miscellaneous
omitted person happen?
I only heard of the existence of
a miscellaneous omitted person,
- I never handled one in real life.
- It's like a god's whim.
Humans call that a miracle.
And we call that
a miscellaneous omitted person.
Then, is your case a miracle, too?
It's even more peculiar. Her name isn't on the list of the
living or the dead, so I don't know how to apply this.
It sounds like a headache. When
will you ever get the papers done?
I know.
Anyway, Sunbae, I heard you moved.
You're not doing a house warming party?
It's a lease.
I need to move, too. I
can't seem to save money.
I don't know if the owner has supernatural sense but she keeps
saying the grim reaper appears in her dream. It's killing me.
That's why I keep telling you you
need to pick a good location.
It's just that I really want to
experience living in a rooftop house.
But isn't it really weird? We're grim reapers, but we need a place to
live. We get sleepy if we don't sleep, and we get hungry if we don't eat.
I'm so tired now from working
late these past few days.
These days, I live on this.
Oh, right. There's a really
pretty girl in the new '23 class.
Where are you trying to run
away to after hitting someone?
What?
Right? You drank alcohol, didn't you?
Work hard.
That's it.
Are you nuts? Who drank?
Hey, your limbs are fine
so stop throwing crap.
Let's go to the police. To the police!
Let go. Let go!
Let go, I said.
- Try to kill me!
- Let go.
Na Kyeong Won, Kim Eu Ryong. Byeongshin
Year, Moosul Month, Gimi Day.
02:22, car accident deaths.
That's you guys, right?
Drink it. It will erase
your memory of this life.
Must I really forget everything?
My resentment towards him, too?
Listen, woman. It's your fate. You're dead
already. Why bother depending on that now?
It's better that you do.
Oblivion is also a consideration from god.
But why do you only give
this to her and not me?
You need to remember what crimes you committed. It's
not even the first time you hit and killed someone.
First, you will regret this moment
you couldn't drink the tea.
Next, you will think about why you couldn't drink
the tea and you will come to a realization.
That you can't undo this moment.
And that you are already
in hell.
Your body will be ripped
in pieces every day.
Every second you feel pain you
will regret what you did.
But that pain will never cease.
Forever.
I did wrong.
Forgive me.
Well, he's quite impulsive.
I know someone who is living in hell with
all the memories of his life intact.
I'm sure he's begged countless
times for forgiveness, too.
But there was no use,
he was still standing
in the middle of hell.
The young grandson of the grandson of
the grandson who left Goryeo with me
is buried here.
I've once thought of
this living as a prize.
But in the end, my living was a punishment.
I could never forget any of the deaths.
Have you been well?
[Yoo Geum Seon]
And you guys as well? I'm
still alive like this
and was not able to be in peace.
[Letters]
Found you.
♪ Through the endless daydream,
I saw you on the way back ♪
♪ There I walk with you in my arms ♪
♪ Through the glory darkness,
unveiling to the twilight ♪
♪ We've been far away from my fears ♪
I told you to stay quietly.
I was. You didn't even realize I came.
You had business here?
I'm done now. I was just about to leave.
But why is it that your grave is the
only one that doesn't have a name?
You always leave where you live like this?
How many times?
I haven't counted.
Hello, I'm Ji Eun Tak.
In about 200 years, I will be your bride.
That's not true.
Maybe not.
But even after 200 years,
you will still be dashing.
You're mean at times but you're growing
up well so don't worry too much.
Well then.
Let's go.
Did you live here for a long time?
From the time that place went from a cabin in a desolate
backwoods to a hotel, I went and came back and again.
This was the first place I settled
in after leaving my hometown.
What a shame. You should've
bought the cabin then.
Then that hotel would be yours.
Is that hotel possibly yours...?
What's with that look?
Do you want to eat this?
Where did you get this from?
You don't have any money.
So I stole it.
Hurry, eat up. We have to
eat and get rid of it.
What?
You believed that?
I stared at it because I was in awe
and they pitied me and gave it to me.
But is that hotel really yours?
- Aren't you running late?
- For what?
For school.
What's the time now in Korea?
10 am.
My teacher's going to kill me.
Should I just live here?
I mean, being an illegal immigrant
is better than being tardy, right?
I think that would be better.
I slept well.
I feel like I woke up from a dream.
I never imagined traveling abroad,
but thanks to you I could even go abroad.
Thank you for today.
Well then...
Since I've woken from my dream,
I should get going to school.
Even if I was a pest to you
today, forgive me for once.
It was probably because I was so excited.
What time is it now? The time, now!
I'm sorry.
You're a senior. How can a senior
come to school at the 3rd hour?
Did you come for school lunch? Or is it
that you don't want to attend school?
You've turned in your application and you're done with
your senior year? Like you already got into a college.
You said you didn't have tuition money.
I'm sorry.
I asked why you were late. I know you're living a hard life under supervision
by your aunt, but you're not the only one who's having a hard time.
Everyone lives hard.
Just because the SAT is almost over and you can't
go to college, you can't bother other kids.
I'm going to university.
What's with the look.
Go! Did someone stop you from going?
You are always this way
even when I'm being nice.
Wait a minute.
How have you been, Ji Soo's mother.
Oh, yes, yes.
You're too kind.
The evening you come home to after getting rained on,
what is the thing that is like an umbrella to you?
A voice that answers when you call.
A memory of seeing the same
thing at the same time.
Those moments when you first
matched your walking pace.
Is someone coming to mind?
Yes, that's the person.
Here's the first song for you.
I'm talking to you.
- Are you busy?
- Yeah, I'm busy.
Then follow me outside.
Follow closely, but not too close.
- It needs to be something so important that I should follow you closely or else you're dead.
- I'm verifying that, too.
My survival.
What are you talking about?
How come you came out from there?
It's surprising, right?
That girl was able to do something
that even the reaper finds surprising.
What, who? Who did what?
Do it again. I'm going
to stick even closer.
- What are you doing?
- What, why? I'm being competitive. Where am I going to?
I'm just a monster. Get lost. Go.
Get lost!
What am I if you just leave like that?
What is it? What can I not do?
- Mr. Tenant?
- Oh, you scared me.
Why is our Mr. Tenant out?
It's cold outside.
What about Uncle?
Inside.
No, no. Actually I came to see you.
- Stay there.
- Oh, yes.
You must really hate physical contact.
Well, it's nothing serious, but I was just wondering if there was
any problems that you're finding uncomfortable in living here?
Like it gets damp suddenly or
really bright outside the room?
I just wish your uncle
would suddenly leave home.
I know, right? To be honest, I really wish my
uncle left to go abroad as soon as possible.
If you get to know him, he's actually quite a big person,
but I don't know why he's staying in Korea like that.
You feel that too, right?
- No.
- Oh, you don't.
But I think I'm going to come here quite frequently
in the future, so what should we call each other?
It might sound really distant
to keep calling you a tenant.
Uncle... is probably too close.
I'll get straight to the point.
Uncle down the hall, save me once.
If some grandfather comes and asks who you
are, can you just say you're visiting?
He would really kill me if he knew I
gave out the room for rent to you.
Who's that grandfather?
My grandfather.
From the first to the very
last, I'll stand by your side.
Really.
I mean it.
If I open this door, it will be Canada.
It will be Canada.
Are you going to use it, student?
No, it's okay.
Senior in high school?
How did you know?
When you're wearing a uniform and have dead
fish eyes, then you tend to be seniors.
Oh... fish eyes.
Where do you live?
I live nearby.
That's good. Take this to eat.
- It's spinach.
- It's nothing great.
I got it from a guy.
Spinach?
Take it home and make sure you
share it with your family, okay?
I'm home.
Where the hell have you been all evening?
It's this time when I finish school
and then come home straight away.
Stop talking back.
- Mom, I'm hungry.
- Me, too, you rascal.
Oh, geez. Other families'
kids are good at staying out.
Hurry up and cook! How many people
are waiting because of you?
Yes, yes.
Reply only once.
Take it home and make sure you
share it with your family, okay?
Mom, mom, look at this. She's
probably planning to go abroad.
I researched this place, and it's Canada.
What? Give me that. Oh, yeah, I
knew you would be like this.
You were going to run away abroad with the insurance
money? And you say you don't have the bank book? Huh?
Give it back, please. I was just
going to keep it as a souvenir.
Why is this a souvenir? When have you
been here for this to be a souvenir?
Oh good. I'm glad I got you today. This
is how you repay me for raising you?
Like this? Like this?
Give it. It's mine so give it please.
She's all excited about running away, I
guess. Looking at how she made kimbap.
- It looks good.
- Where is it, b♪ tch?
Blood, blood.
What looks tasty? Your finger?
Blood.
Why the hell are both of them like that?
Mom, blood! Here! Blood!
Blood.
Where are you running to? Stop there.
Aigoo. Aigoo.
♪ And I'm here ♪
♪ Home, home ♪
♪ With you ♪
♪ With me ♪
She summons me and she can follow me through
the door, but she can't see the sword?
What the heck are you?
In 200 years, I'll be your bride.
I love you.
If she meant that, this is really awkward.
Curiosity will always beat dignity.
I'm very curious so I'll
need to go and ask.
Huh?
We've only just seen each other recently. Why do
you call me again in the middle of the night?
I was very busy at the moment doing something
important. What are you going to do now?
I didn't call you.
- You did.
- I didn't! I'm being serious this time.
Did you just think about me now or not?
Ah, that is...
See! I was right? You
thought about me, right?
Because you keep thinking about me like that, I
was brought out here when I'm busy. How tiring.
You get summoned even when
I just think about you?
It's not exact, but I'm sensitive.
So let's be aware of that, the two of us.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
Why did you think about me?
What was it about?
That is...
Canada was pretty.
It would be wonderful to live there.
I was still happy for a moment.
Those kind of thoughts
obviously reminded me of you.
Your clothes look expensive and your
watch looks even more expensive,
and it seems like the hotel is yours. It seems
like you've got everything that's good,
but why do you still look sad?
It lead to those kind of thoughts...
Well, that's that.
But why were you going round and round in
circles, during the night? It looks suspicious.
How did you know that?
I wish I didn't know, too.
I was waiting for my aunt's
family to fall asleep.
Once they are passed out they won't
even know if someone took them away.
I was going to sleep quickly and
come out early in the morning.
They all fall asleep around midnight.
So are you going to carry on being
suspicious here until midnight?
I'm walking because I wasn't
able to digest what I ate.
I know. You said that earlier, too.
I guess you had a big dinner.
I'm just saying so you don't misunderstand.
And you said that three times already,
as well. You can go if you want.
And you said that three times, too.
Oh my god. Ji Eun Tak's scene of
dating a sugar daddy discovered.
- The man looks obviously in his 30's.
- Crazy.
Hurry and take a picture and
send it to the group chat.
Geez! Why is he opening the door?
Mom!
[Help Wanted]
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Take away?
I'm not a customer, but
I saw the post in front about you
looking for a part-time worker.
- Is the owner here?
- She's here right now.
- High school student?
- Yes.
Ah, you are the owner.
I thought you were a customer
because you are so pretty.
Right? Customers are pretty.
But I don't know when the
last time I saw a customer.
If you have something you're curious
about, please feel free to ask.
For reference, I can meet
all your conditions.
Since I've got nowhere to fall back on.
I lost my parent at the young age of 9 and didn't
have anybody to take care of me (Sa Go Moo Tak)
- all by myself—
- Oh, radish (moo).
Our radish is good here. I don't remember
the last time a customer asked for radish.
Do you want some?
- Thank you.
- Are you poor?
Ah.
- I guess I am on the poverty side.
- What about school? You don't go?
I do. I'm a senior.
You must be happy since you're young.
- Huh?
- Do have business later on?
- No.
- Then starting from today, it's day one for us.
- You can work here.
- Really?
Thank you!
I will work the best I can! Really!
- Okay, you do whatever.
- Yes, I'll get things done well.
- So the chicken mister said it was chicken.
- Yeah, chicken is chicken.
But I don't know when the last time
a customer asked for chicken was.
[BBQ part-timer Ji Eun Tak]
Ah, Mister, what are you doing?
Do you hear my thoughts?
What? He's not coming
even when I think of him.
I finally got a job! The
owner is a total beauty...
You're eating something really expensive.
But you just wouldn't get me $5000.
You've got no thought on using the phone and making
appointments to meet like a civilized person?
- I like this way.
- It's not okay for me.
- You don't think about me?
- You don't come though even when I do.
I promise to meet you
everyday in the future.
I love you.
Smell of steak. I'm hungry.
Ack.
Geez!
- This outfit is better, right?
- What outfit?
Compared to the outfit I wore earlier.
Be honest.
You changed?
Then, does this outfit and this book match?
I think she's going to keep summoning me.
I want to have a perfect and intellectual
look no matter when and where.
- To whom?
- Can you please focus?
Think of this as the outfit I'll be wearing when I
leave this house. That'll make it easier for you.
Handsome! Blinding my eyes. The best!
So it means not this outfit.
Is this LP better or this CD better?
My idea is to look like I listen to classical
and K-pop music all without any bias.
This generation listens
to everything via files.
- Hey, is this painting better or this better?
- Get out.
The idea is that I appreciate
post-modernism to impressionistic art.
This is how you sleep?
What? This is how I like to sleep.
Don't. Is this a room? It's like a morgue.
You don't need a garland?
Let me just sleep.
I'm going to ruin you.
What are you doing?
- The laundry's dry.
- Work hard.
♪ Goblin's underwear is sturdy.
- ♪ It's sturdy even if you pull it.
- Don't do that.
This was your song? I didn't know.
But somehow it was easy to get into.
♪ Goblin's underpants is dirty.
♪ It smells and it's dirty.
- I warned you.
- What in the world did he do to the underwear.
I didn't.
- If there's even a song about it...
- I didn't!
What in the world does one do to
underwear that there's a song?
Was it very... manly?
I said, "Don't!"
A localized thunderstorm and heavy
rain is pouring down on Seongbukdong
bringing inconvenience to the residents.
Everything okay, Uncle?
I mean the heavy rain is only
coming down in Seongbukdong.
But, Uncle...
Why are you so out of sorts?
- Deok Hwa.
- Yea, tell me. Did something bad happen?
Before I tell you about what
bad thing has happened...
there's something I need
to tell you before that.
It's about your family's secret
and my tragic fate.
Don't be startled.
- Actually I am...
- A goblin?
Maybe it's not about that?
Since when did you know?
From when I was 8.
Actually, I started to
suspect when I was about 6.
You bragged about gold to me whenever you got drunk and
you'd say, "Come out, gold," but you don't remember?
Wow, is this for me?
No way.
You're so annoying!
From there, I was sure you
weren't my real uncle.
Look now, too. You're always
like this so how can I not know?
Be careful. I wonder if you're leaking
at home and are leaking outside, too.
So you already
- knew I was a goblin, since you were 6 and all this time.
- Yeah.
But yet you kept
saying "Yeah" to me all
this time since you were 6?
Yeah.
Sir.
Today's localized thunderstorm and heavy
rain must have been quite a surprise.
Seoul weather forecast service
is monitoring the heavy rain
and a heavy rain warning has been
issued for Seoul and Gyeonggi.
There's concern about after work traffic congestion from
slippery road conditions. Next is Reporter Lee Min Soo.
Seongbukdong is getting an even
heavier downpour than earlier.
People's feet are being halted
as they try to leave work.
The police are trying to
reduce traffic congestion
and advise that people use public
transportation if at all possible.
It's raining. It's nice.
What's nice about it? We won't
have customers when it rains.
We don't have customers
even when it doesn't rain.
They're not coming anyway so it's
nice to have the rain at least.
I don't have an umbrella, though.
I have lots. Take one.
I always left it because
it's a pest to take it.
Don't be a pest and bring it back again.
Really?
I have an umbrella now.
Is it the first time
you've seen an umbrella?
Thank you.
I need an umbrella to
appear in my life, too.
It's stale.
Should I give you new ones?
Never mind. I already know what
it tastes like. It's a pest.
You're going somewhere?
Part-timer, that's something
only the boss says.
You just need to play hookie
and play when I'm not here.
No, a worker can't play hookie
just because the boss is not here.
I need to work harder
when I'm not being seen.
If you work harder when you're not seen,
the boss won't know, Part-Timer.
You should play.
She's so cool.
Have a good trip.
Oh, triplets. I'm the youngest one.
Let's have a look. What are
you curious about to be here?
Isn't that something you need to guess?
Something's not going well, I guess?
I wouldn't be here if things were going well.
I'd be sitting at my shop counting money.
Aigoo! You have no luck as far as having children and a husband.
You'll have trouble with the opposite sex and will always wander...
So, I have all kinds of bad
luck including old age, huh?
I should lose weight, huh?
What a cold fate.
You're a lonely orphan
without any relatives.
How did you know that?
Life is like a boat that is
floating on an open sea.
I wish I could be on that
boat with a handsome man.
I see a man. Be careful
of a man who wears a hat.
A very black hat.
I wish that hat-wearing man is handsome.
Where are you going?
Cleaners. It's "dry clean only."
I feel this each time, that
that hat's such a great plan.
So that the deceased can have a
laugh on their final way out.
Don't seek death. Death will seek you.
It's a proven fact.
- I have to wear this so the deceased can identify me and not be seen by humans.
- I see.
I'm glad humans can't see it or you'd
be so embarrassed. Have a good trip.
Are you sure you don't need to iron it?
What era did you come from? These
days they stick well like this.
How about you? Who laminates
maple leaves these days?
The one who's getting this is
from the old days so it's okay.
Who? You've got a boyfriend now?
Hey! What boyfriend!
He helped me find a job so I'm grateful.
What if he misunderstands you after
he gets this, that you like him?
He denies my very existence so he won't.
Mister, I have a present for you...
My scarf. I left my scarf.
Indeed... you see me.
Ten years ago and now, too. Same line, too.
What if the boss locked the door. Dummy.
It's useless. I know you see me. No
one's here to protect you this time.
I know I'm caught.
You moved. Thanks to that I looked for
you for 10 years. Now we meet today.
Then don't look for me.
In this life, we'd call you a stalker.
Do you know that?
I'm going to sue you. My name's
not even on the list of the dead.
It's on the miscellaneous
omitted person list.
Though it'll be a headache due to
19 years of evidence documentation.
Then... now what becomes of me?
I'm going to die? But I'm only barely 19.
People die at 9 and people die at 10, too.
That's death.
But who are you with again this time?
Close your eyes. You can't meet his eyes.
He's the grim reaper.
No. Don't look at his eyes.
It's okay. I know him.
I guess you're working.
I am working, but I don't
know what you're doing.
I'm in the middle of meddling
with human life and death.
That's what I mean. It
seems like a huge mistake.
This kid, 19 years ago, should have been...
Do I look like I want an explanation?
Didn't you learn to pay attention to
the goblin when he's being serious?
Watch it. I might want to meddle
with your life and death.
Let's run for now. There
will be a way if we run.
This way.
It's okay. Just stay. He can't take you.
- He just said he's been looking for me for the last ten years...
- Still...
Even if he's been looking for you
for a hundred years. Even still...
No Grim Reaper can take away a girl
who's willing to marry a goblin.
Especially in front of the goblin.
Oh, then by chance, is she...
Yes, that's right. I'm the one.
That goblin bride you've
heard so much about.
What will you do now? Are you
still going to take me away?
Looks like I'm the bad guy here.
That's the one I'm here for.
Let's talk details later.
We'll see each other again. It can be a coincidental
meeting like today or an appointed time.
Say it. You look like
you've got a lot to say.
See? You're a goblin.
I knew it.
Why did you lie and say
you're not a goblin?
I didn't think I'd see you
again in the beginning.
Who knew you'd follow me through the door?
No one has ever followed me through my door.
How about after that?
I asked you many times after that.
I didn't need to correct myself after that.
From the beginning to now... and even in
the future, you won't be the goblin bride.
Then who am I?
Ghosts always talk to me about the goblin.
They bug me if I don't see them.
If I do, they get clingy.
I'm alive like this...
yet the Grim Reaper says
I shouldn't be alive.
Who am I then?
I told you it's something
you'll have to bear.
I don't think it's something
you can quibble with me about.
So petty...
This is so unfair...
Do you think I really planned on
marrying the goblin when I met one?
Tell me honestly. It's
another reason, right?
By chance, did you say you're not
the goblin because I'm not pretty?
Because I'm so far from your ideal type?
- It's true!
- That's not it.
You always say that's not it. You said
you weren't a goblin, but you are.
You're pretty.
I've lived longer than 900 years. I'm
not looking for a pretty person.
I'm looking for someone who'd
discover something in me.
That's why you, who hasn't discovered
anything in me, you're not a goblin's bride.
That's all there's to it.
That's what I mean by you don't
have an effective value.
It hurts because you
make it sound so simple.
You don't need to be hurt.
Rather be relieved.
If you did indeed discover something
in me, you'd be resenting me.
Then why didn't you insist that you're not the
goblin to the end? Why are you revealing it now?
For the same reason I said I wasn't.
I don't want you to call me out hoping for
something. I'm about to leave this place soon.
To where?
Never mind. Don't answer me.
I'm not curious at all. Who
said I'd be your bride?
At my pretty age of 19,
you think I'm crazy?
I won't call you out again. Relax and go on
with your life. I don't need you, either.
I just think, "Oh, this is
what a goblin looks like."
So, you're finally going to die?
The rumor has it that you'll
die when the bride appears.
Unfortunately, I can't die.
She can't see the sword.
Well, she may not be
able to see it just yet.
Or maybe you have to be completely naked
for her to see that. She's still young.
She's still young, so don't go near her.
Why are you protecting her? You
said she can't even see the sword.
Just congratulate me. I get to live longer.
Go somewhere else and live a long life. I can't
live together with a goblin who meddles...
- with my life and death.
- There is an easy way of you moving out.
The exit is that way.
♪ This beautiful life ♪
♪ I'll stay by your side ♪
♪ I will stand behind you ♪
♪ Beautiful life ♪
♪ Your memory, your scent ♪
♪ It's disappearing one by one ♪
Unni, you're all grown up.
Why do you look at books like these?
Should I say it's like doing a
background check on my boyfriend?
It's kind of like looking
through his Facebook.
You have to do all these
things when you grow up, okay?
Does your boyfriend come out in
fairy tales? Is he a prince?
I know. If he was going
to be in fairy tales,
wouldn't it be nice if he was
a knight in shining armor?
What's this, huh?
This is more fun. Read this one.
[Colorful Goblin]
Thanks.
How about after that? I asked
you many times after that.
I didn't need to correct myself after that.
From the beginning to now... and even in
the future, you won't be the goblin bride.
Gosh... he was just a broomstick.
I'm not going to do this either.
I'll throw it away.
Deok Hwa, you...
Uncle, you were here?
You said you used to smoke and quit.
That was so long ago. It was
350 years ago, 350 years!
Geez...
Sorry.
What's wrong with him?
He's been like that for three hours.
It's so damp in here.
What's with you, Uncle down the hall?
Is this a cumulus cloud? I came
here wanting to ask you that.
Uncle, no rain, okay?
Who'd clean up all that?
Looks like he's thinking about a woman.
He spoke more than three words
to a woman in 300 years.
- He looks like he hurt her.
- What? What did I do? What?
I guess the fight between the husband
and wife didn't end too well.
"We'll see you in four weeks." Is it
something like that? (divorce court)
Wow, do you have a girlfriend, Uncle?
Is she pretty?
- She's 19 years old.
- Geez! Wow! Is she pretty?
I'm not thinking about her. I'm thinking about stock shares.
What are you saying in front of a kid? Hey, you Grim Reaper!
I hope you don't dismiss the Grim
Reaper's ability to foresee.
You Goblin, who's thinking about
a woman in front of this kid...
What?
If you couldn't get her, forget it. But...
if you hurt her, you should apologize like
a man. Why are you sitting here like this?
Deok Hwa, you don't know anything
since you're still young.
- Be quiet.
- I spoke quietly.
A pathetic conversation.
Uncle down the hall, please be understanding. I'm
embarrassed of him wherever he may be. I apologize.
Just be a man and apologize. Be a man!
Ta-da, ring. Ta-da, purse.
Ta-da, credit card.
- Where are you going?
- To the supermarket. How about you?
To the dry cleaners.
This is dry clean only.
- I'll get going first.
- Work hard.
You said you were going to the supermarket.
Is this the supermarket?
You said you were going to the dry
cleaners. Is this the dry cleaners?
So, did you follow me?
She's not here, either.
She's not there? Did you kill her?
That's a very rude remark,
you careless goblin.
Going into someone's home wearing shoes
is more rude, you mindless Grim Reaper.
- Where is she?
- You didn't kill her?
Did you tell her to move?
I came here to tell her to move,
but she moved on her own.
You think I can't find her
just because she moved?
Yeah, you couldn't find her for ten years.
The way I see it, you won't find
her even if she didn't move.
So, where did she move to?
You know, right? Where is she?
It's okay.
I only slept there. It's not
like it was my real home.
Excuse me.
Not here.
Hey.
You see me, right?
Yes, I see you. I see you really well.
Let's talk.
- Where did she go?
- Hey.
You're scaring me.
- Why are you like this suddenly?
- You said I was the goblin bride last time.
Why did you do that?
Oh, that. I heard it from
the grandma with dialect.
The way I see it,
he saved her after seeing her face.
Your mom was good-looking.
So...
like this, she was dying then
her breath suddenly came back.
In the middle of winter, cherry blossoms!
Cherry blossoms were falling
and it was so amazing.
You're saying the goblin
saved my mom and me?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure you and your
mom were supposed to die that day.
Later on the Grim Reaper came.
He got nothing.
So in the end, he saved his own bride.
So romantic.
What that mister said was all true.
I had no right to hate him from the start.
If it wasn't for the goblin,
I wouldn't be born.
And I wouldn't have memories of
living with my mom till I was 9.
Did you get mad...?
At the goblin? Really bad?
What do I do now?
How about
you just come with me?
What do you mean, what do I do?
You have to marry the goblin.
Here.
[bbq Olive Chicken cafe]
[BBQ Part-Timer Ji Eun Tak]
Excuse me. There is a
part-timer here called Eun Tak.
Oh my goodness.
Welcome. Take a seat wherever.
No. I'm not a customer so
tell the owner to get here.
- Quickly. I'm in a hurry.
- Then talk in a hurry.
This lady is the owner.
Oh... you're the owner?
I'm Eun Tak's aunt.
Who did you get permission from to
have my precious niece work here?
She didn't look precious.
- What?
- Do you know "Sa Go Mu Tak?" (no one to depend on)
She's that.
What are you saying? Some Tak?
She's Ji Eun Tak. Did she say she was that?
It's okay. I didn't know either so
I looked it up on the Internet.
This lady... Why are you talking
to me informally (ban mal)?
Right? I hate people ordering
only half a chicken (ban ma ri).
Chicken should be ordered whole.
Why this crazy b♪ tch...
You know, Eun Tak's aunt, your precious
niece should be at school at this time.
Why did you come here?
I tried at school several times,
but there are too many people there.
So cooperate.
I'm just worried because
she ran away from home.
Hey! Are you going to take
responsibility if she goes astray?
I will stay here like I'm nonexistent.
So don't worry about me.
Oppa, it's been awhile.
I'm doing okay.
Except this lady, who must think I
have a good heart because I look good,
is really bothering me.
- That b♪ tch.
- Oppa, do you still beat people up?
You don't feel guilty beating a woman?
Gender equality?
You can't live like that.
What? You're on your way?
The address is...
I'm leaving! I'm leaving! See?
I'm leaving!
What are you talking about? What are
you doing? Your dialect is horrible.
I know. I just tried.
You're doing well? Bye.
Geez, what a crazy b♪ tch.
This girl, wait till I find you.
Why come all the way to my house?
I was just about to call you.
Look. See?
The borrowers live more
peacefully than the lenders.
You think I came all the way
here because I had leftover gas?
I told you I'll pay back as
soon as I find the bank book.
This girl ran away from home. That
puts me in a difficult situation.
You don't answer my calls. That
I even brought my car. Let's go
sightseeing in a nice mountain, Ahjumma.
I-If something happens to me,
you won't get your money.
Her l-legal guardian is me!
Only her mouth trap is alive.
How long have you been talking
about that insurance money?
Is there any insurance money at all?
There is.
Her mom had the infant insurance and
a life insurance that she paid for 8 years
like she knew she was going to die.
It's about $150,000!
But the bank book keeps on disappearing. I get it
reissued and it still disappears. It's driving me crazy!
It's true. That girl has it.
I'm certain.
What school did you say she goes to?
[Hey. I need $30. I'll pay you
back next week. Get back to me]
Student, where are you going?
Who are you?
Why did you run away from home?
It's dangerous.
Why are you doing this to me?
- Why are you...
- Your aunt is very worried. Get in!
I'm curious. To rent this house for 20 years, it must have
cost quite a bit. Where did you get that big sum of money?
People in charge of the funeral put
money on the bier for the dead,
so the dead could pay for the ride across the river to
the afterlife. I've been saving that for 300 years.
So do you think I could
give this house up or not?
Wow. It's been awhile that I
heard the term "saving money."
I have plenty of gold and money.
Do you need pepper?
You don't learn, do you?
That was a plate from Louis the 14th!
Put down the fork.
Put your knife down first.
I really don't know. I really
don't have the bank book.
My aunt has it.
Your aunt says that you have it and
you say that your aunt has it.
Then one of you is lying.
Right?
This girl!
What? You want to really go at it?
Student, we're very impatient.
Do you know where this car is headed to?
A female student goes to such a remote
place and what happens to her...
you would've seen it a lot on TV, too.
Bank book. Where did you
hide the bank book?
I really don't know. Why are you doing this
to me when my aunt is the one with the debt?
Let me out! If you don't I'll report you!
Report? I'm the one who should report you!
Hey, jerk, drive straight!
- Hyung.
- What?
- There.
Preview
Mister, thank you for saving me!
Tell that to the Mr.
Grim Reaper for me, too.
So what exactly am I supposed to see?
I don't know where she is.
She's not calling for me.
She doesn't call so I can't find her.
I guess I thought of you. Briefly.
Promise me one thing.
What promise?
That you won't take her after I leave.
To bid farewell.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
My heart has been in a dizzying pendular
movement from the sky to the land.
Sending out thumps. It was the first love.
Only the goblin bride shall pull the sword.
Written by Kim Eun Sook
Produced by Lee Eung Bok
A romantic curse
A fatal destiny
[ The last adornment of 2016 ]
[ tvN tenth anniversary drama ]