(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
I'm so sorry I'm late.
I find it hard to walk when there's a crowd.
You made it before I aged a year.
- Shall we go to Bosingak Pavilion?
- Before we do,
can we hold hands?
Right now? Just like that?
I'm too curious to wait.
Human's are strange beings. I want to play hard to get.
Do you want to hold my hand?
Yes.
Me, too.
I wan to hold your hand and hug you.
But I should at least know...
whose hand I'm holding and who I'm hugging.
You haven't answered my question yet.
What exactly are you, Woo Bin?
You haven't yet told me how you know my real name.
I'll only let you off the hook this year.
It'll be next year in just two hours.
Is it too much to ask?
I apologize.
Okay.
Shall we call it quits?
You pushed me away from the cars...
and I liked watching you solve math problems with a pencil.
It was all good,
but I can't do it anymore.
Let's say you dumped me.
Don't call me from now on.
Even if we meet by chance, don't say hi.
Happy New Year.
Let's start our romantic night again.
Is it still romantic?
Even more than before.
A dimly lit bar.
Simple foods.
Bitter soju.
A cruel fight.
Romance is everywhere.
If there was just one more thing, it would be perfect.
What?
First kiss.
- What?
- That was just a peck last time.
You can't move, okay?
Meanie.
You...
Did you forget I'm the goblin's bride?
It doesn't work on me.
In other words, you cannot avoid it.
I wasn't avoiding it.
It was hard enough avoiding it the first time.
Perfect.
There is something I didn't tell you.
I saw her past.
- You said it's a secret.
- I think...
she's the reincarnation of your sister.
Are you sure it's Sunny and not you?
Sunny's face in her previous life...
matches the face of that woman...
on the scroll you have.
Are you sure?
What did you see?
The woman I saw...
was standing in the middle of a palace.
She was dressed in white and looked noble.
She took an arrow to her heart...
and collapsed as she bled.
I told you those things.
Maybe not about her clothes...
or about the arrow...
What else? Did you see anything else?
She was on a palanquin and she smiled at someone...
through a small window.
Smiling, she asked,
- "Do I..."
- Do I look pretty today?
A voice answered to her.
- "You look..."
- You look ugly.
Is she...
really your sister?
Yes.
He's a new face.
He's the one who has been roaming about for a long time.
Oh, that one.
20 years ago,
he even escaped from a grim reaper after confronting one.
I think it's been about 20 years.
I came across a deceased soul...
and I had no information on it.
Really? I had a similar experience when I was nine...
It seemed like it had been roaming about for a long time.
It seemed fearless.
I never saw a deceased soul who didn't fear a grim reaper.
I thought it was strange.
Nice to meet you.
So you are the goblin's bride.
Yes, same here.
You shouldn't make yourselves at home in someone's place of business.
You'll keep the customers from coming.
It's time to do business, so please leave.
Cold-hearted brat.
You first. Hurry.
Unfriendly brat!
He felt...
In my 20 years of seeing ghosts,
I've never seen anything like it.
Let's forget.
I'm too busy to think about ghosts.
If I take all the classes within four days,
I'll have to start work later.
Like this?
A love letter? You're so annoying.
I'm too busy just trying to survive, and you wrote a love letter?
I am...
a grim reaper.
I want to see him.
I don't want to see him.
How is it always exactly seven shots?
I know it'll end exactly after seven shots,
but started with "I want to see him."
I want to see him.
I don't want to see him.
Have you ever been hit by peach flowers?
I have.
I got a beating at a shaman's house.
That scars for a while.
The previous ones were better.
Right? They were, right?
Have you...
ever wanted to get your memory back?
No.
What is a memory you've forgotten?
It's like a memory that you never had.
You never had it anyway, so why?
I...
miss it.
Don't.
We are all sinners.
We don't know what that longing will bring.
I know.
I know it.
Each time I long for it,
I don't know where it's going to take me,
and it dreads me.
But...
I still miss it.
It looks like you're drinking too much today.
I got caught. Sunny found out that I am a grim reaper.
Good job.
Where did she get...
a branch of peach flowers in the middle of winter?
Exactly.
What do I do now?
She must be very confused.
What are you worried about?
Since you already got caught, you should hold her hands.
And see if you see my face.
I said I got caught.
So casually hold her hand and see if you see me.
You are greatly mistaken.
Do you know how hard it is to see one's past life?
It comes to you as if someone is suddenly pushing it inside you.
When the lady in the picture came to life, she was so beautiful.
And her beauty totally made me go mad.
She's my sister.
So...
I did see one young and foolish face.
It was that young king.
My foolish sister must've only thought about him.
She doesn't care about her brother at all.
I'm here. What is it?
It's nothing. I'll come next time.
Give it to me. Don't look at my notebook.
Why did you write about me then?
What is this?
Did you forge a document again behind my back?
Stop pretending not to know what it is.
It's a love letter. It's a love letter you wrote.
Did he write a love letter?
He did for his first love.
I wanted to know how it ended and see how special it was.
I was going to ask for your help.
Do you know what it's about? It's not a love letter.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Whatever.
It was very well-written.
"One day after 100 years..."
"When the weather is good enough."
- That's not it.
- That is it.
Deok Hwa read everything to me.
"One day after 100 years..."
"When the weather is good enough."
That's impossible.
Deok Hwa could never read this.
That wasn't written anywhere.
I've been keeping it to myself.
One day after 100 years...
When the weather is good enough,
I hope I'll be able to...
tell her she was my first love.
Right. That's not it.
That can't be right.
Deok Hwa interpreted it for me.
It's a love letter.
When...
you blew away tens of cars,
did you tell Deok Hwa...
that I could help people forget?
No.
Come with me.
How did he know and...
ask me to come along?
Actually,
Deok Hwa found me the maple leaf.
I had lost it.
Guess where this leaf is from.
What's going on?
That's impressive.
Why didn't I realize sooner?
He even dared to put the goblin's house in the market.
I don't know if it was the king, the divinity, or me.
This letter means "to hear".
I found her, She's at the ski resort right now.
That's because your boss was his sister in their past lives.
Shall we...
have a drink?
Finally, the goblin met the goblin's bride.
It's a destiny.
What about Yeo?
How could you make them meet?
One with a sword in his chest and the man who did it to him.
What brings you to my house?
Do you live here?
That's a destiny too.
He was looking for a house anyway.
You need to take down a notch.
What on earth are you thinking?
I love him particularly.
It's been 900 years since Kim Shin has been punished.
Is that still not enough?
That's how substantial one's life is.
Why didn't you create a perfect world...
without a sin in the first place?
Then nobody would look for the almighty.
Every child was conceived with love.
Stop torturing them.
Get rid of the hands that are covering his eyes.
Let them recognize each other.
Let them make their own decision.
It's too bad.
I loved him for his good looks.
They are finally here.
Deok Hwa.
Who are you?
Let's introduce each other.
Please, no...
Please...
Don't pray to anyone. The almighty is not listening.
"The almighty is still not listening."
You were whining.
"The almighty must have had his reason for erasing my memory."
I will live whether or not I remember my memories.
The almighty must have his reasons.
You were guessing my intention.
I was always listening.
You were pleading for death, so I gave you a chance.
But...
why are you still alive?
I never erased your memory.
You chose to have your memory erased and yet,
you think it's the almighty's plan or mistake?
The almighty simply questions.
Fate is the question I throw.
You...
can find the answer.
You can say bye...
to this boy too.
Well, then.
I'll get going then.
Why are you two here?
When did you come?
Why am I on the floor?
No way.
Did I just black out?
But I just had one drink.
Whoever you are,
let me hit you once.
Why would you hit him?
He doesn't have anything to do with it.
Are you siding with him?
I'm sorry I kept asking you to go somewhere with me.
What?
What's wrong with him?
Are you serious?
Are you really Deok Hwa?
He's a butterfly. A butterfly.
You must be drunk.
Come here. Come here!
Let go of me. Let me talk to him.
Let go of me. Let go.
It's hot. It's hot.
It's really good.
It turns out he's a grim reaper.
How did you find out?
I witnessed a very strange moment.
We happened...
to cross paths a few times in my life.
Sorry I didn't tell you.
For a grim reaper, Woo Bin's...
really sweet, gentle, and...
Does he have a clingy ghost ex-girlfriend?
That was the first thought I had.
We aren't a good match. I'm way out of his league.
We live in two separate worlds.
How did you think of that?
I even had this thought.
If he's a grim reaper, then the man who says he's my brother...
must have really lived for nearly 1,000 years.
Is that true? Are you the wife of the goblin?
Technically speaking, I am his wife,
but I'm the breadwinner.
This is insane.
Boss.
Even if you hang out outside of our house,
it's very unlikely that you'll see Woo Bin.
He works late very often.
Give him a call.
How can I when he suggested we break up?
I'd force myself to take his call if he were to contact me first.
Just play along.
Okay.
Boss, I'm really sorry but...
Sure, do what you want.
I didn't say anything yet.
You're in college now and you want to work different hours.
That's incredible.
You're a real human being, right?
Welcome.
It's been a while since I got startled by a human.
Me, too.
Why are we eating chicken anyway?
The owner lives in the flat beneath mine.
We should help our neighbours.
Let's eat up and get going.
Early January is the busiest time of year.
Enjoy your meal.
We didn't order this.
It's on the house. It's a new menu. You guys have a tough job.
Thanks so much for noticing.
It tastes delicious.
What's the matter?
- Eat up.
- I'll dip it first.
How dare a ghost appear in front of a grim reaper?
It has been a while.
I see you have been living as a grim reaper.
What are you talking about? Do you know me?
- I do.
- You can't trick me.
Do you not want to know who I am?
And why I am so fearless as I stand here before you?
But most importantly,
do you not want to know who you are?
Go and hold the woman's hand.
I'm talking about the owner of the restaurant you just left.
People who committed serious crimes are born again as grim reapers.
She will show you what you did.
And also...
what part I played in it.
I never erased your memory.
You chose to have your memory erased and yet,
you think it's the almighty's plan or mistake?
What are you thinking about?
Something I shouldn't think about.
Why are you doing what you know you shouldn't?
If I don't do it today, I might do it tomorrow.
Don't do that. It's a bad time.
We got a warning from the top because of the Janghang-dong case.
What did they say?
"Remember that you are sinners."
It's so confusing and worrying.
Here are this month's name cards.
Was I given an answer...
or a question?
I gave you name cards.
I'm home.
He has three hours.
Cause of death is cardiac arrest.
You should say goodbye.
I said all I wanted to during our lifetime.
I don't want to see him...
feel sorry for me or be apologetic.
See him off for me.
I will.
Tell him to be born again.
In his next life,
tell him not to serve any man and to be free.
Tell him I thank him.
That I was very grateful.
What is going on?
Prepare a black outfit. You'll hear of Chairman Yu's death.
Check on him every now and then.
You're so mean, you don't know how I feel
This is unbearable. My back hurts.
Just wait until I'm CEO.
I'll come here every day, drag everyone out to dinner,
and check their work.
I'll compliment your worst outfit and make you wear it forever.
- Deok Hwa.
- What?
Did Grandpa tell you to watch me from up close?
You need to come with me. Right now.
I don't get off work for hours.
I brought your suit. Change in the car.
What suit?
The man whose every second on this earth was good...
Here he rests.
Yu Shin Woo.
(The man whose every second on this earth was good.)
(Here he rests. Yu Shin Woo.)
So this is what it's like...
to be immortal.
Chairman Yu must keep turning back to look.
He'd be worried about you.
That's why...
the ones left behind...
should live even harder.
We might cry from time to time,
but we should smile a lot...
and cheer up.
You're...
obligated to do that in return for the love you received.
Would you like...
something to warm you up?
I'll have something...
with Deok Hwa when he's back.
What do I do now?
I didn't get to treat him well.
How can he leave me...
making me feeling guilty like this?
How can I keep living while feeling sorry to him?
What do I do now?
How will I live alone?
You're not alone.
Uncle.
You have me.
You and I will be together,
so don't worry.
Uncle...
You should get up and eat something.
Come on, these apples look like rabbits.
Do you want me to make you gold?
Do you want me to walk through walls?
Deok Hwa, you can have my camera.
I know you wanted it.
Forget it. My grandpa got it for you.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you in advance.
I should have given you time to get yourself together.
I regret it.
However, there's order in this world.
I know.
We've been tending a goblin for generations.
Thank you, everyone.
I have to go do something.
I thought he might be bothered by this.
You know what he's like.
I do.
Mr. Kim has been appointed as the CEO.
Grandpa had everything prepared before he left.
I'm glad.
I'm not ready yet.
Right.
I'll start learning the work from the ground up.
I bet that's what he would have wanted.
- Okay.
- I'll also...
start learning go.
Then I'll become your brother, your father,
then your grandfather.
Just like my grandfather.
All right.
(Yu Deok Hwa)
(Kim Do Young)
If someone...
by the last name Kim and first name Shin comes to you...
and says that he is here to retrieve his belongings,
give it to him.
All I've left behind belongs to him.
He will come to you through rain...
and leave as a blue flame.
Then you will know it's him.
He left, right?
Who are... Do you know me?
I do. A kid who is nothing but nice.
That's why you light up this world.
Remember, your good-nature is what will bring you luck.
Sure.
I'm not a kid, though.
Do you want to go for a drink?
You can go drinking with someone beautiful.
You are beautiful.
You should drink with a human.
Bye.
What was that?
Why are you making so much?
Deok Hwa is coming.
Pass me the pepper.
I'm jealous of Deok Hwa. He has an uncle.
Don't mind me.
I'm jealous of everyone and I feel empty these days.
Just tell me right out.
I know you want an uncle like me.
A super handsome uncle.
What is it?
When did you say you became a grim reaper?
Over 300 years ago. Why?
Is something on my face?
It's just that for a second,
I saw a face I didn't see in you before.
Who? What kind of face?
A face I shouldn't see.
Hey. Sit, help, or go to your room.
Why are you prowling?
I'm being proud of you for becoming useful.
An heir of a conglomerate...
should naturally think that work outside of office hours as training.
What is it?
(Kim Woo Sik)
Today is first day of school. I'm a university student.
There is a freshmen party, so I'm wearing a dress.
No.
I'll get going.
Deok Hwa will drive you.
I have an appointment today.
If something happens...
I know.
Perfect, right?
You forgot something.
I know what it is.
I'm not sure why you would close your eyes.
You're perfect now.
Is this the one from Canada?
I'm a bit touched.
By the way, what does this mean?
It's French for "Fate ordained by the sky".
The absolute destiny far beyond the realm of humanity...
That's a word that I like. "Fate".
How did you know?
No blind dates. No romance. No Tae Hee.
No man is allowed within 30m radius of that necklace.
That's what I make of your fate.
Gosh, that's what I decided to go to college for.
There's no other way. That is the deity's will.
You're running late. Go on.
I'm off.
(Eun Tak)
I got to school safely and cheerfully.
I'm sending you this so you won't feel so down.
Good luck on your appointment.
She's wearing the necklace...
and took the picture well so there aren't any men in it.
Good girl.
(Interview for experienced applicants of Chunwoo Group)
I shall follow your order.
Please forgive me.
I will follow you soon.
We must have missed each other...
since I'm still alive.
You must have been very lonely.
Please forgive me.
Mr. Kim Woo Sik, Mr. Choi Sang Gil,
and Ms. Lee Ji Yeon, please come in.
Okay.
I passed?
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Honey.
I passed.
Dad!
Come here.
Should we order jjajangmyeon?
This is the residence the company offers.
For me?
Yes. You did well on the interview.
This is the car the company offers.
For me?
Yes. You did very well on the interview.
Gosh.
This is the name of your son who will be born on the first of May.
He will bring light to this world generation after generation.
My son will?
Yes.
By the way, who are you?
I should have introduced myself sooner.
I'm Kim Do Young, the CEO of Chunwoo Group.
You're the CEO?
I'm sorry I didn't recognize you.
But... I mean...
Why are you giving me more than I deserve?
You saved the country in your previous life.
I did?
Yes.
Hello?
Where are you right now?
Why are you still not home? Do you know how dangerous it is outside?
It's 5pm right now.
The sun is still high up.
You should go easy on the nagging.
What did you say? Where are you right now?
I've been asking since a while ago.
Me?
You'll be surprised if I tell you.
I'm here in this confined space.
Are you kidding me?
Over there.
- One, two, three.
- Look pretty.
It's a good picture.
You managed to put on a smile amid the hustle and bustle.
When do we get out of here?
I don't know. Five minutes later?
Why then?
It might get romantic in the meanwhile...
in this small and confined room.
That won't happen.
I'm pretty sure it will.
Like this.
It's rounded up to 5 dollars and 21 cents.
See? Wasn't that romantic?
Why would you pay me back in a small and confined room?
You should pay my boss back for the sweet potatoes with that money.
Did she tell you to urge me?
You miss your sister, but my boss is living in the present.
It's awkward for you to go see her, but you do miss her. Am I right?
You could go there to pay her back.
I'm making you an excuse to go see her.
I'm going to work. Do you want to come with me?
I do miss her, but she scares me.
I'll go some other time.
This is amazing. You two are realistic siblings.
Let's go out now.
What? Already?
Why?
It's really cold out.
How's school?
Do you like it?
By the way, Tae Hee is...
That son of a...
Was I asking about him? I was asking about school.
I mean...
Tae Hee is going to the US. Major League Baseball.
I read that goblins recognize true talent.
I was going to say that's really cool.
I don't want to brag,
but I've been able to recognize true talent for a long time.
Hwang Hui was the most significant one.
Maeng Sa Sung was something, too.
Sure.
A grown-up is talking here.
I'm afraid I'm a busy person.
I'm late for work.
Look where we are. What are you rambling on about?
I'm off to work.
Okay. Call me if anything.
This is awkward in this small and confined space.
Wait, those two mean the same thing.
I want to come here every day.
Wind bomb.
Come over here.
It's late. Go straight home.
Your grandma is waiting.
We meet again.
Back there, I did not properly introduce myself.
I am Park Joong Won.
You look like you know who I am already.
I do not.
Kim Shin.
Did he not tell you...
that he is the one who killed me?
The punishment that was given him...
grows in weight like life.
The price of my life is in there as well.
What do you want?
Nothing.
I just want to tell you an interesting story.
Since you know me, you must know Yeo as well.
The sword in Kim Shin's chest...
was put there by Wang Yeo.
The start and end of this tragic fate...
was Wang Yeo.
Do you know with whom Yeo now lives?
How could I know?
Yeo is living...
with Kim Shin right now.
That's absurd.
That is correct.
The nameless grim reaper.
He is Wang Yeo.
What do you think will happen...
if the two of them recognize each other?
That is correct.
The nameless grim reaper.
He is Wang Yeo.
What do you think will happen...
if the two of them recognize each other?
Whether or not Kim Shin kills me...
all depends on you now,
as his death is in your hands.
Come to think of it, you control death.
You're wrong.
The grim reaper that we know has a name.
Kim Woo Bin.
Did you ask what it is that I want?
I...
want their demise.
Get out of the way. One for the couple.
No way. I sat down here first.
Yeo is living...
with Kim Shin right now.
This is insane.
Missing Soul.
What? Darn it.
Thanks.
I'm sorry for startling you.
Why are you here? Did you come on purpose?
I felt trapped.
I had no one else to talk to.
What is it?
Is it about my boss?
This and that.
They say if you commit a great sin in your prior life,
you become a grim per.
What sin?
I don't know, either.
But I think...
I may have been in Shin and...
his sister's history.
There are three people who committed great sins in history around then.
Kim Shin, who cut off the heads of the enemies.
Wang Yeo, who ordered the death of Kim Shin...
and his sister.
And the one who led...
Kim Shin and his sister to their grave...
Park Joong Won.
Kim Shin is still alive.
and Kim Sun was reincarnated as Sunny.
That means I am Wang Yeo...
or Park Joong Won.
That's is all I've thought about.
The nameless grim reaper.
He is Wang Yeo.
But...
regardless of which one I am,
I am Shin's enemy, aren't I?
Regardless of which one I am,
Sunny and I...
cannot be, right?
Oh my gosh. I almost hit you.
I'm sorry. Did I startle you?
Yes, a little.
Sorry, but we're closed.
You're right. Okay then.
See you later.
Okay. Come back another time.
No. Never.
Do not serve her any medicine.
Your Majesty reigns over his people,
and it's said Your Majesty is controlled by a divinity.
Apparently, this divinity refers to Kim Shin.
(Kim Woo Bin)
Hello?
Let's meet.
You wanted to break up.
I'm in front of your home.
Wait right there. Is he insane?
How could you just show up like this?
I was home, so I have no makeup on.
I came to get my ring back.
We still have that excuse left.
Why do you look like that?
Didn't you come because you missed me?
I did.
- But?
- But...
I am afraid I may be...
a certain somebody.
I take a step back.
What are you doing?
Everything about me is wrong.
I sincerely hope that this choice...
is the right one.
- Don't do this.
- As I am not alive,
I have no name.
You...
asked after me.
Thank you for that.
I said stop.
The kiss of a grim reaper...
brings back memories of your previous life.
I fear what I was...
in your previous life.
But I wish you are left only with good memories.
I hope that...
a part of them are memories...
of your older brother.
And...
I hope that he is...
Kim Shin.
Your brother has returned in triumph again.
Between the two of us,
whom do you wish to be alive?
- Your Majesty.
- Answer me.
Or have you already made your decision?
Of course, whether I live or your brother lives,
you have nothing to lose.
You're a fool, Your Majesty.
Do you want to die?
Why are you dressed like that?
You are already mourning.
Bring the queen's jewellery box.
Why aren't you wearing anything?
I did not give you these to keep in a box!
I can't tell anymore.
I don't know if my enemies are the barbarians or your brother.
Park Joong Won is your enemy.
Your brother, the man that the barbarians could not kill...
I will kill him today.
Your Majesty.
Your brother's crime...
will be treason.
Wear this ring and greet him...
as my queen.
Whose side are you on?
Even once, were you ever on my side?
Even once,
did you ever care for me?
For one second, did you ever...
love me?
Do not side with him.
That is...
the only way you can preserve your life.
You have to make a choice.
Will you live as my woman...
or will you die...
as the traitor's sister?
The woman who loves you...
is the traitor's sister.
What was that?
What did I see?
That was...
your past life.
Was...
Kim Shin...
in your past life?
Was I...
a part...
of your past life?
Can you...
look into my eyes?
Leave only the shining, happy memories...
and forget...
all the sad and hard moments.
Whether they were in your past life or present...
And...
forget about me.
I hope that...
you at least have a happy ending.
You, over there.
Why are you staring into my shop again?
What is it today?
An accessory? A biscuit? Socks?
I'm not here for that.
I owe you for the sweet potatoes.
Let's say that was my treat.
So, dear brother.
Did the king really say...
I was ugly?
Even if you're on the battlefield,
how can a brother not send his sister a reply?
Are you...
Are you really...
I'm sorry it took me this long to recognize you.
I promised to become happy,
but I couldn't keep it.
I'm sorry.
Persimmon, flowery shoes, and silk.
Thank you.
You must come see me more often from now on.
Can you help me if you're not too busy?
Is something wrong?
Just...
Something is bothering me.
Did you fight with my uncle again?
No.
Even before that.
Ever since that day, it's been happening.
When?
What is it? Are you okay?
That day?
It couldn't be because of him.
We were at a temple then.
- A temple?
- Yes.
He sent up a lantern.
He does it once a year.
He does it in remembrance of the people he owes.
They had two syllable names.
Kim Sun...
and Wang something.
It was in Chinese characters.
What happens if I do this?
A pursued stone.
Hey.
Look at that.
She's acting like she can't see me.
Hey, you little punk!
She's not acting.
She really can't see me.
Me too.
Pardon?
I'm excited to pick you up, too.
I'm so happy you came to pick me up at school.
Forget it.
I was just thinking about something.
Did something good happen?
You look like it.
That took you a while to ask.
My sister, Sun...
finally remembered me.
Really? Really?
That's great news.
How?
I didn't ask her.
You're right.
How did she remember her previous life?
What's wrong?
Are you saying...
Can you...
pull the car over for a minute?
Please listen to me...
without getting upset.
I've thought about it a lot.
What is it?
I believe that you are someone much bigger...
than what I know.
What are you talking about?
I...
met someone deceased,
and I think...
it's Park Joong Won.
How...
do you know Park Joong Won?
I'm sorry,
but overheard what you said...
to the Grim Reaper.
At first, I thought he was just an evil ghost.
However, I can't tell what he's after.
I feel like strange things happening around me are related to him.
Maybe Sunny remembering you...
might be because of him.
I'm glad you told me. Thank you.
I'll drive you home. Stay there and don't go out.
A goblin's house is the safest place.
Okay.
I avoided you for 900 years. I can't believe I ran into you.
How futile.
Do not worry.
I will get rid of you right away.
However,
you must tell me why you suddenly showed up...
after hiding for the last 900 years.
Despite all those years,
you have failed to find insight since you are a mere warrior.
You had your enemy trudge along with you. How pathetic.
I will be glad to tell you.
That tongue of yours is still senile after 900 years.
I will pull out your tongue first.
Then I will cut your body into pieces.
I will do it right now.
You, I or the 900 years.
You will not be able to hurt me with that sword of yours.
Did living as a goblin...
make you think that you actually became the almighty?
I will kill you no matter what, so do not worry.
The longing within makes one die of an unworthy death.
During the 20 years you spent rotting,
Yeo grew powerful...
beyond recognition.
If you speak of that name one more time...
Do you know the identity of the grim reaper by your side?
He's the man who gave you that sword...
and the one who pierced your heart with it.
That man is...
Wang Yeo.
Ludicrous.
Your foolish sister...
fell for him again in this life.
I pity you.
You will never have your revenge.
I heard you cried.
Why? Even I don't cry.
Who is the woman in the painting by the way?
I don't remember. I just feel.
I was just extremely sad.
My heart felt like it was breaking.
A super handsome uncle.
Have you seen a ring like this?
Is the grim reaper in your previous life?
- Have you seen him?
- Excuse me.
What do you think you're doing in my restaurant?
Do you think I'm really Kim Sun because I remember my past life?
Is that man...
really Yeo?
- I have to go home.
- I asked you a question.
Even in this life,
you are...
protecting that fool.
Was I?
Was I really Wang Yeo?
The feelings without memories...
Is that...
the punishment I gave myself...
so I won't forget who I was?
As expected,
it looks like I'm the worst memory.
To you...
and to Kim Shin, both.
You can hear me, can't you?
I hear yours, too.
I hear it very clearly.
Warrior Kim Shin...
greets you, Your Majesty.
(Goblin)
This royal garment...
is without an owner.
Maybe this is...
what you're looking for.
If so,
take it.
It is my royal decree.