When you face a moment at the
brink of life and death...
be sure to pray earnestly
in case a god with a tender
heart is listening to you.
B* stard! Aren't you
going to drive properly!
Hyung, there.
What is this?
- Episode 3 -
Who are those bastards?
Are they Men in Black? (Referring to the movie, Men
In Black, secret organization that monitors ETs)
What is this?
H-Hey, h-hurry and g-go.
Hurry and step on it!
Step on it!
♪ When I’m alone I dream on
the horizon and words fail ♪
♪ Time to say goodbye ♪
♪ to countries I never ♪
♪ saw and shared with you ♪
♪ Now, yes, I shall experience them ♪
♪ I’ll go with you ♪
♪ on ships across seas ♪
♪ which, I know ♪
Mom...
You should get out.
Get your things, too.
Did you get hurt? Where?
Hurt... that is...
What?
"Did you get hurt?" How can you ask that?
When you sliced the car like that?
Wait here for a while.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to kill them?
You're not going to kill them, right?
- No.
- You always say, "No."
You also came with the Grim Reaper. Do
you think that man came to save me?
That sounds more natural.
Don't worry. I won't kill them.
It's just to show how angry I am,
so that they would think
that dying would be better.
Aigoo!
Save us!
Save us! Please save us!
Save us please!
For two days, this road
will disappear on the map.
It means that you won't have any luck
to be found by someone for two days.
It might hurt like you're dying but you won't die.
Fortunately, the police will discover you after two days.
You will pay for your crime at the police station. You
should be thankful that you didn't have to pay me.
At times, a god is hiding
among those you bully.
Say your thanks to that child.
You two had a fight. That's all.
You didn't see anything.
Ah. You won't be able to reconcile forever.
A car...
You didn't bring one?
We don't usually go around in cars.
Ah.
Perhaps...
I'm asking, just in case. Am I dead?
Is this road the way to the afterlife?
This is just a countryside road.
We just saved you earlier.
Then are you going to kill me now?
Am I captured? Alive?
I'm asking out of curiosity. When are we
going to hear, "Thank you for saving me"?
Calm down. We are with a 19-year-old
who isn't done getting mad.
I never knew the two of
you were this close.
For someone who asked to be saved, what should
I do when you bring along the Grim Reaper?
I'm asking out of curiosity. When are we
going to hear, "Thank you for saving me"?
Keep quiet!
Why are you shouting?
Why does this road not
have a single car pass by?
Someone made it so that no car
would pass this road for two days.
I said keep quiet!
Why haven't you left yet?
You said you were leaving.
Soon.
Ah. Don't mind me. I didn't ask
because I was really curious.
I know.
But how did you come? I wasn't able
to blow out the lighter earlier.
I'm not sure. I think I just heard you.
"Save me" or something like that.
I just thought to myself though.
Maybe you thought aloud.
You could have chosen not to come.
There was no reason not to come.
I'm sorry then. You came to save someone who
is not even your bride in your busy schedule.
I did some research.
You were right when you said
I was living on a bonus.
I heard you saved me and
my mom 19 years ago.
So I'm fine being a bonus now.
It was thanks to being born
that I was able to meet my mom,
so I've decided to not dislike you.
- It looks like you dislike me.
- No, I don't.
If I met you again by any chance,
I really wanted to tell you that.
I'm sure you wished not to meet me.
- I think you dislike me, for sure.
- No, I don't.
From now on, I won't
summon you or think of you
and I won't do anything. So you
should be rest assured and leave.
I hope your household stays in peace
and I hope you meet a good person.
A pretty someone who
discovers your sincere self.
Ah, not the face but the heart.
You said you don't look at faces.
It's all cooked so you should eat.
I will be going then.
Wait.
I didn't eat but I'm paying?
It was your idea to eat.
I also didn't eat.
And... I don't have money.
Then I'll pay. You give your time.
Eat before you go.
Right now... are you feeding me dinner?
Yeah.
There's no way those men fed
you before abducting you.
I don't want to. I don't
want to eat with you.
If you want to, then pack it for me. I will
thankfully accept the spicy rice cakes.
You do dislike me.
Here, Uncle, listen carefully.
Eun Tak lost her parents when she was young.
She was abused by her aunt and her cousins.
Shabashaba... How much did she cry?
(Kid's Korean Cinderella song)
Who made her cry? Her
aunt and those siblings.
There's no need to search deeply. The
whole neighborhood knows about it.
Eun Tak's mom left an insurance
payout of $1.5 million.
Since they won't be able to control the money once she
becomes a legal adult, the aunt must be really abusing her.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm in the middle of being shocked
about how useful you are.
A chaebol has to
use money and power to look
into a person's background...
- Where did you get the pictures from?
- I took them while on stakeout.
But I didn't see Eun Tak. She must be busy.
What is that?
Me. It came out nicely.
By the way, Uncle, why did you
ask me to look into this?
To punish them.
How?
Uncle, are you feeling okay?
Is this punishment? It's gold.
How could you give gold as punishment?
- What about me?
- You worked hard.
Why? What about me?
Why can't I receive that?
Didn't I commit a lot of sins?
Aren't I deserving of a huge punishment?
Those bastards. Did they catch her or not?
Why aren't they calling me?
Keep quiet, you punks! Your
mother is worried sick here!
Laughing here?
That money is about to go into
the bellies of those thugs.
You borrowed it yourself anyway.
Oh, right. I should have
starved you to death.
It's no different now, either.
Right. I was the crazy bitch.
What was I thinking to have
two kids a year apart...
- What is that?
- It's gold, you bitch!
Wow, Ji Eun Tak. She changed
all that money into gold.
There was a reason why she
insisted there was no bank book.
This is why there's no bank book.
As soon as the sun rises, let's go to the
pawnshop. Let's split it equally. Equally.
Just you try to pull some tricks.
This bastard... I'm your mom!
Give it to me.
Let go! Let go!
Mom! Wake up! That bitch
Kyeong Mi ran with the gold!
That crazy bitch!
Why is the line busy the whole time?
I know. The line is busy now.
With which bastard is she talking to?
She's talking to this bastard! Hang up!
Hurry! Hurry and grab a taxi!
Taxi! Taxi!
- I'm in a hurry.
- Get out of the way. Move!
Mister, go!
Yes, Grandfather, Uncle is eating...
He has a spoonful and I even
put some kimchi on for him.
Seollongtang (beef bone soup).
Yes, yes.
But, Grandfather, about the card... Hello?
Hello?
Honestly, if you could just say
a word then this problem...
Uncle, are you listening?
What are you watching? What?
Television.
He's a pitiful person. I should not be getting mad
at such a pitiful person, a 3rd generation chaebol.
He was exactly at that age.
Who was?
The king I protected.
He was 17 years old.
You protected a king? Awesome!
Uncle, were you a Nae-si, by chance? (Nae-si
means eunuch - sounds like four-o-clock)
No, I was an Oh-si.
(between 11 to 1)
He's a pitiful person, Deok Hwa.
He needs your help now.
The most splendid hour of the day.
I was blinded
and ceaselessly blamed someone.
Was it the king or god?
Or myself?
I forgot that.
Him?
What?
My rage of 1,000 years. The reincarnation
of the king that killed me.
Look closely.
Did he get reincarnated?
I don't know. If he's reincarnated,
he'll be just that age.
Eunuch. Eunuch. Your Highness. Eunuch.
Forget him. The hatred and sense of
revenge is making you miserable...
Then are you happy because
you can't remember?
I can't know by just looking.
I need to touch him to know.
- What is?
- How am I supposed to utilize you?
What can you find out with touching?
Then again, why do you think he
would be reincarnated as a man?
- Is it her?
- I can't know with just watching. I need to touch to know.
What happens if you touch? What?
It's her! Say that it's her.
I'm prepared to forgive.
- I thought it was a rage of 1,000 years.
- He must have had his reasons.
As you know a rage is everywhere
then nowhere... Where are you going?
What happens if you touch? Why are
you only talking among yourselves?
Aigoo, aigoo.
Oppa!
Greetings, Senior. I'm Grim
Reaper Kim of '22 class.
Reaper Kim of '23 class.
You're working hard. Sit down.
Yes, we will work hard.
Aigoo, so new.
There was a time we were like that, too.
Class of '22, Reaper Kim.
- Rest.
- Yes, we will work hard.
You're here. By the way, Seniors,
why aren't you checking the company email?
You know the miscellaneous omitted persons?
It's been approved and
they've made a task force.
I hope you submit the list
before the end of the year.
I don't have any. You've got two, right?
Who says? Who said I have two?
Everyone says you have two.
- I'll submit it soon.
- I'd appreciate that.
It's time for me to go now.
I'll see you at the winter workshop.
Aigoo, work hard.
That's her. Her.
Greetings, Seniors. I'm
Reaper Kim of class of '23.
- Ah, yes.
- Nice to meet you all.
Go on.
So pretty.
She should be an angel.
Why is she a grim reaper?
Her class is so excited because of her.
You are the one who's so excited
because of her from our class.
Move out of the way!
Oppa! Oppa!
Are you alright?
Then I will be going now.
Bye. And also,
we have a company dinner
at the end of the month.
There's a penalty if you miss out.
I hope you miss out.
Reaper Kim of class of '22.
Did you call the OR?
We don't have time! Hurry up!
Mr. Choi Young Jae?
I'm sorry, later. The
guardian should wait outside.
Age: 33. Byeongshin Year,
Moosul Month, Gisa Day.
Died at 17:41. Cause: Overwork.
It's you, right?
Am I... dead?
Hey! Choi Young Jae!
Choi Young Jae!
No, Oppa.
Young Jae...
- Oppa!
- Choi Young Jae!
Young Jae...
Oppa!
Thanks to your emergency treatment
this patient is saved.
The vitals are stable.
The patient is alive.
It's a relief.
[Application of Miscellaneous
Omitted Persons]
[Goblin Exhibition]
[Goblin Snack Bar]
[Goblin Toys]
I will marry you. No matter how I think
about it, I think you really are a goblin.
I love you!
I found you!
Close your eyes. You eyes can't meet with
him. That person is the Grim Reaper.
I don't know. Whether he leaves or not.
Was it sold already?
No. Why can't this be refunded?
I already told you earlier, customer. If you don't
have the receipt then we can't give you a refund.
I'm not sure if I bought a
book or a person's memory.
Look. If there's something
like this in a book
then what should I do? Give me a refund.
I already told you. You need
to bring your receipt...
I will buy that.
Are you the owner of this memory?
Yes, yes. It's my memory. I will buy it.
It doesn't have an
evidence that it's yours.
Try to guess which neighborhood
this leaf came from.
But then, even if I tell the
name of the neighboorhood
you wouldn't know.
That's right.
I thought I lost it. Thank you.
I get that. I think you're past
the age to be reading that.
No, just for research.
What about you? Why this book?
Ah. I know a goblin.
- Huh?
- What?
Doesn't everyone know a goblin?
Really?
What do you mean, really, Young Woman?
What do you say when someone
asks for the deposit? "No."
This closet is nice.
"I don't want to."
What if someone asks to buy you snacks?
Get lost.
Pay for the book. $10 dollars.
Until when do I have to sit?
I'm sorry.
But,
this book should be
considered a used book, no?
No, I don't want to.
Get lost.
Uncle!
G- G-Grandfather.
I came to see how he was doing
coming from the dry cleaners.
But then, I see there was a visitor.
Ah. A vi-visitor.
Who are you?
My uncle's house...
for what reason did you come?
I am... that person's friend.
I came to play.
Ah! You came to play at
your friend's place.
I see you're a very close
friend of my Uncle's.
Because Uncle is going overseas
you must have came to say goodbye.
Farewell.
Be careful of your health.
Don't come ever again.
I hope you'll be happy and
until you die over there...
Farewell to you. You and I aren't close.
Hurry and go out from my house.
Don't ever come back.
Uncle, why are you acting this way?
Towards your really really close friend.
Do you think it isn't right?
You leave also. Really really quickly.
Wow. How could he do that?
Isn't he too much?
That's what I'm saying.
Right? How could he kick me out too?
Would a real uncle really do that to me?
- He will be going soon.
- That should be the case.
If not, you will be the one to go.
Somewhere.
That place isn't somewhere good, right?
- Come in.
- No thanks.
- No matter how much you plead...
- Not you.
You go to your own house to get scolded.
1-0.
Me? Get scolded? Why will I be scolded?
Did you perhaps tell Grandpa everything?
Wow! So petty!
How much did you tell him? I should
know so that I would match things up.
Did you match with me when you
put the house up for rent?
I can't go. Where would I go?
Even if I die, I will be
a ghost of this house.
Oh yeah.
Good Night 1:1.
Blood... right?
Hey! Grim Reaper! Aren't you
going to clean this up?
Hey! I'm sorry! Clean this up.
Yes?
You,
do you sleep here?
I'm sorry. I was going to tell you
but I keep missing the timing.
I'm really sorry.
But how did you know?
I don't brush my teeth in the store.
I have another proof.
Boss, honestly
I sleep in the store.
Boss, can I inconvenience you a bit?
Boss, I'm sleeping in the shop for now.
As that's my situation for now.
I stayed here well.
I got kicked out of the house.
Please save me.
- I'm sorry.
- Is it because of your aunt?
That's also the reason.
I ran out of places to go.
Aren't you going to ask more?
What's the use of asking? It's
not like it will get solved.
I'm just doing what I can help solve it.
Here, your pay for one week.
I will give you your pay weekly. Why?
If I give it to you monthly,
you might not get it.
Even if you do sleep here,
go to the sauna and wash up
and order out to eat.
Thank you.
If you're that thankful after receiving what
you should get, people will belittle you.
Not for the money
but I am thankful for your coolness.
That money is cool, part-timer.
Go and wash up. Grill one
squid before you go.
Are you going to drink?
No, just the squid. I can't
even put my lips near alcohol.
- Because I get drunk if I drink too much.
- What?
No! No! Cancel that!
You must have been reading a book.
I'm someone who is near a book and has
deep taste in music and paintings.
I'm sorry for disturbing your reading.
I know. Why disturb me? You
said you won't be calling me.
I didn't. It was a mistake.
While grilling the squid, the leg
caught on fire and I blew it.
Was it tasty?
Why are you here? Haven't you left yet?
I was packing my things. I was
packing my books. A lot of books.
Well then, since I need to finish packing.
- Wait...
- You always talk to me when I'm about to go.
It's you who's always leaving
when I'm about to say something.
- I have something I'm curious about.
- I'm not giving you $5,000 (oh baek).
That startled me. I heard it as
you won't confess (go beak).
It's because you always say
things that are out of place.
From where did it start to be my fault?
From there. From where I
should see something.
That's why, what should I see?
In order to have effective value to you.
Are you going to say you
see it if I tell you?
No. Even if I see it I'm
going to say I don't.
If I see that, what if you
start treating me better?
What if you give me $5,000, buy me
meat or ask me if I want anything?
Then it would be very tiring for me.
You're not that good.
It's my first time hearing that.
Really! Really! It's my first time hearing that. Where
are you looking at when an adult is talking to you?
Don't answer if you don't want to.
That... don't you see anything unique?
Something that looks painful.
Ah that...
- You see?
- I thought it was something great.
Goodbye. I'm busy so I will get going.
Hey, do you want to eat meat? Do you
have something you want to have?
- $5,000.
- You said you were busy. Hurry up and go.
Then meat. This way.
It's the last meat. Do you see it?
Yes. It looks really tasty.
I ate well.
I'm asking if you see it?
You don't see it, right?
Are you getting mad at me right now?
- Did you hear it that way?
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
I was going to ask about the fresh juice
but the tone of my voice went up, right?
Fresh fruit juice?
What do want to drink? You
can order an expensive one.
I'm full though. This one, large size.
Aren't you full?
Me too, the same one.
I will help you with the bill.
She's asking about the bill.
I won't pay for it.
What's with you? I though you
said you don't like fruit.
What's with you? Is there
anyone you will kill in here?
I'm a regular here.
Perhaps, is it me? The one
that will die here today?
Perhaps... you lured me with beef
and juice. I got caught with
the two of you in it together?
It's a misunderstanding. Honestly,
I am on the same side as you.
You see the sword. You see the sword.
You will take that sword.
What are you doing?
What do you mean? Why are
you on the same side as me?
What is she? Why isn't she getting it?
She's someone who overcomes
everything you expect.
That means the files would be no joke.
Then, spend a good time. I
have prior appointments.
He really must have came just to
drink juice. That's something new.
But then, why did he say he
was on the same side as me?
It's the matters with the gods.
You don't need to know.
But then, isn't that ahjussi
uselessly handsome?
One needs to be handsome for people to
follow well, do they choose it that way?
Are all grim reapers handsome?
Is that handsome?
Yes! That is handsome.
Then what about me?
Ahjussi... you just look.
Don't drink this. You are full.
Oh, that ahjussi is also handsome.
The water must be nice here.
I will be there soon. See you soon.
I love you.
Honey. I miss you so I
will hurry and go there.
What are you doing?
Something anyone would do.
Are you alright?
Magic.
Oh my. I'm sorry.
I'll untie it.
Yes?
Ahh!
I'm so sorry.
- No.
- It's untangled.
Are you alright?
Yes. Today is a really strange day.
As if I was caught in a magic.
That's why I'm asking,
do you have a boyfriend?
No. My family's very strict.
So they were strict.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I've been single since birth,
because I was waiting for you.
Kiss. Kiss.
Kiss!
Are you Cupid?
That was that, right?
Every 100 years, 1 or 2 people are born
with the same face from the previous life.
For that, I know the man's previous life.
That woman was not to lose that man.
Wow. What is the past life?
Is that the man who saved a country
that I have only heard about?
He was worse than a landlord that
extorted his tenant farmers.
But why did you help? Are you
also granting bad guy's wishes?
Where do you find that? You
make nice people lose hope.
I'm not their guardian god, but rather the guardian
god of the man and woman those two just lost.
I love you.
I love you too.
I miss you so I will hurry over.
Don't hurry, just slow down or
else you'll get hurt. Okay?
Wow!
The man was a liar and a coward.
And the woman was ungrateful.
Now, those two will be each other's hell.
Wow. That's pretty cool.
I make those magic-like moments
for humans once in a while.
But then, from earlier, why are you
talking like in historical dramas?
Just when I thought I figured you out.
Of course. Is my life like this
because I committed a
huge sin in my past life?
Is the punishment being
born as the goblin's bride?
I don't know what you were in your past life. In the present life, it's
still early to tell at 19 years old. And you are not the goblin's bride.
You're not falling for it.
My life's been full of lots of misery
and hardships, but I like my life too.
I received a lot of love from my mom.
I now have an umbrella.
And it's nice to have met you.
It was nice. It's in past tense.
You also have grudges. You haven't
answered whether you see it or not.
Do you see it or not?
My mom said this. A person needs to recognize where he's supposed to lay
down before stretching out his legs and know when it's time to leave.
You understand what I mean, right?
I don't.
It means we're only until here.
I will be going this way. Goodbye.
♪ Through the endless daydream
I saw you on the way back ♪
♪ There I walk with you in my arms ♪
♪ Through the blurry darkness
was veiling on the twilight ♪
♪ We've been far away from my fears ♪
♪ Somewhere I will see you
with the days like a blossom ♪
♪ Blooming all around you so bright ♪
That's pretty cool.
Wow. That's pretty cool.
Uncle, you looked like a painting just now.
What about the uncle down the hall?
- Not yet.
- Well, he must be working overtime.
Uncle. You see, I might become a grim
reaper like the uncle down the hall.
If you open the last room in hallway
of life, there is death, isn't it?
And the one to greet you is
the uncle down the hall.
Wake up. There's no chance with you.
I don't like to say this but in order to become
a grim reaper you need to commit a big sin...
Big sin? What?
How did you know?
Heol! Daebak! (Awesome)
Is he really a murderer?
Wow! You can never know
with a person's face.
Not that. How did you
know he is a grim reaper?
Uncle, don't you feel like
your question is a bit late?
That time, when you were depressed and you were creating clouds and whatnot
in the living room. When the uncle down the hall came in, I was so nervous.
But then that uncle didn't
change his expression.
- What's wrong with him?
- And with me in there you just said yourselves about grim reaper and stuff.
Grim Reaper who's saying all sorts
of things in front of the kid.
I hope you don't find the grim
reaper's ability laughable.
Was that all? His face is all white and
such red lips and wears all black clothes.
I thought it was some celebrity.
Then I will be going then.
You. How did you know I was a grim reaper?
If you do this, then how could I not know?
A person who was there is now here!
Please be careful! Both of
you are so uncontrollable.
I got caught because of you.
Goblin who talks about others.
Look at how you look, if it's because of me. Grim
Reaper who might be a murderer in his past life!
You, it's not like you haven't killed
a single ant and not punished!
Tsk.
He must be so hurt. What should we do?
Don't you see that I'm not
all that inclined either?
A big sin?
Unfilial, disloyal, immodest,
unrestricted, unvirtuous.
Let's not go there. It won't be that.
Yeah. It's not.
Why? Why are you here?
A responsible action. The effort of the
better person, most would call it apology.
I was too much earlier. I'm sorry.
Among these, what is not?
- Unfilial?
- Get out.
I was also too much just now.
I thought you would laugh.
Get out.
What's so important about the past life?
It's not important to me what you did
or what you were in the past life.
- Really?
- Yeah. Because whatever you were, it's unchanging how I don't like you.
I can't laugh.
Even when they first met, I thought Uncle
would kick out the uncle down the hall.
But on the contrary they are
cozily getting along well.
One person is miserable from
forgetting the past life
and one person is miserable for
not forgetting the past life.
Among those two existence they
are relying on each other.
We are just
people who are shortly
passing in their long life.
I see.
But you already knew too?
Jeez, those uncles.
I worry they might get detected outside.
You just worry about yourself.
Stretch arms out. And back.
No way I am your real grandson.
You would never treat your
real grandson like this.
I'm going to take revenge.
As you already know, this is the
building I got for my 9th birthday.
I do know. What did you get
for your 8th birthday?
I received dislike. But
that was all in the past.
- And now as I grew to be an adult...
- You are still being disliked, I'm sure you know.
Since you use the card a
lot without consideration.
So you stopped it.
So I'm telling you this. I'm trying to
find out how to cash out on this building.
So start with vacating this place.
Make it costless and tidy.
First, start with that
chicken shop that's folded.
There's something you need
to know first. First,
that chicken shop has a sign that says
"closed" which means it's closed, not folded.
Second, we didn't come together. I tailed
you, by the order of the chairman, right?
What kind of a tailing is so open...
well I thought we came together.
Let's do this then. Soon, a phone call will come
to the secretary's office. A woman will ask this.
If I work there. Then you can just
tell her I do work there. That's it.
But you don't.
Secretary Kim is seriously...
working so upright.
My grandpa must feel so sturdy.
I need to get a new card.
Please? Just once?
Where are you going?
- Supermarket.
- Supermarket?
Your repertoire is getting
more and more insincere.
You don't see that I'm
carrying a shopping tote?
I didn't know it was a shopping tote.
How can you actually follow me?
You don't trust me?
Have you made yourself trustworthy?
You were going to go to her but since I was going
to follow you, you came to the supermarket.
Last time at the cafe too. You brought
her there but you got caught by me.
I'm not going to take her away.
I'm totally rooting for her now.
Why are you rooting for her?
I'm really on the same team as her. They say
the bride will die if she pulls the sword.
Going forever is better
than going abroad, right?
She can't see the sword right this moment, but I want
to believe in the miracle that one day she might.
I'm wagered my life on that day.
There are lots of people watching here.
Alright. Just promise me one thing.
What, suddenly? What promise?
That you won't touch that kid if I leave.
Really? You're really leaving?
However,
the moment you try to take her away, I
will come straight back to that house.
So leave her be.
When are you leaving?
The day after tomorrow. Happy?
You weren't detected?
How can you come to the house? If
my aunt finds out, we're all dead.
My aunt's family is asleep?
I don't know.
You scared me.
But what brings you to my house?
To see me?
Should I?
What did you say?
I guess I thought of you. Briefly.
So I guess I came to see you.
Why?
I'm not a bride and I'm not pretty.
You keep having to save my life
and I'm just a pest to you.
Why would you come see me?
I guess I wanted to see this.
Now that I saw it, I'll leave. Your aunt's family
disappeared. The house is vacant, so you can go in.
My aunt's family's disappeared?
Really? When?
But how come you came if you didn't know?
Oh, I left something here,
so I came to get it.
What?
Just something.
You don't need to know.
Alright then.
I'm leaving then.
♪ I'll be by your side ♪
♪ It's a beautiful life ♪
♪ I'll be behind you ♪
♪ Beautiful love ♪
♪ Your memory, you scent ♪
♪ It's getting erased one at a time ♪
♪ It's a beautiful life ♪
♪ When memories I shared
with you all disappear ♪
♪ beautiful life, beautiful thing ♪
♪ In your memory ♪
♪ beautiful love ♪
Excuse me. Oppa in black.
You don't need a hairpin?
I don't prefer hairpins.
Then buy one for your lover.
I don't have a lover.
A lover, you could have then not have.
But this, once you buy it,
you'll always have it.
See it in a mirror once, Oppa.
How much is this?
But I grabbed it first. Wait, but
you're crying because of it?
What?
Want me to concede to you?
I don't want to for free though.
If you give me your phone number.
I don't have that kind of stuff.
You don't have a cellphone?
Are you poor?
I don't really have a need for a cellphone.
Are you sure it's not because you
don't want to give me your number?
Concession, cancelled.
Give me your number. Write it down
and leave it here, with the ring.
First, let's exchange our names. You'll
need to know my name to call me.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Sunny.
Seon Hyo?
If that's better for you, go with that. It's just
a stage name so it doesn't really matter what.
Card?
Cash?
Who's going to pay?
It doesn't matter who pays.
Both will end up paying a
very expensive price anyway.
I...
came late.
I'm fine.
This is also my fate.
So go. Don't stop and go to the king.
You're really going to be like this?
I heard you're not even the goblin bride.
Just come with me then.
Mean girl.
You won't listen to me, right?
Fine, I'm just babbling myself.
I'm going to play foul on
all those people you know.
I'm going to kill that woman first.
The &+### shoe! I'll just &#@!
Scary. Hey, that woman's scary.
Boss. Are you alright?
Be honest.
Is my beauty gone these days? I
totally got the vibe though.
He should totally be calling by
now and then some. Why isn't he?
Oh, the ring? That man?
- First, please calm...
- I can't calm down.
He's the best-looking man I've ever seen.
Do you see how hard I work? How I
drink this everyday for good skin?
But why isn't he calling?
Good-looking men always tend to act
like good-looking men. Just forget him.
How can I forget?!
He's the only man that ever conceded to me.
The ring was pretty though.
It seemed perfect for me.
Do you have a pen?
I don't. Just say it.
That was kind of funny.
Is it science?
The finishing of a phone
number is the lips, right?
Careful.
Hello.
What's all this? Is my family moving?
You're not in touch with your aunt?
Your aunt said she's moving.
A new family is moving in the day after tomorrow
but nothing's ready so I'm suffering here.
She moved?
What about me then?
How can you ask me that? You need to ask your aunt
that. Your aunt took away all the deposit money.
If you have something to take, take it.
Lovers
Ji Eun Tak.
Take out everything that's in
that bag and your pockets.
Quickly.
Teacher, this...
Quiet. I see you have all
sorts of stuff for fire.
Cigarettes? You haven't taken out
cigarettes, do you feel guilty now?
Teacher, I really had a reason for this.
I don't smoke cigarettes.
The kids said they saw you smoking.
Let's get it over quickly shall we?
Hold out your hand.
Quickly.
Both of your hands.
Look at how thorough you are.
This is why smart kids are scary.
Ji Eun Tak, I find it very scary when
kids like you are good at studying.
You act nice and pitiful in front of me but
you'll act completely different behind me.
It's kids like you that cause
trouble once in society.
And then the truly good people will be
the ones who pay for it, okay, Eun Tak?
Thanks.
Why alcohol all of a sudden?
What about you? How's
alcohol ever suddenly?
The more the better when it comes to wine, women and meat.
I've kept up with the principles plenty when I was a general.
- You were a general?
- Ha
You were never able to ask me about
past before, how could you dare?
But you don't know what I was.
What were you?
Your stuff?
See how you bluff. What, you were a king?
Have you packed all your stuff?
Ah, my stuff... well, very simply.
Go safely.
- I'll phone.
- You know I don't have a phone.
That's why I said it.
What are you doing? It's driving me crazy. Are
you really like that after one can of beer?
- I don't know where she is.
- Who?
She's not summoning me. Since she's
not summoning me I can't find her.
I thought I was omniscient and there
was nothing I couldn't do, but...
I can't even find her.
All the stuff I have is all just useless.
That's true. Just eating and playing.
Then, what did you do before that?
I have to find her, always like this.
Just phone her, wouldn't she have a phone?
Yeah, I don't know her number.
Now it's best if I don't know.
He found her.
Mum, are you doing well?
Mum, did you go to heaven?
♪ And I'm here ♪
How is heaven?
Is it better than here?
Mom, I...
♪ I'll be here... ♪
Mom, I'm...
not doing so well.
No-one asks how I'm doing.
Again? I'm sick of this. My raining life.
♪ And I'm here, home, home with you. ♪
♪ With me. ♪
It's like this because I'm melancholy.
What is?
The rain. It'll stop soon.
When you are melancholy it rains?
Yes.
Then when there's a typhoon,
how melancholy are you?
That's not me, but the earth's melancholy.
Have you been well?
The rain's about to stop.
My mood just got better.
I didn't summon you though.
Yes, you didn't summon me.
I've been busy as well, here and there.
I've also had a lot to do.
- Now it's going to be a problem.
- What?
Now every time it rains,
I'll think that you must be melancholy.
When I'm already so busy with all the troubles and
hardships in my life, I'll have to worry about you too.
Aren't you cold? Why are
you here like this?
Because I'm unhappy.
Now it'll just become a cold.
- What?
- My misfortunes.
It finds me just when I'm about to forget
and I contract it when it comes time.
Well, it doesn't mean that they bother me. [The word for
'bother' and 'stab' (as in with a sword) are the same.]
You're not saying that you know something, right? [The word
for 'bother' and 'stab' (as in with a sword) are the same.]
Well, I guess there is something prickling you. [The word for
'prickle' and 'stab' (as in with a sword) are the same.]
Stop saying it. The word that
I hate the most is that.
Well then I chose really well!
Keep going with what you're saying.
I expect you won't be able
to hear it without tears.
I'll try to bear it.
Do you perhaps know that saying? 'To
humans, there are four stages of life.'
'The stage of sewing the seeds, the
stage of watering the sewn seeds,
the stage of harvesting the watered seeds,
and the stage of using the harvested seeds.'
How do you know that? That's what
only the deceased says to the dead.
It's my 19th year as a
goblin bride, you know.
I heard what the ghosts were saying.
So it's really unfair.
The life that I can't get past,
is just work and work again.
I can't get past the second stage.
Mourn.
To a kid?
Then?
There's lots. Tap on the shoulder.
Pat my hair. $500?
Ah gosh, your hands?
My hands, since they do a lot
of work, have to rest a bit.
Well.. since they are kept for when I
receive important things, like a bouquet.
What? Why?
Forget it.
Present.
It's pretty right?
- It is pretty.
- It is right?
♪ This beautiful life,
I'll be by your side. ♪
I'll be behind you. ♪
♪ Beautiful life. ♪
What are you doing?
By touching your head,
I'm saying goodbye, since
I'm leaving tomorrow.
♪ Beautiful life, beautiful thing.
When memories with you all disappear ♪
In your memory ♪
♪ beautiful love, beautiful my love ♪
♪ This beautiful life. ♪
Your stuff?
You asked me yesterday.
It's because I want to keep hearing it.
Since it makes me happy.
- You've got a message.
- No, that's the sound of the doorbell.
It's the first time in 60 years.
Yeah... What?
What did I just say?
We're not going to see someone
appear from time to time are we?
Why are you being scary like that?
- Go and have a look.
- I can't though.
Hey what kind of Grim Reaper who boasts and
is so dignified like that can't do it?
And you?
Oh jeez.
Isn't this the Goblin's residence?
This is my house. Did
you come to see me? Me?
Do you have an appointment with me?
No, I found the wrong place-
Did you even let her know your house?
What are you doing here? How
did you know to come here?
I asked the ghosts where the Goblin's house is.
But why is that Grim Reaper at your house...?
I guess a couple fight is going on,
well whatever, sort it out between you.
Since I'm in the middle of being upset.
Do the two of you live together?
Until today. But why did you come?
There was something I didn't have the chance
to say. You know about asking me what I see.
What happens if can see it though?
Why are you asking? You
can't see it anyway.
Who says I can't see it though?
One, if I see it, does it mean we
have to get married straight away?
Two, if I see it, will you give me $500?
Three, if I see it...
will you not leave?
Please don't go. Just stay here, in Korea.
Can you not?
You... do you really see it?
- If I see it?
- Prove it.
You answer first. Out of one, two
and three, what will you do?
You can't see it.
I can really see it though, really I can.
This sword.
♪ I erased you because of
the many painful memories ♪
♪ Because your love pains
me, I erased everything ♪
♪ My love, don't throw me away, me. ♪
♪ My love, I am at your side. ♪
♪ Falling you ♪
She says that she can see the sword! She says
that she's my bride! That means I'm going to die!
Is she really my Uncle's bride? Why
is she my Uncle's bride though?
By God's joke.
It's a perfect house for raising kids. Let's
have kids and live a good lovey dovey life.
Ah, this is why it's called
the burden of marriage.
Ajusshi, is this possibly a honeymoon?
Hello, have you been well during this time?
I've made up my mind.
I have to disappear, before I end
up wanting to live even more.
Before I get even happier. For you,
this is a choice I must
make, to end this life.
♪ If it's a dream ♪
Because you are the Goblin's bride.
♪ I wish I could wake up ♪