strangeness
Why is there no one stopping you along the way?
Feather magic
what are you doing
The colorless city barrier is broken
The passage I'm in will immediately disappear
Did you know this from the start?
I am testing you
test me
Your test will kill me
If you can't even survive this
How do you still lead the five divisions?
How can you sit in such a handsome position
What a pity
Mirror Stage
you failed again
you can lend my hand
get rid of whoever you want to get rid of
But I want the place I deserve
It's good to have ambition
But do you have the ability
Presumably the adults should have no soldiers available now
There's no child left
I can capture the emperor
But please also remember my conditions
nature
师彭 Adult
people arrive
Yan Xi Yan Xi
Yanxi, wake up, Yanxi
Yanxi
go down
This wasn't Yan Xi's original intention at all.
What did you do to Yanxi?
So you arrest me
for this ring
Don't talk nonsense and give me the ring
Yan Xi Yan Xi
Wake up, wake up, Yanxi
what's wrong with you
Yanxi
etc
You can't use this ring
You let me and Yanxi go
I can tell you
How to use the ring
You are not qualified to negotiate with me now
bring it
take it out
king, king
why this time
you didn't react at all
Yan Xi walk
stop
Yan Xi Yan Xi
win
Yes
Free kisskh.me
how are you yanxi
Yanxi, wake up
soy Mujer
don't think you have a king
Just like Neptune and Prince Zhenlan
is a character
If you are naughty again
I'll peel off his skin
Fried Fish Skin Crisp for you
Yan Xi Yan Xi
take away
Yanxi
go
you let me go
Yanxi
what do you think
nothing
If one day you can be like us
1000 years of activity
what you up to
first hundred years
Taste the fine wines of the world with you
seven thousand years ago
The reunion made by Queen Baiwei
It seems pretty good
i want to try
Do you want to see me pop a hundred years of bubbles?
anything else
Come to the Flower God Festival with you every year
make a wish
For a thousand years
Then I can make a thousand wishes
Then you might as well make a wish to me
Probably more likely to succeed
Is there anything anyone wants to do
no
if one person
What did you live for so long?
what i think
It's just that you live well
live happily
live for a long time
even if i try my best
even if i use up all
finally sold out
You two are late
This wishing card is sold out
sold out so early
Now, people are being arrested everywhere
Everyone is rushing to make a wish before nightfall
go home early
Are you saying it's not fair?
My business is getting better
I don't know if it's a good thing
still bad
You two are so lucky
This is the last wish card
Since acquaintance is fate
Then my last wish card
I'll give it to you
thanks
gone
Bai Lin's wish
I will help her finish
Why are you hanging up an empty wishing card?
Many people do not have the opportunity to come to the Flower God Festival
And this empty sign
Free kisskh.me
wish there were more
to fulfill their wishes
Then why did you never make a wish
I wish my wish
can do it by itself
In fact, after a six-star reversal
I figured out a lot of things
a hundred years
For the ashes
I was struggling and scared
But it doesn't matter now
with you by my side
I'm very satisfied
If the reversal is successful
That's a blessing, it's a gift
if not
I don't think I'm afraid
i will succeed
I want to spend the rest of my life with you
Believe me
Although I don't remember everything
but your voice
always in my mind
You said
everything will be as i want
we will survive
we
we will live
So Su G
you are my belief
In the name of the star soul, the blood is the oath
Seven seas live and die together
What's wrong
I remember now
I remember
everything we've ever happened together
every day we spend
i remember
I love you
What's this
on Feather Candle
The Lord of Prey suddenly called our five divisions up to the tower
what do you mean
Lord of Prey noticed it
so you doubt her
caught her
what about her
bring up
Master Shi Peng will be unified in the future
Looking forward to today's gift
Give Fei Lian a way to live
Akira
There's one more thing for you to do
Master Shi Peng, please say
kill the prey
tonight
Since he has noticed
can't drag it any longer
Feather candle is crying again
Back then I took you two brothers and sisters
when I got here
you too
bullied to shame
I cry
It's because I can't see my brother Ah Huan
师彭 Adult
over the years
Not only my brother Ah Huan sees you like a father
Feather candle
I want to call you father too
I also often think
if you two
Free kisskh.me
really my child
that would be nice
Yan Xi Yan Xi
water
no water
Is there anyone here?
where are you coming from?
is there anyone?
Come, come, come, come
Is there any water?
come
Yan Xi Yan Xi
Yanxi, how are you?
Yanxi, why are you helping me?
You obviously don't know me
why help me
How to do how to do
he was hurt so badly
it's over
hurt so badly
same as when i first met you
you wake up
no, wait a minute
At that time, there were snow poppies
I have nothing now
what to do
Nasheng
what
I am here I am here
do not go
I'm not going I'm not going I'm not going
Yanxi
I sometimes think
If only you didn't know me
so
Then you won't be like you are now
If the emperor didn't choose me
I don't have to be hunted everywhere
I can live happily ever after
Yanxi
But if I don't meet you
i won't fall in love with you
I won't meet brother ice cube either
Sister Bai Ying
Brother Prince and Uncle Xijing
days with you
have too many happy hours
Happier than my days in Central State combined
Think about it now
It's not that bad with the Emperor
what are you doing, don't come
what are you doing
where to go with me
I'll kill him if you talk nonsense
don't don't
don't kill him don't kill him i beg you
can you take him with you
I beg you do you want to die with him
no no no
Can you give him a sip of water?
He's thirsty
you let me go
Yanxi, wait for me to come back
When I come back, I will go back to Biluohai with you
Yanxi
you let me go
Your Royal Highness
Did you find Na Sheng?
Cloaks are almost useless
Mirror Lake Chalet
and around all the places they could possibly go
we've all found
still can't find it
Free kisskh.me
Will someone get caught?
Didn't Yan Xi protect Na Sheng all the time?
What the hell is going on here?
No news for so long, I'm afraid it's bad luck
Great Commander
Can this water mirror still find Na Sheng?
Your Highness is completely broken this time.
What about Aying?
It should be at Jinghu Camp
ok i'll go find them
So many people can't beat Yuhuan alone
adult
I will chase back the emperor who holds the sky
No need to
You set a net for me at the Five Masters Hall
As soon as Yu Huan comes back, he will kill him
Yes
I knew it
You are still the most obedient one
Hongyuan they all went to find
Didn't find Na Sheng
Nasheng said before
She felt that something was wrong with Yanxi.
After Yan Xi comes back
There are a lot of things wrong
where is wrong
It must have been Cang Liu's mind control
Little Lord
You're back
What about Yan Xi and Na Sheng?
I'm in front of the mirror city prison
I saw that Sheng was taken away by Yu Huan
He was very cautious and I couldn't keep up
Na Sheng and Yan Xi are not together
no
But I have arranged the clansmen of the post station
continue to investigate his whereabouts
Yu Huan took Na Sheng very quickly.
I'm afraid that Sheng will have a life-threatening worry
So hurry back
Before we went to the mirror city to find out the news
Yu Huan has been wanted by the whole city
where can he go
Shi Peng can't go back there
Yu Huan should take Na Sheng to the mirror tower
You go down and continue to inquire about the news.
Yes
Looks like we're going to the mirror tower
Su G
Adhesion
Use your dragon power
Make the most of it
The freedom we've been waiting for too long
Many people can't wait any longer
This battle is unpredictable
all i can do
only do your best
Master Si wait for me to come back
Peace of the Sea Emperor
adult
I brought you Nasheng, the holder of the emperor's sky
Come in
you don't have to come in
I have something important to give you
Five divisions rebelled
until you betray this
I will give you what you want
what about my sister
Feather candle
He should have gone down to the tower to deliver the edict.
The emperor recognized you
I want to catch more than you
I want the Emperor and Houtu
And Su Gu died together
Just wait patiently
you let me go
Jiuyi diffuses the dense fog
Canglong pulls Baiyu's chariot
The wings of the divine bird are covered with rays of light
The ruler with the power of the emperor
They are finally here
prince brother prince prince
Nasheng
no
Free kisskh.me
Nasheng comes
How are you
i'm fine
What about sister Bai Ying and brother Bingcui?
you didn't see them
No
them
Nasheng
Let's lift the last seal first
until I regain my full strength
meet them again
good
go
It's densely packed with books
how to find
Nasheng
You use the emperor to see if there are any clues
good
Xuan Huang Jing
it was here
just emerging hope
but a fake
unexpected
this last seal
Hidden in this Xuanhuang Sutra
Prince brother
you are finally here
This should be our first official meeting
I should call you the prey
Or Langgan?
Now that you already know, why bother asking?
Aying is in danger
I am the god clan of Yunfu City
you want to beat me
Wait another seven thousand years
that light is
Breaking the military
Destroy the army and recreate the turmoil in the world
The power of the prey inspires the rebirth of the broken army
we need to find him quickly
Otherwise, it will poison the wild life
sister
do you want to find your sister
Who are you
I used to call you
surrender to me
Not only can you protect your sister
You can also get Yunhuang
You didn't always want to climb up
Do you control your own destiny?
What are you waiting for
give yourself to me
good
uncle
What happened
we thought
beheaded
It's the best way to suppress the phantom
Unexpectedly
uncle
kill
escape
must escape
newspaper
Major General Feather Magic
Major General Fei Lian has broken in
We can't stop it
go down
let him in
Yes
Feather magic
I didn't expect someone to stop here
stand there
You are here to avenge Shi Lang
do you think i don't want to
I'm here to persuade you to turn back
back to shore
Why are you turning back
where is the shore
I know you hate Shi Peng for killing your sister
I know you hate the five masters
I've been tormenting you and taking advantage of you
But the people of Yunhuang are innocent
So what
My only relative is dead
I want the entire Cangliu to be buried with my sister
the closest person
My only relatives were killed by you
what more do you want
But what about my relatives?
Because trying to protect me, I already died tragically
do you know
Mermaid's Heart
grow in the middle
and mine
already gone
Yan Xi Yan Xi
Yanxi, you wake up
Nasheng
Sorry
I shouldn't have taken you to Mirror City
do not blame you
Yanxi, I don't blame you
We went through life and death together
We should cherish it
I told you before
when i come back
I will go back to Biluohai with you
would you take me with you
This is the greatest honor of my life
see Neptune
please get up
I don't know why the emperor called us here
A few days ago, the prey escaped
At present, his power is still flowing in Yunhuang
poison the people
control everything
Who is the prey?
I don't know if everyone knows about Yunfu City
Yunfu City is the place where the Nine Heavens Gods live together
seven thousand years ago
Lang Gan came to Yunhuang and became the King of Stars
later became prey
So everything behind this
It's all the prey behind the scenes
That's right
After the Battle of the Mirror Tower
The body of the prey is destroyed by us
but the power
Passed to Feather
The prey has died
Five is dead
Cang Liu respects me now
Yuhuan has become the new master of Cangliu
are arresting those who stop him
Immediately, I invited Prince Kongsang and the White King to come over
Discuss together how to deal with the phantom
I guess everyone already knows that.
We are going to discuss with Neptune
Fight with Feather
Until the time to defeat Yuhuan
It's the day we return to the deserted clouds
Yanxi's order
the days I'm gone
You must protect the Quanxian camp
and all the clansmen
obey
Respected by General Yu Huan
Elder Quan
Neptune ordered
I hope all the elders will help Yanxi together
Protect the spring camp
Please rest assured
I will do my best
you also need to be careful
Yuhuan is now eradicating dissidents everywhere
ruthless means
It's like I've lost my mind
so we have to quickly
Stop him before he completely turns into a madman
The prey came to find me
I promised
Feather magic
He's slowly absorbing your will
Don't be fooled by him
you are broken
If you are bewitched by the prey
Then there is no peace in Yunhuang
more innocent people will be involved
Is this what you want
I just want to turn my back on this world