[English subtitles are available]
[Jun Ji-hyun]
[Ju Ji-hoon]
[Sung Dong-il]
[Oh Jung-se]
[Cho Han-chul]
[Joo Min-kyung]
[Go Min-si]
[Jirisan]
[This drama is
based on the rangers of the national park]
[and all people, organizations,
and incidents are fictitious.]
[Baekdudaegan Ecological Education Museum]
[Cheonwangbong Peak]
[For a long time,]
[many people have visited Mount Jirisan]
[during the long years it has stood.]
[Save Nature, Love Our Country]
[This mountain was
a land of hope for someone,]
[but a spiteful land of death
for another.]
[Many people still bring their
own stories to this mountain,]
[but not all of them return with hope.]
[This place is still at the border.]
[The border between
growing hope and severe devastation.]
[Between life and death,]
[where a beginning
and blood smell coexist.]
Mount Jirisan
is the land
between this world and the next.
[Year 2018]
[Jirisan National Park
Haedong Ranger Station]
[Episode 1]
[National Park]
[Search 1, moving to
the falling rock zone.]
[Volunteer 1, arriving at
the trail entrance.]
Are you new?
Yes, sir.
-I just got dispatched to the Haedong--
-Jung Gu-yeong!
Yes?
Follow him.
-Where?
-The mountain. It's a missing case.
Yes, sir!
You're gonna wear those?
Let's go, hurry up!
[Ranger]
[Quick, get on.
Quick, quick, quick, quick.]
Ranger station to all rangers.
Name of the lost hiker,
Yeom Seung-hun. Age 14.
Time of entry, 11:45 a.m yesterday.
He used the Haedong Ranger Station trail.
[Missing for 23 hours]
[He was bullied...]
[White shirt, grey pants.]
[Bokseon Middle School uniform
with white sneakers.]
[And a sky blue backpack.]
[The last place he used his cellphone
was the Samheungbong Peak repeater.]
[It matches the statement
of the witness who saw him last.]
[The first search area was 3 km
within that repeater.]
[Haedong Ranger Station,]
[Bidam Shelter,]
[and Jangteomok Shelter rangers
made up Search Team 1.]
[Seseok Shelter,]
[Wusong Shelter,]
[Mujin Ranger Station ranger
searched as Search Team 2,]
[but failed to track the hiker.]
[We’ll expand to 10 km
for the second search.]
[Integrated Disaster and Safety
Operation Board]
[Timeline]
[Volunteer fire department takes
section A, the unrestricted trail.]
[Unrestricted Trail:
A waymarked trail, opened]
[for hiking by the law of National Park.]
[Necessary facilities are provided
and managed for the safety of hikers.]
[Special Rescue Squad, section B.]
[Restricted sections C and D
for park ranger teams 1 and 2,]
[Restricted Trail:
A prohibited path by law]
[to prevent wildlife and hiker's safety.]
[This route has a weak reception
with minimum safety ensured.]
[and the support team.]
[Considering the fact that
the hiker had no gear on,]
[the golden time is only 30 hours.]
[It's been 23 hours and
we have 7 hours left.]
-How's the climate?
-The typhoon’s moving north
faster than expected.
[Falling rock! Watch out!]
Step back, it's dangerous.
Hey!
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Bring a stretcher, get an ambulance ready.
Min-seok.
Min-seok!
-Is he all right?
-I think so.
Are you okay?
Yeah, okay.
Search 1, a ranger injured
due to falling rocks...
Are you all right?
Search 1, heading Yangseok Peak now...
And you are?
Kang Hyun-jo. I’m new today.
We sent Min-seok to the hospital.
Take the newbie instead.
Oh, by the way...
Demon Seo is her nickname.
So be careful.
Huh?
Search is done in pairs
You know that, right?
Fix your shoelaces and stick close.
If you lag behind, I’ll abandon you.
Yes!
[Baemsagol Shelter]
[Hwaeomsa Temple]
Volunteer 1.
7 km on the trail.
No missing hiker found.
[Kalbawui]
Rescue 1, at Kalbawui.
We haven't found the hiker.
[Integrated Disaster and Safety
Operation Board]
[Typhoon Bitak is heading north at a
much faster speed than anticipated.]
[It was formed in the sea
southeast of Okinawa,]
[and is heading north at 15 km per hour.]
[It will pass Jeju and Namhae
around 10 p.m. tonight.]
[We're expecting up to 300 mm of rain
in Jeju and Mount Jirisan areas.]
[Please protect your facilities
from the strong wind.]
Seung-hun!
He's not here.
Gwisinbawi, Yangseokbong Peak.
The hiker can't be seen.
We’ll move to Seonghwang Tree.
Seung-hun!
Where’s that?
It's where many people die.
So all the places we’ve searched
so far are suicide points?
Yes. It often happens
more than once at the same spot.
Then... We’ve been looking for a dead kid?
Don’t say such a thing.
Who said he's dead?
We’re trying to find him before he dies.
Wait for me!
[Search 1.]
[Weather’s getting worse. We’ll join
at Dungji Tree and search together.]
[Search 2.]
[At Dosang Falls now.]
[We'll join the search, too.]
[Typhoon Bitak is accompanying strong wind
of over 50 meters per second in speed.]
[It will reach the peninsula
at around 10 p.m. tonight.]
[There is a storm warning
on Jeju and in Jeonnam area.]
Not yet?
Nope.
We pulled out the dogs and rescuers.
Search dogs are useless in the rain.
Okay.
The missing hiker's family is here.
[Search 4.]
He’s the commander of the search.
I’m sorry... because of my grandson.
I'm really sorry.
Not at all.
You must have traveled far.
Please take a rest.
We’ll let you know right away
if we hear anything.
Escort her to the night duty room.
This way, please.
Please get some rest.
[Humidity: 81.5 percent, Wind Speed: 15m/s
Wind Direction: Southwest]
[Search 4. The weather's really bad.]
[What should we do?]
[Search 2, taking a detour.
Water level's too high.]
[Volunteer 1, pausing the search
and evacuating to a shelter.]
Grab him!
Get in!
One, two!
[Search 3, man down!]
-Yours, too.
-Excuse me?
We can pick them up later. Toss yours.
Why are you doing this?
This is a lightning area.
There must be a good reason
we're passing here in this weather.
This is the shortcut.
We can save an hour.
We must join them for search
before things get worse.
Never go near a big tree.
It'll work as a lightning rod.
Grab something else even if you slip.
If there's nothing to grab,
just roll down.
That'll be faster.
But...
Jeez!
Hey! Wait...
Are you okay?
Yi-gang.
Look!
Search 5. Under Bidam Cliff.
We found a backpack
that looks like the hiker's.
You sure?
[It's a sky blue backpack.]
[Bokseon Middle School, Class 1-5
Yeom Seung-hun]
It's his for sure.
The hiker?
Didn't he fall with his bag?
He's not around.
No signs of crash either.
It looks like only the bag fell.
Look.
Isn't this Mount Jirisan?
Sir.
There's a photo of a wildflower
habitat above Bidam Cliff.
I think that was the hiker's destination.
We must search there.
[Wind Speed: 18 m/s]
It takes at least 3 hours
even on sunny days.
It'll take twice as much right now.
We'll go.
Please allow us to search.
[Return.]
[Integrated Disaster and Safety Operation]
Who is it?
Chief.
The 30-hour golden time is almost up.
The missing hiker's not even
wearing proper gear.
If he's alive, we must go now.
He might already be dead.
[He came to kill himself.]
[Sign of suicide]
Are you giving up your life
for a dead body?
[If you get into an accident,]
[other rangers must go help.]
Who'll be responsible for their lives?
[Integrated Disaster and Safety Operation]
Wind speed's over 20 m/s.
There's no time.
Return this second.
[This is an order.]
Withdraw all teams.
Are we really going back?
You said we must look now if he's alive.
Let's go back.
Yi-gang.
Hey, newbie! You alive?
Great job, Demon Seo.
She's so evil.
Why did she drag you to
a lightning zone in the stormy?
Where's Seung-hun?
Worry about yourself first.
Your body's all you have.
Dude, how can a ranger say that?
To a newbie, too.
A ranger must protect the mountain
even if he's torn to pieces, okay?
I'll say this as a team leader.
You must be vigilant.
I'm so sick of this.
I'm sick of you.
All right, yes, sir.
If you're not alert, you'll get hurt.
This is so uncomfortable.
[Missing for 23 hours]
What the chief said is right.
We'll resume in the morning
after the storm's passed.
Get some rest until then.
What do we tell his family?
We tell the truth.
Jirisan National Park.
[So I made a bet with my friends.]
[How high is Cheonwangbong Peak?]
It's 1,915 m.
[Including the stone monument?]
Then it's 1,916.35 m.
I'm hanging up.
Get some rest.
You should get some herbal medicine.
How can a ranger be so weak?
He's not dead.
How do you know?
He's alive. I'm sure of it.
We can't keep searching
based on your guess.
[Date of Incident, Location]
[Mount Jiri Missing Person Search]
[Bokseon Middle School, Class 1-5
Yeom Seung-hun]
[Memorize 30 vocabs, H.W p. 103...]
[Newsletter, Announcing Open Class,
Parent Education]
[15,000 won part-time job, 1,500 won bus]
[3,000 won grandma’s medicine,
11,000 won coal briquette]
[Last text to grandma,
'I’m sorry, grandma.']
[Declared missing after showing signs
of suicide]
[Bullied in school, was depressed when...]
[15,000 grocery, 15,000 part-time job,
3,000 grandma’s medicine]
[You stink]
[Loser]
[Help me.]
Umm...
I didn't know what to tell her.
[I'm sorry, grandma. From My Love]
We had to stop the search.
But we'll resume when
the storm dies down, so...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
[I'm sorry, grandma. From My Love]
[Jirisan National Park
Haedong Ranger Station]
[Wind Speed: 31m/s
Wind Direction: Southeast]
[Date of Incident, Location]
Are you crazy?
Did you follow me?
You think this is a joke?
If I'm crazy, so are you.
At least I'm not lonely since we both are crazy.
I thought...
I'd regret it if I don't come.
Isn't that why you're here, too?
If he really is alive, he'll die
if we don't rescue him now.
Just take me along.
You said search is done in pairs.
If you whine, I'll kill you.
It's not like you'll
give a crap if I whine.
It's much more dangerous than you think.
Isn't our job always dangerous?
Our job is to come back safely
from a dangerous place.
We must support each other.
If you get blown away, so do I.
If I fall, so do you.
So let's both be careful.
Yes, ma'am!
Hey!
What on earth are you doing?
Didn't you hear what the chief said?
I'm sorry, sir. I tried to stop them...
But the wind's slowing down.
Soon the sun will rise, too.
Please let us go up.
The search will start
when the storm passes entirely.
Unpack your gears.
Seo Yi-gang's missing.
So is the newbie.
Their gear's gone, too.
Those fools!
Umm...
She has something to tell you.
Seo Yi-gang.
[Yi-gang, where are you?]
[Answer me!]
Search 5, Seo Yi-gang.
[Where are you?]
-I'm sorry. But...
[-Are you there?]
[The wildflower habitat
above Bidam Cliff.]
Yes, sir.
Seung-hun...
[I'm sorry I made you sad.]
sent a message.
That message we saw
wasn't the last one he sent.
[Do you remember this place?
We've been here with mom and dad.]
[Do you remember this place?]
[We've been here with mom and dad.]
[It's so nice here.]
[Let's come back together.]
[I'm sorry, grandma.]
[I'm sorry I made you sad.]
[No Signal]
[He's still alive.]
He went from a cellular dead zone
to a signal zone on his own.
We're trying to reach him,
but he's not picking up.
I think his battery ran out.
[The support team's on their way,]
[but it'll take them three
and a half hours minimum.]
You're our only hope.
You have to find him.
Let's split up.
Look for the signal zones on GPS.
We'll only search those areas.
We'll look for survival points
not suicide points.
Yes!
[Reception area on the way
from the habitat to Bidam Cliff.]
[He'll be there. Hurry!]
[Golden time's up.]
Even if he's alive,
he'll be ill.
[Those that want to live
instinctively look for these places.]
[Between big rocks.]
[Under a big stump.]
[Among tightly-woven bushes.]
[Under a big rock carved like a cave.]
[Where you can hide from
the wind and rain.]
[Where you can keep warm.]
[He came to live.]
[He would surely have found
a place like that.]
[Jirisan National Park
Haedong Ranger Station]
Any progress?
Not yet.
He's nowhere to be seen.
I've looked in all the places
you mentioned.
But he wasn't there.
[He's still alive.]
[He must be here somewhere.]
But where?
[Those that want to live
instinctively look for these places.]
[Where you can keep warm.]
[Between big rocks.]
Where are you?
What is it?
Have you seen a weird mark
made with twigs and rocks?
No.
Something rectangular.
Never seen it.
Why do you ask? Just look for the hiker.
What about a black rock then?
What's wrong with you?
There must be an oak tree nearby.
Oak leaves were scattered around.
What on earth?
Do you mean Sangsuri Rock?
Is there such a place?
Is it near here?
But that's outside the reception area.
He's there.
He has to be there.
Don't you get it?
If he's there,
he couldn't have sent the text.
We've looked everywhere else.
So please.
Let's make it our final place.
Yi-gang!
Over here!
[I found him!]
[The hiker found under Sangsuri Rock
at Bidam Cliff!]
His state?
Answer me!
[He's unconscious.]
[He's too cold.]
His pulse and breathing?
[Seung-hun!]
[Seung-hun! Wake up!]
Hey! Stop!
You all right?
I'll just carry him on my back.
Put him on my back.
-Be careful.
-Come down carefully!
-Slowly!
-Be careful!
[Ranger]
Are you okay?
Over here!
There they are.
Check him.
Pulse and breathing, normal.
Great!
Take the lady to the hospital.
Yes, sir.
Take care of her.
-See you in a bit.
-Okay.
We're at the bottom.
He's breathing fine, sent to the hospital.
[Come down safe.]
Great work.
Thank you.
Where's Yi-gang?
She'll be passed out.
Well done, Yi-gang.
[Why aren't you responding?]
[Hey! Can you hear me?]
[Hey, Yi-gang!]
[Did she just turn it off?]
Hurry up!
Aren't you going to train?
In just a second...
Are you here to play?
How can you save anyone at that speed?
If Mount Jirisan's one thing, it's big.
Stranded hikers will be dead
while you rest like that.
I think... I'm really dying.
You got your patrol area assigned, right?
Have you been there?
No, not yet...
Our main task is to guard this mountain.
You must have
all the place names, tree species,
and distribution of vegetation
memorized by heart.
Demon Seo...
Do you have a death wish?
Well...
Even if I die...
Can I have a sip of water?
Yes. At Sonbawi.
Okay. Coming.
This is Sonbawi?
Son, as in hand?
They're making it harder to go down.
Why would they have a date at
such a tough place, not a pub?
That's so annoying.
Should I... hold your hand?
Shut it and follow me.
Wait... Slow down...
How did you find this place?
It wasn't me.
He did.
Newbie.
Yes?
How did you know about this place?
Well, umm...
Let's say... the mountain told me.
The mountain?
That's believable.
People have been serving Mount Jirisan
from before the Three Kingdoms.
Being an object of faith
for such a long time
can't just be a superstition.
There's energy in this mountain
that's difficult to explain.
That's what I mean.
This time, for instance.
There's no reception here,
but a text message was sent.
The mountain saved the kid.
Stop the nonsense.
So what is that?
Oh, right.
This...
was how the partisans kept in touch.
When they fell behind
or was out of contact,
they made a code like this to communicate.
That's still there?
They pick a spot
that no one else will discover.
A place that won't be...
destroyed in the wind.
Like this place.
What does that mean?
It was to signal their location.
Or so we assume.
I must go now.
Thank you for calling me.
I'm Kim Sol,
a cultural resources researcher.
If you happen to find another
historical place, please call me!
All right.
This must be quite valuable.
We could...
use this when we can't use radio
or cellphones on unregistered trails.
It's perfect for signaling
a lost hiker's location.
Look.
Pretend these rocks are Bidam Cliff.
Here...
Stick a twig in.
See? It's right where Sangsuri Rock is.
Now tell me.
How did you know?
I saw it.
It's not my first time.
I keep seeing...
where lost hikers are in this mountain.
You really are crazy.
Are we going on patrol?
Wait for me!
I'm coming!
[Year 2020]
[Missing Case Final Report]
The official search at Yiseokjae
is over as of today.
Return to your ranger station or shelter,
and focus on your tasks.
Then...
If we end like this,
what about the lost hiker?
If that many people looked for
over a month and couldn't find him,
it's hopeless.
Leaf season starts next week.
There will be a lot more tourists.
Check the safety facilities
and do a good base duty.
-Yes, sir.
But when are we getting a new member?
We've had a vacancy for a while.
Oh...
Someone's coming.
Really?
Who?
I hope it's someone experienced,
not a newbie like her.
It's someone you know.
Who is it?
[Seo Yi-gang?]
Yes.
The Seo Yi-gang?
No way.
She hasn't quit yet?
She asked to be reinstated.
Not her.
Who is she? Why is this a big deal?
Long time no see.
Yes.
How have you been?
You...
Why are you back?
What do you mean?
She's Ranger Seo Yi-gang,
who knows this mountain best.
You know what I mean.
Shouldn't you be on patrol?
-Grab your gear and follow me.
-Okay...
[Lost Hiker Search Report]
[Informer: Lee Min-seok
Victim: Yang Geun-tak]
Is it a missing case?
Yes.
Yiseokjae, that's near
Yiseok Falls, right?
Where did this person go missing?
There's no witness.
Why are you back?
Have you looked near Gaeam Falls?
That's in the opposite direction.
You know that.
I think we should search there.
Did you get a tip-off?
Please.
Pass me the card.
Just a second.
Sir?
Umm...
What happened to your friend?
What do you think happened on a mountain?
They were stranded.
Stranded?
Why did they have to go up there
in heavy snow?
We almost died rescuing them.
Huh?
Them?
You mean...
Someone else went missing, too?
Why?
[Control room speaking.]
Yes, sir.
I don't understand.
I really don't.
Why did he want us to come here?
Be careful, it's slippery.
Okay.
Gosh.
Wow...
What is this place?
Gaeam Falls.
It's famous for its scenery.
There's not a single ant,
what does he want?
Huh?
Sir.
What's that?
Illegal hiking!
We tell them not to come,
but they still do.
They keep trashing the place,
so we ban them.
Why?
[Name: Yang Geun-tak]
[Missing Hiker: Yang Geun-tak]
[Isolation (got lost)
Wearing a blue trekking jacket]
It's him.
The missing hiker...
we've been looking for.
[Name: Yang Geun-tak]
[Ranger]
[How did you know?]
Hundred of people looked
for over a month in vain.
But you...
You just got here. So how did you know?
I want to know, too.
How did you know...
the missing hiker was there?
[Volunteer Fire Department]
This is...
the Mount Jirisan
volunteer fire department website.
You knew from this?
This is a picture of joint search
with the rangers
during this Yiseokjae accident.
And?
Isn't that the mark you discovered
at Sangsuri Rock?
This one's different.
Only Hyun-jo and I knew this signal.
We decided to use this
to signal where the lost hiker is
when there's no reception.
So this...
pointed to Gaeam Falls?
[Yiseokjae Missing Hiker Search]
This was 3 months ago
during the Mujindong accident.
I also found the mark there.
It was pointing to Seonghwang Tree.
You found the corpse there, right?
Yes.
This was 6 months ago
during the Jeonmukgol accident.
And this one was
the Oerae Valley accident.
Here too...
It pointed exactly to the missing hiker.
That's impossible.
Maybe it was a prank.
It was exactly in the place
Hyun-jo and I decided on.
Someone sent me a signal.
Umm...
If it's between you and
that Hyun-jo guy...
it must be him.
No.
Hyun-jo...
can't come here anymore.
[Name: Kang Hyun-jo]
[Someone...]
[is sending me a signal...]
[from up there.]
I wanted to know who.
That's why I returned.
[Jirisan]
[Why did you go up there that day?]
[I’m here because there’s
something I need to find.]
[What is it?]
[A dead body.]
Go to the headquarters.
I’ll let you know first
if I find anything.
[I saw it. The mark.]
[But this was the only way.]
[Who is this person?]
[Why are you asking
about the yellow ribbon?]
[Mujin Valley, pine tree habitat!]
Park ranger down! It's Kang Hyun-jo.