Unforgettable Love
EP15
I...
Dad
what are you going to say?
I finally...
Lao Qin, shut up.
I won't allow you to say that.
Before I leave...
Don't you say that.
I'm just talking about the card before I left.
Lao Li lost his 20 yuan to me when playing cards.
Has the money transferred to my WeChat account?
You old fool,
you're still thinking about playing cards.
Well, you two
remember that for me.
I am a little bit hungry.
Dad, I made wonton.
It's still hot.
I'll get it for you.
No, No.
I'd better not eat it.
In case
I can't make it to the surgery
and die before that.
If so, I'm wasting the wonton.
There you go again.
Dad, it's not time
to make a joke like that.
Well, no wonton.
I'll make you a bowl of millet porridge.
OK.
Duh...
I...
I want to eat the wonton you made for me.
All these years
I haven't eaten
any food my daughter cooked for me.
Dad
I'm sorry.
I didn't take good care of you.
I shouldn't have said something like that.
Dad
what are you looking for?
In this ward
there's no monitor and recorder, right?
Monitor and recorder?
Right.
What do you want?
Come here, daughter.
The password
is your mother's birthday, the other way around.
What do you mean by that?
Take it.
Here's the money
you sent to me.
I didn't waste it.
Every remittance
I have saved for you.
And
wages in former company
my pension
is this number.
That's all.
Daughter
you got married
without a formal wedding ceremony
and even dowry
I didn't prepare for you.
In such a time
heart surgery is no small thing.
Even if I am optimistic enough
I should be responsible for you and your mom
and leave these matters to you.
Dad, don't talk about that.
Keep this money for yourself.
No no no
It should always be
dad taking care of his daughter.
You know?
I don't want you to grow up.
If anyone is to blame
it's dad's getting old so fast
that troubles my daughter.
Dad
I'll depend on you.
I'll depend on you all my life.
OK, pinkie promise.
Pinkie promise.
By the way
Lao Li's 20 yuan...
I got it!
Don't forget it.
I won't.
Okay, okay.
It's been more than three hours.
It will be OK.
Mom, Yiyue.
You are here, Qiaoyan.
He's been in for hours
and hasn't come out yet.
Mom
the operation has certain risks
however
I analyzed
all the surgical data.
The success rate is not low.
The surgeon, Doctor Xu
is a cardiologist
from GMN Medical Center.
The success rate of his operation
is up to 97.8 percent.
Short term complications
and local recurrence rate
are also very low.
He's the golden hand in heart surgery.
Apart from him
his three assistants
and the anesthesiologist
all followed him
for more than ten years and formed a fixed team.
That would be great.
I will not worry about it.
Just rest assured, Mom.
The operation will take a while.
You two can take a break for a minute.
If you still don't feel at ease
just take a look at
the real time data feedback of the operation.
I've arranged another group of
other experts
to monitor the data at the same time.
Two groups of personnel for double guarantee.
You can rest assured.
These...
Did you do these overnight?
That's what I should do.
Xiaobao is also very worried about you.
Don't worry.
We're in this together.
Thank you.
Dad.
How's it going, Dr. Xu?
The surgery was a success.
Thank you.
Thank you, doctor.
Let's go.
Chicken feet.
It smells good.
You pervert!
I...
Dad
you woke up.
How do you feel?
It hurts.
Straighten your finger.
In the contract
when can I add
the protection of my personal safety?
Never.
You are here, aunt.
Qiaoyan
Xiaowei has told me everything
and I've reminded you, too.
At this moment, nothing
nobody
can stand in Heshi's way.
Look at you
let a stranger's illness
affect your work.
He is no stranger.
He's my father-in-law.
It can be arranged with a phone call.
Why are you wasting your time?
Aunt
perhaps family's company
is also important.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of
things at work.
Take me to the ward.
This way.
Dad, mom.
Aunt.
This is...
Mom
this is Qiaoyan's aunt.
In-law.
You are very kind
to take time out of busy schedule
to visit Lao Qin.
Sit down. Sit down.
Aunt, leave it to me. Please have a seat.
Have a seat.
Sit down, aunt.
Would you like some fruit?
I'm good, thank you.
A glass of water then.
Yueyue, get a glass of water.
Don't bother.
Lao Qin
you don't know
how much your son-in-law
helped this time.
Otherwise, Yueyue and I
don't know what to do.
Qiaoyan is a good son-in-law.
Mom and dad, look what you said.
It's what I should do.
In-law
your family genes
are really good.
When I first met Qiaoyan
I wondered how could there be
such a handsome boy.
And today I saw you
what a beauty.
In the future
if Qiaoyan and Yueyue
have a baby
how pretty it will be, right?
Mom
Yeah
So many people.
Hello, uncle and aunt.
Auntie, you're here, too
Mom and dad
This is my best friend
Wen Gu
The boy is very polite
to come such a long way.
It's what I should do.
Mr. He.
I've got what you want.
Mom and dad, there's something at work
I need to deal with.
I have to go.
Just go.
We are here.
Yes, just go.
Mom and dad have me here.
I mean I can take care of them.
Go ahead.
Call me if you have any questions.
Aunt, let's go.
Have a good rest.
Take your time.
Look at you
you haven't cleaned your mouth yet.
Do you want any more?
want it or not?
What else to eat?
This
Why Xiaobao
suddenly got so close
with a stranger?
Maybe because Yiyue
has engaged in children's psychological work for years.
She has
the qualities that attract children.
I used to think
Xiaobao has child's nature
to like someone
all of a sudden.
But today When I saw Xiaobao
I suddenly wondered
was it really that simple?
You mean
Yiyue approaches Xiaobao intentionally.
This is absolutely impossible.
Thank you
for coming to see my father.
You are very welcome.
I have to go.
Wait
There's one thing
I want to ask you.
What is it?
I used to see pictures of a girl
from the back
at your brother's place.
I thought it was Miss Lin
but now it seems not.
Of course not.
Who is that?
Well...
I'm not sure if I can tell you.
Fine
I'll change the question.
Who do you think
is the person knows Ruowei best
in the world?
Not a big deal.
What do you want to know?
I will definitely tell the truth.
Smart.
You know me.
I'll sell my best friend
without reservation.
If you have any questions in the future
just come to me.
Settled.
Can you tell me now?
My brother has been dreaming of
a girl's back
in recent years.
He just wanted to find out
the girl in the dream.
But don't worry
I think
that girl doesn't exist.
The girl in his dream?
That means
this girl doesn't exist at all?
Certainly not.
I must go.
You secretly
call up the information of Qin Yiyue.
The Information of Mrs. He
you've seen it all before.
It's different this time.
I want to know
her relationship with Xiaobao.
I don't believe
there's such a coincidence in the world.
I'll do it.
Hello.
Qiaoyan.
Mom.
Why is it so noisy over there?
Are you done with work?
I've just finished.
What's the matter?
Come to the hospital.
The hospital?
Is anything wrong?
You have a long journey.
It's fine.
This little girl is really beautiful.
I remembered she was just a kid.
She's grown up
You're right
it's the right room.
A friendly Reminder
you can't run now even if you want to.
Nine times out of ten
they came for you.
This group of relatives and friends gathering together
is not easy.
Yes.
How are you, aunts and uncles?
It's a long way to come
to see my dad.
Have some fruit.
It's what we should do.
Yueyue has grown up, too.
You're so beautiful, Yueyue.
Hello everyone.
How handsome.
Close-up real picture.
Don't be rude.
Brother Qiaoyan, let's take a selfie.
This is my daughter, a medical student.
It's because
she's worshiped Yueyue since she was a child.
She just graduated this year.
Mr. He
is there any vacancy in medical technology
in your company?
What is her subject?
Veterinary medicine, mainly focus on horses.
Maybe my company is not suitable.
Academy of Agricultural Sciences
I can introduce her there
Brother, can I add you on WeChat?
Brother Qiaoyan
can I also add your WeChat?
He's not the same as what is said on the Internet.
He has no official airs.
Yes.
Right.
Talented.
Hello, uncles and aunts.
You are here.
Why so many people?
I don't know either.
Come to the supermarket with me.
Uncle said he wanted a deck of cards.
He said it's so boring.
OK, let's go.
Qiaoyan, I ordered several boxes of fruit.
They are about to arrive.
Would you please come with Ning Fang
to help me move them?
Why do you want them both?
Nothing else.
I just want to see them in the same frame.
Let's go.
Mom.
I'm leaving.
Uncles and aunts, we have to go.
Right, they are busy.
How beautiful!
Come in or not, young man?
Don't hang about.
Wait.
The pores are clean and delicate
but the forehead and nose are oily
Has skin care but not exquisite
The fragrance of wood
fresh and light
Popular taste
but mediocre
Blended T-shirt of
Japanese household brand
Pursuit of cost-efficiency and comfort
but the delicacy is not enough
The edge of the nail is clean and smooth
and smells like disinfectant.
It should be hand sanitizer in hospital.
From the muscles
on his shoulder and chest
his body fat should be about 10 percent
to 13 percent.
I used to think
last time at the hotpot restaurant
was our limit.
I didn't expect...
You can choose not to talk.
In such a small space
every word of yours
can cause a surge of air
blowing in my ear.
It's very uncomfortable.
Don't move.
He Qiaoyan really said that?
Arranged marriage was just a joke?
He said there was not such a thing.
He's not lying to you, is he?
No, he's not that kind of person.
I think
you really
like He Qiaoyan now.
Have some snacks
and stop talking.
It's not me you're blocking.
Even if He Qiaoyan
didn't take the arranged marriage seriously
it's clear that Lin Wei takes it seriously.
She made such a high-profile appearance
at the banquet
and openly
went to work in Heshi Group.
She's obviously telling you
that she's the one.
If you
really like He Qiaoyan
don't be so stupid.
Don't blame me for not reminding you.
Love affair
is like a battle.
let's go.
You want to carry two boxes?
What's up?
Put it down first.
What is cooperation?
The key to cooperation is
fair
and reasonable distribution.
There are three boxes of fruit
and each box is three kilos.
That's nine kilos in total.
I think the most reasonable way should be
one for you and one for me
and the box left
we move it together.
It makes sense.
However
I
didn't plan to carry them myself.
I think so, too.
The key to human progress
is using tools.
Together.
You are just as Yiyue described.
What's up?
Minister Xu of R & D department thinks
the new design of the bracelet
has affected the use of the product
but Lucas insists the design.
So now they two
have reached a deadlock.
Got it.
What's the matter?
Wait a second.
There's something in the company
I need to deal with.
Please tell mom and dad.
Just go.
What's going on?
The meeting of rivals in love is especially envious.
Do you think they two
will have a fight?
Your father's illness
has affected Qiaoyan's work.
Because of the bracelet recently
He Qiaoyan is very busy.
I hope you won't
disturb his work any more.
Otherwise, I won't sit back and watch.
It's our business, what's the matter with her?
Stop looking.
The car drives away.
Jaws of death.
Yiyue.
Yiyue really
likes He Qiaoyan.
Ruowei
do you know this man?
When I came
he was on your seat.
It's OK. You go ahead.
Is that her boyfriend?
No way, he's too low.
Sister, what are you doing?
This bag is worth tens of thousands.
I said don't come to my company.
Why are you here again?
This is your fault.
You have to tell your family
if you change jobs.
I had a lot of trouble finding you.
Alas.
I want to ask you something.
Do you think
this is the most expensive Industrial Park
in this world?
Which moneybag are you leaning on?
The chairman?
This is where I work.
Anything you what to say
go out and tell me.
No need.
I'm good here.
You get up.
Right off.
What a waste.
Or I'll call security.
Let me tell you
I'm not afraid of losing face.
Weiwei.
Good morning.
What's the matter this time?
Lend me 200 thousand yuan.
You bet again.
I didn't bet.
This time a friend of mine
pulled me in.
But the business was a failure
and lost 300 thousand yuan.
I'm not directly
asking for 300 thousand yuan.
Just give me some 100 thousand right now.
Besides paying back the money
there's the decoration of the house
me and mother's living expenses
and
I'm going to marry my girlfriend next year.
Before you lie
can you make a draft?
Can people like you
find a girlfriend?
And
how to decorate the house?
Is our house Queen's garden
that has to be repaired every year?
Can you
find a decent job
to support the family?
Just tell me will you lend me or not?
You make so much money
so you should
share more
for the family.
This is the word a brother
should say?
Sister.
in fact, in my heart
I've been worried about you.
Having been out there all these years
you must have suffered a lot.
I actually...
Sorry, baby
I'm late.
Tell me this kind of thing earlier.
Let me handle it.
I'll take care of my baby.
She doesn't have to suffer with me.
Double rhyme.
What's your problem?
Dude,
did you hear that just now?
Never again
call her sister.
It's greasier than Daqing Oilfield.
She doesn't want to see you at all.
If you are smart, go away.
Who the hell are you?
Who are you?
-She's my sister.   -He's my brother.
Brother, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Just go away.
Go away.
What's wrong?
What's the matter? So mysterious.
No way
where did you find it?
Why it smells like
air fresheners?
Poor little ring.
It has lied idle for so long
in the bathroom.
It's really a sin.
Bathroom...
But have you ever thought about it.
This ring appears
just at this moment.
What does it mean?
It means it's time
for a clean-up.
I am asking you
did He Qiaoyan
give this ring to you?
Yeah.
So is this ring
the symbol of your identity
Mrs. He?
Right?
Right.
So this ring
is obviously a reminder.
It's time to exercise your rights as Mrs. He.
Thunder strikes
to repel the invading enemy
and safeguard your man.
Right?
Is it?
Can you be more positive?
Ouch
Uncle will be up and about soon.
You have to face your crisis in love.
l have to go.
I am late.
Behave yourself.
Bye.
I finally make it to the discharge.
How to describe this?
Right.
There will be a good fortune if you don't die in great danger.
What about my 20 yuan?
There you go again.
Dad, Uncle Li said
he's going to fight you 300 rounds
after you are discharge
with that 20 yuan.
Old fool.
Let's see what I can do to fix him.
You don't have a chance to fix him.
What's up?
The doctor said
you have a serious lack of exercise.
So when you get discharged,
I have to take you running every day.
I have few years left
If I don't play any more, I'll suffer such a loss.
Let me ask you
If you died this time
You couldn't even see your granddaughter.
Do you suffer or not?
That's quite a loss.
You two
can live another hundred years.
How sweet our daughter is.
Where's Qiaoyan?
Oh, right.
Your father's discharged is such a big deal.
Why didn't he come?
Didn't you tell him?
Mom.
It's because
I don't want to disturb his work.
That's fine.
Mommy.
Here comes Xiaobao.
Mom and dad.
You are so busy.
You don't have to come here.
It's what I should do.
I thought you weren't coming.
On my way here
I've been on a conference call
so I didn't get time to call you back.
Mom and dad, your car is ready.
I'll take you home.
That's good.
Let's go.
Don't eat fatty food.
You have to eat something vegetarian.
You just got out of the hospital.
There's no wine.
You shouldn't drink wine just after being discharged.
Fine.
Xiaobao, help yourself.
Dad.
My daughter loves me.
Mom, have some, too.
My son-in-law loves me.
Daughter, eat.
Why is Xiaobao so lovely?
Here, call me grandma.
Mom.
Oh, my poor memory.
Forget it.
Grandma.
Did Xiaobao...
Did Xiaobao call me?
Call me again.
Grandma.
Fantastic.
Xiaobao, call me grandpa.
Grandpa.
He's calling you.
What happened to the child today?
He's enlightened, isn't he?
Fantastic.
Xiaobao, call me daddy.
Say daddy.
Xiaobao, say daddy.
It's daddy.
Mr. He, you need to keep trying.
It's nothing.
That's what kids do.
Maybe tomorrow he will call you.
Take it easy.
Yes.
Let's have dinner.
Come on.
Come on, Xiaobao.
Yueyue, have some yourself.
Hello.
Qiaoyan.
Mr. Jia wanted to see us
at the hotel where his company's dinner held.
It sounds like
he wants to cooperate with us.
OK.
Well
send me the location of the hotel.
Before the end of the dinner
I'll be there for sure.
Mom and dad.
It's something at work.
I have to go.
If you are busy, just go.
The meal is not finished yet.
Xiaobao, let's go home.
Eat something.
You've hardly eaten anything.
Goodbye, Xiaobao.
Drive safe.
Bye, Mom.
Hotel.
Why to meet in the hotel?
Why didn't take me to dinner?
I'm his wife.
Silly girl.
You finish eating and lie down.
Did I give birth to a baby pig?
I'm going out.
What are you going to do?
Your baby pig's backyard
is on fire.
What does that mean?
Sis, please give me your robe.
What?
Don't you say love affair is like a battle?
I'm going to fight.
By the way
your so called imperial mask
please prepare for me, too.
Put it down.
So mean?
Tell me
when, where and who.
Hotel, tonight.
He Qiaoyan and Lin Wei.
At the hotel in the evening?
No wonder you sound the alarm.
You actually need to
take good care of your skin.
Lin Wei is not a small role.
Don't be outperformed by her.
So I come here
for your equipment.
Depends on it.
My skin color
has lightened a lot.
You are
my fairy godmother.
Only a pumpkin cart's missing.
You can have it.
Excuse me
is the pumpkin car
reserved by passenger 6623?
Why are you here, Ning Fang?
I called him.
It's the evening rush.
It's hard to find a taxi.
Thank you then.
Get in the car.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
What's up?
You're taking pictures, aren't you?
Who's taking pictures?
Let go.
Come to the police station with me.
Go.
Hurry up.
What do you want?
How dare you take pictures.
Mr. Jia