Unforgettable Love
EP16
Go.
What?
Hurry up!
How dare you take pictures!
-Mr. Jia.  -Mr. Jia.
Yiyue, let him go.
What are you doing?
This way, please.
Mr. Jia refused to cooperate with Heshi Group.
The cooperation with Mr. Jia
is a crucial step to
the promotion of bracelets.
For this cooperation,
He Qiaoyan has been busy
for over half a month.
I'm so sorry.
I never expected
it would happen.
We had had an appointment with Mr. Jia
at 10 a.m. last Monday,
but because Qiaoyan was concerned about
your father's surgery,
the meeting was cancelled.
Then, Qiaoyan
made lots of efforts to persuade Mr. Jia
to give us
another chance to meet.
But again, you...
Qin Yiyue
Don't you think
you've always been giving Qiaoyan
a lot of trouble?
I know you're not a real couple,
but merely a contractual one.
How did you know?
Never mind how I knew it.
I had wanted to give you
more time to disguise,
but right now, you've
severely affected Qiaoyan's work.
I just can't ignore it.
Even if we're in a contractual relationship,
that's our business.
Stop deceiving yourself.
You clearly know
my relationship with Qiaoyan.
We have an engagement.
He has told me,
that your baby engagement
is just a joke.
It's our two families' business.
Whether a joke or not
can't be defined by He Qiaoyan.
Besides, for Qiaoyan, Heshi Group
is more important than anything.
Do you think
you can compete with the whole He family?
Besides, I can help Qiaoyan
to run Heshi Group.
Can you do it?
Keep it real,
you are from totally different classes.
I'm sorry.
All right, I'll drive you home.
No, thanks.
I can go back by myself.
Dressed like this,
how can you go back by yourself?
Do you want to beat a pervert again?
Dress like this at night,
what's going on in your mind?
Let me drive her back.
You came here with him?
I'll take her home.
Let's go, Yiyue.
I'll go now.
What happened?
I want to drink.
Had a quarrel?
No.
It's just...
I did something wrong.
If you do, just apologize.
If you don't apologize,
nothing will be solved.
Ning Fang,
Do you know that feeling?
It's like,
the God
suddenly knocks my head,
to let me realize
the good merit I thought I had
is nothing but a fake.
It's taken back at twelve o'clock
to its original owner.
You little fool, you are the best.
No one can take it away.
I'm not pretty nor good.
I can only affect his work,
and hold him back.
I...
What are they doing here?
My brother must
be cheated, isn't he?
I must tell him now.
Bro, what's the matter with you?
How can you allow sister-in-law
to drink with another man?
She drank?
You've offended her, haven't you?
Where is she?
Inside.
Why are you here?
Isn't it time for you to go?
Ning Fang
No matter what happens,
I'll make it clear.
Wait for me outside.
You must be Dr. Ning Fang, right?
I've heard of you from Ruowei.
Go, go, go.
I haven't
formally introduced myself.
I'm Wen Gu.
Ruowei's boss.
Go home.
Go home?
Go home with me.
Back to our home.
Qiaoyan, where are you?
Since it doesn't work with Mr. Jia,
We have to quickly propose
Plan B.
OK, I see.
Don't be silly,
I'll take you home first.
There's another meeting in the evening.
He Qiaoyan,
I have no reason
to stand by your side.
What do you mean?
Let's
terminate the contract.
Terminate the contract?
Why do you want to do that?
The validity of our contract
is one year.
There's still much time left.
Xiaobao, he...
he's been able to go to school without crying.
His language ability
is also recovering.
He no longer needs
my whole companion.
I want to devote more energy and time
to my own career.
And,
I don't want to
affect your work any more.
I think what you need to do
is to calm down.
I'll give you two weeks,
two-week paid vacation.
It's me,
who cannot uphold the principle
to be a fake couple with you.
A fake couple?
I'll give my last word:
go home with me.
I've told you, terminate the contract.
You didn't ask me to stay at all...
Sit down.
What on earth can't I let it go?
Do you mean
I can't let go the mansion
or limousine?
I'm not superficial, OK?
Am I that kind of superficial person?
Let me tell you,
what I can't let go is Xiaobao.
Xiaobao and I
are good mates forever.
What?
Did you say I can't let go He Qiaoyan?
You are the one who can't let him go, OK?
He's as cheap as you.
I won't even pay a dime
to buy him!
Turn the light off and go to bed!
It's already midnight,
and what are you doing again in my house?
Well, eat melons.
Eat melons for what?
They contain too much sugar.
Not for bedtime.
Come on,
why does sister-in-law burst into temper?
Is my sister-in-law cheating on you?
Do you think everyone else is like you?
You bastard!
I came here to comfort you,
but you,
do nothing but attack me.
Or because of Lin Wei.
It has nothing to do with Lin Wei.
You and Lin Wei
once had a baby engagement.
About that,
I've explained it to Yiyue.
I've told her
those were just nonsense from elders,
so don't take it seriously.
I'm so relieved.
Relieved? Why?
Neither sister-in-law nor you cheated.
What's left
is not a big deal.
Women, women.
Find out the cause, and remedy the problem.
It's so easy to ease women.
Yue, what's going on?
Haven't I told you to declare sovereignty?
How come it was flipped around?
Good news doesn't come,
bad news has wings.
He Qiaoyan also agreed with it?
Maybe he also realized it.
Since Lin Wei came back,
I
am becoming unnecessary.
Come on in.
Mr. He,
this is Pediatric Psychology Consulting Room.
Of course I know.
Tell me,
why do you want to leave?
I've finished my work!
Besides,
for my career,
I have clearer vision and higher pursuit.
I want to do something extraordinary.
OK, I see.
But I hope
you're not just bragging.
The title of Mrs. He
is no longer what I want.
Pretending to be in love every day
is just driving me crazy!
Anyway, there're so many people who like you,
so I don't want to be regarded as
the one squatting on a toilet...
What did you call me?
A toilet.
Squatting for a long time,
I'll easily numb my legs,
then I'll give it to others in the queue
to use.
Let's put it this way,
I disagree.
Why?
The contract is very clear.
Stage three,
Party B should, within the term of the Contract,
help Xiaobao
successfully enter the primary school,
and adapt to social life.
Yes,
I'm doing fine.
Xiaobao is now gradually
adapting to school life,
and he's getting along with kids
without any discomfort.
I think I have
finished the work successfully.
It seems that Dr. Qin
isn't fully aware of
the definition of social life.
It seems I need to popularize to you
what is social life.
Social life is linked by social relations,
which means to build relationships
with others.
In the field of psychology,
interpersonal relationship
refers to the person-to-person
direct psychological connection.
In terms of that,
Xiaobao haven't done it.
Briefly speaking,
Xiaobao just peacefully
gets into the social environment,
but doesn't
let down his defences
to make friends with others.
Mr. He,
are you talking to a professional
about the professional?
It seems that Dr. Qin
also agrees with me.
I, He Qiaoyan,
never fail in business.
How about that:
as long as you help Xiaobao
to find a friend,
I'll count all your work
done completely.
With contract void and debt cleared,
you'll be free.
What are we doing here?
Meet parents.
Of course I'm a parent.
I mean,
meet parents for what?
Just meet parents.
What were you thinking about?
Xiaobao,
This is?
Guoguo.
Hello, Guoguo.
Hello, Uncle...
Uncle?
Brother.
My name is Cheng Guoguo.
I'm six years old.
I'm an Aries; my blood type is A,
and I live in Xinyang District.
I like painting and dancing.
I serve as an art commissary in the class.
Xiaobao and I
have fun all the time.
He takes care of me and helps me,
and he can do magic of physics.
I really like playing with him.
Okay.
Now that we're here,
if no one opposes,
we'll make an exchange.
Dr. Qin,
they are just children.
Don't mess around.
Exchange friend cards.
Friend cards?
Now we can exchange hugs!
Xiaobao,
you've done a good job!
Guoguo,
thank you for
being good friends with Xiaobao.
The little skirt you are wearing today
is so beautiful!
I love it!
From now on,
You can play with toys.
What's going on with them?
To help Xiaobao,
I made a set of friend cards
to encourage him to make friends
in this way.
It was a one-week
challenge of making friends.
Unexpectedly, he succeeded.
By the way,
just now, did Xiaobao
say Guoguo's name?
Yeah.
Now he's
able to say other names
except for "Mom"?
When he encounters a special situation,
or when he meets
someone he likes,
he can use very simple expressions.
So far,
The upper limit I've heard is
five words.
Then why do we
still need to use cards
or a wordpad?
That means you should keep going.
After my departure,
he'll only rely on you.
Come on, "Daddy"!
All right, I'm leaving.
Let me give you a drive.
No, thanks.
I'll find another time
to come back and pack up.
You're really serious about it.
Our contract
is originally temporary.
No matter when the contract is signed,
all of them will be terminated eventually.
Even if it's terminated,
we can still
sign a new one.
The workload and working hours
depend on your needs.
In addition,
welfare and salaries can be doubled.
Contract termination
has nothing to do with money,
but my career plan.
Fine.
If you have a
higher career pursuit,
I can arrange a
specialized scientific research laboratory,
and the best commissioners.
You can do any research you want.
Thank you,
but that's not what I really need.
You should find a chance
to explain it to Xiaobao.
I should have ended
this ridiculous experience as well
to start my own life.
Do you think this period of time
is ridiculous?
Don't distort what I mean.
In a few days,
Xiaobao' school
will hold a Parent-Child Day.
I'll accompany him
to take part in the activity.
After this,
our contract
is completely terminated.
Here you are.
OK.
You can leave now.
Sorry to trouble you to accommodate Qiaoyan
in the restaurant near Heshi Group.
I do apologize for your inconvenience.
It's OK.
I know Qiaoyan is busy.
Young people
should focus on the career.
Heshi Group owes Qiaoyan its prosperity in previous years.
Heshi is really
striding forward year by year.
Xiaowei is excellent, too.
Young as she is,
she's a famous designer already.
It's just her hobby,
but also her part-time job.
In the future,
she will eventually focus on the family business.
Aunt, Mrs. Lin
There will be a meeting later.
I need to go first.
Enjoy yourselves.
Wait a minute.
We haven't mentioned the most important thing.
Qiaoyan,
Both you and Xiaowei are not kids anymore,
so it's time to discuss
the time to get married.
Get married?
Qiaoyan, we all know that
you've always wanted to
run the business of Heshi well at first,
but marrying Xiaowei
won't affect your plan.
It will help you, instead.
Xiaowei is such a diligent girl.
Aunt, you must be very clear that
I won't marry for family's benefits.
Qiaoyan, you are very smart.
You should know that
the marriage between Lin and He
means a lot
to Heshi Group.
Of course I know,
but I won't sacrifice myself
for the business.
Excuse me.
Excuse me for a minute.
As for Dr. Qin's personal information,
I looked through it again.
Anything special?
We looked up Qin Yiyue's
all experiences from born till now
and her social relations.
She was born in a working-class family.
From childhood till now, she is obedient and excellent.
However, there's only one doubt
in her experience.
When Qin Yiyue was in the university,
she wanted to be a surgeon.
But then,
she abruptly changed her major to psychology.
Why?
According to her teacher,
it's because Qin Yiyue
saved a child
in a car accident,
and got her hands injured.
A car accident?
When?
On the same day as Xiaobao's car accident.
Where was it?
It was probably on Huanshan Street.
Xiaobao's car accident
also occurred on Huanshan Street.
Qin Yiyue
might be that person.
That's why Xiaobao
has a special affection for her.
Does Qin Yiyue
know the truth of the accident?
Mommy.
Your Mommy's not here.
Told you, Mommy's not here.
Mommy, Mommy, Mommy...
Can't you say something else?
Xiaobao!
Mommy!
Xiaobao, Mommy comes here today
to prepare for
the show with you
on the Parent-Child Day.
So,
do you have any show
you want to share with your classmates
and your teachers?
I came here to help Xiaobao
prepare for the performance
on the Parent-Child Day.
I...
I know you're busy,
don't worry.
When I rehearse with Xiaobao,
I'll give you a simple role.
Just practice before the performance.
♪ Blows the wind, shines the moon ♪
♪ Where is the boat floating to ♪
♪ Take the long journey with me ♪
♪ Blows the wind, shines the moon ♪
♪ Where is the boat floating to ♪
♪ Take the long journey with me ♪
Secretary Zhong
Mr. Jia asked me tomorrow
to talk about the bracelet face to face.
Well,
you send
all materials about the bracelet to me.
All of them.
Your improvement solution
will be further discussed with my colleagues
in the R&D Department.
Though it's sort of difficult to change,
it's not impossible anyway.
Excellent!
As soon as your samples are produced,
we can sign the contract right away.
I'm looking forward to your good news.
No problem.
Well then, I'll go now.
There are other arrangements.
Mr. Jia, wait a minute.
Is it convenient for me to ask
what makes you
change your mind?
Well, I didn't change my mind all of a sudden.
Actually, I've always been
very interested in your bracelets.
But last time...
Last time...
Last time, Yiyue
didn't mean it.
No, no, no, you misunderstood me.
Refusing to cooperate with you last time
had nothing to do
with Miss Qin.
It was you and Miss Lin
who never ceased talking about
data this, data that.
In the end, I just couldn't stand it.
Maybe,
you don't know much about me.
In the business,
what I value most
is the usage experience of products,
instead of
something like data.
Mr. Jia, you are right.
Now it's because...
Today,
I'm able to be here to see you
because of Miss Qin.
The day before yesterday,
Miss Qin managed to find me.
It was her who convinced me.
Dressed like this,
how can you go back by yourself?
Do you want to beat a pervert again?
If today
any other accident happens,
how can you deal with it, Yiyue?
Xiaobao,
I've recorded the song
in it in advance.
You can
just listen to the song in it.
Get familiar with it.
Tomorrow, Mommy
can't practice with you,
because I'm going to the villa in advance
with Brother Ning Fang
to set up the venue.
Take it.
Yiyue.
Ning Fang, you are here.
Xiaobao!
Ning–Fang.
You should call him Brother Ning Fang.
Brother.
Good boy.
Give me a hug.
Look at the present I prepared for you.
Do you like it?
Take it.
Go and play.
Packed up your luggage?
Not yet.
I'll think about it later.
Can't let it go?
I just can't let go Xiaobao.
Where's my phone?
It's on this Sunday.
Do you still remember the concert
we missed when we were in college?
I'll make it up to you.
Lin, are you busy?
Do me a favor.
Is there any other way to buy tickets
for Xie Ming's concert?
Cindy,
is it possible to get me two
VIP tickets for Xie Ming's concert?
♪ Blows the wind, shines the moon ♪
♪ Where is the boat floating to ♪
♪ Take the long journey with me ♪
Ning Fang, you are here.
Xiaobao!
Ning–Fang.
You should call him Brother Ning Fang.
Brother.
I forgot to take my phone.
Did you see that?
Look for it.
Can't let it go?
I just can't let go Xiaobao.
Don't be so sad.
You like He Qiaoyan,
which should be a wonderful thing.
Even if you ended up
with separation,
you've also gained happiness in the process.
That's enough.
You're right.
Process is more important than result.
Let's go.