[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode 11]
I don't believe in ghosts,
But
the shelf suddenly
fell down that night,
which really scared me.
Not only you.
Wang Sheng reported to me later.
Even I was scared.
At that time, I thought
I should bring you back right away.
You can't do that.
Brother,
since I was young,
I was born in the palace.
I think I can know the world after reading thousands of books.
But after I left the palace this time, I found that
there were things you can't read in this book.
For example,
I never thought
there were poor children like Tongtong in Lin'an.
there were devoted women like Liu Yiyun.
I never thought
there were shameless men
like Mr. Liao!
Although there are similar stories
in the folk novels,
it's not as good as
what I saw with my own eyes.
So you still want to go back to the Wood Feather House?
Of course.
Please allow me.
Is it because you don’t want to leave Li Qingfeng?
No.
How could I miss him?
Brother, don't you use the reason
to stop me from leaving?
We're just friends.
Friend?
Just friends.
Who gave this to you?
Ur... Let me show you this.
Isn't it fun?
It is made by me in the Wood Feather House.
Isn't it exquisite?
You are so smart.
The delegation of the Northern Zhou arrived in Lin'an yesterday.
What does the delegation have to do with me?
You are the first princess of the Xiao Dynasty
When the delegation is here,
you should show our strength
and uphold our prestige.
Don't go back to the Wood Feather House
until the Northern Zhou delegation leaves.
Brother,
Why not?
I promise
as long as you call me back,
I will come back soon.
OK?
And
there are a lot of work in the Wood Feather House
waiting for me to finish it.
For establishment of Qinghe's house,
we have to finish it. Right?
This is what father taught us.
You brat.
You used our father to pressure me, right?
You can go back.
But I have something to remind you.
You were born in the royal family.
As the first princess,
don't be too capricious.
You can make friends
with Li Qingfeng,
but he can only be your friend.
Yes.
Luo.
Why don't you stay at home for a few more days?
Miss Han went back with me.
It's not convenient to live at home.
We're back!
You are bad.
You just dry your blankets.
Officer,
Miss Chen,
Luo.
Why are you guys back so soon?
I'm bored at home,
and I miss you too,
so I came back early.
Luo,
you can also dry Miss Chen's quilt
out of sunshine.
How is your family?
They are fine.
Look, I'm wearing it.
After you left,
I started to miss you.
Really?
Miss Chen,
didn’t Wang Sheng go with you?
He left?
I didn't know he went home.
He's back
with Miss Qinghe.
Qinghe.
Luo,
I met Qinghe outside the door.
Miss Qinghe.
Have you solved your problems in government office?
I'm here to thank you all.
For that bastard Liao Shisan,
everyone deserves to kill him.
People in the Wood Feather House are all heroes.
When we meet unfair things,
we will naturally give help.
Qinghe, don't be so polite to us.
Yes.
Since everyone is back,
I have a new idea about the rebuilt of the mansion.
Miss Qinghe, if it's convenient,
let's go to the meeting hall and have a chat.
[Miao's Mansion]
Congratulations.
Congratulations! Congratulations! Great!
[Miao's Mansion]
Congratulations!
♫The smile on your lips♫
OK.
It's nice to have you.
♫Like dancing petals falling into my heart♫
♫Weaving the wings of young dreams♫
♫Take me through the long night♫
♫Wait for the dawn of the next second♫
♫Count weathered footprints♫
♫Leaving in the time♫
♫Which is my long journey for you♫
♫Regardless of my own danger♫
♫You are the shining star♫
♫Sparkling in the story♫
♫A glance at you is better than the whole scenery♫
♫Life is gorgeous like beginner's heart♫
♫The young's return like♫
♫Clear and boundless sky yesterday♫
♫We'll meet at a specified date♫
♫Be with you in the long life♫
Miao's mansion.
This is Miao's Mansion.
[Miao's Mansion]
Have some tea.
What do you want to say?
Why are you so mysterious?
Langyue,
do you love me?
Of course I love you.
If I don't love you,
I can't feel happy
during this period of time.
You are such a cute guy!
I thought you were going to say something serious.
Since we love each other,
I'll take you home tomorrow noon
to meet my father.
You know tomorrow is the Zhongyuan Festival.
You don't want to?
No.
Don't get me wrong.
But...
Since I knew how I love you,
I have decided to love you forever.
If you marry me,
I will only love you,
and spoil you.
I won't let you unhappy.
No, I'm not talking about that.
What are you worried about?
Don't you want to get married with me?
No!
What else do you worry about?
Just tell me.
Let's face it together.
OK.
I'll go back with you.
[Li's Mansion]
My Lady,
you forgot your gift.
Oh, yes.
You left in a hurry.
I almost forgot.
Take care.
Architect Chen. Wait.
You can wait for me until we're back.
Master wants to see you.
Young master.
Master and Madam have been waiting for you for a long time.
I know.
Well,
should we go in first?
Let's wait.
But...
I told you to wait.
Yes.
Be gorgeous
and steady.
Brother,
I really have something important.
Nonsense!
Is there anything more important than my business?
You promised me
you can go back to the palace when I call you,
but you didn't say that you would look like this after returning to the palace.
I think you are getting more and more unreasonable.
You’d better stay in the palace
and learn embroidery from aunts.
Don't leave the palace anymore.
OK.
I know I am wrong.
Li Song, what time is it?
Your Majesty, we can move now.
Let's go. Let's meet the the 13th Prince.
Summon the Northern Zhou delegation.
The 13th Prince Yelv Zhigu
Han Tinghui, the Minister of Internal Affairs,
Xiao Xiazhi, the Minister of Rites, please come in.
Yelv Zhigu,
Han Tinghui,
Xiao Xiazhi.
Greetings to you, Your Majesty.
Wish you longevity, Your Majesty!
The three of you come from afar,
you must be tired.
Have a seat.
Give the first seat to the 13th Prince.
Mr. Han. Mr. Xiao. Have a seat.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Today is a private banquet.
Don't be restrained.
I've long heard that
the 13th Prince is the most proud son of the emperor.
It is proved that you are really amazing
among the young princes of Northern Zhou.
I'm afraid no one can compare with you.
I’m flattered, Your Majesty.
Many princes of Zhou have their own strengths.
Some of them look handsome,
others are strong as a tiger.
When I compare with them,
I am only be considered mediocre.
You're too humble.
As far as I know,
the candidate for the new king of Northern Zhou
is you.
You must be kidding.
Father is still strong.
Now he has fought everywhere with ambition.
It's also the time of the prosperity of our country.
We just hope
to realize the dream
of unifying the whole country.
I wouldn't dare to say anything about the new king.
Not bad.
Emperor Zhou can be the king after fighting everywhere.
Since he acceded the throne,
he maintain the rule of turning every man into a soldier.
He led the strong army
and he was invincible all the way,
which is indeed admirable.
But because of that,
the burden of internal affairs
will be fallen on your shoulders.
I still need to ask Your Majesty about
the way of internal affairs.
We two countries can communicate each other
to gain experience.
Let alone asking me.
Summon the Dance and Music House.
The 13th Prince,
do you like
my banquet?
Your Majesty is treating us with hospitality.
I’m flattered.
No matter how good the banquet is,
it is not as good as the people of the Xiao Dynasty,
who can enjoy simple meal in the peaceful country.
The 13th Prince.
It's time for us to talk about business.
Langyue, you can leave now.
Yes.
Wait.
Your Majesty, I have a presumptuous request.
Your Majesty, please allow me.
Tell me.
I came from the Northern Zhou.
I haven't had a good visit in the capital Lin'an.
I just heard that today is the Zhongyuan Festival of the Xiao Dynasty.
May I invite Princess Zhaohe
to enjoy Zhongyuan Night together?
Fine.
Then let Langyue
show you around Lin'an
to appreciate local conditions and customs.
Your Majesty.
The 13th Prince came from afar.
You have to do your best.
Yes.
Thank you, Princess Zhaohe.
How about we drink?
Qingfeng.
Didn't you go home?
Why are you back so soon?
Where is Chen Langyue?
Architect Chen is not in the yard.
Not?
What's wrong with him?
I think it must be related to Master.
Miss. Zhao, why don't you ask him?
No way.
How about you go, Miss. Han?
I?
I...
No, no, no.
How could I ask?
Where is Li Qingfeng?
He...
Luo,
I...
What happened?
I don't know.
Did they quarrel?
I don't think so.
Qingfeng.
Why?
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to break my promise.
If you don't want to go, just tell me.
Why did you lie to me like this?
I didn't lie to you.
Are you trying to make fun of me?
Do you know that everyone in the Li family,
dozens of people,
are laughing at me.
It's not what you think.
Then what is it?
Tell me.
Where did you go? Why didn't you go to Li's?
I had something to do at home. They called me back.
Didn't you say you're going to Li's?
Or it's not important for you
to go home with me?
No.
Chen Langyue, I've made it clear to you.
If you have any difficulties,
you can tell me any concerns.
I can do anything
to face it with you.
But you still don't want to be honest.
You don't trust me.
Why?
I...
You still don't want to tell me?
What else are you hiding from me?
No.
It's not what you think.
I'll give you another chance.
Explain it to me now,
or never tell me that.
Can you promise
don't mad at me anymore
after that?
You can say it first.
I have a distant friend at home.
If you lie,
you can make up a good story.
I didn't lie.
You have a friend at home
who only stayed in Lin'an for four hours.
Why can't you go to Li mansion first
and then go with me
to meet your distant friend?
Even if you went home,
why can’t you let Luo
to inform me?
Li Qingfeng!
He must have offended Master again.
Did anything happen?
I don't think so.
What happened?
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Not necessarily.
What do you mean?
I want to know
whether Miss. Chen and Mr. Li had a quarrel?
Buddy, are you curious about this?
It seems that no matter who it is,
people all like to hear gossip.
Alright, I should go to the next one.
See you tonight.
Take care, Miss Zhao.
It's boring. I'm going to drink too.
I'm going to see my lady.
You haven't answered me yet.
Let's continue.
Go! Go! Go!
Let's go.
My lady, are you all right?
My Lady,
My Lady.
What's wrong?
Mr. Li.
You can't make her angry like this.
She has her reasons.
Please understand.
If she doesn't trust me,
how can I understand her?
My Lady.
Mr. Li just doesn't know what's going on.
Calm down.
Explain it to him.
Don't let him misunderstand you.
Let him misunderstand me!
He questioned me without asking why.
Our love in the past are all fake!
Alright, calm down.
Do you know your mistake?
Well,
Someone is looking for you outside.
[Wood Feather House]
Are you Li Qingfeng?
Yes. Do you know me?
I'm the servant of Architect Chen.
My Young Master
wants to invite you to the mansion.
[Chen's Mansion]
Watch the steps.
This way, please.
This is my Young Master.
Mr. Li, go over there.
I’m Li Qingfeng.
Greetings to you, young master.
I heard you had a fight with Langyue.
Don't look at me like that.
As her elder brother,
I have to control
every move she does.
Young Master, just say it.
That's great.
I'm just curious about your attitude to Langyue.
You can tell me.
I love her and will love her forever.
Forever?
I will marry her.
Did you ask me?
I haven't visited you yet,
and I was invited here.
Did Langyue tell you about her family background?
Do you know
why she didn’t tell you her family background?
Because I've already arranged a marriage for her.
Sugar-coated haws.
Come and have a look!
Qingfeng, go and have a look.
Let's go.
Master is not here. Why are you still shopping?
Wang Sheng went away again.
Otherwise, I'll ask him to drink together.
It's better than walking around here.
Li Qingfeng.
How did you make my Master angry?
I told you, she made me angry.
How dare you?
Calm down, you two.
I believe Miss Chen
must not be the sensitive lady.
Since Luo said she was busy,
it means she had something to do.
What happened to Master?
If anything happens to her, it will be a big deal.
How could she leave Luo alone to spend the Zhongyuan Night?
What is it?
It's just that she's already engaged.
She said she has a distant friend.
No way.
Don't talk nonsense.
How could Master have a marriage?
If she has a marriage,
I can't be busy with all the matters
for the long time.
So she hid it from you too?
Qingfeng,
I think there must be some misunderstandings.
You can ask Miss Chen later.
Her brother told me
Chen Langyue has a marriage.
Brother?
You met her brother?
Yes.
What?
What's her brother's name?
Chen Houzhi.
[The country is prosperous and the people are at peace.]
[People are long-lived and rich.]
Have you heard of this?
Come on. Take a look.
Come here.
Great!
[People are long-lived and rich.]
[The country is prosperous and the people are at peace.]
[There is good weather for the crops.]
What are they singing?
I've never heard of it.
[People are long-lived and rich.]
[The country is prosperous and the people are at peace.]
[There is good weather for the crops.]
The costumes and vocal
should be the same as Mulian Saves her Mother.
It should be a poetic drama from the central place.
It's rare in Jiangnan area,
so it's normal that you don't know.
Great! Great!
[People are long-lived and rich.]
[The country is prosperous and the people are at peace.]
[There is good weather for the crops.]
It seems that it's always like this.
Miss Chen seems to mean something.
I'm just sighing.
Don't get me wrong.
Please don't misunderstand.
After all, I came with the delegation
to promote peace between the two countries.
Got it.
Let’s watch the show.
Li Qingfeng.
Well, how can we go first?
We just came out.
Don't stay together for too long.
That's right.
It's not interesting.
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go.
[Spring Tea House]
[Guanglaishun Inn]
Let's go on a boat and travel the lake.
Tonight,
half of the performers in Lin'an
will dance on the lake.
There are poem club on the boat,
which was organized spontaneously.
There are many lanterns by the lake as well as many mosquitoes.
I think we should go to the East City Square to make a wish.
Look at a Kongming lantern flying in the night sky
defined against the stars.
Such a brilliant scene can appear
only once a year.
Don't miss it.
Yes.
I also think Kongming Lanterns are more interesting.
Since we have different opinions,
how about we travel separately?
Otherwise, someone will be unhappy.
What do you think?
That makes sense.
I've been in Lin'an for so long,
but I haven't had a trip to lake.
If possible,
I want to see
the beautiful lake tonight.
Anyone else?
Don't you want to go?
Miss Han.
It seems that what happened tonight is destined.
Niaoniao, let's go.
OK. It doesn't matter.
OK, let's go.
Let me tell you.
The moon will be very round later.
Li Qingfeng, what about you?
Where do you want to go?
I just want to take a walk.
Then I’ll leave Luo to you, Mr. Meng.
We should learn to help others.
Bye.
Why are there only the two of us?
I just want to take a walk.
Miss. Zhao, please yourself.
There's nothing to go shopping alone.
If you don't mind, let's go together.
There's nothing to mind.
Let's go together.
Don't get me wrong.
I don't want to go with you.
It's just that we're the only ones left.
Actually,
I've prepared a surprise for you and Miss Chen.
I want to tell you two tonight.
Unexpectedly, Miss Chen is not here.
Surprise?
I got a job for the Wood Feather House.
You will like it.
Work?
This job is different.
It's easy and meaningful.
After the Zhongyuan Festival,
I'll tell you the details.
Here. Slow down.
Boatman, take a boat.
OK. Choose one.
Is the price of the boat the same?
It's the same. Choose whatever you want.
This one. It is bigger.
Sure. Please.
Come on.
Give me your hand.
Be careful.
That. That!
Ladies, welcome to come again after eating.
Fortunately, we don't miss the time to set the lanterns.
What is this?
Sir, this looks delicious.
Lady,
this is called Crispy Yellow Dough.
Isn't this a yam?
Sir, I want one.
OK.
Thank you.
Lady, take it.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
Is it good?
Delicious.
This lantern is so beautiful.
The material is delicate and the painting is good.
As a painting on the lantern,
it's rare to have this artistic one.
It is because they choose the right lantern paper.
What do you mean?
The thickness of the lantern paper is suitable,
so the green light can come through the lantern.
The light and the painting can set each other
to create the atmosphere.
I see.
Sir, how much is this lantern?
Lantern riddles must be guessed right
before you can buy it.
If you can guess the riddle on the lantern in the first time,
you can buy it with the original price, 300 coins.
If you guess it twice, the price will double.
If you get the answer three times, the price will double again.
After that, you can guess any riddle
and the price won't rise again.
If the riddle can't be guessed, the price will double.
This method is interesting.
Let's guess this one.
OK.
Ninety nine.
This riddle is too short.
How can we guess?
Ninety nine. Not one hundred.
It is character Bai.
Yes!
Sir, is it Bai?
You are so smart.
Congratulations. You got the answer right.
This lantern is made by Bai Laoer at Tianqiao Shop.
I'll sell it to you with 300 coins.
I'll buy it.
OK.
Miss Zhao, if you like it,
I'll give it to you.
That's great.
Wait.
This lantern is so beautiful.
Sir, I want this lantern.
This is the 19th poem tonight.
The one who guesses three poems successively
[It was the Zhongyuan Festival when I came to the world, which is not like Xuandu where people are free forever.]
[Burning incense lonely in the temple, I know my teacher has long been yearning for Yujing Mountain far away.]
will be able to enter the poetry boat
to drink and write poems with all the scholars and talents.
Everyone, please.
[It was the Zhongyuan Festival when I came to the world, which is not like Xuandu where people are free forever.]
[Burning incense lonely in the temple, I know my teacher has long been yearning for Yujing Mountain far away.]
It was the Zhongyuan Festival when I came to the world,
which is not like Xuandu where people are free forever.
Burning incense lonely in the temple,
I know my teacher has long been yearning for Yujing Mountain far away.
It's a good poem.
Are they asking us to guess the poem name?
Yes.
As long as we say the poem name and the author,
they'll show next poem.
The one who guesses three poems successively
can get on the boat of Jiangnan Poetry House
to attend the poem club.
I see.
Do you know the author
of the poem?
I happen to know this poem.
It's "To Master Zhang on Zhongyuan Festival",
which author is a scholar named Linghu Chu.
Then you can answer!
I remember.
This poem is "To Master Zhang on Zhongyuan Festival".
The author is Linghu Chu.
Congratulations!
We were too slow.
We were a little slow.
That's the way of preemptive answer.
But it doesn't matter.
Anyway, we're just wandering.
It doesn't matter if we get on the boat or not,
or do you want to get on the boat?
I can't even guess poems,
let alone write poems.
I thought you wanted to get on the boat.
You know each other?
Is this your distant friend?
Yes, this is my friend from afar.
What do you think?
It's also the secret
you can't tell me?
You talk nonsense.
You are out of all reason.
Miss Zhao, let's go.
Give me the lantern.
OK. Wait.
Sir, we want this lantern.
Lady,
I just said...
I know.
You said we should guess riddles.
He can guess it, so can we.
So the reason you recite poems
is to have more discussions
in business.
Yes.
The poem and lyrics are used to cultivate emotions,
but I use it as a business talk.
Isn't it funny?
I just don't understand.
Not just poems,
I learned and understood other aspects
as long as they can help my business,
such as popular opera,
the taste of food,
and even brothel.
I know it better than anyone else.
Just for business?
That's right. That's my dream.
Dreams?
I know the position of businessmen is low,
but I still want to be a businessman.
I believe in business rules.
In some perspective, these business rules
are my life credibility.
Only in business,
I can find
my own way to survive
and my value.
Value?
It is indispensability.
According to my opinion,
in our life,
we need the  indispensability.
Miss Han.
I want to ask you a silly question.
Go ahead.
Would you like businessmen?
I hate businessmen.
Sorry.
I don't mean I hate you.
Don't get me wrong.
Mr. Luo. Are you alright?
If I offend you...
No, it's OK.
But I think
you are different from ordinary businessmen.
Can the businessman like me
like you?
Luo.
Have you decided what wish you want to make?
I hope my lady...
No.
I hope the princess
can be healthy and safe every day.
I also hope she can be happy every day
and finally realize her dream.
What about you?
I...
Except Master,
you have to make a wish for yourself.
I have no wish.
I just hope
to serve the princess all the time.
You have to get married.
You should make a wish for yourself
to find a good husband.
I don't want to get married.
After you meet your lover someday,
you will not think like that.
Trust me.
It begins!
Hurry!
I'll count to three. Let's do it together.
One, two, three.
Let it go.
Make you wish quickly!
I hope in the future,
I can as happy as tonight every day.
By the way,
I hope Luo
find her lover as soon as possible.
Mr. Meng.
What wish did you make just now?
I just said it.
What?
Didn't you hear me?
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
Besides what you just said,
nothing else?
No.
What else?
What about the princess?
Master?
I really forgot Master.
Forgot?
Was it because I was mad at she and Li Qingfeng?
They had a fight,
but I'm not angry anymore.
I must think she is a princess.
I can’t imagine what wish I can make for her.
I see.
By the way, Luo,
does Master have a marriage?
What are you talking about?
How is that possible?
Yes, I told him it's impossible.
Li Qingfeng is insane.
Let's not talk about this.
Come, I'll take you to eat something delicious.
According to the rules,
you must guess the riddle on the lantern
to qualify as the competitor of them.
It's not difficult. Come on.
Miss Chen.
Let me do it.
I'm new here.
I really want to experience it.
Please grant me my wish.
OK. You must win the competition.
I will try my best.
Miss Chen.
Mr. Li and I
were abandoned by those two pairs.
Don't get me wrong.
Miss Zhao, don't worry.
Of course I won't think too much.
Today I just want to be against Li Qingfeng. He has weird temper.
It's not hard to guess the answer.
Well, I'll make another riddle with the riddle.
It will become more difficult.
Sir?
Please.
Ninety nine. What's the another riddle?
One in hundred.
The answer of ninety nie is Chinese character "Bai",
and that of one in hundred is also "Bai".
He can get the answer quickly.
It's amazing.
You are really talented.
Then this competition is fair.
Please.
I’m He Zhigu.
May I know your name?
You don't need to know.
In the Rat Year, spring is coming.
The spring breeze returns home.
It's about to start. It's interesting.
A decent man doesn't meet the emperor.
Sorry, Mr. Li.
A decent man doesn't meet the emperor?
The answer is also Li.
Answer the riddle with a riddle. It is amazing.
Miss Chen.
Shouldn't you be happy?
Yes.
Good job, Mr. He.
Three or five roads outside the border.
The answer is an idiom.
Three or five roads outside the border?
Three or five roads
What?
Mr. He, can’t you guess?
The answer is
nonsense.
He is really mean.
Miss Chen, why are you laughing?
Mr. Li, it's my turn.
Listen carefully.
When writing, it is square.
When drawing, it's round.
It is short in winter.
It is long in summer.
The answer is a character.
I got it.
The answer is... Mr. Li.
Actually,
Getting the answer when guess riddles
is not difficult.
What do you mean?
When we count one to ten,
you should make another riddle with the same answer
and match both sound and sense with my riddle.
Then you'll win.
If you can't, you'll lose
and I'll buy this lantern for Miss Chen.
Do you dare?
Within ten numbers, the riddle should be matched with another.
How is that possible?
Oh no!
OK.
Miss Chen, tell me.
What is the answer?
Character Ri.
Ri?
How can we make the riddle?
He is going to lose.
Ten.
Li Qingfeng.
Let's not gamble with him.
Eight.
Give him the lantern.
Seven, six, five.
No.
Four, three, two, one.
What do you mean, Mr. Li?
You can't guess?
Or are you wasting time on purpose?
There's a fish in the East Sea.
It has no head or tail.
Take out its spine.
It is the answer.
The answer is character Ri.
Ri?
I lost.
I admire you.
Thank you.
I announce
the winner of this riddle competition is Mr. Li.
Mr. Li.
This lantern is yours.
Miss Chen.
Your friend is really literary.
I can only give this lantern to him.
Forget it.
It's just riddle guessing.
He is still a fool.
Can you tell me now
who he is?
You are good at guessing, so you can guess again.
You are unreasonable.
# 赵小姐
Let's go.
Mr. Li.
You must be curious about my identity.
How about this?
I'll make another riddle.
If you can guess it,
you will know who I am.
My riddle is
one pen
can write two people
and three ears.