Our Secret
EP17
It's our Comics Club.
This is the club's pictorial.
Anyway, the task to select candidates
will be handed to you.
I truly trust your vision.
President
This is the pictorial you asked me to draw last week.
Right, Ding Xian.
Let me introduce her to you.
This is the chief editor of Dream Journey Press.
She's also the organizer of this competition.
This is Ding Xian.
Pretty good!
A freshman?
Have you ever taken part in
other competitions organized by other presses?
No.
Drawing is just my hobby before.
Well, your president is right.
The girl
is truly talented.
I feel so relieved that you have such a great drawer.
I'll leave to you the rest of the issues of the competition.
I should go now.
Okay. Take care.
How's that? Are you interested in the competition?
President, I have something to do.
I'll go now.
How do you know I like this?
It's a gift from the store.
Don't be like before,
sleepless after drinking coffee.
You've been doing the paper for two days,
and you haven't finished yet?
Stop doing it if you can't.
Didn't you forbid me to join in the scientific research group?
It's none of your business.
The store's closing. Go back earlier.
Let me walk you balk.
Didn't you say you wouldn't go back to the campus?
I will go to the laboratory tomorrow morning.
To save the time.
What are you smirking about?
Nothing.
Wait!
Who is it?
Is it our Zhou Siyue, Boss Zhou?
Why do you come back to the dormitory?
I should guarantee that stalker
doesn't reappear.
Stalker?
Just tell me
you sent Ding Xian to her dormitory!
Did you?
Tell me! We're brothers!
Morning.
Morning, bro.
You look so different after sleeping in the dormitory!
Have a look.
Circuits and Electronics: Data Integration of Analog and Digital Electronics.
Haven't we learned it as freshmen? Why did you do with it?
To have a review.
What a complete one!
If any student
who wants to join in our group this year finds this,
he or she will be so happy!
Are you going to bribe a girl with this?
You can tell me, and I'll borrow you.
No.
If I do what you said, I'll make it by myself.
-Give it back.  -Wait.
You…you've already made it.
Borrow it to me. Do me a favor.
What can I get from it?
You see,
if I succeed,
I'll serve you in any way you like.
Let me tell you, I know a girl.
She lives in the same dormitory as Ding Xian.
So beautiful!
Okay. I'll borrow it to you.
If you succeed, treat me a meal.
Of course!
I'm leaving.
Didn't you just come for a while?
To get more sleep.
Bye-bye.
Don't worry, Jiayu.
The material can really help you a lot.
Thanks, Yuan.
We can be WeChat friends.
If you have any question, just ask me directly.
See? Yuan Fang
is really blunt at reading other people's mind!
Ban Jiayu has no reactions at all.
Obviously, she has no interest in him.
Why does he still help her?
What's this?
A test material given by Yuan Fang.
Well, I don't understand
why you want to join in the scientific research group.
Tiring and hard to pass the test.
See? Here comes the instruction.
Let me see.
Ding Xian
What about copying one for you?
Great! I really need it.
Before answering any question,
be careful of
the information given by the question.
This question.
Prove…
I bet you didn't read it carefully.
You even didn't notice the wrong word.
Who'd like to
find wrong words on the paper?
I do.
Hello.
I want to ask you something.
How to order food on my phone?
Could you please teach me?
According to your demands,
click the goods on your phone,
and pay the bill directly.
Then you can take your food by the counter with the number you get.
But there's no introduction of the food in this page.
Could you please give me some recommendations?
What's your specialties?
You can order according to
the menu.
Can I add you as a WeChat friend?
I'll often drop by the store!
This is the QR code of the store.
If you need to order a seat,
you can scan the QR code directly.
I'm sorry.
Go!
What? Hurry up!
Aren't you busy?
I should eat anyhow.
Isn't the test coming?
Why do you have time to be here?
Don't worry.
I accidentally got a good treasure.
I'm sure I'll pass the test.
The scientific research group of Professor Ye
is not that easy to get in.
I also felt I had no hope.
But after reading through the material just now,
I find it much easier to understand.
I suddenly understand so many knowledge nodes in it.
See?
There're a table of content and conclusions,
and examples of wrong answers.
So thoughtful!
Seriously,
the strange habit to pick up wrong words
is really like yours!
Are you kidding me?
Did I really have an illusion?
Don't think too much.
Ding Xian
If now I still
want to persuade you not to do it,
am I too late?
It's good you're clear about it.
Then wish you good luck.
Thanks.
Why don't you give me a meal? I also want to eat.
I'm a guest today!
I also want to eat!
Let me tell you.
I've inquired about it yesterday.
The list is shown up today.
Ban Jiayu
You must be in it!
I dare not see it.
Let me help you to look at it.
Help me to look at it.
Okay.
No, there's not.
Don't look for my name if I'm not there.
Aren't you worried?
I didn't have any hope at the beginning.
I can change another field.
Well, it's just a choice.
Ding Xian
You got in!
See? She got in!
Look!
I've told you that you would be chosen.
I got in! I got in!
Siyue, the girl called Ding Xian we met last time
really got in our group.
Is she junior to you?
No.
We were classmates in senior high school.
She studied in the high school for another year.
I didn't expect that she could get such a high grade!
She makes me a little bit astonished.
Her solutions to questions are just like yours.
It's not strange that she got in.
She is always a clever student.
Zhou Siyue! Zhou Siyue!
I passed…
Here she comes.
Sorry, Professor Ye.
I didn't see you just now.
I've seen your paper.
Pretty good.
But after getting into the scientific research group,
there will be an assessment period.
You should be prepared.
I will. Thank you, Professor Ye.
Continue your chat.
Great!
I approached closer to studying abroad with you!
It will be more difficult in the assessment period.
If your task is not passed,
you have no way to get into the core experiment group.
Don't always discourage me.
Ding Xian
Are you sure you will like to do all of these?
Doing experiments,
writing programs,
and collecting data every day.
You won't be interested in all of these.
If you like these,
why won't I?
Alright. I won't bother you.
I'm leaving now.
The fried chicken is ordered by me!
I fetched it!
You want to eat?
Then apologize to me.
Call me daddy if you want to eat.
-Daddy.  -Sorry.
Okay. Okay.
Here you are.
Disgusting!
Tell you something.
Ding Xian has got in our scientific research group.
Good. She's close to you.
Good?
Think about it.
Ding Xian reviewed for another year.
She was so arduous for me.
She got into Hua Qing University for me.
And she got in the scientific research group for me!
She doesn't like these at all!
Just like Kong Shadi.
If Kong Shadi
gives up what she likes
because of you,
do you like it?
So I ran away from her.
In my opinion, even so,
you must
have no way to resist from showing her your love.
No way.
I don't believe you.
In the next three months,
we'll do a task assessment every month.
The student who passes all assessments
is able to stay eventually.
For the first week, Dong Zhengfei will
lead you to get familiar with the environment.
From the next week,
every student should hand in your new task.
I won't say any other words.
Dong Zhengfei, make an arrangement.
Okay.
Follow me.
The laboratory
is open for 24 hours every day.
Professor Ye gives classes
from 6:30 pm to 10:30 pm.
As for other time, you can arrange by yourself.
However, if you really intend to
join in our scientific research group,
you should sacrifice
all the time for entertainment
and stay in the laboratory from day till night.
Be prepared at any time.
Have a seat.
The scientific research
is truly a boring thing to do.
And because of it,
everyone should be fully concentrated.
If you don't have enough passion,
you'd better give up as early as possible.
Come on!
I'm sure I'll stay in the scientific research group!
Why are you in such a hurry for a whole day?
Lou Feng. Do you have anything to eat?
Yes.
Hurry up.
Another one.
No. I really have no time.
I'll go now.
Get another one!
There's no time!
I'm sorry. I'm late.
Again? Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
The assignment is… Let me see…
Love is always making people tired!
Don't slack off!
Professor
Did you hand in your task?
Almost done. Give me another five minutes.
Why should I wait for you?
Everyone's handed in theirs!
Is that your attitude to do scientific research?
Do you have sense of time?
I'm sorry.
Go back now.
No.
Bugs in the program
haven't been found.
You'll tire to death sooner or later.
You do much more things than me,
but why aren't you tired?
You should ask yourself
why you make yourself so tired.
Run the following program…
No way! Ding Xian!
Are you living in the library?
Professor Ye has told me.
As long as I can answer this question,
the assessments in the next three months will be exempted,
and I'll be a true member of the group.
What if…you cannot solve it?
Pack up and go.
Professor Ye
You are deliberately making hard on her.
She's making hard on herself.
If the question is given to juniors or seniors,
they may not solve it.
What's going on?
The code is wrong.
Siyue
Not only her.
You also should figure out
what on earth you are doing.
I won't make mistakes again.
What are you looking at?
Give me an idea.
In what way
can I talk with him?
Ask him how to solve the question.
Good idea.
Well, hello.
I have a question. I don't know if you have any time.
Could you please have a look at it?
Okay. Let me see.
You're only a freshman.
Why does your professor give you such a hard question?
It's a question given to Ding Xian by Professor Ye.
Only when Ding Xian solved the question
can she stay in the scientific research group.
What a surprise!
She's really hard-working!
She does this for his high school classmate Zhou Siyue.
The girl works late at night every day.
She's tired as a dog!
Just to get in the scientific research group,
and to go abroad with him.
Is she
that confident?
Let me tell you,
in order to get in the scientific research group…
I cannot solve the question right now.
It's okay.
Add you as a WeChat friend.
If you solve the question, send the answer to me.
Okay.
There's only one quota for the overseas exchange every year.
Does Professor Ye really appoint Zhou Siyue secretly?
How's that?
I've got his WeChat!
I mean the question.
The question? He doesn't know how to solve it.
That hard?
Does Professor Ye
make it difficult for you deliberately?
I'll go now.
Bro, I'm also leaving now.
Bye-bye.
Zhou Siyue
The assignment given by Professor Ye
is out of my capability.
I won't help you.
Please.
No way.
Help me!
Only once!
Don't act like that!
Please! Only once!
Have you done the experimental demonstration?
Not yet.
Then in accordance with your thoughts in your mind,
write those codes down.
No need to read books?
It's of no use to read so many theories.
If you don't practice,
you cannot find the true question.
Write them down first.
What are you doing instead of solving the question?
I cannot help doing it.
Sorry.
What do you think of my drawing?
Better than solving the question.
Really?
I don't think it's as good as my drawings before.
Before?
What did you draw?
It's a secret!
As you wish.
Didn't you say it was a secret?
How could you tell me?
Anyway, I like you, and I like to draw.
They're not secrets anymore.
Ding Xian
Actually, I just hope
you can choose
what you really like to do.
I will.
So don't talk to me anymore.
I should try to solve the question.
Communication is forbidden.
Mr. Zhou
You've finished?
Finished?
Zero point.
Why?
What about the bugs of the information security?
The information holes are so obvious.
Didn't you notice them?
If someone from the tech company
gives you a task,
you will be sued now.
Didn't you tell me to write in this way?
So we've found the problem.
Redo it.
Zhou Siyue
I think now we're
just like when we were in senior high school.
When division of Arts and Sciences, you taught me mathematics.
You are just... like before.
How?
You're mean like before.
You're also the same.
You still don't make any progress.
According to your present professional level,
you should consider changing your major.
Don't be too harsh on me!
I'm only a freshman.
No one cares if you're a freshman or not.
They only know that you're a student from Huaqing University.
Besides,
it's you who must get in the scientific research group.
If you don't pass the assessment,
it's pretty normal.
Professor Ye is strict.
Besides, I also think
you don't need to get in the scientific research group.
Zhou Siyue. You really look down upon me!
Besides, I have you, such an expert!
I'm sure I'll pass it.
What do you mean?
I ask you for a favor, and you act like this?
Wait me for a while.
The university holds a fraternity for the freshman.
Are you going there with me?
No.
Zhou Siyue
It's not good if you keep like this.
Don't you have many
entertainments before?
Why do you stop chatting with others who are alive?
Do what you should do in every period,
so that you won't regret.
Boring.
Fine.
I should learn from you. I won't go there, either.
I'll go back to the laboratory.
Do what you should do. No regret.
Ding Xian
Where are you?
Are you okay?
Why are you hiding here stealthily?
Why are you so timid?
Who is timid?
Don't talk nonsense!
Didn't you leave? Why do you come back?
The power's off.
What if the data are missing?
Shouldn't I come back and check?
I'll go.
Didn't you say
that you wouldn't help her
after she got in the group?
What were you doing?
I didn't resist it.
What did I day?
You're so stubborn!
Eat your food!
Eat with me!
No. I won't.
If people are iron, food is steel.
You'll be hungry if you miss one meal.
You work and study every day,
and often do experiments late at night.
You should take care of your health.
You know?
How can you stay active if you don't eat?
Why do you act like my mom?
Come here. Good boy. Have a meal.
Come on. Come on!
The pork hock tastes good!
Do you have any problem with your brain recently?
What?
Chopsticks.
They're opposite down.
Professor Ye
Did I pass it?
Pretty good.
But there's another one
who used the same solution as you did.
You know who I'm talking about.
Professor Ye
It's true that I asked Zhou Siyue for help.
But, I…
You understand Zhou Siyue better than I do.
He has a great passion on scientific research.
And he can pass the passion
to others.
He's the one whom others want to chase after
but cannot be caught up with forever.
Ding Xian
You're very clever.
You should know what to do.
Chocolate! Let me eat one.
No way.
It's a present for someone else.
I'll buy it to you next time.
A present?
Is the robot
drawn for Zhou Siyue?
What's Zhou's feeling?
What do you mean?
You've been chasing him for such a long time.
If you two
are really good as what you said before,
he should have
expressed love to you now.
I didn't ask him to be my boyfriend.
Then what do you want from him?
I didn't mean it.
I just think you chased him so hard.
I feel pretty bad!
I think
being happy is the most important thing.
As long as you don't regret.
Okay. I'll go wash now.
Go to bed early.
Good night.
I don't care if you like Zhou Siyue or not.
But, Ding Xian,
I cannot feel your passion about the scientific research.
I don't know how much
you know about the prospect of the major.
I also don't know how you plan for
the future.
I just hope
before deciding to do scientific research,
you can think about it clearly.
You should be clear if Zhou Siyue is not here,
what on earth your choice is.
Ding Xian
Dong
Did you pass the exam set by Professor Ye?
Kind of.
Will you go abroad?
I'm still trying.
Actually, I always think
you're such a smart girl.
Why do you waste
your time on such kind of things?
What do you mean?
You're just like a tail of Zhou Siyue.
I really admire you.
You're able to give up so many things
for the person you like.
But I don't think it worth
doing it.
Dong
Whether it's worth or not isn't judged by
how much you paid out.
It's true that Zhou Siyue has marvelous
professional competence.
You are willing to
do anything you don't like for him,
but he will definitely not give up what he likes
for anyone else.
For example,
giving up going abroad for you.
It doesn't matter.
I don't expect him to do anything for me.
Then what if I tell you that
it was him who told Professor Ye
that you're not capable of doing scientific research?
It's not important.
Ding Xian
I'm sorry, President.
What did you just say?
I said thanks for
the task today.
It's okay.
Hello.
Hello, Zhou Siyue.
Where are you?
Do you have anything to tell me?
I knew you must be here!
There's another problem in the program.
Please help me check it.
Thanks.
What are you busy in doing?
You didn't reply to me on WeChat every time.
I was doing experiments.
But you shouldn't always be in the laboratory.
So boring!
Why don't you join in our Comics Club?
It's so fun!
Right. We recently received an invitation
of a drawing competition.
Drawing competition?
Right.
The winner can sign with
the Comics Press directly!
Did Ding Xian take part in it?
She?
Actually, I thought she was really talented.
If she took part in the competition,
she might get a reward.
But she refused.
She said she was too busy to take part in it.
I don't understand what a freshman like her
is busy in doing.
I've helped you revise it.
No other problems.
However,
if you deliberately modify the program,
I won't help you.
You found it anyway.
Okay. If you have nothing else to do, just leave.
Okay. Let me treat you a meal.
Why are you touching my thing?
What?
Isn't it just chocolate?
Why did you say like that?
The chocolate is given by someone else!
Why are you so fierce to me?
I didn't know it was given by someone else!
I'll just buy you
the same kind of chocolate!
So mean!
Thanks.
Did you finish making tools?
Almost done, President.
Wait me for a while.
Ding Xian, what's wrong with you today?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
Are you going to have a rest?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
It's almost finished.
I won't retard the rehearsal tomorrow.
Okay.
President. Does Xing Lufei come here?
They're asking for costumes again.
Wait a minute.
I'll call her.
Okay.
What's the hurry? Here I come.
Great! Xing.
How are the costumes prepared?
They've decided. We only need another two.
Look at my chart.
Check what steps haven't been finished.
Xing, where is the chocolate from?
Zhou Siyue gave it to me.