[English subtitles are available]
Why did you pour the tea?
Follow me.
Master.
Why don't you allow Eleven to go enjoy the music?
It's rare that Nanxiao's musicians give performances.
She poured a pot of tea.
I'm punishing her by asking her to copy tea names.
Master.
Are you kidding her
because she can't speak?
Famous tea is expensive.
But she wasted it at will.
Shouldn't she be punished?
Do you feel grieved?
You should know the value of a cup of tea
can afford days
and even a month of food for common people.
You like to drink tea.
So I bought you tea.
But I don't want you to be arrogant
and unaware of how hard common people's life is.
You should cultivate virtue by staying thrift.
You are the future Crown Princess.
You should set an example.
What's wrong?
Jr. Prince of Nanchen's disciple
should remember it, but it has nothing to do with the name of Crown Princess.
I'm willing to be punished.
Most of the tea comes from Nanxiao
and the Jiduo Dynasty.
I handled that from the Jiduo Dynasty.
Wait. Let me find it out.
This one.
Yes, that's it.
Look at the words on it.
Abstruse writing.
But it says cinnamon.
Cinnamon is not tea?
Then where's the tea then?
When did you learn Jiduo's language?
When I went to the temple
to pray for you guys these two years,
I met monks from
the Jiduo Dynasty
and I learned it from them.
Since you can learn their language,
you must often go to the temple.
I would go there when I miss you guys.
No wonder Xie Yun always became wordy
when he went to the battlefield.
He said there is a little sister
waiting for us at home
and we should not lose our lives.
He knows you best.
The four of them are guards from the imperial palace.
They follow to protect me.
Zhou Tianxing.
Feng Qiao.
Greet Your Highness.
I know you.
You are a meritorious general following Jr. Prince of Nanchen
to suppress the Six-garrison Rebellion.
Where is my uncle?
Master is in the camp.
He left us to entertain Your Highness.
Uncle really loves soldiers as if they were his children.
It seems he is going to spend
the New Year with generals and soldiers.
Is there any scenic place
in his mansion?
I don't want her
to feel chained when seeing me for the first time.
There is a garden
with pavilion, pond and beautiful scenery.
Shiyi often practices instrument there.
Then I'll go there.
People in the mansion
are talking about Prince of Guangling.
They said he has been good-looking since he was a child
and he is famous outside the palace.
What they said is true.
He is a quite handsome man.
Why should we judge people by appearance?
Good look is not a disadvantage.
The emperor of Xiyan State a hundred years ago,
Murong Chong,
was imprisoned as a toy-boy and suffered humiliation when young
because he looked even
better than women.
Isn't it because of good look?
It was really a pity for you
to lose ability to speak these years.
No matter he is your future husband
or just a guest from afar,
you should show hospitality.
You are more like the descendant from the Cui family than I am.
How I wish
you were me.
Here is my respect, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
It's not Central State here.
No need to be polite.
Stand up.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I finally don't need to
see you through portrait.
In Central State, I often heard that
Nanchen Royal Mansion is magnificent.
But I didn't think so.
Now when I'm here,
I realize it is true.
Your Highness, don't be misled by the public.
For what?
My master is not extravagant.
But as the prince guarding the borders,
his residence must be magnificent
to win the hearts of the people.
You are afraid that I will take him
as a disloyal minister like other princes?
I dare not think so.
I'm not that blind and stupid.
Other royal families and fierce generals
might be rebellious
or wait for an opportunity
to rebel
when they take control of
thousands of military soldiers.
But uncle won't.
Beichen is so lucky to have him.
It's against the rules.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I'm just caring about you.
Show me your hand.
There are doctors in the mansion.
I'll see them by myself.
Let the imperial doctor see her hand.
Now!
Yes.
How did you get hurt once you met him?
Is it an arrangement of the fate?
He was closely surrounded by
four guards with knives.
Even the maids and chamberlains had left,
they guarded him also.
Is he still afraid there would be
assassins in Nanchen Royal Mansion?
That's the strange point.
Your Highness.
How is she?
She is all right. Don't worry.
As soon as I saw her,
I had a mood
that I can't tell.
Although I'm have been castrated,
I'm still human.
Since I'm human, I know emotions.
She is different from that on the portrait.
She won't stand still to let me see her.
She will be afraid
and then get away from me.
Uncle is not in the mansion.
We have to find a good reason to see him.
Today is your birthday.
What's your wish?
Let me tell you what gifts I've prepared for you.
Your Highness is a guest.
No need to spend money on me.
Here is my respect, Your Highness.
You two generals finally came.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Your Highness, what can we do for you?
I've prepared good wine and food.
I want to go to the army barracks with you
to celebrate Eleven's birthday.
The mansion is like a family.
I think
Eleven must want to celebrate her birthday
with her family.
But the Royal Army has strict rules.
Outsiders are not allowed to enter the camp without permission.
Am I an outsider?
I mean those without military status.
What if I have an imperial edict
to reward the army on behalf of His Majesty?
In this case,
I'll make an arrangement right now.
I just wanted to give you a birthday present.
I didn't know you have an edict.
I'm sorry for embarrassing you.
Never mind.
It's okay because it is you.
Your Highness.
The poison has been completely cleared.
Master.
Eleven comes.
Isn't she in the mansion?
Prince of Guangling brought her here.
He said he wanted to hold a birthday party for her
and took this opportunity
to reward the army on behalf of His Majesty.
Let's go and welcome them.
Uncle.
Prince of Guangling.
Are you injured?
Xie Yun, take Eleven to see the military doctor.
Yes.
Prince of Guangling.
Take a break in the tent.
No hurry.
It's rare to enter the army barracks.
I wonder if you are free
to show me around.
All right.
Come with me.
Show me your hand.
Master would be worried
if the military doctor didn't check your hand.
Although imperial doctors
have high official titles and read a lot,
they have less experience than
our military doctors.
I'm flattered.
They have already used
good medicine for treating wound.
But I have
folk prescription
which is better than this medicine.
I'll get it right away.
How did he treat you?
With courtesy and integrity.
You are shy.
I've brought Tusu Wine.
Okay.
Since you don't want to say,
forget my question.
Be careful.
Place everything well.
Yes.
It smells good.
It's all your favorite dishes.
Master, I've brought Tusu.
Tusu?
Dinner prepared tonight
looks a little shabbier
compared with Tusu, Xie Yun.
I'll kill some fat sheep.
Give me a knife.
Here.
This cup of Tusu
is for our guest from afar,
Prince of Guangling.
Thank you, uncle.
I also take this cup of wine
as a toast to all of you on behalf of His Majesty.
I hope the general can win every battle,
so the emperor doesn't have to spend money on building the Great Wall.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Thank you, Prince of Guangling.
This toast is for
the generals and soldiers
who sacrificed in the rebellion suppression.
Happy New Year.
I hope there would be
no flames of war in our country.
May the people of Beichen live, work and multiply
in peace and contentment
within the wide territory of the country.
May the people of Beichen live, work and multiply
in peace and contentment
within the wide territory of the country.
Finally, I want to say that,
it is Eleven's birthday today.
I hope
she could be happy every day here.
Eleven.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, Master.
Okay.
Everybody, sit down.
Here, Chen.
Sit here.
Okay.
Thank you, adoptive father.
Eleven, who is that?
It's the military
advisor, Xie Chong.
Your Highness.
The climate of the Western State is different from that of the Central State.
Please drink this bowl of medicine while it is warm.
Rest early.
Cheers. Cheers. Cheers.
Eleven.
Feng.
You...
I can speak.
Great, great!
If aunt knows
you can speak again,
she would be quite happy.
All right, stop standing.
Sit down and talk.
Here.
Hey,
make room for me.
Come on.
Xiaoyu.
Everybody.
Today is my sister's birthday.
And she finally
can speak.
I take this opportunity
to propose a toast to you all!
Cheers.
Cheers. Cheers.
All the way here,
I often hear a passage.
I specially recited it
and want to read it for you.
What is it?
Beautiful bones are rare in the world.
There are people who have such bones, but not beautiful skin,
or have beautiful skin, but not bones.
And Jr. Prince of Nanchen
is the only one
who has both beautiful bones and skin.
Common people said
he is rarer than emperors.
Yeah, yeah.
Xiaoyu,
there are outsiders in the army.
Don't talk nonsense.
Are there any outsiders in the army?
Prince of Guangling is right here.
Cui Feng, how is Shouyang?
Shouyang is all right.
But soldiers are missing you
and looking forward to your coming.
Why are you hiding there?
I come to apologize.
Come and sit down first.
What wrong did you do?
I know the military rules are strict.
But I didn't stop Prince of Guangling.
He is a prince.
But you are just a minister's daughter.
How could you stop him?
But we are all happy that
we can celebrate your birthday together
in the army barracks.
Here you are, Pepper Wine.
I'll drink alone?
OK, I'll accompany you.
Tusu bids farewell to the old and Pepper Wine welcomes the new.
Let's take it for celebrating the New Year in advance.
Are you afraid of getting drunk?
God.
This is cup of Pepper Wine
is not for future
or wealth.
I only wish it could bless master
and senior brothers
and senior sisters safety
every year.
Good news.
Where is master's good news?
It has been two months.
Why hasn't there been good news yet?
It's never been that long.
Where are the six garrisons?
I don't even know them.
Where can I find master
if he dies?
The six garrisons are in the north,
north of the Central State
and northeast of the Western State.
If he dies,
he wouldn't want you to go find him.
He will be buried
where he dies.
You haven't slept?
You will be buried
where you die?
Why don't you let me find you?
Once I die,
everything I leave will be empty.
Even if you find and see me,
you would feel nothing
but sad.
Sleep tight.
Master.
Have you seen Eleven?
She is in my tent.
She stays here so late?
She occupies your tent.
Why don't you stay with her?
What about you?
I'll just walk around.
Mind your business.
Do you...
You used to sleep in master's study
when you felt tired after practicing instrument in the past.
Only you
dared to do this.
Xiaoyu.
What's wrong?
Where have you been these two years?
Master, Tianxing
and I went to the North.
After pacifying rebellions in the six garrisons,
we went to Pingzhou and Shanggu.
Xie Yun
and Feng Qiao are in the West.
Your brother is in Shouyang.
We seldom meet.
My brother
is going home, too.
Then we won't talk about him.
I remember.
I have something for you.
This is a soft armor
a princess wore before.
I was afraid I would lose it,
so I wore it all the time.
It's for you.
I'm not going to the battlefield.
I can't use this.
Take it.
Don't refuse.
Everything on me
is all from master.
I have nothing myself.
It's not easy for me
to get such a treasure.
You must take it.
In my heart,
you are the princess
of our Nanchen Royal Mansion.
This suits you.
What's good to be a princess?
They are royal and noble.
Everyone envies them.
But I don't.
I envy you.
Envy me?
You joined the army with Tianxing in early youth
and suffered a lot with master.
But I just came to enjoy the fruit
and contribute nothing.
Actually, we're all late.
In master's most difficult time,
he got it through by himself.
You know how many
troops the late emperor gave him back then?
In those years,
the imperial clan took control of the army to protect their own interests
and refused to give up any troops.
When master left the Central State,
he had cavalry of only 20,000 people
and infantry of 10.000 people.
How could he win with such few soldiers?
He brought a box of official seals
and an edict with him
when leaving the capital.
He could be able to appoint
any official below the sixth grade along the way.
Master went all the way south
and used these official seals to recruit soldiers and horses
and formed a hasty army.
He made the name of Jr. Prince of Nanchen
resounded all over the world
by successively winning battles
and recovering territories.
Tianxing and I
were orphans escaping
to the temple.
After master recovered the lost land,
we decided to join the army together.
The Jr. Prince of Nanchen you want to see
is him.
Your Highness.
These two children had been yelling to
see you outside the military camp.
What's up?
Join the army.
You look young.
Why do you want to join the army?
You're not old.
I'm not young.
I just look young.
You know what?
Your Highness looks
similar to your age,
but he's been through many battles.
I'm not afraid of many soldiers
but no one will join the army.
The Royal Army will return to the Western State tomorrow.
I'll give you a night to think about it.
If you are not afraid of death,
just follow me.
Since then,
many years have passed.
I think
we would be killed on the battlefield
or die of old age in the barracks.
What can you do when you are old?
Feed and wash horses.
Or clean the barracks.
As long as I can stay in the army,
I can do anything.
Yeah
As long as you are here.
Let's find something to eat.
Over there.
Let the cook
make some hot for General Hong.
Yes.
Wait.
General Hong
is a bit shy.
Tell the cook that
it's because I'm hungry.
Yes, Your Highness.
Do you all have wives and children?
Will anyone bury you if you are dead?
I dare not to get married.
I don't think I have tomorrow.
Even if you want to get married,
they dare not marry their daughter to you.
Xie Yun
always looks for food at night.
He told me
the cook always secretly
leaves some pancakes for him.
Why is there nothing left today?
General Hong.
I patrol with Shiyi tonight
and heard some noise here.
So I came to have a look.
His Highness is hungry.
He asked us to cook some food.
If you like,
I can cook some for you as well.
I'm okay.
But I'm afraid Shiyi will be hungry.
So you can make cook some as well for her.
Send it to my tent,
no, to the main tent later.
OK.
General Cui.
Who's inside?
It's His Highness.
He used to come to light a fire
before a war.
But I've never
heard of an expedition this time.
Go get my reed flute.
Yes.
I aroused your interest?
No one in Shouyang understands me.
It's rare to come back.
I want to play a song with you.
Okay.
Our first Confucian general in Shouyang.
Who said this?
Who do you think would say this?
It must be General Hong.
You are awake.
Xiaoyu.
Who plays the music?
Master likes to play music before war.
It's rare that he plays music not for war
but for pleasing himself.
Master.
General Hong.
You got up late today.
It's Shiyi's fault.
Then I'll leave her to you.
In this camp,
only you two are idle.
Then I'll train the soldiers.
I'm idle?
Scouting camp.
Military training.
Yes.
How did you two take the swords?
Take them well.
Line up.
Yes.
They seem to be afraid of Xiaoyu.
In the barracks,
it's much harder for a female general
to convince soldiers
than the male generals.
I'm sorry for
losing my courtesy last night.
Never mind.
Let me show you around
the barracks.
Pay attention to the action.
When the army comes to a place,
Xiaoyu's scouting camp
will choose a place for the army to be stationed.
The infantry will cut down trees and build wooden walls
to form a military camp.
Tighten your thighs and clamp the horse's back.
Stop shivering.
Look at you.
Get up.
Yes.
Why are there wooden horses in the stable?
It's much more expensive to raise a war horse
than raising a soldier.
So when they train at ordinary times,
they all use fake horses.
Xiaoyu said
our dynasty conquers land with cavalry.
War horses are the most precious.
Continue.
I'll eat if you don't eat.
Master.
What's wrong?
The food is not to your taste?
I...
He acts as if he was in the Buddhist Tower of the mansion.
He is blind to kindness.
You can't
look down on him.
He used to be
a man of letters and martial arts in Nanxiao.
He once conquered
a galloping war horse alone.
He has much better martial arts than you do.
No need to mention the past.
Let me try your martial arts again.
I admit defeat.
You can't just admit defeat through words.
You have to fight with me.
My apprentice
used to live along the river for half a month
to learn to swim.
You have nothing else to do.
Besides chanting,
you can do some exercise.