When I saw my wife for the first time,
she was like Kim Hee Sun.
She was charmingly pure and alluring.
Not only she has dark and long hair,
but she has a fair skin too.
Honestly, I'm a fan of Kim Hee Sun.
But she's more beautiful than her.
Excuse me...
Are you Choi So Hae?
Goodness.
It's so bright.
It was already ten years ago.
Everyone goes through a burnout period,
and actually, that's because of problems they faced.
The problems they faced?
Jin Mook.
Did your wife changed compared from ten years ago?
No.
You said she's not much different from ten years ago,
but Jin Mook, you must have felt tired of it now.
If that's the case, whose problem is that?
Is it because your eyeglasses were too familiar to her?
Or is it because your wife hasn't changed at all?
Then, what should I do?
You need to exert effort.
But how?
So Hae.
Talking about one's own matter could be difficult,
especially between those modern
people who lack communication.
My role is to only listen to someone.
Not to judge you.
It's just fine,
so feel free to speak.
My husband...
...has Kim Hee Sun.
[ Kim Hee Sun ]
[ My Husband Has Kim Hee Sun ]
The first time I felt it strange...
...was three months ago.
Welcome home.
What did you do?
You watched TV?
What's that?
[ Screenwriter, Kim Joo Hoo ]
It's your birthday, you know.
Today?
Who?
Every day with you...
It's your birthday, for me.
You could have just bought some meat.
Hwan Hee,
you feel good that I came home early, right?
Yes.
If I eat with both of you,
will your Mom like it?
Mom will like it even more.
Wow! Almost all are side dishes.
I could be healthy with this, am I not?
Let's eat dishes...
...with vegetables together so we can maintain our health.
Yes.
What are you doing?
You're smiling?
Why you're like this suddenly?
You're asking because you don't know!?
I'm really sorry.
For what?
For everything.
What everything?
Just everything.
So what do you mean!?
I got it, so I'm sorry.
I told you, for what!?
Let's just forget this.
What do you mean!?
Every day with you...
It's your birthday, for me.
Women's intuition has always been scary.
If not that he cheated on you,
don't tell me,
he said anything offensive?
"Every day with you..."
"It's your birthday, for me."
Oh my goodness.
How was that?
From what I think...
What is it?
I'm 99% certain that he cheated on you.
Indeed.
He's just the same as Chul Min's father.
Once men start doing that,
they will often do that in the future.
They suddenly become better towards you.
They suddenly became polite towards your family.
For the last time,
try to confirm it.
Usually, Hwan Hee's dad doesn't
lock the phone's screen, right?
Right.
Just in case,
if you were able to unlock its screen,
you'll become totally certain.
Eat this and cheer up.
It starts right now.
No, I won't eat. I don't have appetite.
Don't be like that. Just eat a little.
I won't.
I said just eat.
I said I won't!
All right, listen up.
First of all, you need definite proof.
After checking your husband's phone messages and call history,
take those with you.
These proofs will play a useful role
when you make choices for the future.
First,
the phone's password.
My birthday.
Hwan Hee's birthday.
Though it won't be the case, I'll try my birthday.
My phone number won't be tailed.
0000.
[ Please enter it after 30 seconds. ]
Gosh.
Damn it!
Gosh!
What are you doing?
It's just what you have seen.
I just want to...
Don't go over here!
I want to be alone.
I just want you to give my phone.
I see... Your phone.
Sorry.
My phone's battery is almost dead.
Okay, here. I'll give your phone.
Can you unlock your phone's password?
I want to make a call.
Use the landline.
You still can't unlock it?
Right.
Then, try to use this method.
Hwan Hee.
You see,
don't you find reading books boring?
No. I find it fun.
I see.
Even so,
when you were still little,
you just have fun playing games.
Playing games all the time is not that fun.
I'm just saying playing too much of those is not good.
Honestly, there are many advantages in playing games.
A moderate amount of playing
games improves brain activity.
You can also move your fingers.
It also improves your creativity,
it stimulates your nerve cells.
I mean...
You'll have lots of ideas
spending time in playing games.
Mom.
Yes?
Do you want to play a game?
No.
It's just that I hope you'll play games too.
Fine.
I don't even think about playing games.
It's making me crazy.
Dad.
I want to play a game on your phone.
Kim Hee Sun?
Kim Hee Sun...
Damn it!
Kim Hee Sun!?
That's unbelievable.
How could every man think the same?
He keeps saying that Kim Hee Sun is beautiful.
She's like the barmaid.
What?
Kim Hee Sun.
The first beautiful woman in our country.
I heard that on bars,
they used her name as the stage name.
How did you know that?
My husband...
...has Kim Hee Sun too.
That bastard!
But,
if that's the case,
would it just be fine?
What?
I mean,
they have always been very nice to guests,
so they won't really attempt to cheat.
At best, they just want to get some air.
You wench, seriously!
Why!?
I cheated!
Hey, why are you like that?
Have you ever seen someone like this from the start?
It all starts from cheating,
then one eventually disappears
and left his or her children.
It's like that.
Pull yourself together, wench!
If not because of Hwan Hee,
I should have already divorced with him.
Having a marriage life without trust...
...is just meaningless like an empty shell.
Then...
I only have two options.
Whether secretly prepare for another marriage after divorce,
or else,
I'm going to cheat on him.
Both will just make your family get shattered.
Not at all.
I'll cheat in order to protect my family.
Those are my only two options.
Jin Mook,
Talking about one's own matter could be difficult,
especially between those modern
people who lack communication.
My role is to only listen to someone.
It's just fine,
so feel free to speak.
My wife...
...has another man.
Every day with you...
It's your birthday, for me.
You could have just bought some meat.
She was quite embarrassed about it.
It was good from the start.
But why?
Wow! Almost all are side dishes.
Let's eat dishes with vegetables together
so we can maintain our health.
What are you doing?
She suddenly started to lose her temper.
What did I said?
What do you call a person who's lying?
A bad person.
Did you really just wanted to play games on my phone?
Mom told me not to say it.
Your wife is addicted on playing games?
Not that.
When I was dating her,
if I mention a character of the game,
her expression suddenly changes.
Anyways,
my brain gets drained out...
...trying to look for a desirable reason.
Dad, please help me in my English homework.
Well...
Just ask your Mom for help.
She said she has headache
and told me to go to you.
My head is in more pain than her.
Just go and ask your Mom for help.
Got it?
Do something else first.
The only reason to let time pass by...
...is that I, who dominates everyone's eyes,
am called by the world.
It's a man's intuition.
It has always been accurate.
She's cheating on me, right?
Right.
It's exactly the same as my wife did.
Have you unlocked your wife's phone screen?
No.
Then, after you head home now,
don't do other things.
Try decoding your wife's phone password.
If you have unlocked the screen,
then you'll be certain.
That will be certain.
But what if her phone's screen is locked?
You have to unlock it.
No matter what, you must have to get proof.
Let's try it until the end.
First of all...
0000.
0000?
[ Lee Dong Sung ]
I have fun today. I'll see you next time.
Hey, keep your heads up. Okay?
The start goes right now.
I'm not craving for it now.
Look at you.
You have to hold on with the alcohol's power.
You can't do anything without this.
I hold on with this too.
You must definitely drink. It's all right.
How can I drink at this situation?
Auntie.
Please give us a bottle of soju.
Coming.
But,
you see, there's something I'm curious about.
women can tolerate men's cheating,
so men must definitely endure women's cheating too.
My Grandpa was also like that.
My Grandma did it.
An eye for an eye. A tooth for a tooth.
So you mean...
You're going to cheat on her too?
You?
What are you doing?
You're already awake?
You're making me confused.
Huh?
Shall I send you to the kindergarten today?
Wait a second. You have to write XX here.
What else can I do in this situation?
I still need to exert more effort.
For goodness sake.
There are some things that cannot be achieved, punk.
What are you talking about?
There are three things that
you can't restrain yourself from doing it.
You can't do it, no matter what.
First,
holding back your shit.
Second, watching porn.
Third,
restore the broken relationship
between a husband and wife.
You can never cope up from those.
Then, what do you want me to do?
You want me...
...to get a divorce?
You have to take a strong medicine.
A strong medicine?
What do you mean?
You startled me.
You're late.
Why not take a seat?
It's just.
What did you do?
I watched a movie.
I wanted to ask whom she have met with,
but I couldn't dare to say it.
My pride could get hurt.
Starting next month,
let's use our own money for the expenses.
What?
I said to use our own money.
I mean, what are you talking about?
I said that I'll manage our finances from now on.
As you wish.
Even if you want to have a divorce.
Divorce?
If not because of Hwan Hee,
I should have already divorced with her.
Having a marriage life without trust...
...is just meaningless like an empty shell.
Then, what are you going to do?
I only have two options.
Whether I'll manage our finances,
or just let those to be wasted.
Both will just make your family get shattered.
Not at all.
If I were in charge of the finances,
it's most likely that I'll be able to protect my family.
I have to have money in order to cheat.
Those are my only two options.
I became hesitant.
Thinking that I really wanted to cheat...
...so I have to protect my family...
...is just making me worried that it will hurt me.
I'll feel shameless to see my daughter Hwan Hee.
It's not an easy matter, indeed.
Someone within the family is cheating.
I realized I want to bury it in my heart,
but I felt getting so angry again.
I kept picturing out my husband and Kim Hee Sun...
...having a good time together.
But still,
you want to protect your family.
But,
this person just keep adding fuel to the fire.
Just go and ask your Mom for help.
Do something else first.
The only reason to let time pass by...
...is that I, who dominates everyone's eyes,
am called by the world.
In the end,
I followed my friend on a meet-up.
She is my friend, Chae So Hee.
She is a single mom for almost a year.
That's why, she came here
to be in a relationship with someone.
Say hello to them.
Nice to meet you all.
Welcome.
Oh, Hwan Hee.
I guess I'll go home late.
Just ask your Dad to buy delicious foods for you.
Okay. I got it.
I'm sorry.
Your phone is very old.
I didn't expect to see it from someone right now.
Nice to meet you.
Pardon?
He was a pretty good-looking man.
We had nice conversations.
He majored in Western arts.
I felt that he has a profound insight too.
And...
And what?
He attentively listened to what I have said.
I like paintings with many eaves.
Have you been to Karat?
No.
The scenery there is like this.
Please wait a minute.
I just coincidentally gave you this.
You don't really have to do this.
Goodness.
I don't know what to say. It's weird.
You should really want to see her.
I really want to.
I have fun today.
Well, So Hee.
You see...
She will return to Korea next month,
want to see her together with me?
Pardon?
Her name is Hwan Hee, right?
It would be great if she joins with us.
Both of you have daughter.
You're both related in many aspects.
You liked the same book too.
Do you feel discomfort somewhere?
My heart trembled.
I mean, but you know what,
when I thought of Hwan Hee,
I suddenly woke up from my senses.
I wanted to protect my family,
not the one who'll broke it.
so I hoped that my husband could unlock it as soon as possible,
with my phone's password, 0000.
I hoped that he will pull himself together...
...and that he will change.
So, did he changed?
I guess so.
He started doing things that
he never done for the family before.
Even if you knew that he's cheating,
he has already made plans ahead.
He seems to be cheating on me.
He never mentioned about that matter?
Yes.
You're not even angry about it?
You must totally became indifferent.
You think so?
Yes.
[ You damn bastard ]
Do you think he'll get better and change himself?
If he wants to become better,
he must be totally honest with me.
My husband really likes her.
He must have totally fell in love with Kim Hee Sun.
But he felt sorry towards me.
That's why, he did the household chores.
Yes, sir.
At the pub on the intersection?
I'll go there right away.
Yes. Okay, sir.
My boss said that he was near on our place.
Hwan Hee, I'll go out for a moment.
Okay, Dad.
It's all because of her.
Kim Hee Sun.
You're so mean.
I heard of a young woman's voice.
My intuition tells me.
That it was her daughter.
Kim Hee Sun could be a single mother.
Or she could be divorced.
No.
It's a woman's intuition.
That bad woman must have a daughter.
Oh, I beg your pardon.
I'm certain.
It must be that bad woman's daughter.
That couldn't be the case.
I mean, how could you just conclude it
based on your intuition?
The more you start thinking pessimistically,
you'll be able to do do nothing.
Well, I was just...
Just have a positive thinking.
For Hwan Hee's sake.
Honestly speaking,
there are no men who don't cheat
on their wife these days.
Just be more understanding.
You'll feel more at ease.
You're a bit strange.
Was it obvious?
I mean...
To tell you the truth,
I have reconciled with Chul Min's father.
You startled me.
You're late today.
That day, I felt something different.
What did you do?
Looks that he would like to ask
about the man I've met before.
I watched a movie.
I felt that I was right.
Let's tell the truth...
...and ask for the truth.
But...
Starting next month,
let's use our own money for the expenses.
What?
I said to use our own money.
What are you talking about?
I said that I'll manage our finances from now on.
I was dumbfounded.
Unsatisfied from cheating on me,
so he wanted me to use our own money.
As you wish.
Even if you want to have a divorce.
Divorce?
I have doubted him.
Use this.
No. Let me pay for it.
No way.
It's me who asked first to watch a movie.
Please just use this.
Dear customer, your credit card is over the limit.
I see.
Please use this.
This card has been deactivated.
Oh, you can just use this.
Compared to my tough life after getting married,
I'm in favor of living comfortably.
What is she saying!?
You have to live well.
Get up.
Just tell it right away.
Get up!
Speak out.
What are you doing?
Didn't I told you?
I said that I'll manage our finances from now on.
I said it too.
That I'll divorce you.
So what?
What?
So what do you want to say?
Let's divorce.
Fine. Let's do that.
I have tried my best to not to go beyond that,
but in the end, that's what happened.
A person's effort could be at its limits.
Thank you for all this time.
Then, when are you going to do it?
He said that we'll go to the court next Monday.
It's...
...really over now.
Want me to prescribe you medicine?
It's okay.
I can manage myself.
So Hee.
For the last time,
how about talking with him sincerely?
Your husband must be in a situation.
Maybe,
there could be...
...a thick wall that's between us.
It could have started long...
...before this happened.
Dear Kim Hee Sun Unni...
Aunt?
No, it's Unni.
Hello.
I'm Kim Hwan Hee, a 7 year-old girl living in Paju.
There's something I would like to say to you,
so I am writing this letter.
My father's name is Kim Jin Mook.
Because of a woman, my parents got in a quarrel often.
It's all because of her.
Kim Hee Sun.
You're so mean.
My mom had badmouthed you.
[ Greek and Roman Mythology ]
Because of Zeus's adultery, Hera was totally vexed,
to the point of her being called the goddess of jealousy.
The fight between my parents has evolved into a battle.
And also...
Say it.
What are you doing?
I said that I'll manage our finances from now on.
I said it too. That I'll divorce you.
So what do you want to say?
Let's divorce.
Fine. Let's do that.
Divorce, huh.
The saddest moment in my life
is when my parents have divorced.
Why do you find it the saddest moment?
Between my mother and father,
I have to choose one of them.
I can't sleep well day by day.
I'm a fan of yours.
Please break up with my Dad.
Thank you.
By the way.
And besides, you are really beautiful.
Why?
You're anticipating a letter from someone?
Yes.
Really?
Which room number do you live?
I live in Room 503.
Wait a second.
Goodness. What to do?
There's nothing for Room 503.
Have a good day.
Okay.
Mom.
You're up?
Yes.
Hwan Hee.
I'll leave you first to your Grandma
early tomorrow morning.
Can you stay with her just for few days?
Why?
Me and your dad has something to do.
What is that?
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
Yes, mother.
You can just come here right away.
Okay.
They are almost here.
Hwan Hee, are you ready?
That's why,
because of Kim Hee Sun,
your parents are going to have a divorce,
thus, you're looking for her.
Yes.
They'll really have a divorce because of her?
So Uncle, can you please keep this a secret?
How do you know where Kim Hee Sun usually goes?
[ Kim Hee Sun ]
[ Taxi fare, 58,000 won ]
We're here.
When I searched online,
I found out that the taxi fare from
Paju to Gangnam is 58,000 won,
but I just exactly have 57,800 won right now.
What can I do?
Pardon?
You don't have to pay me.
Uncle, you have to make money too.
It's not good to hear that
our economy is in a bad state.
But instead,
be sure to stop your parents from having a divorce.
Promise me.
All right.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Where are you going?
I want to meet Kim Hee Sun.
You made an appointment with her?
No.
You came here without it and alone?
Yes.
I thought there's something
going on with my dad and her.
Wait a second.
Yes. There's someone who's looking for Kim Hee Sun.
Yes.
I see. She's just a kid.
Okay.
What to do?
She's not in the office right now.
When will she be here?
I'm not sure.
She may be at her home.
Her home?
Any place you know where she probably goes?
No.
I tried contacting her, but there's no answer.
Have you tried contacting Ji Hyo's family?
Yes, but they said they haven't met her.
By chance, did you find something strange with your child?
Why a young child like her fled out?
There's nothing really serious.
Uncle,
those under the age of 7...
...can take a free ride on the subway train, right?
Yes.
You're 7 years old?
But where is Seongbuk-dong?
Why?
Want to eat some dumplings?
Well, not at all.
But which way shall I go to Seongbuk-dong?
Seongbuk-dong?
Where at Seongbuk-dong?
To where Kim Hee Sun lives.
What?
Grandma, which way is Seongbuk-dong?
Seongbuk-dong?
It's over there.
I'm finally here.
Who is that?
I'm already here, though.
Kid.
Hey, kid.
Unni...
What's wrong?
Can you please break up with my Dad?
But,
did she really looked for Kim Hee Sun, right?
Why ask if you know that?
You know it?
You keep calling her name every day,
even in actual.
What do you mean in actual?
You've cheated with her!
What?
Stop pretending.
Do you think I don't know?
I've seen everything on your phone.
About Kim Hee Sun.
You just looked at the name,
not on the phone number, didn't you?
What?
It's your phone number.
I said it's yours.
You've been doing your best,
so I changed your contact name into Kim Hee Sun.
This is from a famous American psychiatrist
and psychologist named Wilton Erikson...
[ The person's first name was altered ]
...who developed the treatment.
I often recommend it to those husbands
who are in a languish state.
Good results have been confirmed many times.
From now on,
whenever your wife makes a phone call,
and when Kim Hee Sun's name popped up,
you will think about her and your wife at the same time.
Even if you don't call and
already got used to hearing it,
just when it comes up,
you will get hypnotized from it.
[ Kim Hee Sun ]
My wife is Kim Hee Sun.
Kim Hee Sun is inside of me.
[ Kim Hee Sun ]
[ You damn bastard ]
So are you cheating on me?
You've gone out with that jerk Lee Dong Sung!
How could I cheat on you?
I've been doing my best for my daughter.
Anyways, you have met with him.
Right. We have met.
But,
nothing happened.
How could I believe you?
Try to think of it.
if I have cheated on you,
do you think I'll save my phone password as 0000!?
It's really Kim Hee Sun.
Thank you so much.
I'm truly grateful. I don't know to repay you.
I'm truly grateful.
Hwan Hee has worried a lot.
That you two will have to have a divorce because of me.
There's really nothing on between the two of you?
That's right.
You're serious, aren't you?
There's really nothing going on with us.
I have promised to Hwan Hee.
Shall we have some wine?
Well, if you want to.
So you were not really in a relationship.
For goodness sake!
You were not in a relationship at all.
Thank you so much, Kim Hee Sun Unni.
[ Kim Hee Sun ]
[ My Husband Has Kim Hee Sun ]
[ Thank you to Kim Hee Sun for the special participation. ]
Transcriptions (and some translations) by: void_spell