[ Peach syrup, 1,000 ml ]
[ Peach syrup, 700 ml ]
One day, my ear has suddenly started to bleed.
[ Woman With Bleeding Ears ]
It had started on that day.
Hello.
There will be a fire inspection,
so an alarm will sound later.
Please don't be surprised, everyone.
[ Screenwriter, Baek In Ah ]
With the thunderous noise from the sky coming,
it has started thereon.
Ma'am, are you okay?
At first, I was shocked so I went for a checkup.
There were no abnormalities found.
You're on good condition.
Just in case, so I underwent for a CT scan...
It's clear.
It's just normal.
[ Neuropsychiatry ]
Your ear keeps bleeding?
Then, you must consult with an otolaryngologist.
Why come here?
Gosh. Won't you keep quiet?!
I want to go home!
Just go back on your own, then!
No.
- Why won't you listen?
- I want to go home!
Be quiet!
I didn't expect the sound's harshness would be so strong.
I'm going home.
Ms. Kim, what are you doing?
Yes, Ma'am.
Why are you blocking your ears inside the office?
Is this place a library?
That is...
My ear has bled again.
Does it keep bleeding?
Yes.
Why on earth it's like that?
Have you went to a hospital?
Yes, but they concluded it's on good condition.
Oh my! What shall we do with that?
I mean, our eyes shed tears,
our nose could get runny and get nosebleed,
but for ears, it's only earwax though.
Would someone like that?
That's what I mean.
Does the bleeding make it hurt?
Yes.
It's somehow painful.
When on earth did that started, huh?
Have you experienced it before?
Yes, one day...
I guess I have experienced this a week ago.
What's this?
What's going on?
Is it because you've caught up smog from China?
No way.
Then, why? What's the reason, huh?
Why? Why? Why?!
That is...
If I keep hearing things I don't like,
my ear starts to bleed.
Oh my!
Really?!
No, Ma'am.
But the thing is...
Well, I'm not yet totally sure of that.
Right. That probably must be.
That could happens if someone is sensitive.
It's not fine for me though.
Okay.
Then, just get back to work.
I'm going to grab some coffee.
I mean, Ma'am...
I feel something is wrong.
Hey, are you okay?
About what?
Ms. Im told me something about you.
If you keep hearing things you don't like,
your ear starts to bleed.
She told everyone to be more careful about you.
What's the point of talking about that to her?
You should just roughly respond.
I mean, she keeps disturbing me.
It's now my calm dinner.
When you hate to see me and decided to leave,
That's what I thought.
I'll quietly let you go.
I'll pluck an armful of azaleas...
...in the Yaksan hills at Yongbyun.
When you hate to see me and decided to leave,
I'll quietly let you go.
Can he understand my situation?
He's now ecstatic from singing,
but he should have an idea that
someone's ears have bled.
When you hate to see me and decided to leave,
I'll quietly let you go.
I think an ample morning doesn't exist at all for me.
Have a nice meal.
Just enjoy eating.
Ms. Kim.
Instant noodles again?
Pardon?
I felt lazy after waking up in the morning.
Goodness. What a pain, this woman.
Goodness.
Oh my!
Your ear has bled again.
I mean, what's wrong, seriously?
Oh my.
I thought I could eat my food,
but I have eaten bad remarks instead.
I mean,
everyone here is also busy,
Just follow the schedule.
Why suddenly let us pick up the goods on Friday?
That is...
DR suddenly asked those to be delivered.
We are going to deliver too.
When I get back, I have to pull up
the truck to get the goods.
What did you say?
12 trays to be picked up in the morning?
When can we deliver it? When will we be back?
I mean, things like this...
...needs to be discussed
with the department beforehand.
Shall we just obey right away when
you let us pick the goods without notice?
Are you ignoring us because we were poorly educated!?
Ms. Kim.
You're trying to speak something on your mind...
...and stand up against me!?
Pardon?
Goodness.
You're really getting on my nerves, Ms. Kim.
I'm afraid...
...that my subordinates won't be
able to speak up in the future.
What did he said?
He couldn't take it.
That's ridiculous.
He doesn't even deliver,
but he picks it up by himself instead.
I knew he was just sitting all day long
and play computer games.
That's what I mean.
Yes, this is from Seonghae.
Oh, Ms. Kim.
Yes, sir.
Can the caramel seasoning arrive on Friday?
The goods are already available and shipped,
but the logistic department couldn't pick those up.
What?
Why?
He said there were too many deliveries.
If there are mistakes this time,
we will really compensate for those.
We'll be totally out from the DR.
Goodness.
We must finish it by Friday.
I got it.
I'll talk with Mr. Seo about that.
Yes, sir.
What did he said?
He wants to talk to him personally.
Ridiculous.
He couldn't even dare to act against Mr. Seo.
Obviously, he'll just confront him through reasoning.
Contacting my dear president.
Oh, sir. Hello.
Have you eaten?
Did you really watered the flower pots
early in the morning?
Yes. We watered those every day.
Why do the flowers in the
president's office always wither?
He's asking why the flowers gets withered?
I've been scolded before.
Is it due to poor condition
that they keep getting withered?
We obviously water those every day.
The plants in the president's room may have felt bad.
That's why, they wither.
You see,
I heard that plants can hear what humans talk.
Fine.
I guess it's better for them to die than...
...being like someone with bleeding ears.
Pardon?
I'm not talking about you.
Oh my.
This pest.
Why did it came here?
Oh my, where did it go?
Oh my, it's there.
You're dead meat today!
It's the first time in my life
that I felt sympathy for the flies.
You see,
this needs to be washed.
It's dirty because of the blood.
Goodness.
You see, President.
I have been concerned about
the company's future development.
What I mean is that it
doesn't take much longer...
...to get a good hold of the time.
Of course, I have to pick those up.
I'll pick up and deliver those right away.
- Next week...
- Goodness. Look at him.
He's not as good as a fly.
Please don't misunderstand it.
Sir, are you free on that day?
Our meeting ends here.
There's one last thing that I got concerned.
There were some people who didn't
greet the president after work.
Don't you know the basic etiquette?
You must greet even when you leave.
Don't be late in the morning.
Even if you're late for a minute or two,
it will still be accounted for.
When you're on field work,
you can go home after right away.
Submit the leave application in advance
for it to be properly approved.
It's not allowed, unless you submit the application.
This won't do.
I've heard about some people recently.
That they didn't feel happy...
...when the president say few words to them.
Don't you know the basic etiquette?
I mean, as seniors,
we instruct and explain everything
by saying just in few words.
If you're not happy because of it,
how will you able to improve yourselves!?
No!
Not here!
Absolutely not here!
No! Absolutely no!
Don't do it here! No way!
Ms. Kim.
Why are you blocking your ears as someone's talking?
You don't want to listen to what I'm saying?
I mean, that's not it.
I think my ears will start to bleed.
So your ears bleed because you keep
hearing things you don't like?
No. That's not it, sir.
Why is it not?!
Are you just ignoring what everyone says!?
I mean, I didn't thought of you that way.
You're really something.
My apologies.
Make a written apology.
Pardon?
I said make a written apology.
I can't just overlook this.
Yes. I understood.
Goodness. This person.
You're even not willing to make one.
I was afraid to resign before,
so I made a written apology.
I was afraid to be sanctioned too.
I mean, are you a beggar?
Why is he like that? I didn't even said anything.
You're still young.
- You like to earn for nothing?
- I said I'll make one!
Darn it!
I'm doomed.
What's wrong with her?
You can't just go on your own
when I'm not yet finished talking!
[ Written apology ]
Gosh. What shall I write here?
To be honest,
haven't you keep screeching at me like
an oriole who's singing Ave Maria?
Or in any case...
If you don't like me,
then just fire me.
And give me my unemployment benefits!
I don't want to write even a character here!
You there.
Yes.
Did you really wipe the president's cup
in his office this morning?
Yes, Ma'am.
Why?
He said something again?
I mean, he said it's still dirty.
He thought it was not wiped at all.
Those coffee residues can't be wiped out.
Really?
Then, what shall we do?
Then, just tell him that
he'll wipe it off by himself.
You can tell it to him instead.
I'm not as intellectual as you.
Yes?
Oh my.
I have no choice but to shut up,
or else, someone's ear will bleed again.
I have to treat that person well.
Gosh. I'm exhausted.
Gosh. My head.
Darn it.
It's unusual that I'm experiencing this one.
Why should I do this here?
But still, when I'm with my boyfriend,
my ears won't start bleeding.
That's because...
...we don't even make any conversations.
Why did you date me?
What?
Have you even look at me when we met today?
If you eat while playing with that,
then just eat by yourself.
I see.
You're embarrassed to eat on your own?
Same goes with marriage too, right?
You're already an adult,
but a bit embarrassed to live alone.
Why won't you eat?
Oh, I'm just thinking of something.
There's no reason for us to break up,
so we continued dating,
but how many couples date
in order to get married?
I haven't decided whether to break up or not,
but how many brides and grooms
are ready to get married?
In front of them, who are happy for their future,
what's waiting ahead of me?
It's been 5 years, and they're still
jumping around as always.
Our landlady ’s grandson is too healthy, right?
Let's just sleep for a while.
I can do it.
It's worst to get up early in the Golden Week.
Your wedding is just few days later.
Yes.
What's wrong with your face?
Your ears have bled again?
That's one of it.
Tell me.
After being a mom, did you find
your baby's weep disturbing?
What do you mean?
Well,
If I become a mother, will I think
the baby's weep fine for me?
No.
I'm a mother,
but I totally can't bear hearing the baby's weep.
No matter how great my maternal love is,
he keeps crying here and there,
then takes out his dung.
I felt angry and frustrated as he's my child,
but even if he cries, I could just hug him.
Don't you find baby's dung stinky?
Since he's my child,
no matter how stinky and dirty it is,
I have to endure it.
If I'll have a kid,
I may not stand the baby's weep,
and may be dead from too much bleeding.
Is it that serious?
Would that be fine?
Gosh. I don't know anymore.
Does your ear often bleed?
Not that often.
More than that,
I'm really stressed that it keeps bleeding when I'm working.
All this time, I've been restraining myself from this.
Our society is like this.
What to do?
Well, I'll just have to tolerate it.
What's more ridiculous is...
...I'm afraid of being discovered
not to listen to what they said...
...and that makes me shiver.
The other party doesn't speak decently,
but instead just awfully says
unreasonable things towards me.
I mean, how mighty they are
that they could act like that?
Is it because of their job positions?
Age?
Then,
When I be promoted to that position later on,
will I treat my subordinates that way?
When you get there, you will have to make a choice.
That could happen,
but you can treat it in a different way.
Before that happens,
will I even be able to have choices?
Why none?
You can stand up against them and
hand over your resignation letter to them.
Right.
That could be possible.
Don't restrain yourself too much.
Maybe, it will really bleed too much and cause you death.
You must not die.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
Mom, when did you came?
I just came.
Hey, why is your house so messy?
Even if you live here, you need to clean up.
This is troublesome.
You didn't called me in advance
and you suddenly broke in here.
I called you, this wench.
I did it but you didn't answer your phone.
Goodness.
The fresh-baked clams are inside your fridge.
You like eating those, aren't you?
Those were bought by your father
at the bridge raft last weekend,
so don't let it go to waste.
Remember to eat on time.
Okay.
Mom.
Why?
Do you remember Hoonie?
Who?
Cha Jae Hoon.
I was close to him when I was at the hospital.
Don't remember? He's the one who's
heart was not on good condition,
and every time he feels bored,
I would be the one next to him.
Oh, right. I remember him.
Every time you were out of the ward,
I know you went to him.
Why did you suddenly think of him?
It's just.
Goodness.
He accidentally contacted me two years ago...
...as we haven't seen each other for decades.
Since then, I have no contact with him.
Make time to meet him.
Why?
Are you jealous that he meet
only with his other friends?
No way. How could I get jealous?
[ Written apology ]
Shall I just resign here?
To my dear staff,
don't you felt bored?
No.
Shall we play the ladder game
for the one who'll pay the snacks?
Okay?
I don't want to.
I have just eaten a little during lunch, you know.
Ma'am, what number will you choose?
I'll choose number 5.
5?
Wow.
Oh, Ma'am, you'll only pay 2,000 won.
I guess I'm the lowest.
I also provided one for the logistics department.
I'll just go to there, since I have
to give them a schedule too.
Really?
Thank you.
Sir.
We're going to buy food for lunch,
what number will you choose?
What?
We're about to buy food for lunch, you know.
Right now...
There's still numbers 8,9, and 12 remaining.
Is that what the employees doing there?
Don't you know that we're working right now!?
I could just break your belly into pieces!
You're just a group of nerds who didn't suffered,
while we're just fools who were relentless!
Oh, it really is.
I'll choose number 12.
It would be great if my brain exploded.
I might as well explode my brain...
...and die in front of that bastard's family.
Shall I just resign from work?
Resign?
Why?
It's just that I felt exhausted.
Hey, everyone's having hard time.
There's no one who don't feel that.
It's more exhausting for me as my ears keep bleeding.
Hey, that's a mental issue on your part.
You're fighting spirit is like this tofu.
It will break the more you'll try to catch voices from others,
that's why your ears will bleed.
What?
Like tofu?
Right.
Tofu.
How are you going to resolve that later?
Or else, try hypnotizing yourself after closing your eyes.
After closing those,
think that it will be fine.
You may heard nonsensical things from someone,
but since you're not like that,
you'll just shake it off.
Just like that.
If you resign now,
do you think you'll be able
to work at other companies?
There is someone who's a pain everywhere you go.
Even if you felt and able to adapt to such person,
unconsciously, you'll later found out
that an upgraded one has arise.
It's a matter of handling your mentality.
You see,
shall I just not have a baby?
What are you saying suddenly?
I mean, if the baby cries,
my ears will just bleed.
Then, if he or she keeps crying,
my ears will keep bleeding too.
I mean...
Just because you hate hearing it crying,
you don't want to have a baby?
Are you on your senses?
But anyways,
can you be a bit concerned for me?
You don't even care what I think?
That's not what I mean.
It's meaningless if we live together without children.
To be honest.
Just eat.
Hey, that's a mental issue on your part.
[ Written Apology ]
The aforementioned, on October 15, 2019,
done something that's unexpected and unintentional.
I apologize for the inconvenience.
Ms. Kim.
You're not yet aware how severe the issue was?
Pardon?
You brought inconvenience to everyone.
Do you think this is the appropriate word for that?
Besides,
are you sure it happened unintentionally?
You must be lying.
I'm not lying about that.
Rewrite it again.
[ Seonghae F&B, Logistics Department Manager Go Ji Hwan ]
This time,
the company's business card has changed its style.
But Manager Go said it's the
first time he have it on his life,
so he distributed these cards to everyone.
Oh, it really is.
[ Seonghae F&B, Logistics Department Manager Go Ji Hwan ]
I'm going to stomp over your precious name.
[ Seonghae F&B, Logistics Department Manager Go Hwan ]
[ Gohwan, a Korean term for testicles ]
I have spent the whole night
modifying the business cards.
Ms. Kim.
I heard you are late today.
Yes.
I was late for 5 minutes.
Do you find us easy?
Last time, during the meeting,
haven't I told you not to be late?
You have done it.
But why were you late?
I'm really sorry.
Are you done with the written apology?
I'm writing it as of the moment.
What makes you stall long for that one?
About that...
I precisely don't know what should I write there.
Do I need to let you know that, huh?
Are you a grade schooler?
Even these days, they know how to make it!
This is just darn nonsense!
Woof, woof!
I didn't hear it.
Ganjang, gongjang, gongjangjang.
[ Soy sauce factory ]
Dwinjang, gong...
[ Soybean paste ]
Are you listening to me?
Yes.
Pardon me. I'll make it right away.
You can go.
[ I deserve to die. ]
I deserve to die.
Just kill me.
Ms. Kim.
Pardon?
I'm talking about this.
Why take vacation leave for two consecutive days?
I have to go for a honeymoon,
as my wedding ceremony
will be held this Saturday.
And I heard that I can only take three days off...
...when on leave for marriage purposes.
So what?
I have return home on Thursday night,
and only go to work at Friday morning.
Even still,
this won't do at the first place.
Everyone did it too, though.
Really?
This won't really do in the first place.
I mean, marriage is not really a grand thing,
Why have to do this?
You have even violated some regulations.
What's this?
He's telling me not to attend on it?
This won't really do in the first place, huh?
Since the higher-ups approve this,
I'll let it go this time.
What's so great about holding a wedding?
Why have to show it off, huh?
Is that for you to show off at that age?
Why talk about age here?
No. No way.
I need to get my grip.
Before...
- I'll recite a poem for a moment.
- ...a female staff here got married.
- Look up the sky until I die.
- She should have resigned.
Why talk about women here?
- No. No way.
- That woman now is seriously...
No way.
- When the leaves were blown by the wind, I feel sad.
- After she got married, she later become pregnant.
- Why pregnancy suddenly?
- By then,
she applied for maternity leave again.
I guess she just take it up for granted.
Her fellow colleagues' works will increase.
Why she don't know that?
I'm... doomed.
The vacation must be justifiable.
She definitely brought over
her friends to get her things.
Look at you. Again.
Goodness. Even if I want to talk,
I can't freely talk at all.
Even if I talk here...
I'd rather just be knocked out.
Yes. They are ready to be delivered tonight.
There will be two batches of goods
next Tuesday and Thursday, right?
Yes.
Then, we'll get the first batch next week,
as there are more deliveries
in the start of the month.
Then, let's try it this Saturday.
Let's do it that way.
I understood.
He still haven't realized it?
Probably, he didn't find
his name precious at all.
Goodness.
What I've done all night was just nothing.
Oh, Ms. Kim.
You see,
How long will it take to transport
the almond syrup goods through air?
First, you need to know if
the factory has inventory of those.
If there is, shall it take a week long?
Yes.
Can you look for other ways?
After I have inquired about the
approximate budget, I'll inform you.
Are you ready for your wedding ceremony?
Well, we're on the final process for it.
Whoa! Then, you'll be
a middle-aged woman soon?
Indeed.
That...
Do your bleeding ears have been already fine?
Not at all.
They're still not fine.
What did your groom said?
He must be too worried.
He said that it's my fault
and due to my weak mentality.
Isn't that a disorder?
It's not like you catch cold
due to mental illness, right?
That's what I mean.
Sir.
Yes?
Excuse me, about my business card...
Can you reprint those again?
Why? What's wrong?
It's just that I need more of those.
I'm asking you.
That can't be.
I already told you that it can't be.
I just printed two batches for you two days ago.
But you have already utilized all of those.
Does that make sense?
It's not that I used it all.
I have lost all of those.
If you lost them, it's your responsibility.
Anyways, right now, it can't be.
So, after time passes by, come here later.
Okay?
Darn it!
Sir, this is list after adding the other commodity.
They added caramel syrup?
There are two boxes left and they're not enough.
Yes.
I mean, Ma'am.
Darn it!
I want to feign ignorance.
Sir, your name is Hwan?
Gohwan?
What!?
I want to laugh like crazy at him.
Gohwan...?
I haven't done anything on those vigorously.
It has already withered, Ma'am.
Can we become adults too?
Shouldn't adults have fun like us?
Shall we play like adults?
Play like adults?
What's that?
Just like playing as a doctor or policeman.
Playing like them being adults.
Hey, we don't even know how an adult acts like.
It's not like we even have uniforms of those persons.
Then, what would it be?
My mom said it.
Adults can make their own decisions.
Decision?
We already decided what to do now.
Whether to wear a yellow or a blue shirt.
Whether to eat jjajjangmyeon or pork cutlets.
Idiot. I'm not referring to that one.
It's the decision you want.
The most important decision.
The one that's most important?
For instance,
whether I'll choose to save myself or not.
Whether I able to save myself or not?
[ Director's office ]
Sir.
Here's the air freight information you've asked before.
Oh, thank you.
Your marriage day is tomorrow?
Yes.
Don't get nervous. Just do well.
Well, there's really nothing to do.
After being make-upped,
I just have to sit and wait.
Wear my wedding dress.
And then enter the venue.
The photographer will make me laugh.
It's a special day for you
so you have to be happy.
Others will make you laugh.
I don't know about that.
You'll getting married for money?
Why you don't look happy?
Do I have to laugh all day?
It's not an amazing wedding ceremony.
Of course, it's an amazing one for you.
Ms. Kim.
Yes.
You're getting married tomorrow?
No need to be too nervous.
Even if it's special, it will just be ordinary the day after.
Just think that you are in
a drama where you starred in.
Yes.
After you get married, when are you going to have a baby?
You're going to have one right after?
No. We have to make things slow.
While you're still young, you have to do it.
You even know that it's not too early.
Recently, I heard many persons were infertile.
It won't be possible to
have a baby at that time.
I see.
Darn it. Why issue for a quotation again?
Is this person mentally ill?
I mean, how could this person do this?
What did she said just now!?
It looks like she got annoyed with me.
I must be mistaken, right?
You want it to be true?
Right. I must be.
Second son: Chu Jae Young
GROOM'S PARTY
BRIDE'S PARTY
On 11:00 a.m.,
at the 3rd floor's banquet hall
Parents: Chu Gil Yong
Parent: Kim Myeong Shik
Park Myeong Ja
Eldest daughter: Kim Soo Hee
These two are standing in front
to be blessed for their marriage.
Well, everyone, it's like loving the country, right?
After you get married,
your dream child will be born.
Why he's talking about the country?
For the country's development...
Til the day when Mt. Baekdu's worn away...
- ...and the East Sea's water run dry
- Please keep that in mind.
We have to reflect from being extravagant
and doing unjustifiable things.
- Singing the national anthem won't do.
- We should be patriotic.
- I'm totally doomed if this wedding dress...
- We should help the country...
...drips with blood.
- Shall I recite numbers?
- The people must be educated...
- 4 times 11 equals 44.
- As a citizen of the country...
- 44 minus 12 equals 32.
- Don't be indolent in loving the country.
- 32 divided by four equals...
- Otherwise...
...28.
Bride.
What did you said just now?
28.
[ If read in Korean, it's a curse word. ]
28!?
Hey, are you crazy!?
Even in your marriage life,
you can find your happiness.
As the saying goes, self-cultivation and family management.
The idea is to make the family become stabilized.
A family is also as important as
giving importance for our country.
There may be contradictions everywhere.
So if you have different opinions,
you need to communicate more...
...and solve the problems together.
Bride.
Someone is talking right in front of you.
What's with that attitude of yours?
Bride.
You think my time is more than enough...
...just to witness your marriage?
What's going on?
I have no idea.
Is her ear bleeding?
What's wrong with you, huh?
- What is she doing!?
- Are you kidding with us?
I decided not to continue this marriage.
I...
...am going to save myself.
As I've eager to become...
...such an adult.
I'm totally doomed.
But, it somehow made me felt relieved.
Hey, do you know this?
What again?
I heard that grown-up sea squirts have no brains.
Geez. You're just lying.
I'm serious.
When they're young, they have to find for themselves,
so it exists on them.
When they grow up,
they have to settle for a place,
cram their brain first,
and wait for the food to flow towards them.
Do those grown-up sea squirts knew
that they don't have brains?
I don't know.
I'm not like them,
so how could I know?
It's a magpie.
Hey, wait for me!
Soo Hee.
Mom.
Mom, when I was young,
I read a book titled "The Hope of Flowers".
The book says that the larvae
crawled on the larval pillars.
we don't know what's inside,
but something interesting happens there.
Makes me feel creepy.
It will struggle itself and comes out later.
But I feel that way recently too.
I feel that I can't choose to abandon the pillar.
It looks like I'm in a post-apocalyptic state.
You...
But I decided to come out from the pillar,
and won't get trampled from now on.
You liked folding these stacks of paper.
But I don't know if you still like it or not.
[ Late Cha Jae Hoon ]
[ April 13, 1988 - November 29, 2019 ]
So this is how I have grown up.
I...
...have grown up like this.
There will be a fire inspection,
so an alarm will sound later.
Please don't be surprised, everyone.
[ Cha Jae Hoon ]
[ Obituary Notice of Late Cha Jae Hoon ]
[ Vacant: Seongdong Funeral Hall, Room 2 ]
[ Cha Jae Hoon ]
[ Obituary Notice of Late Cha Jae Hoon ]
[ Vacant: Seongdong Funeral Hall, Room 2 ]
[ Memorial Park, Lily Mausoleum ]
You survived from that painful surgery,
but how could you die from a traffic accident?
You were already dead.
I always feel...
...that I'm already dead too.
You see, these are the gifts I received.
Seriously.
Then I'll wire the money to you exhaustively.
Fine.
Don't you know what I've been
going through because of you?
Tell me.
Why have you done that?
It's because of the butterfly.
What?
I want to be like a butterfly.
Hey.
Have you really gone nuts?
We just interact with each other.
Both of us know that too.
But,
just interacting with each other
until we get married...
I think that's unreasonable.
You and I should choose to give up long ago.
Hey, even still, you put me
into shame during the wedding...
So you don't feel much when you lose me?
What?
You have lost me.
Rather than being hurt from losing me,
you're still in confusion and felt ashamed.
That's what makes it worst.
Know that?
ENG translations by Kim Jong Il, Kim Jae Hyun,
Lee Myung Ho, M.D., Alex Rose are also available.
[ Azaleas by Kim So Wol ]
[ Special thanks to Go Chang Soo ]
When you hate to see me and decided to leave,
I'll quietly let you go.
I'll pluck an armful of azaleas...
...in the Yaksan hills at Yongbyun.
Hey! Shut up!
I'm really sorry.
Yes. But you see...
I've been telling you and endured it for already five years.
Oh dear, you've endured it for so long.
Right.
Since you were married, you'll going to move out?
No, I won't.
I see.
So that's why you look brighter than before.
You've been enduring it for five years,
and you came up here after all this time.
I decided to stop it now.
What?
I mean, my ear.
I decided not to make it bleed anymore.
What?
It was me who poke fun with your business cards.
You must have gone nuts!?
You don't need to remind me.
I know that I'm a woman too.
I learned about who you are too, Sir.
Geez.
What the hell are you saying?
You don't even know...
...that your name got mocked up for three times.
Right.
Was it two words?
That...
Go Hwan?
What the hell are you doing!?
Ms. Kim.
After on a honeymoon,
the coupe should give out little gifts.
Didn't you gave something?
You didn't even come to my wedding, weren't you?
I sacrificed that day,
but still, I gave you wedding money.
I see.
Thank you for the 30,000 won.
When is the housewarming party planned?
No, we don't have that.
I mean, why?
Why won't you do it!?
Of course, you have to do it.
I'm going to have a divorce.
What?
Already!?
You shouldn't have big conflicts. Get along well.
You will often get into quarrels in the future.
Gosh. Men must have virtues.
Just try to endure it, okay?
I'm a very nice person,
so I can't endure it on my own.
I mean, why?
Oh my.
Did your mother-in-law nags you so much?
Goodness. Even still,
you should reflect on it more.
After all, it takes patience,
or else you can't resolve it.
It's not about my mother-in-law.
Me?
What's wrong with me?
You're talking about Manager Im?
She speaks like that.
Oh my, when did I do that?
This person is not even aware
of her own behavior.
You're even unclear of your actions too.
What did I do?
You keep talking about women every day.
What era do you think are we now?
When did I? Seriously!
Hey, Manager Im. I didn't thought
that you're not open-minded.
Try to go for a DNA test.
Your degree of being uneducated
is not only twice but quadruple!
What!?
The two of you are compatible to talk with each other.
Please continue having exceptional conversations.
You.
Are you joking?
It's just the same as before.
And also, what is this? Huh?
In addition,
If you refuse to accept it,
then it is understood that
I will write a resignation letter.
Hey you.
Have you gone nuts?
I already got a mental health check-up,
so I really don't know, Sir.
Just remove that additional part,
then submit it again.
Yes. I understood.
I am really an adult now.
Translations (and some transcriptions) by: void_spell