[ Seoul ]
[ For hire ]
Oh, please come in.
To Noryangjin, please.
Noryangjin?
Where shall we start?
You're not friends?
That is to say...
How many times has it been like this?
[ Screenwriter, Sae Bom ]
That's nothing.
Got married at a young age?
Don't you felt wronged?
My brother must have felt it more.
I'm more committed than him.
Hey, you didn't listen to what I said?
Hey!
Uncle.
Can I get inside?
Yes. Please get in.
[ Blackout ]
How much alcohol have I drank?
Gosh.
You reek of alcohol.
I want the spicy one.
Goodness.
It's 2,000 won.
Try changing your perfume.
How much have you drank?
You don't remember, right?
I have been telling you often,
it will be a painful habit if you keep getting drunk.
A pain of being alcoholic.
You'll totally be in a worst state.
You're not looking good too.
What did you say?
Why are you here?
You said you're on vacation.
When did I?
This crazy punk.
You made phone calls during shift hours and messed up.
Where's your car?
My car is...
You don't know where it is and just got drunk?
I mean, not that.
Darn you.
Hey, In Young.
Pardon?
Take back the car from him.
Okay, sir.
[ Call log ]
You didn't call us until 8:00 p.m. yesterday.
The night-duty chauffeur paid for the expenses.
I mean,
you're not even our boss's son.
You didn't even have a sufficient standing.
Kept being instructed every day.
Why did your hometown junior helped you?
7787.
Especially...
What's wrong with you?
Hello.
I was the chauffeur from yesterday.
Mister.
Oh, you're here.
Why did you have my service car?
You see...
But I still haven't got the service fee.
[ Mihwang Transportations ]
Oh well,
thank you.
I mean...
I'm not referring to that.
Well, this one.
[ I'll pay the chauffeur 10 million won. ]
[ November 11; Payor, Yang Ik Seung ]
The chauffeur...
How many zeros are these?
Ones.
Tens.
Hundreds.
Thousands.
Ten thousands.
Hundred thousands.
Millions.
Ten millions.
Did you came back from the U.S.?
It's still early in the morning.
Are you making fun of me?
No, sir.
It's clearly written here.
There were even fingerprints on it.
[ I'll pay the chauffeur 10 million won. ]
[ November 11; Payor, Yang Ik Seung ]
What's this?
Blood?
Right.
I mean, you don't remember what happened yesterday?
You were soaked in blood,
and then you asked me to bring you to Seoul.
Oh my, I remembered it.
If there is no conclusive evidence...
No. No need for it.
Does this make sense?
You should use your common sense.
But you see, my service fees.
How dare you accused me?
You have already made a promise.
It's here.
My service fees.
At 9:07 p.m.
Backward at 37 seconds.
At 3:01 a.m.
Why was this punk here?
You were soaked in blood,
and then you asked me to bring you to Seoul.
What's this now?
What's this?
You crazy jerk.
What on earth have I done?
Try to remember it.
Remember it.
Remember it. Remember it...
I guess no one's inside.
There's definitely someone here.
Just open the door.
Open the door.
Shall we get the arrest warrant and come back?
The suspect will ran away while we have to get that.
You want to catch him?
Hurry up and open the door.
[ Seoul ]
Are you serious?
You'll pay me double?
A young guy like you doesn't even know
that money could be scary.
Is 10 million the name of your dog?
I mean, I felt you were in danger
when you were inside.
I shall just...
If we'll go there, I'll surely remember it.
Whether if I really owed you 10 million.
About that...
Maybe you could have peripheral neuropathy.
That could happen to a driver with a crumbling stomach.
Chronic gastroenteritis,
gastric ulcer,
esophagitis...
You could have an enlarged prostate.
Do enlarged prostate and digestion have connection?
You think the world looks easy for you?
You must be afraid of nothing at this age.
10 million...
To live in this world,
you must know which is dung or soybean, punk.
Persons like you...
...must not be afraid of how terrible money is.
You're still damn young, so you should live properly.
How will I able to live properly?
Just shut up and focus on your driving.
Yes.
But you don't really remember at all?
It just happened not long ago.
If I remember it,
will I be in front of you now?
Other than those twelve bottles,
let's see if I can still remember anything.
Hey kid,
did you have enough sleep?
It's a bit hard for me at 8:00 p.m,
so notify the company.
Try to consider my situation.
I have to make progress too.
You and me... Together, we have...
Dear customer, sorry to say this.
But I'm off-service now.
Take me to Gangseong City.
Gangseong City?
You'll be charged for a high fare.
I'll give you 400,000 won.
Of course, 400,000 won.
How shall I say this?
What's wrong with our call?
For the meantime, go to the company first...
I'll contact you as soon as I arrive.
I can't hear you. I'm hanging up.
Ma'am, it's Gangseong City, right?
I'll send you to the destination
safely as soon as possible.
Let's get driving.
Ma'am, we have arrived.
Ma'am.
We have already arrived.
We have arrived, Ma'am.
Ma'am.
You see...
I guess she was knocked over at Seoul.
Darn it!
Did I stepped on shit? I can't get paid with this.
We even came afar.
[ Building No. 101, Room 203 ]
Building No. 101, Room 203.
You see, Ma'am.
Ma'am.
Your taxi fare is 400,000 won.
I'll be getting your taxi fare.
I carried you on my back,
so my back feels a bit painful.
Goodness. You gave me this much money.
Goodness. Thank you so much.
Have a good night, Ma'am.
You just left her like that?
It was at 3:00 a.m. that I caught up on you, uncle.
[ I'll pay the chauffeur 10 million won. ]
[ November 11; Payor, Yang Ik Seung ]
What's this?
For goodness sake! I was really scared.
You said to go so we set off right away.
But along the way, you keep saying something.
Was it the bag?
Yes, it was.
You kept saying that I should bring the bag.
Could it be in that bag,
there are money?
What on earth had really happened at that time?
The weather here is quite good.
Are you okay?
Hey.
You said you need money, right?
Mister.
Did you kill a person?
Darn it!
I said I didn't.
That blood from yesterday...
You were almost the culprit.
Let's go and see that woman first.
Whether you got drunk,
stole a bag, and killed someone.
We'll find those out.
Pay me double.
I shall just...
There's no one.
The door is open and the inside looks clean.
It was really a fuss yesterday.
I didn't know what was going on.
Take a peek.
I don't hear anything from the inside.
I said I'm right.
How long did she took bath last midnight?
I mean, there is suitable time for her to do that,
but the sound of water
didn't made me fell asleep last night.
The sound of the water flowing...
...must be on the upper floor or above than that.
I couldn't find who's liable for it.
I have no idea whatsoever.
When I first saw her, I felt that
she's not an ordinary woman.
She must have committed something and avoided us.
I have to let her know that
she must not shake up things here.
Then,
shall we check it through the CCTV's?
[ CCTV on record ]
Darn it.
All these wild boars must be caught.
Goodness.
As soon as they entered in the area,
they made a mess.
What do you want?
Well...
We are looking for the security guard on duty.
Yes. That's me.
We have something to ask you.
So what are you asking for?
What's the selling price of a room?
I mean,
there are even cheap places around here,
why need to know a room's selling price?
Are you from Seoul?
Yes.
I plan to buy a house.
I guess you're from this town, right?
Then, where do you want to live?
At the seaside.
For goodness sake.
There is sea everywhere.
Our country has many seas on all sides.
But,
why is he like a dog
who wants to take out shit now?
Well...
We're asking about the guard on duty here.
Ah, you mean Mr. Kim.
He took a rest today...
...and be on duty tomorrow evening.
That punk...
He didn't even know those wild boars made a chaos here.
Wait a second.
He could have...
...drank all night and lay down early morning.
You can ask everything from me.
Mr. Kim didn't know anything.
I am the chief here.
That... CCTV still works, right?
Protection system is more important, you know.
What are you saying?
These things haven't already functioned.
And besides, for all those residents living here,
we don't really need that protection system.
Why?
Because my eyes are already like a CCTV.
It's delicious. Eat a lot.
Let's just go.
Pardon?
Let's go out for some drinks.
What about our matter?
I didn't even remember and found someone.
What can you do with someone
who has been drinking all night?
I told you that we must look for the bag.
None. Such thing didn't exist.
Let's take a rest.
But you said that you'll pay me double.
Look at you. You're just totally into the money.
This one.
This 10 million won.
There could have been this amount in that bag.
I've clearly seen what happened.
Your whole body was in a mess,
and you had that expression
when someone gets caught.
[ I'll pay the chauffeur 10 million won. ]
[ November 11; Payor, Yang Ik Seung ]
Goodness.
Spit it out right now!
Spit it out, quickly!
I almost got choked.
I will give you the taxi fare to and from Seoul,
so just drive the car properly, you punk.
This is crazy.
Why?
What's wrong?
Goodness.
I have taken the money.
I won't mind about her.
All right. Let's get going.
Goodness gracious.
Excuse me, Ma'am.
Ma'am.
Ma'am, I have brought your bag.
Ma'am, you see...
This one needs to be settled at once.
What the heck is inside of here?
My shoulder gets habitually dislocated.
Goodness. I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
It's not me.
I didn't kill her.
The woman was dead.
Someone died?
I said I didn't kill her.
At that time when I brought that bag there,
she was already dead.
What's in that bag though?
Money.
See that. I've told you there's money on that bag.
Where is that bag now?
Damn it!
A person was dead and you're just caring for that?
I mean,
you said you didn't kill her.
Then, how to say it...
Shall we just leave that bag with 10 million
and go back to Seoul?
Let's go.
To that woman's house.
Everything started there.
Pay me double.
I'll try to find out where that 10 million is,
so just take the 40 million and leave.
If you will do it, I'll be surely grateful for that.
Okay, let's get going.
Forensic investigations have been advanced now,
but I didn't kill her.
The truth will definitely be revealed.
I didn't kill her.
The bag.
She has no family nor relatives.
I'll just mourn for her and pretend I never saw it.
The black box?
It's already broken anyways,
so it won't function.
I am sober.
I am absolutely sober.
This is just once in a lifetime.
I can only become successful at once.
I just saw someone came in.
Goodness. Why are you so into it?
Someone will definitely come out from there.
That woman doesn't live here,
she just only come here occasionally.
How long has it been empty here?
I said it's not possible as there were no sound at all.
Shall we try calling the police?
What will they do?
All right.
I think this will work.
What?
You see, it works.
Goodness.
If we'll go in, we may get reported for trespassing.
I have to see it clearly first before we'll decide.
Or else, I won't be able to sleep well.
But the sound could have came from above,
came from below,
went back down,
or they could be anywhere.
What are you saying?
It won't open...
It opened...
It got used up so it become different.
We'll just let the police come here.
Right.
Uncle.
Uncle!
How can you sleep at the moment?
Did I really kill that woman?
Something came out?
What situation did I get into?
What did I do?
Did I really kill that woman?
Why does it matter? The place is even clean.
How was the body got hidden?
Why are they over there?
Excuse me!
I can't contact Mr. Kim.
He was on duty yesterday.
Well, yes.
After he got drunk, I couldn't contact him for a day or two.
But do these people know him?
I think these people are not from here.
They came from Seoul.
Why go all the way from here?
They were here to look for an apartment.
Apartment?
Why is that?
You're going to redevelop the area here?
Oh my goodness!
Seriously!?
- I've been waiting for it to happen.
- I mean...
How much is the value of this area?
Be quiet first!
Please.
No.
We just went here as the atmosphere here feels good.
What's good with it?
His hometown is around here.
You should have told us.
I think people come here to see the house's selling price.
Well then.
Excuse me.
By chance...
Are you the driver on that taxi,
with plate number 4922?
Yes, it is.
You shouldn't park it over there.
It has been blocking the way from the start.
Goodness. Why did you have to park it there?
Take it out, hurry!
Hurry up and go.
I'm really sorry. We'll take it out right away.
Excuse me.
Yes.
You haven't really seen Mr. Kim?
Well...
I don't even totally know who is Mr. Kim nor Mr. Park.
We have just arrived here last night.
You haven't seen him?
Who are you?
It seems that I killed them all.
I must have really killed them.
I killed them all.
I'll just drive.
I killed them all...
I killed them...
What are you doing?
For goodness sake.
I'll just surrender.
Move to the side first.
How could you not put it in when it's just light?
Please remember it.
Please remember it!
Please try to remember it!
Please!
Please remember it!
I'm alcoholically demented.
I can't remember what happened today, on the next day.
Where are you going!?
So you mean it's here, right?
You had drinks with someone?
When a woman was lying dead over there?
No way. You must have been mistaken.
That's not true.
I drank with someone here, for sure.
Man to man.
Who could that be?
Who was that?
Please come in.
So where's the bag?
The bag?
I don't know that too...
I mean, how could you only remember that one?
What's this?
Have the wild boars came here?
What's going on?
Goodness. You scared the hell out of me!
I'd like to say something about that person too.
Why? What's wrong?
Gosh. I couldn't sleep well last night.
All because of that person.
Go and help me
by telling her to keep her voice low.
No way.
I'll just be making a fuss.
Don't you know how is the world, these days?
If police do that kind of thing,
that will just mean bullying. That won't do.
Then, how can I live now?
Why you can't live?
I...
You have to hurry up or else we'll get caught.
The bag.
Just focus on the bag.
A big-sized black leather handbag.
Okay?
How did you know that?
That it was a big-sized black leather handbag?
Yes.
There's nothing special about that bag.
I mean, aren't all handbags' features like that?
But why can't you focus?
Our most important task now is that bag.
To find that bag.
That's just simple, isn't it?
Right?
How did I went here and put the money in the bag.
No.
Hey you.
A person was dead,
but you keep talking about it...
Just shut up!
The bag!
You said you put the money there?
Please focus on your task.
With that bag, my life will become easy.
If I have that, my life will change.
Have you become dumb?
You weren't able to calculate it?
I really need that money, you know.
You're a security guard?
Yes.
A resident below has complained that it was too noisy.
But who are you?
The one who lives here just lives alone.
Well...
I'm here to see my cousin.
Oh, so you're here to see her.
Where's the one who lives here?
She's not here.
She didn't come home yet.
You must be drinking right now.
Something good happened with me.
I...
I planned to drink by myself here.
Want to have a drink with me?
I'm alcoholically demented.
I can't remember what happened today, on the next day.
I was drinking here.
You already said that before.
Someone drank with you.
So, where's the bag?
I'm asking you, where is the bag!?
The bag...
Oh, right.
I mean, the bag is...
The bag was here.
I'm certain that it was here.
It's definitely here.
Have you remembered it all now?
I mean, the bag is...
The bag was here.
I'm certain that it was here.
It's definitely here.
Have you remembered it all now?
You bastard!
I remembered it all.
I remembered it all now.
You killed her!?
I told you that you must definitely find that bag!
But why have you offered me to drink?
For you to get drunk and fall asleep.
I have to look for the CCTV.
Have more of this.
Eat some side dishes too.
This is making me crazy.
Where is that bag now?
Who are you?
The security guard has disappeared.
Hey, errand boy.
It's the first time I saw you.
You're the chauffeur, right?
Yes.
Seriously! Look at you gazing at me.
Go and run an errand for me.
[ Room 203, Building No. 101, Se-eun Road 30, Gangseong City ]
It's at Gangseong City.
It takes about 5 hours to arrive there.
When you're done, go home.
The VIP...
...was a bit angry,
so send her home safely.
Don't waste time wandering around.
Hey.
you're leaving right away?
What to do with this? Ask her.
You don't know how many people
in the world have no money, right?
The money you can't eat and get even if you die.
The money I haven't seen in my life before.
I will change.
Goodness.
Have a good night, Ma'am.
Ma'am.
I have brought your bag.
Everything has been prepared.
I didn't do it all by myself.
Who do you think benefited from it?
Want to have a drink with me?
But no matter how I look for the bag,
I couldn't find it.
Hey, I'm going back now.
Right.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to kill you right away,
so I drank with you.
Since you have to find the bag.
Goodness.
The unlucky you was about to take it,
so I made up a scene
where you have to be involved.
Who's there?
Damn it.
Are you drunk or what?
Now, there's one step left.
I said focus.
If you find the bag, everything is over.
But if you can't find it,
you'll die before me.
Blood?
Right.
I was the chauffeur from yesterday.
[ Taxi ]
Hello.
You've done well.
All that's left lies on you, Uncle. Got it?
So if you want your life to be spared,
hurry up and remember it.
Otherwise, I will do any means
against you, just to find that bag.
The one who can save you...
...is only me.
Think carefully.
Uncle.
Want me to buy something
for your hangover, huh?
You told me to have an upright life.
Then, you're trying to teach me how to live a decent life?
You must have to start living with a spiritual life.
Or else,
you have to die.
[ On patrol ]
Goodness! Why won't it goes in!?
[ Few days later ]
[ Fixed Notice Board ]
[ Looking for a missing person ]
I didn't see those persons from Seoul now.
He said he wanted to buy a house here.
Goodness.
He must have been crazy at that time.
They just wanted to live mightily.
I mean, Mr. Kim said that the area here nastily stinks.
Why is the area here tough?
There's even nothing here.
I've been missing him since he was not on duty.
[ Security Guard, Mr. Kim ]
Damn it. Mr. Kim, seriously!
Goodness!
This person, seriously!
What kind of flower did he grew here?
[ 6:00 a.m. ]
Excuse me...
Excuse me.
[ Blackout ]
Translations (and some transcriptions) by: void_spell