1
00:01:18,190 --> 00:01:19,930
<i>Help me.</i>

2
00:01:21,420 --> 00:01:23,080
<i>Help me.</i>

3
00:01:42,550 --> 00:01:44,150
<i>Is there anyone...</i>

4
00:01:45,240 --> 00:01:46,730
<i>...outhere?</i>

5
00:01:46,990 --> 00:01:50,570
= Everyone Is There =

6
00:01:52,550 --> 00:02:01,150
7

7
00:02:13,650 --> 00:02:16,480
Right. She is still unconscious.

8
00:02:16,490 --> 00:02:18,090
Her family could not be reached.

9
00:02:18,270 --> 00:02:21,800
Her mother just died recently.

10
00:02:21,810 --> 00:02:26,280
His father worked overseas.

11
00:02:26,960 --> 00:02:28,620
No evidence of sexual violence...

12
00:02:28,620 --> 00:02:30,120
...was found.

13
00:02:30,570 --> 00:02:31,920
She just experienced trauma.

14
00:02:32,530 --> 00:02:36,280
Previously, there were reports of allegations
violence at school,

15
00:02:36,690 --> 00:02:39,880
But, it's just a fake report.

16
00:02:40,250 --> 00:02:41,840
Investigation will start soon.

17
00:02:41,850 --> 00:02:44,070
About that path...

18
00:02:44,070 --> 00:02:46,070
because CCTV footage was not found.

19
00:02:46,070 --> 00:02:49,380
Is it possible that this was all planned in advance?

20
00:02:55,740 --> 00:02:57,270
Excuse me!

21
00:02:57,270 --> 00:02:58,920
The patient is awake.

22
00:03:02,930 --> 00:03:04,650
Yoo Soo Yoon?

23
00:03:06,770 --> 00:03:07,910
Are you okay?

24
00:03:09,870 --> 00:03:10,890
Ah...

25
00:03:12,230 --> 00:03:13,250
I'm a cop.

26
00:03:14,290 --> 00:03:17,650
You were found unconscious
and brought here.

27
00:03:19,050 --> 00:03:20,180
Do you remember?

28
00:03:23,380 --> 00:03:25,050
At that time,

29
00:03:25,050 --> 00:03:26,760
Who were you with,

30
00:03:26,760 --> 00:03:28,450
What were you doing,

31
00:03:28,930 --> 00:03:30,250
Can you tell me?

32
00:03:33,720 --> 00:03:34,890
Soo Yoon.

33
00:03:36,690 --> 00:03:37,890
Soo Yoon.

34
00:03:42,050 --> 00:03:43,120
You're cop?

35
00:03:43,490 --> 00:03:44,230
Yes.

36
00:03:44,230 --> 00:03:45,690
Take it easy.

37
00:03:46,070 --> 00:03:47,630
This patient just regained consciousness,

38
00:03:47,630 --> 00:03:50,560
You can't interrogate
without the permission of the guardian.

39
00:03:50,560 --> 00:03:52,160
She still in shock.

40
00:03:53,610 --> 00:03:55,520
Soo Yoon, are you okay?

41
00:03:56,540 --> 00:03:58,610
I'm very worried.

42
00:04:13,210 --> 00:04:14,290
Hey,

43
00:04:14,290 --> 00:04:16,360
Control yourself.

44
00:04:16,490 --> 00:04:17,440
What are you saying?

45
00:04:17,770 --> 00:04:20,540
Why did you bring family's suspect...

46
00:04:20,540 --> 00:04:22,360
...to the victim in here?

47
00:04:23,850 --> 00:04:25,070
I cannot believe this.

48
00:04:25,230 --> 00:04:26,850
A family's suspect?

49
00:04:26,850 --> 00:04:28,480
Why do you call us that?

50
00:04:28,490 --> 00:04:29,560
As if everything was our fault.

51
00:04:29,690 --> 00:04:32,440
If indeed you are all not involved,

52
00:04:32,450 --> 00:04:33,750
Why come here?

53
00:04:33,760 --> 00:04:35,840
We don't want our child to be affected by it.

54
00:04:35,850 --> 00:04:37,540
You think we'll just keep it quite?

55
00:04:37,540 --> 00:04:39,560
Guilty or not,

56
00:04:39,560 --> 00:04:40,780
Let us handle all of it.

57
00:04:41,770 --> 00:04:44,630
Your daughters brought her,

58
00:04:44,630 --> 00:04:47,490
Everything was recorded on CCTV.

59
00:04:48,070 --> 00:04:48,960
Huh?

60
00:04:49,270 --> 00:04:50,890
They even went to the mountain.

61
00:04:50,890 --> 00:04:52,470
So what?

62
00:04:52,470 --> 00:04:53,920
They went home together...

63
00:04:53,920 --> 00:04:55,120
...then split at the end of the road.

64
00:04:56,290 --> 00:04:57,030
Ah...

65
00:04:57,960 --> 00:04:59,360
They called her.

66
00:04:59,760 --> 00:05:01,090
At 2 O'clock in the morning?

67
00:05:01,690 --> 00:05:03,760
On the way to the dark mountain?

68
00:05:04,650 --> 00:05:05,850
Enough.

69
00:05:06,650 --> 00:05:09,290
If they make a mistake,

70
00:05:09,650 --> 00:05:10,980
Just call her parents,

71
00:05:10,980 --> 00:05:12,530
We solve the problem.

72
00:05:12,530 --> 00:05:13,960
Just because our daughters--

73
00:05:13,960 --> 00:05:14,960
Hey!

74
00:05:16,340 --> 00:05:18,540
Do you she is a joke?

75
00:05:24,470 --> 00:05:25,890
I want to rest.

76
00:05:33,250 --> 00:05:34,440
You sleep well?

77
00:05:36,230 --> 00:05:39,520
If not comfortable.
Just say it.

78
00:05:41,580 --> 00:05:42,540
For instance,

79
00:05:42,540 --> 00:05:45,120
When you suddenly wake up at night.

80
00:05:46,890 --> 00:05:50,360
Since then, she stopped talking.

81
00:05:51,270 --> 00:05:54,050
She may have amnesia.

82
00:05:54,050 --> 00:05:56,540
She seems to have a psychological problem.

83
00:05:57,130 --> 00:05:58,580
Commonly called aphasia.

84
00:05:58,580 --> 00:06:00,240
I knew it would be like this.

85
00:06:00,650 --> 00:06:02,080
Thank you, Lee Seon Saeng.

86
00:06:02,450 --> 00:06:04,960
The cop still not get any statement.

87
00:06:04,960 --> 00:06:09,920
Even the victims didn't make any reports of violence.

88
00:06:10,650 --> 00:06:12,140
Maybe this,

89
00:06:12,140 --> 00:06:13,180
will end soon.

90
00:06:14,490 --> 00:06:17,560
You must be very surprised.

91
00:06:17,690 --> 00:06:19,140
Don't be like that again.

92
00:06:19,290 --> 00:06:21,810
If this case happens again,

93
00:06:21,810 --> 00:06:23,810
Our school's reputation will look bad.

94
00:06:23,810 --> 00:06:25,720
If it happens,

95
00:06:25,720 --> 00:06:27,610
Who will suffer?

96
00:06:27,630 --> 00:06:28,980
Must be students, right?

97
00:06:30,760 --> 00:06:32,760
If the student has a criminal record,

98
00:06:32,760 --> 00:06:34,840
It going to be hard to enter college.

99
00:06:35,010 --> 00:06:37,830
And it will complicate their lives.

100
00:06:38,740 --> 00:06:39,940
Lee Seonsaeng,

101
00:06:39,940 --> 00:06:42,400
All for them.

102
00:06:42,410 --> 00:06:43,680
For the sake of our students.

103
00:06:49,320 --> 00:06:50,690
She never...

104
00:06:51,470 --> 00:06:53,120
...saw her father's face?

105
00:06:53,670 --> 00:06:54,650
<i>Yes.</i>

106
00:06:55,030 --> 00:06:56,180
<i>But,</i>

107
00:06:56,180 --> 00:06:57,580
<i>Her father didn't talk much,</i>

108
00:06:57,580 --> 00:06:59,690
<i>So I decided to come back.</i>

109
00:07:00,810 --> 00:07:03,080
<i> I'll call you when I arrive in Korea.</i>

110
00:07:03,490 --> 00:07:05,520
You could just call her,

111
00:07:05,850 --> 00:07:07,200
Why bother there?

112
00:07:08,010 --> 00:07:09,030
This is the result?

113
00:07:10,130 --> 00:07:12,280
<i>What can we do if his father</i>
<i>don't care about her?</i>

114
00:07:12,580 --> 00:07:13,690
<i>Jeez.</i>

115
00:07:13,690 --> 00:07:14,840
<i>I don't blame her.</i>

116
00:07:15,690 --> 00:07:16,490
<i>However,</i>

117
00:07:16,490 --> 00:07:19,780
<i>This case will be transferred to another team.</i>

118
00:07:28,470 --> 00:07:30,320
Shit. I've come this far.

119
00:08:18,890 --> 00:08:20,230
You want to die?

120
00:08:39,580 --> 00:08:41,630
Turns out you are very weak.

121
00:08:45,490 --> 00:08:47,410
You think if you die...

122
00:08:48,410 --> 00:08:50,440
...you will live another life?

123
00:08:52,640 --> 00:08:53,940
I'm not making fun of you.

124
00:08:54,690 --> 00:08:56,040
As these people do.

125
00:08:58,610 --> 00:09:00,740
My name is Kang Il Young.
Counseling guidance teacher.

126
00:09:00,740 --> 00:09:01,520
You?

127
00:09:04,720 --> 00:09:06,270
If you don't wanna talk,

128
00:09:06,270 --> 00:09:07,760
Do I need to tell?

129
00:09:09,930 --> 00:09:12,600
Your name is Yoo Soo Yoon.
16 years old.

130
00:09:14,850 --> 00:09:16,450
Maybe,

131
00:09:16,450 --> 00:09:18,320
You can die...

132
00:09:18,870 --> 00:09:20,830
...before you turn 17 years old.

133
00:09:24,340 --> 00:09:26,780
Your brow is so beautiful.

134
00:09:27,920 --> 00:09:31,320
It is a waste if you keep getting hurt.

135
00:09:37,850 --> 00:09:40,040
I came here because the cop can't solve it.

136
00:09:40,740 --> 00:09:41,670
I heard...

137
00:09:42,050 --> 00:09:43,490
...you were bullied by your school friends.

138
00:09:43,920 --> 00:09:45,320
Since when that happen?

139
00:09:45,610 --> 00:09:47,760
Are you always being taken to the mountains?

140
00:09:48,160 --> 00:09:49,270
Or this is the first time?

141
00:09:52,050 --> 00:09:53,230
It alright.

142
00:09:54,010 --> 00:09:55,780
Everything is clear.

143
00:09:57,360 --> 00:09:58,540
Beaten,

144
00:09:59,030 --> 00:10:00,830
Crawling on the ground,

145
00:10:02,010 --> 00:10:03,250
Beaten again.

146
00:10:05,930 --> 00:10:09,540
They must have laughed
seeing you asking for help.

147
00:10:10,630 --> 00:10:12,070
Even,

148
00:10:12,070 --> 00:10:13,870
They got to take off your clothes.

149
00:10:13,870 --> 00:10:14,800
Go away!

150
00:10:16,090 --> 00:10:17,050
Finally you talk.

151
00:10:17,050 --> 00:10:18,580
I said go away!

152
00:10:20,690 --> 00:10:21,780
Go away!

153
00:10:31,760 --> 00:10:33,030
Don't die.

154
00:10:39,530 --> 00:10:40,480
Wait for me.

155
00:10:41,520 --> 00:10:42,580
I'll come back.

156
00:12:07,050 --> 00:12:08,380
<i>Don't die.</i>

157
00:12:09,360 --> 00:12:10,450
<i>Wait for me.</i>

158
00:12:11,430 --> 00:12:12,610
<i>I'll come back.</i>

159
00:12:33,180 --> 00:12:34,230
You're fine.

160
00:12:56,180 --> 00:12:57,680
I thought you were dying.

161
00:13:01,360 --> 00:13:03,030
I am surprised,

162
00:13:04,070 --> 00:13:05,560
You quite strong girl.

163
00:13:13,380 --> 00:13:14,320
I bought you this.

164
00:13:15,610 --> 00:13:17,640
I thought you needed it.

165
00:13:27,180 --> 00:13:30,050
If I were you,
I'll embarrassed half to death.

166
00:13:33,830 --> 00:13:36,190
Let's behave ourselves until you get transferred.

167
00:13:37,810 --> 00:13:40,070
Don't do silly things that are not important...

168
00:13:40,070 --> 00:13:41,680
...like making a police report.

169
00:13:49,650 --> 00:13:51,800
I heard your father talking to the cop,

170
00:13:52,730 --> 00:13:54,630
That he doesn't care about you.

171
00:14:00,530 --> 00:14:02,160
Why don't you just die?

172
00:14:05,210 --> 00:14:06,640
You changed your clothes.

173
00:14:11,610 --> 00:14:13,160
Get well soon, Soo Yoon.

174
00:14:39,850 --> 00:14:40,920
Ready?

175
00:15:17,490 --> 00:15:19,850
If you afraid of being alone,
I'll accompany you--

176
00:15:41,720 --> 00:15:43,240
Why are you acting like this?

177
00:15:45,210 --> 00:15:47,430
I thought you needed...

178
00:15:48,380 --> 00:15:49,320
...Me.

179
00:15:49,320 --> 00:15:50,630
What if not?

180
00:15:56,720 --> 00:15:57,490
Really?

181
00:17:05,120 --> 00:17:06,030
That...

182
00:17:40,450 --> 00:17:41,580
Aish!

183
00:17:41,960 --> 00:17:42,960
What the hell!

184
00:17:59,920 --> 00:18:00,920
What are you looking at?

185
00:18:02,890 --> 00:18:03,940
Yoo Jung Yoon.

186
00:18:11,010 --> 00:18:12,070
You...

187
00:18:13,650 --> 00:18:15,120
...apparently still alive.

188
00:18:16,720 --> 00:18:18,010
What is it!?

189
00:18:18,030 --> 00:18:19,210
Kim Jung Hee...

190
00:18:24,520 --> 00:18:25,690
Right?

191
00:18:27,630 --> 00:18:28,830
Our mother's name?

192
00:18:33,410 --> 00:18:35,380
House down there.

193
00:18:37,210 --> 00:18:39,740
I'm Soo Yoon.

194
00:18:41,630 --> 00:18:43,740
I do not care.
Get lost.

195
00:18:56,340 --> 00:18:57,610
We're twins.

196
00:18:58,610 --> 00:19:00,070
Mom...

197
00:19:01,180 --> 00:19:03,090
...didn't know she was pregnant...

198
00:19:03,870 --> 00:19:05,450
...when divorced with dad.

199
00:19:08,890 --> 00:19:10,870
I thought...

200
00:19:11,560 --> 00:19:13,630
...she can take care of us.

201
00:19:14,670 --> 00:19:15,610
But,

202
00:19:17,160 --> 00:19:18,880
When I was 4 years old,

203
00:19:20,360 --> 00:19:22,250
She send me to my dad.

204
00:19:41,010 --> 00:19:47,490
I thought it was difficult for her to support us both.
I understand that.

205
00:19:49,850 --> 00:19:52,250
After my mother died,

206
00:19:53,760 --> 00:19:55,800
I try looking for my twin,

207
00:19:57,540 --> 00:19:58,690
But she...

208
00:20:01,230 --> 00:20:02,690
...just vanished...

209
00:20:03,690 --> 00:20:04,890
...from this world.

210
00:20:53,810 --> 00:20:54,940
Interesting.

211
00:20:56,560 --> 00:20:57,810
Yoo Jung Yoon.

212
00:20:59,540 --> 00:21:00,470
Right?

213
00:21:02,810 --> 00:21:03,870
Are you cop?

214
00:21:03,870 --> 00:21:04,580
Why?

215
00:21:05,140 --> 00:21:06,890
Did you do something wrong??

216
00:21:08,940 --> 00:21:09,960
Jeez.

217
00:21:10,520 --> 00:21:11,960
Get lost.

218
00:21:12,410 --> 00:21:14,140
I'm a counseling teacher.

219
00:21:14,830 --> 00:21:16,450
And she's your twin.

220
00:21:17,430 --> 00:21:18,470
You know, right?

221
00:21:18,670 --> 00:21:19,990
ASk Soo Yoon,

222
00:21:20,710 --> 00:21:21,630
Something happened to her.

223
00:21:21,630 --> 00:21:22,830
Then what do you want?

224
00:21:22,830 --> 00:21:25,090
I want you to help me.

225
00:21:27,340 --> 00:21:29,380
What is this person talking about?

226
00:21:29,930 --> 00:21:32,830
She was bullied to death.

227
00:21:34,340 --> 00:21:37,120
Just help her and
ask what happened.

228
00:21:37,120 --> 00:21:38,450
You said you were counseling teacher?

229
00:21:38,450 --> 00:21:40,320
You do it for a money salary.

230
00:21:41,670 --> 00:21:42,830
Correct.

231
00:21:42,830 --> 00:21:44,730
I really should help her.

232
00:21:44,730 --> 00:21:45,540
But,

233
00:21:45,980 --> 00:21:47,890
There is nothing I can do.

234
00:21:48,490 --> 00:21:49,830
Only you can.

235
00:21:50,380 --> 00:21:53,720
I don't care what happens.

236
00:21:53,850 --> 00:21:55,230
Want to hear the story?

237
00:21:55,230 --> 00:21:57,780
Before you told me, I already laughing.

238
00:21:57,780 --> 00:22:01,890
The people she left behind
still alive without her.

239
00:22:01,890 --> 00:22:04,670
This is what I have learned in my life.

240
00:22:05,940 --> 00:22:08,400
School teach me nothing.

241
00:22:08,590 --> 00:22:09,770
Therefore,

242
00:22:10,590 --> 00:22:12,890
I want you to teach her.

243
00:22:12,890 --> 00:22:14,760
Teach her what is shattered hope.

244
00:22:30,180 --> 00:22:31,380
I've been in the position.

245
00:22:31,380 --> 00:22:34,450
In the same position as Soo Yoon.

246
00:22:35,380 --> 00:22:36,690
I've been bullied.

247
00:22:39,520 --> 00:22:42,410
10 years have passed,
and it's still very clear.

248
00:22:43,250 --> 00:22:45,150
Real wounds,

249
00:22:45,850 --> 00:22:48,740
Then it turned into scar.

250
00:22:49,290 --> 00:22:51,140
I'm in a lot of pain,

251
00:22:51,960 --> 00:22:54,070
But I have to forgave them.

252
00:22:55,470 --> 00:22:56,580
Then this wound...

253
00:22:57,120 --> 00:22:58,410
Who will heal that?

254
00:23:02,230 --> 00:23:03,690
I am surprised,

255
00:23:04,350 --> 00:23:06,050
I got through it.

256
00:23:08,250 --> 00:23:09,430
Being bullied helplessly...

257
00:23:09,430 --> 00:23:11,390
...and shown to parents...

258
00:23:11,390 --> 00:23:12,730
Even...

259
00:23:13,790 --> 00:23:16,950
...I think this is all my fault.

260
00:23:18,090 --> 00:23:19,410
Finished?

261
00:23:20,410 --> 00:23:22,520
When I saw Soo Yoon, I realized.

262
00:23:23,690 --> 00:23:26,720
The world will not change.

263
00:23:27,140 --> 00:23:30,120
I want her to endure like me.

264
00:23:31,690 --> 00:23:33,630
How tragic.

265
00:23:37,490 --> 00:23:39,160
But, how about this?

266
00:23:40,670 --> 00:23:43,120
I've never been in that position.

267
00:23:46,210 --> 00:23:47,830
There's something in your pocket.

268
00:23:48,760 --> 00:23:51,070
It must have been recorded on CCTV.

269
00:23:51,760 --> 00:23:53,070
What next?

270
00:23:55,070 --> 00:23:57,200
Negotiate it while I want.

271
00:23:57,430 --> 00:23:59,010
You need money, right?

272
00:24:04,520 --> 00:24:07,430
You're an interesting woman.

273
00:24:07,430 --> 00:24:10,210
I'm just beware,
that you don't betray me.

274
00:24:11,070 --> 00:24:12,210
Follow me.

275
00:24:32,070 --> 00:24:34,030
You live alone?

276
00:24:34,870 --> 00:24:36,090
Crazy.

277
00:24:36,360 --> 00:24:39,690
How about a while for you...

278
00:24:40,140 --> 00:24:41,720
...stay together?

279
00:24:43,890 --> 00:24:44,690
Hey.

280
00:24:45,180 --> 00:24:46,380
I don't like it.

281
00:24:46,540 --> 00:24:48,870
Then, we three stay together.

282
00:24:50,090 --> 00:24:52,650
I have to witness this plan.

283
00:24:53,760 --> 00:24:54,760
Plan?

284
00:24:57,160 --> 00:24:58,720
Ah, I don't know

285
00:24:59,160 --> 00:25:02,050
But, why should I stay
with bullied student?

286
00:25:04,740 --> 00:25:05,760
Hey, idiot.

287
00:25:07,210 --> 00:25:08,760
If you can't change,

288
00:25:08,760 --> 00:25:10,120
How about we switch positions?

289
00:25:11,320 --> 00:25:12,540
That's how you live.

290
00:25:15,720 --> 00:25:16,690
Switch positions.

291
00:25:28,360 --> 00:25:31,250
That's my plan.

292
00:25:42,650 --> 00:25:45,010
Shit! You're so annoying!

293
00:25:45,030 --> 00:25:46,920
This is only temporary.

294
00:25:47,010 --> 00:25:48,410
You want me to go to school,

295
00:25:48,430 --> 00:25:50,880
Wearing a uniform like a fool?

296
00:25:51,430 --> 00:25:52,780
How about her?

297
00:25:53,410 --> 00:25:54,780
Steal a motorbike like me?

298
00:25:54,780 --> 00:25:56,560
She will be transferred

299
00:25:56,560 --> 00:25:57,340
But,

300
00:25:58,140 --> 00:25:59,210
Before that,

301
00:25:59,430 --> 00:26:01,070
I want you to take revenge.

302
00:26:01,070 --> 00:26:04,320
Why should I be involved?

303
00:26:10,430 --> 00:26:11,540
I'm not interested.

304
00:26:12,230 --> 00:26:13,210
Good Luck.

305
00:26:13,470 --> 00:26:15,410
Rich stupid woman,

306
00:26:15,410 --> 00:26:16,990
With a crazy teacher.

307
00:26:40,540 --> 00:26:42,630
What are they talking about?

308
00:26:51,540 --> 00:26:52,430
<i>Don't!</i>

309
00:27:11,030 --> 00:27:12,030
Is this you??

310
00:27:17,940 --> 00:27:19,090
What is going on?

311
00:27:19,090 --> 00:27:20,760
It's not that you changed your mind?

312
00:27:24,540 --> 00:27:25,870
Look at this!

313
00:27:26,010 --> 00:27:27,320
You have to see this.

314
00:27:27,650 --> 00:27:28,720
Hey, look.

315
00:27:28,720 --> 00:27:29,630
I do not want!?

316
00:27:29,630 --> 00:27:30,560
I said look!

317
00:27:45,520 --> 00:27:47,400
This laughing woman...

318
00:27:47,980 --> 00:27:49,360
...where can I find it?

319
00:27:50,960 --> 00:27:52,250
How about at school?

320
00:27:54,550 --> 00:28:06,150
321

321
00:28:37,740 --> 00:28:39,580
School is still the same.

322
00:28:42,160 --> 00:28:43,230
Hey, hello.

323
00:28:44,250 --> 00:28:46,090
Look at this audience.

324
00:28:51,090 --> 00:28:52,340
<i>What is wrong with her?</i>

325
00:29:07,540 --> 00:29:08,470
What is going on?

326
00:29:08,780 --> 00:29:10,400
You go to school too.

327
00:29:11,250 --> 00:29:12,030
Hey.

328
00:29:12,210 --> 00:29:13,780
I feel sorry for you.

329
00:29:17,050 --> 00:29:17,850
Huh?

330
00:29:19,690 --> 00:29:21,180
She's looking at me, right?

331
00:29:23,090 --> 00:29:24,880
I'm scared.

332
00:29:25,120 --> 00:29:27,080
How funny!

333
00:29:30,160 --> 00:29:31,520
You're wearing the uniform I gave you?

334
00:29:32,720 --> 00:29:33,630
Soo Yoon.

335
00:29:34,120 --> 00:29:35,960
You have no shame, right?

336
00:29:38,540 --> 00:29:39,680
If you are in her position?

337
00:29:39,690 --> 00:29:41,280
- Never!!
- No.

338
00:29:42,870 --> 00:29:44,320
You wicked!.

339
00:29:44,320 --> 00:29:45,180
It's you.

340
00:29:46,210 --> 00:29:46,650
What?

341
00:29:46,650 --> 00:29:48,120
You bought this?

342
00:29:53,690 --> 00:29:54,560
True.

343
00:29:56,410 --> 00:29:57,960
This is your voice too.

344
00:30:06,340 --> 00:30:07,580
How dare you!

345
00:30:07,940 --> 00:30:09,430
Try laughing again.

346
00:30:09,740 --> 00:30:10,810
Same, right?

347
00:30:10,850 --> 00:30:12,830
How dare you?!

348
00:30:23,780 --> 00:30:25,980
The way you laugh is annoying.

349
00:30:30,580 --> 00:30:32,940
Let me go!
I said let me go!

350
00:30:38,340 --> 00:30:40,410
Go to hell with your laughing!

351
00:30:41,540 --> 00:30:43,940
Did your laughter pass down from your mother?

352
00:30:43,940 --> 00:30:45,490
Or from your father?

353
00:30:49,580 --> 00:30:50,720
What are you guys doing!?

354
00:30:58,230 --> 00:30:59,180
Yoo Soo Yoon.

355
00:31:00,320 --> 00:31:01,880
What are you doing?

356
00:31:01,890 --> 00:31:03,090
Yoo Soo Yoon.

357
00:31:04,830 --> 00:31:06,090
Yoo Soo Yoon.

358
00:31:08,580 --> 00:31:09,850
So apparently.

359
00:31:09,850 --> 00:31:11,920
What did I do?

360
00:31:18,380 --> 00:31:19,470
Too far, huh?

361
00:31:21,450 --> 00:31:22,210
What?

362
00:31:22,430 --> 00:31:24,740
You think about your actions too..

363
00:31:25,520 --> 00:31:26,890
Like the earlier incident.

364
00:31:27,340 --> 00:31:28,630
Once...

365
00:31:29,410 --> 00:31:30,430
Three times?

366
00:31:30,430 --> 00:31:32,180
What are you saying, bitch!?

367
00:31:32,180 --> 00:31:33,360
In the future, it will be five times.

368
00:31:33,360 --> 00:31:37,340
You can repay me on the road to the mountain.

369
00:31:38,320 --> 00:31:40,340
Here,
Right here.

370
00:31:40,340 --> 00:31:41,230
And here.

371
00:31:41,230 --> 00:31:42,430
Enough.

372
00:32:00,720 --> 00:32:02,120
Who asking you to go out?

373
00:32:02,450 --> 00:32:03,490
You bad girl!

374
00:32:03,670 --> 00:32:05,030
Aish!

375
00:32:05,650 --> 00:32:08,560
Who are you calling bad?

376
00:32:10,180 --> 00:32:11,270
I know.

377
00:32:12,720 --> 00:32:14,670
It's hard to be a teacher.

378
00:32:17,830 --> 00:32:21,010
You just doeverything
according to orders.

379
00:32:23,270 --> 00:32:25,380
You think everything will be resolved?

380
00:32:26,610 --> 00:32:29,140
Nothing will happen
the next two day.

381
00:32:31,340 --> 00:32:34,870
How do you think Yoo Soo Yoon feels?

382
00:32:35,450 --> 00:32:38,090
If she allowed all of this,

383
00:32:38,090 --> 00:32:39,670
You think she will get better?

384
00:32:39,670 --> 00:32:40,960
Aren't you leaving?

385
00:32:40,960 --> 00:32:43,120
If I become the servant,

386
00:32:44,140 --> 00:32:46,140
I don't want to be treated like that.

387
00:32:46,140 --> 00:32:48,830
People determines their own life.

388
00:32:50,720 --> 00:32:52,580
That's what I want to say.

389
00:32:53,850 --> 00:32:55,010
You understand?

390
00:33:14,780 --> 00:33:15,580
Hey, fool.

391
00:33:23,140 --> 00:33:24,050
Gift for you.

392
00:33:37,580 --> 00:33:40,960
<i>Let me go!</i>
<i>I said let me go!</i>

393
00:33:44,050 --> 00:33:46,200
<i>Go to hell with your laughing!</i>

394
00:33:46,890 --> 00:33:49,230
<i>Did your laughter pass down from your mother?</i>

395
00:33:49,230 --> 00:33:50,760
<i>Or from your father?</i>

396
00:34:13,630 --> 00:34:15,250
You choked her...

397
00:34:17,030 --> 00:34:18,610
...and record it?

398
00:34:21,490 --> 00:34:22,600
Have you seen?

399
00:34:24,230 --> 00:34:25,890
I am just joking.

400
00:34:27,160 --> 00:34:29,180
Isn't that what you want?

401
00:34:31,850 --> 00:34:33,140
Let's just be clear.

402
00:34:35,180 --> 00:34:38,740
Being impulsive doesn't work, right?

403
00:34:39,610 --> 00:34:40,890
Then what do you want?

404
00:34:41,960 --> 00:34:44,520
If the dog leash is removed,
they can bite humans.

405
00:34:44,520 --> 00:34:45,430
Do what you want.

406
00:34:45,430 --> 00:34:46,430
But,

407
00:34:48,120 --> 00:34:49,740
Don't let Soo Yoon get hurt.

408
00:34:50,490 --> 00:34:52,270
Because you guys are different.

409
00:34:53,780 --> 00:34:55,470
What nonsense!

410
00:34:58,490 --> 00:35:00,490
What about the transfer process?

411
00:35:00,890 --> 00:35:03,180
I couldn't go to school.

412
00:35:04,450 --> 00:35:07,180
Today was really fun.

413
00:35:07,580 --> 00:35:09,830
I don't know what incident I did,

414
00:35:09,830 --> 00:35:11,940
Everyone thinks I'm stupid.

415
00:35:11,940 --> 00:35:12,940
Jung Yoon.

416
00:35:14,050 --> 00:35:16,430
It's not difficult to hit people.

417
00:35:16,430 --> 00:35:17,210
But,

418
00:35:18,720 --> 00:35:21,070
The consequences that come after 
are hard to forgive.

419
00:35:22,540 --> 00:35:24,050
How naive.

420
00:35:24,610 --> 00:35:26,690
If they admit their mistake,

421
00:35:26,690 --> 00:35:28,850
Maybe Soo Yoon can come back.

422
00:35:28,850 --> 00:35:31,050
You just have to
hold out until it happens.

423
00:35:31,760 --> 00:35:33,430
You are herreplacement.

424
00:35:34,360 --> 00:35:36,480
Also, Soo Yoon ...

425
00:35:38,450 --> 00:35:40,800
...won't let this drag on.

426
00:35:42,430 --> 00:35:44,410
He is stronger than you.

427
00:36:34,760 --> 00:36:36,470
Just a second.
Pull over.

428
00:36:36,920 --> 00:36:37,850
Okay.

429
00:36:42,870 --> 00:36:44,740
Yoo Soo Yoon.

430
00:36:47,810 --> 00:36:48,690
Ah...

431
00:36:48,690 --> 00:36:49,870
Here the things...

432
00:36:49,870 --> 00:36:51,360
You don't know me?

433
00:36:53,190 --> 00:36:54,630
I'm a cop.

434
00:36:54,930 --> 00:36:56,530
We met at the hospital.

435
00:36:58,990 --> 00:37:01,690
Have you started school?

436
00:37:02,050 --> 00:37:03,070
There's no problem, right?

437
00:37:03,070 --> 00:37:04,070
No.

438
00:37:04,790 --> 00:37:05,610
So.

439
00:37:06,870 --> 00:37:08,570
You've started talking.

440
00:37:09,470 --> 00:37:10,790
Are you fascinated?

441
00:37:10,790 --> 00:37:12,450
That is not what I mean.

442
00:37:12,450 --> 00:37:13,670
I'm just grateful.

443
00:37:15,330 --> 00:37:16,690
Did you change classes?

444
00:37:20,190 --> 00:37:20,890
Ah...

445
00:37:21,410 --> 00:37:23,760
What am I talking about?

446
00:37:24,930 --> 00:37:26,930
If you do not mind,

447
00:37:26,930 --> 00:37:28,770
I'll talk to the school ...

448
00:37:28,770 --> 00:37:29,790
Forget it.

449
00:37:30,870 --> 00:37:32,010
What is the point?

450
00:37:33,350 --> 00:37:33,990
Ah, I see.

451
00:37:35,010 --> 00:37:36,890
If something happened,

452
00:37:36,890 --> 00:37:39,210
Don't forget to call me.

453
00:37:39,210 --> 00:37:40,350
My number is still the same.

454
00:37:40,850 --> 00:37:43,170
You still have my business card, right?

455
00:37:48,810 --> 00:37:49,970
It was gone.

456
00:38:02,790 --> 00:38:03,590
Soo Yoon.

457
00:38:06,190 --> 00:38:07,590
The one who can help you ...

458
00:38:08,170 --> 00:38:10,530
...only adults
Don't forget that.

459
00:38:19,330 --> 00:38:21,130
The one who can help you ...

460
00:38:21,130 --> 00:38:23,130
...only adults

461
00:38:25,550 --> 00:38:26,850
I like being an adult.

462
00:38:28,590 --> 00:38:31,270
There are two kinds of adults in this world.

463
00:38:31,530 --> 00:38:35,110
A fool adult but with good heart.

464
00:38:38,230 --> 00:38:40,270
And crazy adults ...

465
00:38:41,270 --> 00:38:43,670
...that can change the world.

466
00:38:45,310 --> 00:38:46,080
Adult...

467
00:38:49,070 --> 00:38:50,270
Hey, idiot.

468
00:38:51,110 --> 00:38:53,360
Have fun with your money.

469
00:38:53,370 --> 00:38:55,530
Why do you live like this?

470
00:39:01,110 --> 00:39:03,130
I bought it for you.
Gift.

471
00:39:05,090 --> 00:39:06,010
Our birthday.

472
00:39:14,630 --> 00:39:15,630
Aish.

473
00:39:15,970 --> 00:39:17,400
Should this be?

474
00:39:19,850 --> 00:39:23,440
I can't give you a gift.

475
00:39:24,310 --> 00:39:25,570
And also,

476
00:39:27,290 --> 00:39:30,030
I never celebrate birthdays.

477
00:39:52,950 --> 00:39:54,530
I miss mom.

478
00:39:56,510 --> 00:39:57,330
Pity you.

479
00:39:58,470 --> 00:40:00,290
Why was I born?

480
00:40:03,490 --> 00:40:05,050
I feel jealous ...

481
00:40:05,950 --> 00:40:07,450
... you live with her.

482
00:40:08,170 --> 00:40:08,990
Hey.

483
00:40:08,990 --> 00:40:11,790
You never lived in poverty.

484
00:40:11,790 --> 00:40:13,250
You live at home like this,

485
00:40:13,250 --> 00:40:15,850
You don't have to work.
Be grateful.

486
00:40:16,930 --> 00:40:18,520
Think about it,

487
00:40:18,890 --> 00:40:19,850
Before this,

488
00:40:19,850 --> 00:40:21,750
Didn't you
let mom go first?

489
00:40:25,450 --> 00:40:26,070
Shit.

490
00:40:28,190 --> 00:40:29,890
Are you cursing?

491
00:40:30,710 --> 00:40:32,070
Very funny.

492
00:40:33,650 --> 00:40:34,970
Do you think your actions are funny?

493
00:40:36,410 --> 00:40:38,530
You're just like me,

494
00:40:38,870 --> 00:40:40,330
Aren't we compatible?

495
00:40:41,950 --> 00:40:44,610
You mean to say we're the same?

496
00:40:45,690 --> 00:40:47,650
It's just you, idiot.

497
00:40:48,190 --> 00:40:50,310
Hey, stop already.
Just eat.

498
00:40:56,210 --> 00:40:57,110
This is delicious.

499
00:41:21,710 --> 00:41:24,390
Can I meet mom if I die?

500
00:41:25,790 --> 00:41:27,010
If you die,

501
00:41:28,330 --> 00:41:29,430
It's all over.

502
00:41:29,790 --> 00:41:30,890
No regrets.

503
00:41:33,850 --> 00:41:36,610
I'm confused why they beat me.

504
00:41:37,450 --> 00:41:39,830
Are they going to hate me to death.

505
00:41:42,070 --> 00:41:43,670
Even if there is a reason,

506
00:41:43,670 --> 00:41:45,330
I'm ready to accept it.

507
00:41:45,330 --> 00:41:46,190
But,

508
00:41:48,410 --> 00:41:49,690
What is the reason?

509
00:41:50,710 --> 00:41:51,730
Soo Yoon.

510
00:41:54,430 --> 00:41:56,430
All of this is wrong.

511
00:41:56,430 --> 00:41:57,870
There's no need for a reason.

512
00:41:58,530 --> 00:41:59,770
About Jung Yoon,

513
00:42:01,950 --> 00:42:05,640
She looks more like mom.

514
00:42:06,830 --> 00:42:08,150
Even though she didn't realize it.

515
00:42:11,810 --> 00:42:12,910
I have no idea.

516
00:42:14,030 --> 00:42:15,370
In my opinion,

517
00:42:17,290 --> 00:42:19,210
Only you are real.

518
00:42:20,870 --> 00:42:21,970
I know it.

519
00:42:25,090 --> 00:42:27,030
I'm watching her well.

520
00:42:28,350 --> 00:42:32,360
If I were more like a mother,

521
00:42:34,110 --> 00:42:36,830
Mother could not possibly leave me.

522
00:42:39,450 --> 00:42:41,230
It could happen.

523
00:42:42,670 --> 00:42:43,690
But...

524
00:42:45,610 --> 00:42:47,110
Your mother ...

525
00:42:47,930 --> 00:42:50,390
... could have left you
because she trusted you more.

526
00:42:52,570 --> 00:42:54,850
Even if she is not by your side,

527
00:42:54,850 --> 00:42:56,970
She believes you can survive.

528
00:42:57,770 --> 00:43:00,670
And become stronger.

529
00:43:06,410 --> 00:43:08,110
As well as you,

530
00:43:08,650 --> 00:43:10,790
Can I be an adult?

531
00:43:13,770 --> 00:43:15,850
I really want to forgive them.

532
00:43:18,750 --> 00:43:19,730
I...

533
00:43:21,490 --> 00:43:22,770
... with my resolve.

534
00:44:19,410 --> 00:44:21,730
I didn't know she was back.

535
00:44:21,730 --> 00:44:23,350
We were also surprised.

536
00:44:23,350 --> 00:44:24,810
She's even more stable.

537
00:44:24,810 --> 00:44:27,690
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.

538
00:44:28,470 --> 00:44:29,610
Forgive me.

539
00:44:29,790 --> 00:44:31,610
What if that bitch ...

540
00:44:31,610 --> 00:44:33,770
... want to get her revenge?

541
00:44:33,770 --> 00:44:35,990
It will not happen.

542
00:44:36,330 --> 00:44:37,830
You don't have to worry.

543
00:44:37,830 --> 00:44:39,390
I'll take care of it.

544
00:44:39,390 --> 00:44:40,570
Anyway,

545
00:44:41,750 --> 00:44:44,070
Finish without a fuss.

546
00:44:44,690 --> 00:44:48,290
Soo Yoon will be transferred soon.

547
00:45:56,850 --> 00:45:57,810
Yoo Soo Yoon!

548
00:46:00,050 --> 00:46:01,950
What happened? Soo Yoon!

549
00:46:10,830 --> 00:46:12,110
Are you okay, Soo Yoon?

550
00:46:12,850 --> 00:46:14,590
You didn't do anything wrong.

551
00:46:21,750 --> 00:46:23,070
I'll get you a drink.

552
00:46:32,050 --> 00:46:34,130
I told you this
won't work.

553
00:46:45,550 --> 00:46:56,150
554

554
00:47:13,450 --> 00:47:16,530
<i>About this video,</i>
<i>Have your parents seen?</i>

555
00:47:16,770 --> 00:47:18,810
<i>Police, Seonsaengnim?</i>

556
00:47:18,810 --> 00:47:20,560
You crazy?!
What do you want ?!

557
00:47:21,060 --> 00:47:21,730
= Yoo Soo Yoon =

558
00:47:24,650 --> 00:47:26,570
- Hey ...
- <i>Don't talk much, come over here.</i>

559
00:47:26,570 --> 00:47:28,720
Or I'll post this video.

560
00:47:28,720 --> 00:47:29,390
Your parents,

561
00:47:29,390 --> 00:47:30,050
Seonsaeng,

562
00:47:30,050 --> 00:47:30,910
Police,

563
00:47:30,910 --> 00:47:32,950
Especially for your great mom.

564
00:47:32,950 --> 00:47:35,890
I can also send this to the TV station.

565
00:47:38,130 --> 00:47:39,190
Interesting, right?

566
00:47:45,090 --> 00:47:47,250
Find this dead woman.

567
00:47:48,240 --> 00:47:49,730
= Mother =

568
00:47:58,030 --> 00:47:58,850
<i>How?</i>

569
00:47:59,590 --> 00:48:00,950
<i>What did your mother say?</i>

570
00:48:01,690 --> 00:48:03,470
<i>I have nothing to lose.</i>

571
00:48:20,410 --> 00:48:21,770
I'll kill you.

572
00:48:28,130 --> 00:48:30,090
Shit. Where is he?

573
00:49:06,850 --> 00:49:08,710
You really came.

574
00:49:09,390 --> 00:49:10,750
Do you know where this is?

575
00:49:15,950 --> 00:49:18,070
How did you find this place?

576
00:49:25,150 --> 00:49:26,210
The right place.

577
00:49:27,890 --> 00:49:28,990
No one,

578
00:49:29,890 --> 00:49:31,270
No CCTV,

579
00:49:37,850 --> 00:49:39,370
When you fall asleep,

580
00:49:40,130 --> 00:49:41,650
I recorded you.

581
00:49:44,030 --> 00:49:46,160
If I spread this,

582
00:49:47,070 --> 00:49:48,600
How the public will responded?

583
00:49:59,130 --> 00:49:59,730
You.

584
00:50:01,130 --> 00:50:02,330
Know what this is?

585
00:50:06,150 --> 00:50:07,530
This,

586
00:50:09,970 --> 00:50:12,680
Just a sip is enough.

587
00:50:24,510 --> 00:50:27,080
It's just water, you bitch!

588
00:50:30,730 --> 00:50:32,610
Stop it. What is your problem?

589
00:50:34,450 --> 00:50:35,390
Stop it.

590
00:50:35,390 --> 00:50:36,330
What happened to you?

591
00:50:36,590 --> 00:50:37,670
Why only now?

592
00:50:41,490 --> 00:50:43,280
Why did you do that to me?

593
00:50:44,630 --> 00:50:45,790
I didn't do anything wrong.

594
00:51:09,650 --> 00:51:10,470
How?

595
00:51:11,670 --> 00:51:13,330
You think it's water too?

596
00:51:16,250 --> 00:51:17,930
This world...

597
00:51:18,490 --> 00:51:19,790
... looks transparent ...

598
00:51:20,470 --> 00:51:22,330
...like water.

599
00:51:24,050 --> 00:51:25,310
Although different types.

600
00:51:27,650 --> 00:51:29,090
You're curious, right?

601
00:51:39,490 --> 00:51:40,490
Let me go.

602
00:51:41,610 --> 00:51:43,570
I am wrong!
Forgive me!

603
00:51:45,570 --> 00:51:47,590
Do not like that!

604
00:51:48,570 --> 00:51:50,560
I am just kidding.

605
00:51:53,620 --> 00:51:55,760
You've done this too.

606
00:51:57,530 --> 00:51:58,230
We...

607
00:51:59,370 --> 00:52:01,730
... makes no difference.

608
00:52:13,050 --> 00:52:14,210
Let's make it like this...

609
00:52:16,890 --> 00:52:18,690
I'll give you a chance
to run away.

610
00:52:22,110 --> 00:52:24,080
I will chase you,

611
00:52:25,230 --> 00:52:26,770
You just run.

612
00:52:29,970 --> 00:52:31,400
If you succeed,

613
00:52:31,410 --> 00:52:32,950
I will delete this video,

614
00:52:33,550 --> 00:52:35,450
Like nothing happened.

615
00:52:36,310 --> 00:52:36,990
How?

616
00:52:40,210 --> 00:52:42,090
If something happened,

617
00:52:42,790 --> 00:52:44,550
I'll call 119 for you.

618
00:52:49,990 --> 00:52:53,160
Even if you don't
care whether I live or not,

619
00:52:55,690 --> 00:52:57,430
I won't kill you.

620
00:53:45,290 --> 00:53:46,290
You come.

621
00:53:46,990 --> 00:53:48,650
Why just arrived?

622
00:53:49,670 --> 00:53:50,810
This is very interesting.

623
00:53:52,690 --> 00:53:53,730
Don't be like this.

624
00:53:54,510 --> 00:53:55,390
Please!

625
00:53:57,750 --> 00:53:58,670
I do not want.

626
00:54:02,850 --> 00:54:04,130
Help me.

627
00:54:06,170 --> 00:54:07,010
No.

628
00:54:08,610 --> 00:54:12,110
This is not what I wanted.

629
00:54:16,210 --> 00:54:17,130
Don't!

630
00:54:18,350 --> 00:54:19,430
You stupid.

631
00:54:20,850 --> 00:54:23,230
You haven't realized
after what she did?

632
00:54:34,050 --> 00:54:35,170
Are you shocked?

633
00:54:36,050 --> 00:54:37,270
We're twins?

634
00:54:41,790 --> 00:54:42,990
Look at her,

635
00:54:44,310 --> 00:54:46,950
We're the same, and this is better.

636
00:54:46,950 --> 00:54:48,150
To confuse you.

637
00:54:49,890 --> 00:54:50,950
Please.

638
00:54:53,010 --> 00:54:54,150
Please.

639
00:54:57,810 --> 00:54:59,010
Where are the police?

640
00:55:12,870 --> 00:55:14,550
From now on listen to me.

641
00:55:23,290 --> 00:55:24,330
So...

642
00:55:24,890 --> 00:55:27,270
Yoo Soo Yoon did that?

643
00:55:29,890 --> 00:55:30,450
Hey.

644
00:55:33,550 --> 00:55:35,450
This isn't just an accident.

645
00:55:35,450 --> 00:55:36,970
The victim's parents reported him.

646
00:55:36,970 --> 00:55:38,510
The victim is being treated.

647
00:55:38,510 --> 00:55:39,530
Is this on purpose?

648
00:55:39,530 --> 00:55:41,530
The victim's hands and feet were tied.

649
00:55:43,310 --> 00:55:46,170
The location of the incident
on the road to the mountain,

650
00:55:46,170 --> 00:55:49,310
There were no witnesses at the time of the incident.

651
00:55:51,770 --> 00:55:53,170
How confusing.

652
00:56:02,790 --> 00:56:03,870
Why did you do that?

653
00:56:04,970 --> 00:56:06,920
You're not a bad girl.

654
00:56:08,810 --> 00:56:09,990
What happened?

655
00:56:27,670 --> 00:56:28,670
Just stop.

656
00:56:28,670 --> 00:56:29,230
What?

657
00:56:29,230 --> 00:56:32,010
We will not testify.

658
00:56:33,430 --> 00:56:34,350
Soo Yoon.

659
00:56:35,410 --> 00:56:37,730
If you choose silence,

660
00:56:37,730 --> 00:56:39,210
There is no point.

661
00:56:39,550 --> 00:56:41,110
Currently, the victim was--

662
00:56:41,110 --> 00:56:44,430
Your conclusion,
she is a victim, right?

663
00:56:46,170 --> 00:56:48,550
This case had happened before.

664
00:56:49,090 --> 00:56:50,070
You remember?

665
00:56:50,730 --> 00:56:52,810
When the victim regains consciousness,
we settle it in peace.

666
00:56:52,810 --> 00:56:55,890
Maybe, with a little compensation.

667
00:56:55,890 --> 00:56:56,730
Compensation?

668
00:56:57,850 --> 00:56:58,990
You want to negotiate?

669
00:57:14,370 --> 00:57:16,240
We will contact you later.

670
00:57:22,970 --> 00:57:23,930
Please stop here.

671
00:57:24,610 --> 00:57:26,510
Don't bring Soo Yoon
into trouble.

672
00:57:27,970 --> 00:57:28,800
Understand?

673
00:57:28,950 --> 00:57:30,670
They are very attractive.

674
00:57:32,270 --> 00:57:33,730
With this,

675
00:57:34,610 --> 00:57:36,870
A suspect
can be a victim, right?

676
00:57:36,870 --> 00:57:38,090
You pity him?

677
00:57:38,550 --> 00:57:39,770
Am I cruel?

678
00:57:40,670 --> 00:57:42,380
Human gets their senses ...

679
00:57:42,380 --> 00:57:45,140
... when they ara suffocated,
unable to breathe, and nearly died.

680
00:57:45,770 --> 00:57:47,630
They will realize that.

681
00:57:48,330 --> 00:57:50,780
Until their sight is lost.

682
00:57:51,470 --> 00:57:53,350
That's how it feels to choke.

683
00:57:57,970 --> 00:57:59,510
I think I failed.

684
00:58:01,070 --> 00:58:02,830
She will improve, right?

685
00:58:04,050 --> 00:58:05,610
She will smile again.

686
00:58:08,750 --> 00:58:10,930
Wait for me.
We go home together.

687
00:58:22,770 --> 00:58:24,570
Damn damn girl!

688
00:58:24,570 --> 00:58:25,830
Evil girl!

689
00:58:29,710 --> 00:58:30,490
Ēomon.

690
00:58:30,490 --> 00:58:32,890
- Stop it!
- Do not do it!

691
00:58:32,890 --> 00:58:35,790
Why were you released?

692
00:58:37,470 --> 00:58:38,550
Ahjumma,

693
00:58:39,750 --> 00:58:40,650
Try laughing.

694
00:58:41,870 --> 00:58:42,510
What?

695
00:58:42,510 --> 00:58:46,750
I wonder
who your child's laughter follows.

696
00:58:47,170 --> 00:58:49,270
Is he happy to live
by hurting other people.

697
00:58:49,270 --> 00:58:51,470
You deserve to die.

698
00:58:51,470 --> 00:58:53,370
Ahjumma, it is all because of your daughter.

699
00:58:54,890 --> 00:58:56,310
I just scared her.

700
00:58:56,310 --> 00:58:57,070
Let go!

701
00:58:57,070 --> 00:58:58,690
She started first.

702
00:58:59,760 --> 00:59:01,070
So,

703
00:59:01,070 --> 00:59:02,780
You hurt her?

704
00:59:03,690 --> 00:59:04,920
By taking her to the mountains?

705
00:59:06,380 --> 00:59:07,270
Yoo Soo Yoon.

706
00:59:08,810 --> 00:59:10,320
Die you.

707
00:59:10,650 --> 00:59:11,480
Die!

708
00:59:11,490 --> 00:59:13,340
I'll leave without regrets.

709
00:59:14,520 --> 00:59:15,960
Your daughter has
lied a lot.

710
00:59:18,410 --> 00:59:19,290
Yoo Soo Yoon.

711
00:59:19,560 --> 00:59:22,230
Aish!
Yoo Soo Yoon! Yoo Soo Yoon!

712
00:59:23,410 --> 00:59:27,320
The Yoo Soo Yoon
you are looking for is at home.

713
00:59:27,320 --> 00:59:30,630
If you keep
calling me by that name,

714
00:59:32,050 --> 00:59:33,760
I'm going crazy.

715
00:59:33,870 --> 00:59:34,810
What?

716
00:59:34,830 --> 00:59:36,720
I don't think I need to be clear.

717
00:59:38,070 --> 00:59:40,320
I'm above the law at this age.

718
00:59:40,470 --> 00:59:44,320
Too bad you
can't punish me.

719
00:59:44,690 --> 00:59:46,030
So,

720
00:59:46,850 --> 00:59:49,990
I'll kill that bitch!

721
00:59:50,010 --> 00:59:52,730
Who?
Who do you mean !?

722
00:59:54,830 --> 00:59:56,870
Counseling guidance teacher.

723
01:00:07,940 --> 01:00:09,160
You heard it, right?

724
01:00:09,780 --> 01:00:11,720
See!
She's a terrible killer.

725
01:00:12,140 --> 01:00:13,430
She will kill!

726
01:00:20,070 --> 01:00:22,210
<i>The teacher cannot be reached.</i>

727
01:00:22,580 --> 01:00:23,840
<i>There is also no social media.</i>

728
01:00:23,850 --> 01:00:24,960
Who reported it?

729
01:00:25,430 --> 01:00:26,600
<i>Yoo Soo Yoon.</i>

730
01:00:26,610 --> 01:00:27,320
Okay.

731
01:00:27,320 --> 01:00:29,440
I'm heading towards the mountains,

732
01:00:29,450 --> 01:00:30,600
You go to the hospital.

733
01:00:37,490 --> 01:00:39,520
There were other people in the car.

734
01:00:39,740 --> 01:00:43,520
At the same time that
girl is with us.

735
01:00:43,520 --> 01:00:44,610
The victim will immediately come to his senses.

736
01:00:44,630 --> 01:00:47,140
This is no big deal.
All will be resolved.

737
01:00:47,140 --> 01:00:48,090
By the way,

738
01:00:48,090 --> 01:00:51,630
if they continue like this
Will they be successful?

739
01:00:51,630 --> 01:00:53,960
Ah ...
Just driving you crazy.

740
01:00:54,120 --> 01:00:58,230
<i>Yoo Soo Yoon yang</i>
<i>you are looking for is at home.</i>

741
01:00:58,250 --> 01:01:01,040
<i>If you continue</i>
<i>call me by that name,</i>

742
01:01:01,560 --> 01:01:03,250
<i>I'm going crazy.</i>

743
01:01:04,520 --> 01:01:06,120
I have somewhere to go.

744
01:01:06,120 --> 01:01:06,960
Where?

745
01:01:14,030 --> 01:01:14,940
thanks.

746
01:01:18,160 --> 01:01:19,320
What happen?

747
01:01:20,810 --> 01:01:22,180
Hey, what's the matter?

748
01:01:48,850 --> 01:01:50,210
<i>The victim is aware.</i>

749
01:01:50,430 --> 01:01:52,160
<i>It's hard to say,</i>

750
01:01:52,630 --> 01:01:55,250
<i>Looks like someone else.</i>

751
01:01:55,670 --> 01:01:57,380
There are other people there.

752
01:01:58,890 --> 01:01:59,830
Other people?

753
01:02:00,210 --> 01:02:02,720
I'm not alone.

754
01:02:04,890 --> 01:02:06,320
<i>I'm not alone.</i>

755
01:02:09,530 --> 01:02:11,280
<i>Very weird.</i>

756
01:02:20,940 --> 01:02:23,070
She saw
other people around her?

757
01:02:23,090 --> 01:02:23,960
<i>What?</i>

758
01:02:24,870 --> 01:02:25,850
<i>A moment.</i>

759
01:02:27,830 --> 01:02:28,980
<i>Can be.</i>

760
01:02:28,980 --> 01:02:30,050
<i>She saw someone else.</i>

761
01:02:35,140 --> 01:02:36,560
Hey, what do you mean?

762
01:02:36,560 --> 01:02:39,780
This means that there is someone
other than Yoo Soo Yoon.

763
01:02:40,780 --> 01:02:41,720
What?

764
01:02:43,170 --> 01:02:44,200
Okay.

765
01:02:50,760 --> 01:02:51,740
<i>You come.</i>

766
01:02:52,830 --> 01:02:54,720
<i>Why just arrived?</i>

767
01:02:56,410 --> 01:02:57,830
<i>This is very interesting.</i>

768
01:03:03,940 --> 01:03:04,980
<i>Don't be like this.</i>

769
01:03:06,610 --> 01:03:07,610
<i>Let her go.</i>

770
01:03:11,160 --> 01:03:12,210
<i>I don't want.</i>

771
01:03:17,050 --> 01:03:18,320
<i>Don't be like this.</i>

772
01:03:22,070 --> 01:03:23,230
<i>Shit!</i>

773
01:03:23,650 --> 01:03:25,850
<i>You haven't realized yet</i>
<i>after what she did?</i>

774
01:03:26,780 --> 01:03:30,160
<i>Stop it.</i>

775
01:03:31,920 --> 01:03:33,120
<i>Glad to see you.</i>

776
01:03:33,140 --> 01:03:36,320
<i>I'm a counseling tutor.</i>

777
01:03:36,320 --> 01:03:37,320
<i>Are you scared?</i>

778
01:03:38,090 --> 01:03:39,490
<i>You want to live?</i>

779
01:03:40,540 --> 01:03:41,880
<i>I'm not making fun of you.</i>

780
01:03:42,070 --> 01:03:46,980
<i>Every one,</i>
<i>want to live before death.</i>

781
01:03:49,120 --> 01:03:50,470
<i>All of these...</i>

782
01:03:51,690 --> 01:03:53,250
<i>... the actions of Yoo Soo Yoon.</i>

783
01:03:54,010 --> 01:03:55,920
<i>Now, the victim--</i>

784
01:03:55,920 --> 01:03:58,980
<i>Your conclusion,</i>
<i>she is the victim, right?</i>

785
01:04:00,490 --> 01:04:03,070
<i>This case had happened before.</i>

786
01:04:03,630 --> 01:04:04,720
<i>You remember?</i>

787
01:04:05,450 --> 01:04:07,810
<i>When the victim regained consciousness,</i>
<i>we finish in peace.</i>

788
01:04:08,090 --> 01:04:09,740
<i>Maybe, with a little compensation.</i>

789
01:04:13,830 --> 01:04:16,580
<i>Yoo Soo Yoon,</i>
<i>who have been victims,</i>

790
01:04:16,580 --> 01:04:18,830
<i>experiencing psychological anxiety.</i>

791
01:04:19,610 --> 01:04:21,410
<i>After the incident that night,</i>

792
01:04:21,920 --> 01:04:24,250
<i>She called to herself.</i>

793
01:04:25,340 --> 01:04:28,720
<i>Her coarse twin, Yoo Jung Yoon.</i>

794
01:04:30,760 --> 01:04:34,320
<i>and her guidance counseling teacher, Kang Il Young.</i>

795
01:04:37,560 --> 01:04:39,920
<i>It's just Yoo Soo Yoon's fantasy.</i>

796
01:04:40,690 --> 01:04:41,760
<i>119, right?</i>

797
01:04:41,760 --> 01:04:43,610
<i>Her feelings are so devastated,</i>

798
01:04:43,610 --> 01:04:45,180
<i>There was an accident.</i>

799
01:04:45,450 --> 01:04:47,250
<i>Until it appears</i>
<i>multiple personality.</i>

800
01:04:48,430 --> 01:04:50,030
How is Yoo Soo Yoon?

801
01:04:54,070 --> 01:04:57,290
Even though you're busy, don't forget your medicine.

802
01:04:57,780 --> 01:05:00,380
<i>She solved this problem</i>
<i>with her friend,</i>

803
01:05:00,380 --> 01:05:01,560
<i>and dropped out of school.</i>

804
01:05:02,580 --> 01:05:05,270
<i>The last time I saw her ...</i>

805
01:05:50,960 --> 01:05:52,890
<i>I stopped thinking for a moment.</i>

806
01:05:54,230 --> 01:05:57,140
<i>Are they all real?</i>

807
01:05:57,840 --> 01:05:59,420
<i>They all...</i>

808
01:06:00,260 --> 01:06:01,760
<i>... not fantasy Soo Yoon,</i>

809
01:06:01,760 --> 01:06:02,920
<i>But real.</i>

810
01:06:03,270 --> 01:06:04,340
<i>At that time,</i>

811
01:06:05,050 --> 01:06:06,890
<i>When there isn't</i>
<i>no one beside her,</i>

812
01:06:08,010 --> 01:06:10,670
<i>there is no</i>
<i>anyone who protects her,</i>

813
01:06:11,890 --> 01:06:13,180
<i>Are they there for her?</i>

814
01:06:24,380 --> 01:06:26,090
Are you missing anything?

815
01:06:29,870 --> 01:06:31,340
Your expression is so calm.

816
01:06:33,450 --> 01:06:35,270
Are you okay without me?

817
01:06:36,050 --> 01:06:37,470
Dont worry.

818
01:06:38,470 --> 01:06:39,940
Just say it if you want.

819
01:06:40,250 --> 01:06:42,010
I'll listen
to it one last time.

820
01:06:43,670 --> 01:06:45,180
The last thing
I want to say ...

821
01:06:48,450 --> 01:06:50,070
I dream.

822
01:06:51,850 --> 01:06:52,940
You made me curious.

823
01:06:52,940 --> 01:06:55,090
I want to be
a guidance counseling teacher.

824
01:06:56,330 --> 01:06:57,600
Like you.

825
01:07:02,960 --> 01:07:04,410
I go first.

826
01:07:34,030 --> 01:07:35,380
<i>Help me.</i>

827
01:08:07,850 --> 01:08:10,960
<i>The victim was found too late.</i>

828
01:08:11,560 --> 01:08:13,690
<i>The victim's body will be removed immediately.</i>

829
01:08:14,340 --> 01:08:16,230
<i>The victim was identified immediately.</i>

830
01:08:17,040 --> 01:08:18,040
<i>The victim named ...</i>

831
01:08:28,040 --> 01:09:14,060
832

832
01:09:14,110 --> 01:09:17,620
833

833
01:09:20,970 --> 01:09:21,880
834

834
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000
<!-- Generated by GOM Subtitle Module v2.2.10.0-->
