Qin Dapao, listen.
I have my own principles.
Discipline should be kept.
Of course, sometimes, we can be flexible.
But
don’t bargain with me.
Why do we have to listen to you?
You have a lot of people.
None of you would admit
that you’ve eaten it?
Don’t make me look down on
you and your soldiers.
I’ll take responsibility for them. So what?
Enough. Stop it.
I’m going to find Niu Mancang.
Are you threatening me?
Why would I threaten you?
Do you know chalk from cheese?
Let me put it this way,
here are two choices for you.
First, impose punishments on one of you.
Second, impose punishments on two, three,
or four of you. You’ll be included.
Choose between them.
I told you
I’ll take responsibility.
Just punish me.
I already told you
this offer would be rejected.
Now there are
two choices for you.
Make a choice again.
It’s easy to choose between them, isn’t it?
Song Jianshe.
Stop fancying yourself as a smart guy.
I already told you
if you want to punish someone, just punish me.
I don’t want my soldiers to get involved.
Why are you so ruthless? Will it do you good?
You have no idea!
How stupid you are!
Company commander, don’t worry. I’m fine.
It’s no big deal.
I’m okay.
[Confinement Room]
Please take a seat.
Chief Song, sorry,
I made trouble for you again.
Our deputy company commander told me
it’s pretty serious.
But I don’t think so.
I killed a villager’s pig.
Let’s compensate him.
I’ll give him all my stipends.
Besides, Chief Song, you’re nice.
You have your own principles
but you always treat others humanely.
You seem to be strict
but you only inflict mild punishments.
You care about your soldiers.
No way.
What do you mean?
This time I won’t be merciful.
Why?
What happened today
is like a fire.
I believe some people will be affected.
The commander of the military district
has already given instructions to us.
We have to find negative models.
It’s me, right?
Will I be jailed for catching the pig?
No, you won’t.
But you’ll be discharged from the army.
Well,
I have a question for you.
Now you have to tell the truth
to me.
It was proposed by me.
It’s my idea.
It has nothing to do with them.
I mean the truth.
Loyalty
and friendship.
Some people like to
talk about these two things
but I’m not interested.
Don’t treat the discipline of the army
like it’s nothing
for protecting others.
Did you hear me?
Who can I protect?
What about Gu Yiye?
No way.
Chief Song,
how can I protect him?
We’re in the same boat. Listen,
he’s always so arrogant.
Everyone is sick of him.
I’m sick to death of him.
Think about the way he usually behaves.
I don’t even want to talk to him.
Stand up.
Stand up!
Sit here.
Gu Yiye
lives next door.
I spoke to him just now.
He said it was proposed by him, right?
I can guess the answer straight away.
He’s stubborn.
No.
He said
he didn’t propose killing the pig
but he killed the pig with you.
Is there any difference?
Of course there is.
Sit down.
You want to take overall responsibility,
right?
But Gu Yiye said
he killed the pig with you.
You two will share the responsibility.
They’re different.
Please note that
if you approve your testimony,
you’ll have no chance to
compete with him in the future.
Listen to me carefully.
It’s not that you’ll have no chance to win.
It’s that you’ll have no chance
to compete with him.
Before you put on the military uniform,
you were able to regret the things you did.
However, now you’re in the uniform.
You should try to
resolve issues.
Dad,
I believe
Gao Liang will take overall responsibility.
Should I also take responsibility?
I’ve already taught this to you.
What do you think?
I got it.
Emotionally, trust Gao Liang.
Tactically,
always leave some leeway.
Correct.
But it’s very boring
and disgusting.
Do you want to do the right thing
or something that seems to be good?
I got it.
To people, important things are
love
friendship,
loyalty
and dignity.
But to a strategist,
all of them can be put aside.
Do you want to be Xiang Yu
who committed suicide by the Wu River
or Goujian who ate dirt
to take his revenge?
You don’t have to be a hero
but you have to be a winner
because you’re a soldier.
Come on.
Let me get it straight for you.
After it happened,
Gu Yiye behaved himself.
He insisted
he would take half of the responsibility.
Qin Hanyong was patching things up
on a matter of principle,
but I have to think of a way
to resolve the issue.
As your direct supervisor, Qin Hanyong
should also take responsibility.
Gu Yiye and you
will share the responsibility.
I’m
kind of
unlucky.
I’ll write a review,
hand it to my supervisor
and make an apology.
Chief Song.
I think…
You’d better come down to earth.
Ten years ago,
I would do the same thing as you.
I would take overall responsibility.
However, I regretted it later.
If you do it,
I believe you’ll regret it in the future.
Even if I’ll regret it,
I can’t hurt others.
We all did that on a voluntary basis.
No one got hurt because of what you said
except yourself.
Do you remember
the song that Gu Yiye sang at the night
before new recruits left the company?
Do you remember it?
I also sang it.
It doesn’t matter.
You always compete with others.
I mean before he sang the song, he said
soldiers
should protect people who love them
and who they love.
I think there’s one more thing.
They should also protect themselves.
Chief Song,
I understand what you mean.
You’re trying to help me.
You want me to agree with Gu Yiye
on what he said
and tell a lie.
But actually, telling a lie
will not
do others any harm.
And I’ll be able to save myself.
Yeah, right.
Sounds
great.
But if I do that today,
it’ll haunt me all my life.
The last ten seconds.
Please note that
you’re different from Gu Yiye.
There’s no turning back for you.
Both of you stick to your rules
and demand justice,
but
you have to pay a lot more than he does.
If he molts,
you’ll have to
crush your body and shatter your bones.
Being a winner is harder than being a hero.
It’s not difficult to take the right step
as long as you want to take it.
But it’s difficult to
take all the right steps in decades
because it requires you to
confront your nature
and throw away
all the emotions and weaknesses
that ordinary people have.
Dad,
can I make a mistake sometimes?
No.
Even if someone wins 20 games in a row,
he’ll lose everything
as long as he loses one game.
Now you
insist you take overall responsibility.
About him,
even if he insists he take half of
the responsibility,
he’ll be released soon.
But what about you?
No one can save you.
Do you understand?
Chief Song.
Thank you.
But
I can’t do that.
I’ll take overall responsibility.
Otherwise, how to prove that
I’m better than all of them?
Right?
Then good luck.
[Rules of Food Usage]
Company commander.
Hail, division commander.
It’s only been half a month.
Look. There’s little food.
We have to rely on it
until the end of this month.
The food is enough for other companies.
Why is it not enough for your company?
Because they’re not backward company.
They don’t have to earn a reputation
by spending more time
on the training ground.
The more they practice, the more they eat, right?
Then how to complete the Long March?
Are you a ruffian soldier of the old society?
You bled and sweated at the front
so you robbed people of their food, right?
We were completely unaware.
You don’t have to take the opportunity
to give us a hard time, do you?
Give you a hard time?
Gao Liang killed someone’s pig, didn’t he?
Did I wrong him?
What’s the song that you learned
on your first day in the army?
Three Disciplines and Eight Notes.
We can’t even take a needle from people,
let alone a pig.
Division commander,
Gao Liang really didn’t know
the pig belonged to someone.
He thought it’s a wild boar.
Wild boar?
Division commander, the trap was there.
In the deep woods,
a pig suddenly appeared.
And it was dark at that time.
People all hurried to
get the pig out.
Who could know
it’s a swine pig?
That kid
is really good at digging holes.
He found such a place.
He’s an expert.
An expert is going to be fired.
Why is it so hard for me
to do everything?
It’s okay.
I can take off the military uniform
and go back to fix the Earth.
What?
Are you threatening me?
No.
I dare not do it.
I just want to tell you
even if I’ll be demoted
to platoon leader, sergeant
or new recruit, it’s okay.
Please do not punish Gao Liang.
It’s not his fault.
You turned from a ruffian soldier
into a warlord, didn’t you?
Are you helping your friend?
Listen, Qin Hanyong,
it’s the revolutionary army.
You don’t have a chance to do that.
Did you hear it?
Yes, I heard it.
Division commander,
there’s a wild boar.
Hu.
Hu!
Division commander, you’re amazing!
You’re able to kill a pig?
So easy.
When I was a new recruit,
I learned how to kill a pig
from my company commander.
- Therefore, the army is a big school.
- Come on. Hurry up.
I’ve been a soldier for almost 30 years.
I can do anything
except giving birth to a baby.
- Division commander.
Why didn’t you tell me that you’re here?
You came here in time.
Do something.
Soldiers are tired after the training.
Come on.
Help me put the pig on the table.
- Hurry up.
- Yes.
Leave it to us.
No.
Go back to take a rest.
Let’s eat pork at night. Go back now.
- Yes. Gather, everyone.
- You can go.
- Come on.
- Come on. Let’s do it.
Cadres, come here.
Hurry up.
Remove the hook.
One, two, three.
Chen Dashan,
tomorrow,
send cars to the division’s farm
to transport 10,000 kilos of rice,
and over 10 pigs.
Do a survey.
See
if any company is short of food.
Just give the food to them.
Yes.
Gosh!
Division commander,
how generous you are!
It’s not free.
Your Regiment 720’s
training has to reach a higher level.
Don’t be the last one in every test.
You score 0 point.
It’s humiliating, right?
I promise I’ll complete the task!
Song Jianshe.
Yes.
Your Military Affairs Unit
just stiffly followed the rules.
There’s a lack of knowledge
about the cause and the effect.
You mishandled the issue.
I suggest that
you reconsider the punishment for Gao Liang.
Division commander,
the punishment that inflicted
by the Military Affairs Unit
is in conformity with the regulations.
Besides,
our investigation is complete and accurate.
If you want us to investigate again,
there has to be solid evidence.
Otherwise,
the punishment cannot be changed.
Song Jianshe.
Yes.
You’re tougher than Qin Hanyong.
Division commander,
I’ve always been a tough guy.
Song Jianshe!
Division commander,
I know about it.
You can’t blame Song Jianshe.
The military district directly ordered him
to do that.
There’s a great deal of pressure on him.
Jianshe dares not neglect it.
Gao Liang is a naughty boy.
He made a mistake before.
He’s almost discharged from the army
during the last exercise.
Besides,
his physical fitness is not very good.
Well,
the kid who performed well
in the night shooting last time
is not Gao Liang.
His name is Gu Yiye.
He’s also involved in that matter.
Anyway,
he’s not the mastermind.
Think. People
are different.
You’re talking nonsense!
What’s wrong with soldiers
who don’t have good physical fitness?
Do they have to die?
No.
Lei Feng. Dong Cunrui.
If they’re in your regiment,
will you be able to
find that they’re good soldiers?
Today I’m gonna protect him.
Dispatch him to my office.
Let him be my public servant.
No, division commander,
he…
Let me set an example to you.
I’ll show you how to train soldiers.
[Be frugal and against waste.]
Comrades,
this is Jiang Nanzheng.
She’s from the Communication Company.
She’s lucky today.
She can feast on pork with us.
Great!
Today, there are two pieces of good news.
First,
during the field combined training,
Commander Zhao Hongying and me
held a paring event.
Today, she’s here to send the report.
The report is also a letter of challenge
so we have to practice more
and reply to the female soldiers.
Sir!
I want to be the messenger.
Sir, please let old soldiers have a try.
Sir, new recruits can’t do that.
Let us have a try.
Enough.
Jiang Nanzheng
got this opportunity
because she’s the training pacesetter
of the Communication Company.
If you want to
send letters to female soldiers,
show me your achievements.
The second piece of good news is that
our division commander
will take his team
to inspect our company.
Guys,
greet them warmly
and behave yourselves later.
Yes!
Stand up, everyone!
Good.
Where are people who killed the pig just now?
Sir!
Hail, chief!
Let’s shake hands.
Chief, thank you!
Chief, thank you.
Why is there a female soldier?
Chief,
she’s the training pacesetter
of the Communication Company.
She’s here to pair with us.
Training pacesetter?
What’s your name?
Chief, my name is…
Jiang Nanzheng!
You seem to be popular
with soldiers of the Ninth Company.
Division commander, can we start to eat?
Please advise us.
Let’s get started.
Yes.
Smell good, right?
Yeah, the best.
Thanks, division commander.
- Have some more. Don’t starve yourselves. - Okay.
Nanzheng.
Have some more.
Don’t starve yourself.
Thanks, division commander.
Taste good.
Mancang,
chief is here.
Jiang is sitting next to him.
Keep it down.
Commander Qin said that
Gao Liang is still grounded.
Don’t worry.
Chief is not always here.
I’m sure that
Qin Dapao will not miss the chance.
Hail, chief.
Go ahead and eat.
Have some more. Don’t starve yourself.
- Okay.
- Thanks chief.
Have some more.
Smell good, right?
That’s right.
Oh my goodness.
That smells so good.
Come on, chief.
Stop.
They are not for you.
They are for the cooks and duty officers.
Qin Hanyong.
Yes sir.
Replace these dishes
with comrades’ daily ones,
regular dishes.
Yes sir.
Division commander.
Nanzheng.
What’s wrong?
Have some more.
This meat is the best.
How come you don’t eat some?
I’m not hungry.
It seems that you have lots of leisure time.
Nothing compares to the Training Company.
Check them out.
It will not be enough even butchering another pig.
Listen.
After the meal, we’ll have a meeting tonight
till 12 o’clock in the evening.
Nobody’s going to say that they are hungry.
Why do you stop?
Eat up.
I’m done.
I’m full.
Nonsense.
A pig weighing one to two kilograms,
and struggling for hours,
taking the breath out of you.
You call it “full”?
Comrades,
I always focus on your training,
instead of daily lives.
These days,
I’ve been such bureaucratic
and starved you all.
I apologize.
I promise that
I’ll change from now on.
I’ll not leave you starving.
You can learn the skills
of protecting our country with strengths.
I hope that you can all work hard,
just as this little female soldier,
and be the model soldier in the training ground.
Okay.
If you’re full, then let’s go.
Stand up.
Qin Hanyong.
Yes sir.
Take a bowl of braised pork with dark soy sauce
to Gao Liang.
We’ll never have this kind of meat
if not for his trap.
Division commander,
the dish has been sent.
Then send another one.
Tell him to look clearly,
this is boar.
Yes sir.
[Be frugal and against waste.]
[Quantitative Evaluation Column of Training
of the Ninth Company of Regiment 720]
You are so lucky.
[Learn from Comrade Lei Feng. Mao Zedong]
If it weren’t for the division commander’s help,
you’d have to wait a lifetime
to wear that suit again.
You should cherish it
and work hard at division headquarters.
Company commander,
I’ve thought about it in the Confinement Room.
Seek truth from facts
and pursue honor.
Let’s put aside the honor.
When you get to the division headquarters,
keep one word in mind:
hardworking.
Work hard, study hard and practice hard.
He likes that kind of soldier.
[Equipment bag]
I'll keep that in mind.
Company commander,
I’m sorry.
Come on,
why are you talking so much?
Get in the car.
Yes sir.
Do you want to leave
without saying goodbye?
I’ll let you have the position of Vice Sergeant.
You owe me.
I'm leaving,
and I can’t hear you showing off your knowledge to me every day.
A good memory is not as good as a pen.
This is for you.
[Notes]
I know you secretly study
and take notes in private.
When you get to the division headquarters,
you’ll have plenty of time to study.
There is a library in the division headquarters.
If you borrow good books,
don't forget to share them with us.
I'm leaving and you don't forget to show off.
Gao Liang,
you should work hard when you arrive at the division headquarters.
The soldiers from the ninth squad
are gold everywhere.
Yes sir.
♫ My brother, the victorious trumpet has sounded. ♫
All attention!
Salute!
♫ I ignite myself. ♫
♫ With all my courage, ♫
♫ I face everything, never shirking, ♫
♫ since we’re together. ♫
♫ One life, one destiny. ♫
♫ Locked arms are more powerful than gunfire. ♫
Go for it, Gao!
Gao.
- Take care.
- Go for it.
♫ I ignite myself. ♫
Brother,
In the ninth company,
not only did Gu Yiye despair,
but so did I.
However,
if not those moments of despair,
I really do not know what is unforgettable,
what is reluctant to part with.
I have fallen deeply in love
with this group.
It’s my home.
It’s the second most important part
of my life.
Wei Chenggang, the platoon leader of the first platoon,
[Division headquarters of Division 234]
had excellent military qualities
when he was a sergeant.
[Create a new situation in
the revolution and modernization of the army]
Under his leadership,
the whole squad ranked top in the regiment
Jiang Nanzheng.
in terms of overall performance.
Gao Liang.
Why are you here?
Your face is so dirty,
did you just drill a mine shaft?
Come on.
I've come a long way and endured the hardships of a long journey.
Do you understand?
What's wrong? Who bullied you?
Who else could it be?
I wanted to do extra training on the machine,
but the sergeant didn’t allow it. She asked me to sweep the floor.
[Make the army more glorious,
make the flag more colorful]
Jiang Nanzheng.
Can't you focus a little bit?
Sergeant Han.
Gao.
Why are you here?
I’ve come to work for the chief
Really?
Of course.
Why are you laughing?
I was laughing at
which chief has such a good eye.
[Create a new situation in
the revolution and modernization of the army]
You’d better believe it.
I was really transferred here.
The chief
attaches great importance to me personally.
But mainly because
my personal qualities are better.
Do you feel a strong wind?
Gao Liang,
would you like to go to the infirmary
and check your tongue?
Jiang Nanzheng.
How can you talk to your comrade like that?
I need you to sweep
that sanitation area over there.
Go ahead.
Fine.
Hurry up.
Gao,
I heard that
the regiment will expel you from the army.
That's all history.
Now I'm reused.
You’re great.
[Fight for the revolution and modernization
of our army]
[Division commander]
Come in.
[Notice]
Sir.
You, who are you?
New recruit Gao Liang.
So, you are the new public servant, right?
Yes, right, right.
Wait a second, the division commander will come out in a minute.
Just see what he plans to do with you.
The report on building the readiness road
from our company,
what does the leaders think?
It was reported 2 months ago.
The military district is investigating.
It’s been 2 months and they are still investigating?
They did have too much things, big and small, on their hand recently.
No matter what you have,
you can’t let it get in middle of building the readiness road.
Now everywhere in the country
is reaching for Four Modernizations.
These heads of the military district,
what are they doing?
You tell me where it’s stuck on?
It’s stuck on who’s hand?
I’m going to make it ugly.
Comrade Zheng Yuan,
I know you are worried,
but as the secretary of the divisional Communist Party Committee,
I have to remind you
that we are having the Meeting of the Standing Committee of the CPC.
We need to be respectful to the superiors.
We should not have liberalism.
Political commissar,
I have to
have liberalism today.
You tell me,
which leader asked us not to build the road?
It’s Deputy Commander Xiao.
He said we should do more investigation,
then no one dared to say anything else.
Let’s put this topic aside.
Come, let’s get to the next topic.
[Meeting Room]
The next topic is…
[Create a new situation
in the training of the army]
[Work hard and strive for
the party's main task in the new era]
We have to set these all down this time.
Yes, sir.
The division commander just raised a few questions, take them down.
Division commander!
Let me do a little introduction.
This is my new public servant.
How is him?
Handsome, huh?
Don’t hurry to clean that dirt.
You’ve got all dirty.
Tell political commissar,
where are you from?
Sir,
I’m from Regiment 720.
How long did you walk?
I walked over half a day.
My car broke down twice on the way,
or I would have been here before noon.
You heard that, political commissar?
Over 60 kilometers,
it takes over half a day.
What if there’s a war?
How can I not be so angry?
If that can solve the problem,
I’ll do it with you,
for three days and nights.
So, political commissar,
can the divisional Communist Party Committee
turn in another report?
Are you still thinking about that?
As long as I’m the division commander,
this readiness road must be built!
Comrade Gao Liang,
from now on, we share a dormitory.
I’m political commissar’s public servant.
I’m Zhang Yuejin.
Comrade Lei Feng’s fellow-townsman.
My home is in Wangcheng in Hunan,
comrades in the office all call me little Wangcheng.
I got here after I was a new recruit.
You are transferred from frontline Training Company.
I hope you can infect me
with your community-level good habit.
Comrade little Wangcheng,
you’re here longer.
Tell me,
what do public servants do?
I’ve got it organized
so you can start with ease.
A few important things:
get up at five thirty everyday
and change the water from yesterday.
Division commander likes to read and sleep late.
You need to get exactly on time
and wake commander up at six twenty-five.
He has simple food so he doesn’t go to canteen.
Get him a steamed bun,
an egg, and a bottle of water.
He reads the materials in the morning.
Give him the breakfast when he gets in the car.
Oh, right,
medicine.
The division commander never really had a meal,
so you have to let him take stomach medicine.
Here.
[Diary]
Let me tell you,
the smart and dumb soldiers
I know,
they all write diaries.
I learnt it from Lei Feng.
Keeping diaries reminds me to improve myself.
It also lets me go over my mistakes every day.
This is called
taking one step every day.
Who’s the dumb soldier that keeps a diary you were talking about?
Not you, it’s a comrade friend of mine.
His name is Gu Yiye, really dumb.
You should not look down on
comrades who use hard work to make up their shortcomings.
Division commander keeps a diary too. You don’t know that, right?
For some decades.
They filled several huge boxes.
Really?
Where are they? Let me have a look.
What are you thinking!
Division commander’s diary
are all kept in boxes in the book shelves
and locked.
If I got a chance to read,
I would definitely want to learn from it too.
[Division 234. Zhengzhoubei Railway Station]
Zheng Beizhan from the Third Red Company,
Division 234.
[Division 234. Zhengzhoubei Railway Station]
Is this our division commander’s box?
It’s his.
But it says Zheng Beizhan. How can it be our division commander’s?
I just heard it in pieces.
Division commander used to
go away from the field force for some time,
and then went abroad working for
defence and foreign policy.
Really mystical.
Then he went back again.
He had a different name
before.
My father
used to be the company commander of the Third Red Company.
He left
when I was born.
Did he die?
Divorce.
How many commanders from the Third Red Company
who had participated in the battles
are still in our military district?
Zhou Xiangqian, Zhao Zhanlei,
and our division commander Zheng Yuan.
What a coincidence!
[Raise vigilance]
One, two, three, four.
Gao Liang.
Nanzheng.
How dare you being so arrogant
and ask sergeant to tell me to run to see you?
Do you think that you can control the whole army
being the public servant of the chief?
No.
Here’s for you.
Freshly picked litchis. They’re sweet.
I’ve taken several of them.
That much!
Thanks.
Don’t send me anything next time.
Just tell me.
What do you want from me?
You could not just come here and send me these litchis, couldn’t you?
No, no.
That...
Jiang Nanzheng.
Return to the team right away.
The competition is about to start.
Noted, sergeant!
Talk to you next time. I’m in a hurry.
And that...
I...I know who your father is.
Don’t...don’t look at me like that.
It’s frightening.
I told you right away
once finding it out.
I told no one. And...
it’s nice to have an amazing father, isn’t it?
I have the access.
And I want to create a chance
for you and your father to know each other.
How about that? Okay?
I’ll help you.
I don’t need your help.
No...
Number two chief is connecting with colonel of Regiment 720.
The First Company, Regiment 720, disconnected.
The Fifth Company, Regiment 720
is connecting with the First Company, Regiment 720.
Training Unit, Regiment 720, disconnected.
Stop.
Five minutes and five seconds.
Zero mistakes.
Well done, sergeant!
Two seconds less than your best record.
Keep on trying.
Yes.
Nanzheng,
you’re up.
Just be yourself.
Ready,
go!
The First Company, Regiment 700
is connecting with the Fourth Company, Regiment 720.
Military Affairs Unit, Regiment 700
is connecting with the First Company, Regiment 700.
The Third Battalion, Regiment 702
is connecting with the First Battalion, Regiment 702.
The First Company, Regiment 700, disconnected.
Number one chief
is connecting with colonel of Regiment 700.
Colonel of Regiment 700
is connecting with on Military Affairs Unit.
The First Company, Regiment 720
is connecting with the Sixth Company, Regiment 720.
Wrong.
You were connecting to the Ninth Company.
The Third Battalion, Regiment 720, disconnected.
Number one chief, disconnected.
Training Unit, Regiment 702
is connecting with the Second Battalion, Regiment 702.
Wrong. You were connecting to the Ninth Company again.
Number two chief
is connecting with colonel of Regiment 720.
The First Company, Regiment 720, disconnected.
The Training Unit, Regiment 702, disconnected.
The Ninth Company, Regiment 720
is connecting with the Second Company, Regiment 720.
Stop.
Six minutes and thirty-five seconds.
Three mistakes.
Jiang Nanzheng,
this is not you.
What’s wrong with you?
You’re clearly absent-minded today.
What happened?
Are you sure to let her take the honor?
Yeah.
Commander,
although she scored less
than Song Xiaoluo today,
Song Xiaoluo has practiced for three years
while Jiang Nanzheng, three months only.
She’s amazing.
Really potential.
I’m aware of that.
But what happened to
Jiang Nanzheng today?
I should take the blame.
Recently,
I assigned the health work of the battalion
to the squad.
They have issues with me.
That’s taken out on me.
But no worries.
I’ll deal with it.
Giving this to Jiang Nanzheng
means that you give up
the seat of promoting cadre.
Do you know how scarce
this kind of opportunity is?
I know.
Therefore, unless you take the examination
to promote cadre in the future,
this will be your last chance
to fight for it.
Are you sure about that?
I’m the sergeant.
That’s what I ought to do.
That’s not what a sergeant has to do.
Company commander,
the competition in the army
aims at selecting the best soldier.
Jiang Nanzheng, with her gift
and more hard work,
will definitely surpass me in no time.
I’ll have a lot of trouble with my ego
if stifling her like this.
Company commander,
you know...
I may not be the best,
but I have my pride,
my dignity
will not allow me for doing this.
[Raise vigilance, defend the motherland, be strict with requirements, and make solid preparations.]
Stand up.
[United and tense, serious and lively. ]
Sit down.
Now I’d like to make an announcement.
According to the research decision of company party branch,
and the consent of Regimental Communist Party Committee,
comrades Song Xiaoluo and Jiang Nanzheng were selected as
the reserve members of our company
to participate in this telecommunication contest of
the military district.