It's mine!
This is mine!
He tore my doll.
He should pay me.
We spent one coin each
to catch
this doll.
Why give it to you?
You see.
You catch the doll together,
which means you must be good friends.
You can't break up
just because of a doll.
Is friendship more important
or the doll more important?
- The doll!
You can't reason
with the children.
I just asked that
there are dolls catching machine
in the nearby mall.
We can catch two dolls
for them.
Let's go.
I'm not good at it. You're good at it.
Hurry up.
I really want you to win once
and show me.
Avoiding can't solve any problems
but only make us lose more.
All right.
You take care of them for me.
I'll give a doll to you
right away!
(Promulgating the law gives us an explanation
and learning the law gives us strength)
Sit still.
How did this happen?
Who tore that?
Just solve the problem!
Why bother to take her catching a doll?
=Episode 9 Law Eliminates Disputes
Indulges in Kindness and Avoids Evilness=
(Chong&Wei Law Firm Qian Wei)
=Legally Romance=
Come on. Have a try.
I can't catch one
even if I try a hundred times.
But Li Chongwen was good at
catching dolls last time.
Sure enough,
he also wants to
show off his skills this time.
I won't speak out what I know.
Let him perform
if he wants to.
I can't do that.
Come on.
I have bad luck.
It's okay. Have a try.
No. You go ahead.
OK. I'll do it.
Let me tell you.
In fact,
this machine has a probability.
As long as you find the chance,
you can catch it.
I couldn't afford to play these games
when I was a child.
I could only watch them on the side.
After watching long,
I understand how it works.
Come on. I'll catch one for you.
All right.
Wow. You're great.
But the dolls inside
are really ugly.
Except for that little tiger,
it looks better.
By the way,
I'm curious about something.
You're just a freshman.
How can you understand
so many laws and regulations?
From housing disputes
to private lending,
you know more than
those senior students.
If you have a boss
who forces you to
read all kinds of laws and contracts,
you can also do it.
Boss?
Who?
Who is your boss?
They're still waiting.
Catch it as soon as possible.
Watch me catch this.
Here is the peacock.
If you like playing with this frog,
just take it.
A brother should be humble.
Do you know?
Now do you know
what is the inviolability
of citizens'
legal private property?
Got it.
Now that you understand it,
what should you do?
Make up.
Make up?
How to make up?
Let me see.
That's good.
We're back.
Did you quarrel?
No.
What is this?
You made it up with each other?
Very sensible.
Come.
This is your reward.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- No quarrels in the future.
Let's go.
You are a great and handsome guy.
How many skills I don't know
do you have?
What do you mean?
Well, I mean
when did you learn paper folding?
What is this?
Did you see that?
Children are the same as adults.
What they say
is not necessarily the same
as what they think.
Right?
They care about each other's feelings.
They just need an opportunity
to make it easy.
What are you doing?
None of this is for you.
This is a special one for you.
What is this?
Guess it, Qian Wei.
Don't you know everything?
Such an obvious pig.
Can't you see that?
You're the pig!
Hey.
Have you considered
what I just said to you?
What?
Children are the same as adults.
What they say is not the same
as what they think.
You didn't even listen.
I won't give it to you.
Do you have this here?
Have you finished sending these?
Yes.
Classmates.
You worked hard this morning.
Look what surprise
I brought you.
One for each.
Thank you, senior.
- Here you are.
- Thank you, senior.
Thank you, senior.
You've had a long day.
Yours.
Thank you, senior.
Here you are, classmate.
Pocket Monster.
Thank you, senior.
How cute!
Yours is cute, too.
You liked this one
in the morning,
right?
Almost every catch can get it.
The hit rate is already very high.
Do you have to be so persistent
in catching tiger cat?
It is what I want most.
Do you understand?
It looks
like a little tiger
and people dare not approach.
In fact,
it's a delicate kitten inside.
I didn't realize it could be changed.
Isn't this the same as you?
Senior, are you too biased?
You gave ugly dolls to us like
frogs and mice.
Why did you give Qian Wei
a lovely cat?
- Yeah. What's this?
- Yeah.
It's all because of luck.
I can't catch
all the same ones, right?
By the way,
this is for you.
Here you are.
This tastes good.
Senior, how do you know that
I like this taste.
It's delicious!
This is simply…
You know me too well!
How did you know that?
Qian Wei didn't eat just now.
She accompanied me to catch the dolls.
That's why I buy her a cup of milk tea.
If I knew you liked it,
I'd bring you one, too.
No problem.
That's enough.
After all, she can't eat
something too sweet.
I can drink it for her.
This milk tea is particularly delicious.
I suggest you taste it, too.
I strongly recommend it.
Look at senior.
Here comes another
strange pair.
Sure.
Fate is wonderful.
Well.
Lunch break is almost over.
Let's go.
- The resident should be here later.
- Let's go.
OK.
Put the garbage away.
Good-tasting.
Right?
I'll buy you one next time, too.
I'll buy you one more, too.
I'll give you a strawberry flavor.
How about it?
It's sweeter.
This is what I like.
You like the taste, too?
Lady.
You have to help me!
You help me!
Grandma, don't worry.
You sit down and talk to me slowly.
You see.
The money I put in here
is all gone!
I saved my pension
for several years.
Grandma, don't worry.
Why don't we call the police for you?
Has anyone else
been in your house recently?
(Mobile phone money
saved for grandchild)
Yes.
Li next door.
He helped me
fix the water pipe at home yesterday.
He stayed in my house for a long time.
It's him.
Grandma?
What are you doing here
instead of staying at home?
- Let's go. I'll take you home.
- Shen.
Shen.
I lost so much money.
I have to call the police.
I can't go back.
- Let's go. I'll take you home.
- I can't go back.
I can't go back.
Aunt.
Here's 30,000 yuan
from your grandson's bag.
Since the amount
of theft is relatively large,
we'll take him back to the Bureau.
Impossible!
Policemen.
Is there
something wrong?
My grandson is very well-behaved.
He can't do such a thing.
I'm sorry.
I know it will make you sad,
but we must do it.
I remember it.
This 30,000 yuan
is the pocket money I gave him.
Policemen.
I'm old and confused.
You see.
If you want to catch someone, catch me.
Come and catch me.
Aunt.
Grandma, don't worry.
They just take Shen
to take a note.
He'll be back soon.
Right. Right. Right.
Take a note.
No way.
No one
dares to
take my grandson away today!
He lost his father
and mother since childhood.
He hasn't had a good day
with me, an old bone.
I didn't teach him well.
I made him be like this.
- Grandma, don't…
- Aunt.
Grandma.
Help her up.
I made him be like this.
Get up. Get up.
Aunt. Aunt.
Get up.
Aunt, please get up.
He'll be back in a minute.
(School fee saved for grandchild)
(Mobile phone money saved for grandchild)
What's up?
You find a way
to put his grandmother away.
I'll fix it.
You'll know in a minute.
Hurry up.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
I'll take you home.
You are really…
Your grandmother is so old.
It's not good for her to pull like that.
If you have something to say,
say it nicely.
What do I want to say?
Just let her go home with me.
Grandma.
How about this?
You can come to me later
and sort things out
from beginning to end.
I'll help you solve it,
okay?
OK. I'll go.
Classmate.
Your grandmother is
asking for our help here.
We can't ignore anything.
You sit here.
Grandma, you sit here.
Where's the money?
What else are you doing
to promulgate the law?
You can't even catch a thief.
What are you doing here?
What?
You just lost your money
for two seconds.
You are in such a hurry.
Have you ever thought about
how worried is your grandmother?
Well done.
Promulgating law, right?
I think you are
theft and liars.
I'll call the police in a minute
and catch you all!
OK, you call the police now.
When the police comes,
who do you think the police will catch?
That money is mine!
Yours?
Let me tell you.
The amount of your money
has exceeded 30,000.
According to the provisions
of the criminal law on theft,
even if your grandmother
doesn't pursue you,
but the police verify it,
you can still be sentenced.
I know you don't want to
make your grandmother sad.
See.
It's not easy for
your grandmother saving this money.
Do you bear?
(Mobile phone money
saved for grandchild)
(Bicycle money saved for grandchild)
We have another option
besides handing you over to the police.
You go with me now
writing a guarantee.
Write down
your own crime
and promise
(Bicycle money saved for grandchild)
that you will never commit it again in the future,
(Cotton-padded jacket money saved for grandchild)
and I'll wipe out
today's affair.
Otherwise,
let's go to
the public security bureau now.
OK.
Sister.
How much money can you make
from this job?
This is a public welfare activity.
In other words,
it does no good for you
to catch me, right?
How about this?
I'll give you two thousand yuan.
You just pretend not to see anything.
Let's break up peacefully.
Still playing tricks
with me here, right?
I'll send you to the police today!
No. No. No.
I'll write it. I'll write it.
I'll write it.
Don't play any tricks.
Write the guarantee quickly,
give the money back to your grandma
and apologize to her.
It's not easy for your grandma
to raise you.
I'll keep this guarantee.
If you dare to do it again
in the future,
I'll send you in myself.
You hear me?
(Letter of Guarantee Dear sister:
I'm sorry, because of my momentary greed,)
(I stole grandma's money.
Now I know this behavior is immoral.)
(Shen Tao)
Can I have the money back?
Give it back.
It feels distressed
like I lost
two thousand yuan.
Grandma, we found the money.
Let's go home.
Okay. Okay.
Here you are.
That's nice. That's nice.
Let's go home. Let's go home.
If so,
my daughter's affair
can be solved.
That would be great.
I'll leave first.
- OK.
Take a break first.
Here you are.
What is that look?
Eat it or not?
If you don't eat, give it to me.
What do you want?
Strange.
Originally, I thought
you were just solid in theory,
but I didn't expect you
to have a good way
to mediate.
What?
Envy me for my rich source of cases?
Yes.
If all the lawyers
were like you,
they would receive a lot of cases.
(We are taking actions)
But the lawyers' fees
(in promulgating and learning the law)
will drop sharply.
Don't you like money best?
How did you learn it
in legal history class?
The law eliminates disputes.
Civil disputes, right?
That's not the art of law.
That is also the art of mediation.
For mediation,
you can't bring people
extra trouble
for the sake of
more lawyers' fees.
Sometimes,
litigation is really not
the only choice,
not even the best choice.
The truth is true.
But it's strange
that such words
come out of your mouth.
Very strange.
Why do you study the law?
By drawing lots.
When I was at school,
my parents quarreled
because I had to apply for a major.
My mother
wanted me
to be a doctor like her.
My father
wanted me
to be a judge like him.
(We are taking actions)
There were quarrels all the time.
(in promulgating and learning the law)
They couldn't make up their minds.
We could only draw lots.
Then I chose to major in Law.
Therefore,
I don't think
being a judge is just me talking.
In fact, it has been decided long ago.
So Lu Xun
inherits his father's career as a judge.
Then what changed him
and
made him a lawyer?
What about you?
Do you have anything
you want to do?
No.
When I went to school,
I just wanted to do everything
seriously.
But I didn't know
how dreams feel
to me.
So actually, I envy you.
You have a passion
and a
sense of justice.
I think you will be
a good lawyer.
(Zhanying Law Firm)
(Judicial examination)
(is the basic threshold for entry.)
(We don't need)
(people who can't even
step over the threshold.)
Check in at eight tomorrow morning
with the signed contract.
(Labor Contract)
Your position is my assistant.
I read your resume.
Although Chong&Wei Law Firm
has closed down,
several cases
were beautifully done by them.
It must have something
to do with you.
Capable person
shouldn't be tripped over
by the threshold.
I believe
you will be a good lawyer
in the future.
Really?
See you tomorrow.
Thank you, Lawyer Lu.
I will work hard.
Unexpectedly,
Lu Xun was the first person
to believe in my ability
even at that time and now.
You have a good taste.
Now the great lawyer in the future
has to work hard.
Come on.
All right.
Then I have to work hard, too.
I asked that
the students would come out in batches.
That girl would be in the last batch.
When she comes out later,
if there's someone nearby,
you two just go up and hold them.
If there's no one, just do it.
Big brother.
We just want a piece of paper.
Is it worthwhile?
What's on your mind?
If I can't get that piece of paper back,
your brother would be caught
by the police.
Do you want someone to cover you?
Big brother.
Let's show her our strength.
So you're a hooligan.
We should have called the police
and send you in.
You're with them, aren't you?
How dare you come here?
You're bored of living.
Bored of living?
As social scum
as you,
you won't regret anything.
I really have to show your grandma
what the virtue
of her baby grandson is.
Like to be nosy, don't you?
I will…
I will take your arm off
and make it as clothes hanger.
Do you know what it is?
This is proof of your ignorance.
In a legal sense,
this is evidence of my self-defense,
What?
Well, I mean…
Now it's my turn!
Big brother.
What are you waiting for?
I didn't expect
such a polite and modest gentleman
in school
to have such a side.
What are you doing here?
What are you doing?
Come down and help!
He has helper.
Fight with me.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
I'm not interested in fighting violence
with violence.
I am just passing by.
Solve your own private affairs
yourselves.
Beat him!
Hit the below one.
Left.
Right.
Be careful of your back.
It hurts!
Senior.
You can do that.
Hold on a little longer.
You can keep your mouth shut!
Look out.
You beat harder! Pull away.
Here comes the police.
Who called the police?
Stop! Don't move.
I did.
And I'm a witness.
Get down.
So weak to fight.
You can keep your mouth shut.
You are strong
GO.
(Public Security)
Thank you, policemen.
Finished recording?
They
are identified crime of picking quarrels
and provoking troubles
I also…
What are you doing?
I also reported
Shen's larceny.
It may take a while.
I bought you some medicine.
I don't know which one is proper.
Choose it by yourself.
Did you
in case
Shen may take revenge on Qian Wei?
I knew it.
Well,
the milk tea wasn't wasted.
Thanks.
You're taking advantage of
legitimate loopholes.
Qian Wei won't appreciate
this kind of protection.
It's enough as you appreciate.
Senior.
OK, OK.
I know what you want to say.
Meeting violence by violence
is not
the best way,
but it's enough for me.
Qian Wei is innocent and kind.
In her
point of view,
justice can defeat everything.
But the villains won't stop doing evil
due to your kindness.
Only punishment can stop them.
This is the point of law.
Yes, yes, yes.
I get it.
I know that sometimes
we need the special measures
to protect people.
But according to Kant,
The moral rules of human society
need to be examined.
If everyone
insists on violence,
The most violent
individual will become
justice itself.
We study law
to become the constructor
instead of destroyer of law,
right?
But sometimes,
construction is
based on destruction.
Who said that
only destruction brings construction?
We can also construct
on an empty space.
Give me a piece of white paper…
Enough. Let's go.
Let's go.
OK.
Bye-bye.
Where's Lu Xun?
He hasn't finished the documents.
He's gone after
Chongwen left.
You two…
What's wrong with your arm?
Well,
There's a case of neighborhood dispute.
We are inquired to
make a field visit.
Senior was in a hurry
and fell from the motorcycle.
Yes.
I fell accidentally.
It's OK.
Chongwen.
Come here.
I have something to tell you.
There's a deep cooperation
between
AES and our university.
So, the first demonstration students
of Qingyun Project
are especially important.
I've applied for you.
Qingyun Project is held by
AES.
Chongwen,
among all the students,
I appreciate you the most.
So, I want you to work as an intern
in legal assistance foundation
set by Qingyun.
Well…
On the one hand,
the project is proceeding fast,
I need an assistant.
On the other hand,
the most importantly, I want you to
get more working experiences.
What's more,
the scholarship will be
more favorable.
Well, Professor Wang,
I haven't been graduated.
For the project
with large amount of working capital
like the foundation,
I'm not experienced in it.
What are you worried about?
Everyone starts from scratch.
I'm confident in you.
Listen,
AES is willing to help the young lawyers
to establish careers.
If you stand out
and let them notice you,
your life will be different,
you know?
I'm the person with experiences.
Listen,
There're only a few chances
in a person's life to succeed.
Think about it.
Seize it.
Don't be regret.
OK.
I'll take the chance.
Think about it.
AES.
What is AES?
It's a quite famous
leading company
with rich capital and seniority.
Such a good company
cooperate with our university.
Is it making charity?
Maybe they're thinking about
the long-term development
and wants to build a good fame.
Is there a written contract
or agreement
about the project?
Professor Wang didn't mention that.
I'll ask him later.
You should always be careful.
You have to analyze
whether it's sugar or poison
inside the cakes people give you.
Are you worrying about me?
No, no.
Qian Wei.
Why is there a paragraph
missing in your record?
Take a look.
And the
Article 129…
What are you doing?
Why do you peep at my stuff?
I've finished cleaning.
Do you need help?
Yes.
Come here.
Everybody comes here.
Come on.
Look who's here.
Your teacher's wife.
My wife.
Mrs. Yuan Qiao.
She is also the teacher
of students' affairs office.
She knows you've worked hard
and brought you some cakes.
Come. Chongwen, come to help.
Come on.
Coming.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mrs.
Come on, try it.
Thank you, Professor Wang.
I want this.
You've working hard.
Take your time.
- I've made a lot.
- Thank you.
It's for everyone.
Thank you, Mrs.
Thank you, Professor Wang.
Thank you, Professor.
Thank you.
It looks delicious.
You're worked hard today.
Come back to rest
after eating the cakes.
You have to continue the work tomorrow.
OK.
Thank you, Professor Wang.
Bye-bye, Mrs.
It's for everyone.
Come, Chongwen.
Come on.
Thank you, Professor Wang.
Sorry, Mrs..
Try it. Try it.
Take your time.
Come.
It's OK.
I know you've worked hard today.
It's late now.
After eating it.
Come back to take a rest.
OK.
So delicious.
It's none of your business.
You don't know
how complicated it is.
As for Professor Wang Ruogu's
divorce case,
do you know all the time
that Mrs. Yuan has been suffering
domestic violence?
We've won the case.
They're divorced.
And I've helped my litigant
win the custody of their child.
We don't have to concern
about the other businesses.
If I didn't
visit Mrs. Yuan,
and found out
that she's been suffering domestic violence
and that her schizophrenia was caused
by the domestic violence,
when would you tell me?
When we providing
legal suggestions,
we concentrated on
her psychological state all the time.
But this is caused
by our litigant.
Could you please calm down?
We lawyers are passive.
We can't
choose the litigant by ourselves.
Yes, but I've said that
I wanted to help the weak.
Helping the litigant
to bully the opposite
is against my original intention.
I can't let my life
be stained.
Could you please listen to me?
Indeed.
I know this is immoral.
But thanks to Professor Wang,
I own my life today.
Without him
who asked me
to join in Qingyun Project,
could I graduate successfully?
And this law firm was built
with his support.
Besides, there's no record
nor injury identification
about Mrs. Yuan's domestic violence.
Without evidence,
we can't win the case.
Do you remember that?
Also here,
when the law firm was just open,
You said you wanted to
be a good lawyer,
to help the weak,
and eradicate the injustice.
How much do you remember now?
It's hard to meet the opposite interests
and conform to opposite sides.
A good strategy
can help your litigant
but also hurt the opposite.
There's no way
to make the best of both worlds.
Our lawyers' work
is to protect the litigants' interest
as much as we can.
This is our profession.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You ensured your profession.
How about your morality?
You're only
finding excuses
for yourself.
It's right that
we have to help the side
we choose.
But the problem is that
you made the choice at the beginning.
(Business Records)
(Labor Contract)
(Party A (employer): AES Group)
(Party B (employee): Li Chongwen)
Are you going to leave the lawyer firm
to be the Legal Personnel of AES?
I was about to
take a chance
to tell you.
Also introduced by
Professor Wang?
How ridiculous I am to
talk about morality with you.
You've changed your dream.
I haven't.
You're my dream all the time.
You're enthusiastic
and innocent.
If you continue to be like this,
you'll be hurt
by the reality so badly.
All the efforts I made
are because of you.
Do you understand?
Even if I'm hurt so badly,
I have a clear conscience.
How about you?
(Qian Wei)
(Chong&Wei Law Firm, Qian Wei)
(Labor Contract)
Let's go.
Thank you, Professor Wang.
Professor Wang is so nice.
I wish my boyfriend in the future
can be so considerable.
Excuse me, Professor Wang.
Could you please
check the record for me?
I'll wait for you outside the gate.
OK.
Professor Wang.
The roads are complicated,
and are unfamiliar to Mrs.
Let me see her off.
OK. OK.
Hurry up.
Mind your business first.
OK.
Go, go.
Thank you, Professor Wang.
Let me take them, Mrs.
It's OK, I can handle them.
Mrs., your hands are hurt.
I was knocked
when I made cakes by accident.
Eat the fruit.
Eat it.
Eat, it's fresh.
Could you just stop it?
Ziqi is little,
and so lovely.
Why did you do that?
You made everyone
so painful, you know?
Don't you know how much I love you?
Let's divorce.
Divorce?
Why divorce?
I've worked so hard for our family.
You don't have a job.
Why do you want to divorce?
Why?
Mrs.
You are hurt badly.
Let's go to examine it.
Never mind.
Don't' make a fuss.
(There're only a few chances)
(in a person's life to succeed.)
Think about it.
Seize it.
Don't be regretful.
The lawyers settle the disputes,
encourage kindness
and distance the crimes.
If you're
puzzled one day,
think about this sentence.
Don't take so-called morality
and procedural justice as excuses
for yourself to hurt others.
Mrs. Yuan,
I know we're the outsider,
and are not proper to something.
But for your goodness,
I want to remind you.
If you're hurt again next time,
call the police
and examine the injuries.
Keep the evidence.
Violence is violence.
Don't trust
the lie of love.
If you don't
take actions now,
when you can't stand it,
you are left with nothing.
Mrs. Yuan.
You know our phone number.
If one day
something unexpected happened,
or you want to
make some changes,
Please contact us.
We'll help you.
Thank you.
If these words were heard
by Professor Wang,
you'll lose the scholarship
of Qingyun Project.
Just now,
it came across me
a sentence you said,
lawyers encourage kindness
and distance the crimes.
We're like the weather conditions
to inform those
who don't know the danger is approaching
to take umbrellas.
I was hesitant just now.
It's their domestic affair.
I don't know whether I should interfere.
But when I saw
your worrying facial expression
which is like
the prediction of
dark clouds in my mind.
Qian Wei,
remember that,
I won't be the person
you said.
Good.
My foresee didn't come true.
I hope you'll never be
that kind of person.
Super Mary
is holding mushrooms
fighting with monsters
and grows stronger.
but it gradually forgets
that the goal of the journey
is to rescue the princess.
Well,
are you the princess?
I'm princess' dad.
OK.
Princess' dad.
What did Mrs. Yuan say to you?
Do you know that the person
suffering from domestic violence
wears long sleeves even in summer?
I saw the injuries in
Mrs. Yuan's hands.
My dad
knows many
good lawyers.
They can help.
According to the present situation,
if the litigant doesn't claim,
we can't interfere.
But I reminded her
to protect the evidence.
If one day,
they have to confront,
she can provide the strong evidence
to protect herself.
But I'm planning
to write a paper
on it.
Let's bet on
who will publish a paper
on Legal Study.
So naive.
I have a question for you.
You said you wanted to
be a judge.
How would you judge
in this case?
All the evidence prove
that the party is with tendency
of domestic violence.
But he has prepared
all the
evidence
against the victim.
How would you judge?
I can only conform to
the judicial procedure.
Both parties have the right to
defend themselves.
Of course, I'm sorry
that I can only judge
according to the facts and evidence
they provided
and their debate.
But you know,
in real life,
many people can't
get the favorable evidence
due to various reasons.
I know
it's procedural justice.
It's the foundation
of substantive justice.
You mean,
if procedures are ruined
and rules are overthrown,
law will be
of no significance.
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I've got countless things to do♪
♪Possibilities never end♪
♪I force myself to do it all♪
♪I'm lucky to have you in my future♪
♪Who will do everything with me♪
♪Even if I have to lose♪
♪Numberless things♪
♪Even if I have to lose everything♪
♪I can't live without you♪
♪One of seven billion♪
♪I also cherish your soul so much♪
♪Girl I swear I love you♪
♪Without reservation Be my only girl♪
♪You're my only girl♪
♪The most beautiful memory♪
♪The most special definition♪
♪Yeah baby♪
♪I'll fight the world for you♪
♪I want to grow old with you♪
♪And travel around the world together♪
♪Wherever you are♪
♪It's my whole world♪
♪I'm your umbrella♪
♪I'll shelter everything for you♪
♪Let's travel
across the most beautiful border♪
♪Without saying goodbye♪
♪What has excited us♪
♪Our love in the precious life yeah♪
♪Lie down and enjoy the sky♪
♪I hold you in my arms♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪You still need me♪
♪How to prove♪
♪You know♪
♪How much I love you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪For the rest of your life I will♪
♪Keep all my promises♪
♪For you♪
♪What's to be continued♪
♪Prediction♪
♪You're exactly the one
for the rest of my life♪