A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
EPISODE 15
Hello?
There's more to shoot?
Are you sure?
Why wasn't I aware?
All right.
"A music video series?"
Was I blind at that time?
How did I miss this part of the contract?
Qingqing.
Why are you up so early?
What's up?
It's nothing.
I guess I just fell into Situ Feng's trap.
A horrible trap.
I was told that you could even
skydive over there.
I want to go so badly.
-I really want to go!
-So cool!
Hey.
What are you guys talking about?
You sound so excited.
Hey, did you know, soon, we'll be leaving
for our college excursion.
College excursion?
It's for everyone in the Student Council.
A two-day and one night trip.
Is it like a field trip
for elementary students?
-What's so different about this excursion?
-Gosh.
Perhaps, you're not aware
that Ming De College excursion
has its traditions and is very popular.
It's the best time
to confess to the person you like.
Countless of romantic relationships
happened during this event.
Are you sure?
Of course, I am sure.
Look.
This couple.
That couple.
And that couple.
They were all a product
of last year's excursion.
Furthermore, the Leonids meteor shower
is happening this year.
The success rate for love confessions
will surely increase.
Qingqing, do you have someone you like?
Me?
-Yes, do you?
-She's blushing.
-Who is it?
-No one!
All the guys here are too immature
for me to like them.
Class is starting.
Let's go.
Gu Nanxi.
-Yes?
-Class is starting.
Yes, it's starting.
It's starting.
Most of you would have heard
that the time for
Ming De College's excursion has come.
Calm down!
For this excursion,
we'll be going to Luzui cliff.
It'll be a camping trip
for two days and one night.
The trip is set for this weekend.
Don't you have a music video shoot
this weekend?
How did you know?
I'm your assistant.
Isn't it normal for me to know?
There is going to be credits
given for this excursion.
Unless it is absolutely necessary,
you cannot excuse yourselves.
See.
I can't excuse myself.
If Situ Feng is going to the excursion,
does that mean I won't have
to shoot the music video?
Hey, Chen Qingqing.
Does it make you that happy
to go camping with me?
Situ Feng, why are you so shameless?
Hello, Daniel.
Okay.
I got it.
That conversation was so short.
I suppose his manager is really efficient.
Hello, Daniel.
What's up?
Qingchen, here's the thing.
Situ Feng has plans for this weekend.
He's going to his college's excursion.
It's compulsory.
There'll be last minute changes
for our music video shoot.
Qingqing seems to be in a good mood.
Why is she giggling?
who is she talking to?
I see.
That's too bad.
I was all prepared for it.
But don't worry.
School is more important.
No, it's not cancelled.
We're just changing the location.
They will be going to Luzui cliff
so we'll shoot our music video there.
It was originally an outdoor shoot anyway.
Camping will start right after
the shooting.
We're killing two birds with one stone.
It might trouble you.
I hope you're okay with it.
No.
Don't worry, it won't affect you
that much.
I'll send you the schedule later. Bye.
Hello? I'm not finished yet. Hello?
Hello?
I wasn't even done yet.
What's wrong with you?
Are you high on drugs?
It's all because of you.
Because of me?
All right, you're dismissed.
Hand in your 10,000-word report
by tomorrow.
Ms. Chen.
Yes? How can I help you?
It's about the excursion this weekend.
Can I apply for a leave of absence?
Qingqing.
This is a compulsory trip
for all students.
We can't allow it.
Even Situ Feng can't excuse himself.
He has to come after his shoot ends.
Then is it possible for me
to go there a bit late?
I promise I won't be late
for the gathering, please?
Pretty please?
Can I?
All right.
Try to come as soon as possible.
Am I hallucinating due to extreme hunger?
The old witch is smiling now.
I think I'm hungry too.
LUZUI CLIFF
Okay, cut! That's a wrap.
-Thank you, director.
An assistant accidentally spilled
some of the warm water.
This is all we have left.
Qingchen, drink this. It'll warm you up.
Thank you.
Your hands are cold.
Why don't you drink it?
I'm all right.
My body can take it. I don't feel cold.
You should drink it.
The shoot was a success today.
The two of you look great together
and your chemistry has gotten better.
This...
How do you say it?
I have an eye for talent.
I've even thought
of your onscreen couple name.
Any guesses? Yes or no?
It's called Fengchen Couple!
Daniel.
Is my car ready?
-I'm in a hurry.
-It's over there.
Ready to go at your command.
What about me?
-How do I leave?
-Another car is on the way to fetch us.
-Just hang on for a while.
-Okay.
Hello?
What's the matter?
Well...
Our car broke down on the way here.
We might need to wait a little more.
So you're saying...
So I'm saying you can wait here with us.
Qingchen, are you in a hurry?
I...
Why don't you go with me?
My driver can drop me off
at the camping site
then send you off to town.
Should I tell him I'm heading
to the campsite too?
But we can't go together.
Don't trouble yourself.
I don't have any plans later
so I'm not in that much of a hurry.
Why don't you take his car?
I have no idea what time the other car
can make it here.
That's right, it's better to be in a car
-than to wait here.
-That's right.
They're right. Let's go.
Okay, screw it.
Okay.
Would the two of you follow us
to change your outfits?
Okay.
Fengchen Couple!
Isn't it awesome? Tell me it's awesome!
-It's awesome.
-Can't you add a little more zest?
Can't you say it like it's really awesome?
Qingchen, you did a good job today.
You did a better job than me
even with your packed schedule.
Whereas for me,
this is my only trip for today.
Right, last time I said
I'd take you to Yuncheng.
Gu Nanxi invited you several times,
but you weren't available.
There's always a chance next time.
Screw that. Let's do it today.
Luzui cliff is a popular destination
in Yuncheng after all.
But...
Didn't you say that you were free?
Yes, I did.
But the thing is
everyone there is your classmate
and I don't know anyone.
I don't think it's a good idea for me
to show up like that.
Don't worry, they're all really friendly
and Gu Nanxi will be there too.
You know him, right? Let's go.
But...
What do I do with Chen Qingqing now?
Gu Nanxi.
Qingchen?
What are you doing here?
You should thank your friend.
He dragged me here.
What a surprise, isn't it?
Yes, what a surprise.
But in a panicked kind of way.
Have a seat.
Please.
Situ Feng came with someone really pretty.
I saw them just now.
Could they be a couple?
Who would date Situ Feng?
His fans will get really mad at her.
-Hey, Xinya.
-Feng.
Why are you here?
Isn't this our beautiful Miss Qingchen?
Yes, it's me.
It has been a while.
You're not a student from Ming De College.
Why are you here for our excursion?
Xinya, stop it.
We're all friends.
That's right, we're all friends.
-Can't we just hang out?
-She's my friend?
Chen Qingqing is gone,
but now Qingchen is here.
This sucks.
That's right.
Where's Chen Qingqing?
She's going to be late.
She told me that she's still on the way.
Give her a call.
Why isn't she picking up?
Chen Qingqing is an idiot.
Why is she running off on her own?
Chen Qingqing is a smart person.
She's going to be fine.
Don't worry.
Yes.
I don't think that classmate of yours
is unreliable.
Maybe she just didn't want to come.
This isn't an easy place to find.
Could she have really gotten lost?
Of course she wouldn't.
She's always full of ideas.
-Let's inform the lecturer.
-No.
This won't do. I will go look for her.
-Gu Nanxi, take care of Qingchen for me.
-Okay.
Hey, Feng.
Look around.
It's too dangerous
to be going around alone.
Let's just wait a little longer.
Xinya, I will be back soon.
Qingchen, I'm sorry.
I'm going to look for someone.
I'm sorry, guys.
I need to go to the washroom.
I'll go with you.
It's okay.
I'd like to walk around on my own.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to get myself lost
like that friend of yours.
Chen Qingqing!
Chen Qingqing.
Where did you go?
Why didn't you pick up your calls?
My cell phone's battery died.
What happened to your leg?
It's nothing. I'm here
because I wanted to use the washroom,
but when I came out of the washroom,
I noticed all the trees here
looked the same
so I walked around
and that's how I got lost.
Then I realized,
there were so many steps here
so I walked and walked
and sprained my leg.
Sit down, let me have a look at it.
-I...
-Mind yourself.
It's not a big deal. Seriously.
Where does it hurt?
-Here.
-Here?
It's your ankle again?
You're going to develop
chronic injuries, you know?
It's not that serious.
Don't lie to me.
Do you know everyone's worried about you?
Worried?
Are you saying you're worried about me?
Of course.
I was not the only one.
Gu Nanxi was also worried.
So was Fangfang.
Everyone was worried about you.
Can you walk?
Of course I can walk. Do you want to bet?
I can even run 100 meters
and be way ahead of you.
Just like this.
All right, save your energy for now.
Slow down.
Let's take baby steps.
Is your ankle really fine?
I have a friend to introduce you.
Friend? What friend?
Her name is Qingchen.
Qingchen?
Yes, I've told you about her many times.
Slowly. We're back.
-Hi, Munian. Gosh.
-Slow down.
-You're finally here.
-Yes.
You didn't pick up our calls.
We were really worried.
I'm so smart.
What could've happened to me?
-Am I right?
-You're right.
All you know is how to sprain your ankle.
I told you.
You guys were worried for nothing.
Hey.
Where's Qingchen?
Well, she said she wanted
to walk around for a while.
It's been half an hour.
Could something have happened?
Gu Nanxi.
This place is so isolated
for a girl to be alone.
You should look for her.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing. I just choked myself.
This is just a thought.
Maybe Qingchen
just wanted to have a look around
and spend some time by herself, you know?
Perhaps you guys shouldn't disturb her.
Hey, this won't do.
I brought her here.
I can't let her get into any accidents.
I'll have to go look for her.
I think I'm going to the washroom now.
I will be right back in a while.
Wait for me, okay?
Please help me look after this, thanks.
I'll be quick.
I'll be really quick!
Qingchen!
Were you looking for me?
We've found Qingqing.
I'll introduce you to each other.
-What?
-Let's go.
Where's Qingqing?
Qingqing, where are you going now?
To the washroom.
Where's Qingchen?
Hey, where's Chen Qingqing?
Where's Chen Qingqing?
Why is she gone again?
I'm going to look for her.
I'm sorry, please excuse me.
I need another visit to the washroom.
-Chen Qingqing.
-Yes?
Gu Nanxi.
Why are you here?
Were you looking for Chen Qingqing?
Let me help you check
if she's in the washroom.
You don't have to pretend anymore.
I already know everything.
Qingchen is Chen Qingqing.
When did you find out?
Actually, it's been a while.
Why didn't you tell me?
I believe you have your reasons.
Otherwise, you wouldn't want
to trouble yourself like that.
That's true.
The reason I'm here is because of my dad.
You probably didn't know this.
I've never met my mom and dad
since I was little.
My grandpa was the one who raised me.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
After my mom passed away,
my dad disappeared.
That's why I disguised myself.
I came to this college
without telling my grandpa.
It is all because I wanted
to search for my dad.
He graduated from Ming De College too.
Have you found anything yet?
This was what I found recently.
Not only was my dad an honors graduate,
he was also the president
of the Student Council.
No wonder you've been asking me
about the Student Council.
So are you planning
to ever tell Situ Feng about this?
Actually...
I haven't thought about
how to tell him yet.
But I do realize that my lies
are slightly getting out of hand.
Once I have the information I needed,
I will leave this place.
Gu Nanxi.
Can you please help me keep this a secret?
Okay.
Qing...
Now, I'm confused over what to call you.
I can swear to you
that my name is real.
Chen Qingqing is my real name.
All right, Qingqing.
I promise you.
But you have to promise me this too.
If you're facing any difficulties,
you need to tell me.
Never keep it to yourself.
-Okay, I promise.
-Okay.
I was wondering about you guys.
Where's Chen Qingqing? Did you see her?
Well, Qingqing ate too much earlier
thus Qingchen and I think
we should let her rest.
Then I shall go look for her.
-Don't!
Well, she could be sleeping
so let's not disturb her.
That's right.
But Chen Qingqing...
Class President, where are you guys going?
It was on the news that
the meteor shower will start
around seven in the evening.
We will be able to see the meteor shower
if we go up the hill.
After that, it's the campfire party.
Don't let the lecturer hear us, let's go.
That sounds interesting. Let me tag along.
Feng.
Let's go watch the meteor shower.
What about Qingqing?
Don't you worry.
We should go watch the meteor shower
with Xinya.
Just as we said before,
we have to show Qingchen around Yuncheng.
You should come too.
Let's get going or we will miss it.
Let's go.
Fangfang, let's walk together.
Here.
It's steep here, mind your steps everyone.
This path seems dangerous.
Plus, there are so many girls with us.
I think we won't be able
to reach the peak in time.
There's no phone connection too.
For the sake of safety,
why don't we go back down?
I agree.
Yes.
Safety comes first.
It feels eerie here
and it gives me the chills.
Let's head back.
I agree.
Let's go then.
Okay, let's go.
-Feng!
-Xinya!
They fell down. What should we do?
No, I need to save them.
-Feng!
-Calm down, Xinya!
Situ Feng!
Qingchen!
Feng!
It looks very steep.
Xinya, why don't you go back with the rest
and call for the rescue crew?
No! They're in danger right now.
How do you expect me
to leave them like this?
We're not leaving them.
We just need to think
of an effective strategy to save them.
Hua Munian, please call
for the rescue crew.
Xinya, we need the rescue team
to save them.
Hurry up!
Don't worry.
Wait for me here.
I'll be back very quickly.
-Hurry up!
-Hurry!
Class President, you should stay here
so the rescue crew will know
where to look for them.
I'll try to search for a way down.
Wait for me here.
Situ Feng.
Situ Feng, what's wrong?
Are you injured?
How are you feeling?
It should be fine.
Let's go. Let's move over there.
Slowly.
It should be fine.
I lost my phone. What should I do?
I lost mine too.
It's getting so dark here.
Without our cell phones...
What if Gu Nanxi can't find us?
What's going to happen to us...
Don't you worry.
I'm here.
Stop crying now.
It's freezing here.
Your tears will turn into ice
and it'll look really weird.
Why are you so talkative today?
Right, here.
Take it.
It'll keep you warm.
Gu Nanxi!
Anyone?
Hello!
Is anybody around?
Did we fall too far for them to hear us?
Probably, but I'm sure
they will come for us.
It's cold out here.
Let's go inside and rest.
This is a good opportunity to be a hero.
Gu Nanxi should be here.
I didn't expect
someone as serious as yourself
would choose a time like this
to make jokes about the situation.
Qingchen.
-Yes?
-What's wrong?
I'm not sure.
It hurts here.
Let me have a look.
You're injured here.
I like you.
Goodness.
What did I do?
Why am I being an idiot?
Qingchen.
When did you start liking me?
I'm not sure.
Maybe...
Maybe since the first time I met you.
Perhaps I've already liked you then.
I'm afraid that if I don't tell you now,
I might not have a chance later.
Qingchen.
I'm sorry.
I already have someone I like.
Who is she?
Chen Qingqing.
Chen Qingqing is the person I like.
I'm sorry.
So...
When did you start to like her?
Well...
At first,
I thought
she was rather special
even though she was troublesome at times.
She was
very stubborn.
She never cares if the whole world
thinks she's wrong.
She's still going to persevere.
Whenever we spend time together,
I feel very comfortable and relaxed.
I can just be myself without feeling
the burden of being an idol.
Later on,
gradually, I realized that
unknowingly, I began
to take notice on everything she does.
I keep on looking for her.
Whenever she interacts with other guys,
I would feel frustrated,
lousy and throw a tantrum at her.
Until one day,
I saw she was wrongly accused.
Then I knew
Chen Qingqing
is just like any other girl.
She too needs to be loved and cared for.
From that moment,
I was certain
that I have fallen for her.
I have fallen deeply for her.
I want to hold her in my arms
and protect her
even if
the world is against me.
Qingchen, look!
It's the meteor shower!
If Chen Qingqing was here,
it would be perfect.
Let's make a wish.
Okay.
Qingqing, don't tell me
that you like Situ Feng too?
What do you think of Gu Nanxi?
Did she find out
what happened at the cave?
She seemed furious
whenever I mentioned Qingchen.
Where's Qingqing?
She asked me to tell you
not to go see her.
Excuse me.
Stop running, you pervert!
We need to catch this pervert!
The reason you came to this college
was because of your dad, wasn't it?
So it was all a lie.
Liar!
If you ever need help,
you should come and look for me.
-Happy Birthday, Qingqing!
-Happy Birthday!
How did you know today was my birthday?
Baby, you should thank our president.
Thank you, Gu Nanxi.
Subtitle translation by June Tian