EPISODE 8
Situ Feng is so stingy.
Even the filming
of the music video is done at school.
What am I going to do
if someone recognizes me?
The female lead is here.
-Hello.
-Let's go to the dressing room.
-All right.
Daniel, the female lead is here.
-Qingchen, you're here.
-I'll leave her to you.
Where's Situ Feng?
What's going on?
Even the female lead is here.
Look at her, Mei.
This is the music video's main actress
who's perfect in terms of acting skills
-and appearances.
-Hello.
Come here, everyone.
Please get to know the female lead.
All of you must have synergy
to create a good music video.
Hello.
What's with the scarf?
It was raining when I was coming here.
It's for me to cover
my hair from the rain.
-I see.
-You can remove it now.
Take it off.
It's you.
Hello.
Nanxi.
Xinya.
You two...
Do you know each other?
Well, we've met once.
Hello.
When did you arrive?
This is our female lead, Qingchen.
Isn't she great?
Hello.
-Hello.
-Situ Feng.
Excuse me.
I think I should fix my makeup.
Sure.
Please excuse me.
Well, let's go through the script, okay?
-Come, let's go through it.
-All right, let's go.
Let's go, Mei.
I'm the Head of Entertainment
for Ming De College Student Council.
I'm here to provide aid.
What's with this guy?
You...
What's the color of your lipstick?
It's gorgeous.
Why is everyone so polite to me recently?
Right here.
This is the storyboard
for today's music video.
All of you can take a look.
Qingchen.
After this, we have a piano scene.
You don't have to actually play it.
Qingchen.
If you don't know how to play it,
I can teach you.
You should at least know
the basics if you want to act.
Hey!
I think I never said that
I can't play the piano.
My goodness.
I can't believe that you're so good at it.
A German classic,
Brahms's "Hungarian Dances No. 5".
Situ Feng.
Why are you filming the music video
on my birthday?
I don't care.
You and Nanxi!
Both of you need to celebrate my birthday.
Xinya, why don't you rest at home?
After we finish our filming,
let's watch a movie together.
You must keep your promise then.
Of course.
-Bye.
I think you will definitely
be the first generation
of a well-rounded artist
if you join our agency now.
Nanxi.
What are you looking at?
You're so into her.
She's the girl
I met at the wedding last time.
There were so many girls back then.
Why are you interested in her?
No, I just find her interesting.
Interesting?
With the agency's resources,
we can make a film just for you.
She's a bit interesting.
Aren't you only interested in Qingqing?
No way!
How is that possible?
Even someone who is picking
her nose is prettier than her.
The director is here.
This is our director.
-Hello.
-Hello, sir.
For this music video,
it's about a tormenting love.
Situ Feng and Qingchen
is a couple who just broke up.
Situ Feng, you're trying to make her stay.
The two of you will look at each other
right next to the piano.
But Qingchen shows a determined face.
Okay, you two should rehearse.
Get to know each other first.
Let's go over there.
Well, Qingchen.
This is your first filming, right?
You can ask me if you have any questions.
Do you have any questions?
No.
I just want to say.
All the tabloids mentioned that
you're a cold-hearted king.
But I can't believe that
you're quite friendly
towards girls in real life.
Actually, I don't really talk to girls.
It's just that...
What is it?
It's nothing.
When we're filming,
you need to think about your sad memories
so that you'll feel down.
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
Did you notice that
Situ Feng's isn't as cold as usual?
I think I saw him smiling.
Am I dreaming?
No, you're right.
I noticed it too.
Three, two, one.
Situ Feng.
You were so mean to me
when I was Chen Qingqing.
Now that I look beautiful,
you're trying to make a move.
Go to hell!
I'm sorry.
Are you okay, Situ Feng?
I'm fine, sir.
All right, let's do it again.
I'm sorry, sir.
Let's do it again.
-That's all for now.
-I'm sorry.
Okay.
Let's take a break.
I was...
Why were you so careless just now?
You always put your foot below mine.
I'll get a glass of water for you.
Despicable!
You always forced me to get water for you.
I have a sensitive stomach.
I can't drink cold water.
All right, I'll get hot water for you.
Sorry for the trouble.
Mr. Situ Feng.
Do you want me to burn my tongue?
I'll get a warm water then.
Thank you.
You don't look like a local.
I'm from Jincheng.
I just came here.
I believe you haven't had time
to tour around Yuncheng.
Yuncheng is really fun.
Really?
You'll know it when I bring you out.
You know my friend, Nanxi.
Don't you?
Cut! That's all for today!
Thanks for your hard work.
I can't believe that
you can play the piano well.
I heard you're from another city.
If there's a chance, I'll show you around.
There's no need.
I'm just having a short layover
before continuing my travel.
I'll leave after some time.
-Actually--
-It's okay.
I got her contact number.
I'll add you on WeChat.
For courtesy, we'll show you around.
-Yes.
-Since you insist...
All right.
My goodness!
I don't know who leaked the news.
Your fans have gathered outside.
I don't think they'll leave
if they don't see you.
What should we do?
What can we do?
We promised to watch a movie with Xinya.
If your fans discover us, it'll be...
Why don't you leave
while wearing this outfit?
-What?
-Again?
Okay, I'll check the situation first.
You should change your clothes.
Right, Qingchen.
I already transferred your pay.
Please check your account.
That was fast.
-Yes.
-Didn't you say that
it will take some time?
It's my own money.
Yours?
That's right.
The entertainment industry is complicated.
Did you do this for another purpose?
Gosh, what are you saying?
I knew you need the money
so I wanted to help you.
Who knows when will
your payment be approved?
Take a look.
I borrowed money from 9FBank app.
Return the money to me
after your payment is approved.
I'll pay back the money then.
The interest is lower
than a credit card's.
Plus, the procedure is simple.
My kindness has gone to waste.
I shouldn't have helped you.
Sorry for the misunderstanding.
Today, we must see
the female lead of His Highness's
new music video.
That's right! We must judge
whether she's worthy or not.
You're right.
Could that be her?
It looks like her.
Her dress looks the same
from the fan club's morning news.
I guess she looks decent enough
not to embarrass His Highness.
She looks a bit strong.
Is she going
to do anything to His Highness?
She won't. Look at the man next to her.
They look so close.
I think it's her boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
-We don't have to worry then.
Qingqing, thank you
for collecting the surgery fee.
But how did you get so much money?
I borrowed it from Situ Feng.
Didn't you say
that you're his fake assistant?
What happened?
Why would he lend you money?
You know that
Situ Feng is very warmhearted.
Plus, he earns so much money.
This much money is nothing to him.
But the money is life-saving to me.
I must thank him tomorrow.
That's not necessary, Fangfang.
You know it too, don't you?
Situ Feng won't admit that
he has helped others.
Right?
Fangfang.
Aren't you the guy
who stole the microphone?
Dalei, it seems like she recognizes me.
In case she knows that we're from Class 4,
will she inform our teacher?
Will the school expel us?
You're so dumb!
If you don't tell her
that we're from Class 4,
how could she know
that we're from Class 4?
Right, don't you dare say
that our boss is from Class 3.
Right, I can't tell her
Hey, idiots!
We're from the same school.
Can't you do everything in secret?
Chen Qingqing.
Why are you so afraid?
I just wanted to ask you out.
You won't reject me, right?
Yiyang!
Why did you bring us here?
We don't have any grudges with you.
Why won't you let us go?
Who brought her here?
Look at her, sir.
She's Qingqing's best friend,
Zhang Fangfang.
It's like "Buy one, free one."
I took her in case you needed her.
"Buy one free one"?
Did I give you the permission?
Do you think this is McDonald's?
I'm sorry.
I just want to use both of you
to meet an old friend, Situ Feng.
You won't mind, right?
You took us here so that Situ Feng
comes and save us?
Yiyang, I'm telling you.
Don't dream about it! It's impossible!
Situ Feng is a playboy.
He doesn't have the time for us.
We'll see later
whether he has the time or not.
Hello?
Situ Feng.
I heard you're close with your deskmate.
What do you want?
Qingqing is with me now.
She doesn't...
Look good.
What did you do to her?
Have you gone mad?
Let's have a chat
at Xiqiaotou Amusement Park.
If you don't come,
I can't guarantee Qingqing's safety.
You're dead if you touch
even a strand of her hair.
What's the matter?
Yiyang kidnapped Qingqing.
I'm coming with you!
Yiyang!
Hey, Yiyang!
Why are you doing this to Situ Feng?
Didn't you say that he won't come for you?
Cut the crap!
Nobody will get hurt if you cooperate.
I'm scared, Qingqing.
Don't be afraid, Fangfang.
Don't worry, I'm here.
Nothing will happen to us.
If they hurt us,
I won't let him go even if I'm dead.
Dalei, why don't we let them go?
Did you hear what she said?
She won't let us go even if she's dead.
Can you two cut it out?
You can either let us go
or operate this machine for us to enjoy.
All right. You want to play, right?
I'll let you two enjoy it.
Let me check your safety belts.
Let me tell you something.
Safety belts aren't safe.
When I was a child,
originally, I had an IQ of 250.
After that, while I was on a bus--
Let me go!
I'll let you fully enjoy it.
Hello?
Dalei! Don't mess with it!
Stop it right now!
Stop it!
All right, wait for me!
Ye Bei!
Dalei!
Hang on, I'll save you now.
Hurry!
You...
That's too dangerous!
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
WORK IN PROGRESS
Hang on.
Let's go in.
Where's Qingqing?
Your Highness.
Why are you so nervous?
Are you so worried about your girlfriend?
Yiyang.
Qingqing isn't my girlfriend.
Let her go.
Don't hurt the innocent.
If there's any problem, come at me.
Innocent?
Isn't Xinyu innocent as well?
For knowing a killer like you.
Yiyang!
It wasn't Situ Feng's fault.
Shut up, Gu Nanxi!
You're a goody-two-shoes
who acts nice to everyone.
-Are you getting used to being a dog--
-Yiyang!
I'll admit that it was my fault.
Don't drag others into this mess.
All right. You'll admit it, right?
Yet, you continue to be an idol.
You're still the descendant
of Situ family!
How can you say that you admit it?
You even used Xinyu to write a song.
Don't think that I don't know about it!
Let me tell you.
As long as I'm alive,
don't think of escaping
from the sins you have committed.
What do you want to do?
Don't ever sing "Breath" again.
Xinyu's death was my fault.
I'll always owe her my entire life.
Yiyang, let me make it clear for you.
I will never owe you!
Qingqing doesn't owe you too!
Because of Xinyu,
you can't live like nothing has happened.
You keep on mentioning Qingqing.
Do you deserve that?
Stop it, Yiyang!
What's the point of hurting yourself
and Situ Feng?
None of you can live your lives normally.
Do you have a conscience?
He caused Xinyu's death!
How can I let him go?
It's Xinyu!
-It was just an accident!
-Get out of the way!
Yiyang!
Let go of him!
Situ Feng!
Get off of him!
Sir, Qingqing ran away.
-What?
-I'm sorry, sir! I'm sorry!
-Chase after her!
-But she went into Hauntedland.
I'm scared.
Are you afraid of me?
Yes, but I'm more afraid of Hauntedland.
How useless!
Let's find her.
Situ Feng!
I'm warning you.
What happened today can happen again.
-Qingqing.
-Yes?
I'm scared.
Don't worry, Fangfang. Stay with me.
We'll be fine.
Fangfang, I think
there's an exit in front.
Qingqing!
Where are you?
I'm scared.
Here.
Nanxi, go to that side.
I'll go to this side.
Let's meet at the exit.
All right.
Qingqing!
WORK IN PROGRESS
What a heroic act.
Why weren't you this brave back then?
-Yiyang, get out of the way.
-Where do you think you are?
Is this your house?
You can't leave as you please.
What do you want?
For Lan Xinyu,
you dragged an outsider into this mess.
It's pointless after all.
It's because she has
a relationship with you.
I can let her go today.
But
you must do what you promised.
Okay, I promise you.
Who is it?
It's me.
Yiyang?
What's the matter?
I sprained my ankle.
Give me your hand.
Don't waste time.
I'll bring you out of here.
Hang in there.
Get on the motorcycle.
You can put your arms around me.
Hello? Nanxi. I've saved Qingqing.
Wait for us outside.
This guy, Yiyang...
Is his brain flooded with powder?
Qingqing!
Chen Qingqing.
You were awake just now, weren't you?
Chen Qingqing!
Situ Feng?
Where is this place?
A Ferris wheel?
Wasn't I at Hauntedland just now?
Why am I here, Situ Feng?
Your acting is too much.
Let me take a look, Situ Feng.
What happened to your face?
I'm fine. How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
It has nothing to do with you anyway.
Let me take a look.
Thank goodness you didn't lie to me.
Don't you know that
you're being rude right now?
Do you know that it's rude to talk to me
because you're so short?
Come over here.
What do you want?
What's wrong?
Are you that great
just because you're tall?
Can you simply squeeze
my face just because you're tall?
Stop fooling around.
Do you still want to take advantage of me?
No one was taking advantage of you!
Qingqing.
I told you not to touch me.
-What's wrong?
-It's my fault for falling down.
Mind your own business!
Let me take a look. Don't move.
Get up first.
Can you get up?
Did you sprain your ankle?
Why are you so careless?
-Be gentle.
-Let me check.
You're always so careless.
So sloppy.
It hurts.
Does it still hurt?
Does it feel better?
I drove all over Yuncheng
to find an unattractive person like you.
Are you saying that I'm ugly?
Hey, you're so rough.
How would I know that you're so weak?
You fainted because you were scared.
It wasn't because I was scared.
I fainted because I fell down.
So you're not a coward,
but you lack the sense of balance.
You're strong-willed,
but your body is weak.
Who are you calling weak?
You're doing it again.
I'm sorry.
Stop fooling around. I'll send you home.
It's swollen.
Can you still walk?
I can't.
I'll carry you then.
Get on me.
Will anyone still believe
the words of a liar?
I'll tell everyone about your evil deed.
Why is it locked?
Did you know Lan Xinyu?
Hey!
Don't meddle in other people's affairs,
especially in this matter!
I don't want to release this song.
I'll bear the consequences myself.
You look so pretty today, Qingchen.
Yes, we're friends.
So are you only friends
with beautiful girls?
Who is Qingqing to you then?
Subtitle translation by Michelle Chai