EPISODE 7
When breathing hurts without you
It's such a great song!
With more than a million reposts on Weibo,
goodness, this is an achievement.
We should take advantage
of the song's popularity now.
We'll include "Breath"
into your upcoming album.
This could be a great opportunity
to make a fortune.
What do you think, Ms. Wang?
Good.
Since it's so well-received,
you guys should give it a go.
Under one condition.
I want this song to go viral.
Not a problem, Ms. Wang.
I will do my absolute best
to make this album a hit.
Good, I have to go now.
Carry on with the discussion if you will.
-Got it.
-Okay.
We should see Ms. Wang off.
-See you, Ms. Wang.
-See you.
-Take care, Ms. Wang.
-Bye.
I didn't expect Ms. Wang
to have a change of mind.
Daniel, you're looking good today.
You're good at sucking up to others.
Daniel, thank you.
I'm your manager.
You don't have to be so polite.
Speaking of Hebiancao,
don't you remember anything about him?
Hebiancao?
Why are you bringing this up?
Look, there was only a small group
of media representatives that day
and I didn't see other people.
That means that Hebiancao
is very likely to be your classmate
who has admired you for a long time.
That couldn't be. Hebiancao created
the comic to spread rumors about me.
Hence, I have a reason to believe
Hebiancao is a girl.
They say they're not into you,
but their action proved otherwise.
They say they don't like you
when in fact they do.
What are you doing?
Did you forget that I am a girl?
I could sue you
for defamation of character.
I keep on forgetting
to treat you like a girl.
Chill out.
QINGQING'S ERRANDS SERVICE
OPEN FOR BUSINESS
Our secretarial department has been
documenting all new registrations.
It has been going well.
Chen Qingqing.
Are you waiting for my invitation
to take down the meeting minutes?
I'm ready, chief.
Please go ahead.
Moving on, we might need help
from other departments...
Bye.
Oh, right. Chen Qingqing.
I almost forgot to tell you.
Your final task for this training
is to take all of these student IDs,
make sure to stamp
and register each of them
before distributing
to the respective student leaders.
Please finish it today.
And thanks in advance for your hard work.
We've got to go now.
There's so much to do!
NAME: LAN XINYA
Are you trying to gang up on me?
Just you wait
until it's your payback time!
Fangfang.
What's wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
I'm okay.
I'll feel better after a nap.
Fangfang, what do you feel like eating?
Fangfang.
Is there something bothering you?
Actually, my dad is hospitalized.
What happened to your dad?
Should I go to the hospital with you?
It's all right.
My dad has always been sick.
This time he needs surgery.
It's going to cost more than 100,000 yuan.
I have no idea
how I am going to afford it.
Fangfang, don't you worry.
Take it easy, I'm here.
I will help you find a way.
It's okay, Qingqing.
I will try to solve it by myself.
I'm going to the hospital tonight.
I won't be having dinner with you later.
I've got to go.
Bye.
These three girls, aren't they...
They're here, let's go.
Xinyan.
Have you noticed?
The way people are looking at us today.
Isn't it rather strange?
Yes.
Judging by the way they look at us,
it seems like they're just admiring us.
Perhaps it's because of our powerful aura.
BARE FACE REVEALED
IMPENDING DOOM, ABSOLUTE HORROR
Fangfang, I've figured out a solution.
A solution for what?
A solution for us to raise a large sum
of money for your dad's surgery.
Look.
"Female Lead Audition for a Music Video"?
You're not missing
this important information, right?
"Prize money of 150,000 yuan."
But you missed
this important information here.
"Outstanding qualities are required."
Outstanding qualities?
I have them.
-Qingqing.
-Yes?
I know you're really trying to help me,
but you don't have to try so hard.
I'm not.
It's simply a role for a music video.
How difficult can it be?
Don't worry.
How can Chen Qingqing
be so full of herself?
Look at her.
She has the guts to join the audition?
-Qingqing.
-Yes?
Are you going to audition
for our campus' music video?
Yes.
The 150,000-yuan worth of prize money
is going to be mine.
My application form has been filled out.
I'll submit it after this class ends.
Then I'm off to practice
for my performance.
Hey, I suggest that you skip the audition
so that you don't trouble of yourself.
I, Chen Qingqing,
am not someone
who admits to defeat easily.
Don't assume that everyone is like you,
who judges people by their looks.
I--
I am going to use my talents
to prove everyone wrong.
FEMALE LEAD AUDITION FOR A MUSIC VIDEO
Wait for your number to be called.
Next.
Hi, I am here for the audition, thank you.
Hi.
You may go home and wait for our call.
-Next.
-Hey, wait.
The other girls are all waiting here.
Why should I wait at home?
Just go home and wait.
-Please leave.
-Exactly, hurry up and leave.
Stop blocking others from the queue.
-How annoying.
-Get lost.
There were rumors
about you joining the audition.
I didn't believe it at first.
Apparently, it's true.
So what if it's true?
Are you not aware that they're looking
for someone with outstanding qualities?
Look at yourself.
Do you really think you could be
in Situ Feng's music video?
What?
This is Situ Feng's music video?
Stop pretending.
Back then, you pretended to be
his assistant.
Now, you're trying
to approach him on purpose again.
Who wants to approach him?
I can't wait to get away from him.
Anyway, let me tell you this.
I'm going to be the female lead
in this music video.
It's better for you to give up now.
I almost forgot.
It seems someone's application
hasn't been accepted
and was eliminated right away.
Lan Xinya!
All right, I've got to go.
My time is precious.
Bye.
A music video by Situ Feng?
There's no way I'll ever be in it
even if he begs me to!
But the prize money...
Gosh.
For the sake of Fangfang,
I will sacrifice myself.
No one will recognize me
without makeup anyway.
No.
Grandpa's men could already
be here in Yuncheng.
Why do I have to deal
with these shallow people
and put up with them ordering me around?
But without the prize money,
Fangfang won't be able
to pay for the surgery.
Hi.
Your name is Qingchen?
I'm sorry, I didn't provide my picture.
That's not a problem.
I left out my phone number too.
No worries at all.
I think you're a great fit for the role.
Please take a seat.
Thank you.
I am so jealous.
-I'm so jealous.
-Who is that?
-Lan Xinya!
-She's outstanding!
-She's lovely!
-She's the best!
Welcome, everyone.
Congratulations, all of you for advancing
into the second round of the audition.
We have a test for you today.
Please act out an emotional scene
as if you've been dumped by your lover.
Your act should portray
how miserable you are after such breakup.
Shall we start?
Go to hell.
Why would you leave me?
How could you?
Should I look it up online?
HOW SHOULD YOU FEEL AFTER A BREAKUP?
That's it!
The girl without any facial expression.
Yes, you.
You have a unique style and composure.
I like how you stared
at the breakup text messages,
looking all dejected and exhausted.
Your acting
was how I imagined
the female lead to be like.
You were born to be an actress.
I think she's the right girl for the role.
However, why do I find your face familiar?
Have we met before?
Are you sure?
I don't find your face familiar.
As the saying goes,
"Swans are beautiful,
but they all look similar
while it's easy to spot an ugly duckling."
Since you're the chosen one,
I'll cut to the chase.
Situ Feng is the male lead
of this music video.
Situ Feng. Do you know him?
There's a reason
this audition was kept a secret
as we want to keep the mystery alive
for this music video.
I hope you'd understand.
Shooting will start next weekend.
You should get prepared before that.
Are there any questions?
I have a question about my prize money.
When can I get it?
You're selected to work with your idol.
Aren't you excited?
Why am I constantly
running into odd people these days?
As for that 150,000 yuan,
it will be given to you
once the shooting ends.
We can meet up then.
By the way, this video
that you'll be shooting
is Situ Feng's latest single.
"Breath."
"Breath"?
Yes.
Here's the demo.
Bring it home and listen to it.
Keep this to yourself or that 150,000 yuan
might slip away.
Qingqing, you're back.
Fangfang.
I'm sorry.
I didn't make it through the audition.
It's okay.
I'll think of other ways.
Fangfang, don't worry.
Before this coming weekend,
I'll solve this problem for you.
It's okay.
Please trust me.
-Let me handle this.
-Okay.
I'll make a move first.
QINGQING'S ERRANDS SERVICE
LITTLE BEE, A BOX OF CHOCOLATE
"Little Bee, a box of chocolate"?
Why can't I remember
selling chocolate to this person?
Little Bee?
What kind of name is that?
Weren't you eliminated from the audition?
Why are you so late?
It's none of your business.
Qingqing, don't be sad.
It's okay that you're eliminated.
I've already told her
not to embarrass herself.
From now on,
you should learn to talk less.
I don't want others
to know that you're my assistant.
I don't want to look stupid.
You're right.
I didn't make it.
Thanks for your concern.
I wasn't concerned at all.
You seem to be good at eating.
If you join an eating contest,
maybe you will stand a chance.
Apologies, Your Highness.
You shouldn't have placed
your foot underneath mine.
Do you know it's blocking my steps?
Also, to have your foot stepped on
by someone like me
must have hurt real bad.
-Qingqing.
-Hang on.
Can you share some gossip
about Situ Feng with us?
I don't want to talk
about that person today.
But...
I have a question for you guys.
Do you know who is Little Bee?
Of course I do.
Little bee buzzing
And off they fly into the bushes
That's not what I meant.
That's not it!
I don't know about Little Bee,
but I do know about Situ Feng.
Hey.
Why don't you guys
go ahead to the canteen now?
You guys go ahead.
I left something in the classroom.
Wait for me.
LITTLE BEE
Little Bee!
I caught you!
-What are you doing?
-Lower down your voice.
-The class next door can hear you.
-Situ Feng.
The burden of being an idol
has robbed you of your abilities
to buy your own food?
I have to do this to stay in shape
and my diet is restricted by my agency.
Snacks are prohibited.
If I get caught,
it's considered a violation
of the contract.
So what if you've got so many supporters?
You can't even eat a bar of chocolate.
If you agree to one of my conditions,
I'll keep this a secret
and I won't tell anyone.
-Condition?
-Yes.
What condition?
If you agree to help me run errands,
then I'll keep this secret for you.
Are you trying to use me for publicity
to get more customers?
Listen to me.
It's never going to happen.
Situ Feng, think about it.
If you help me run errands,
it's an opportunity to exercise
and stay in shape.
You could eat plenty of snacks.
Nobody would notice.
What do you think?
Let me tell you.
This chocolate
honestly tastes amazing.
Do you want to have a bite?
Are you sure you're not going to have any?
Why don't I
give you two more? What do you think?
Isn't that Situ Feng?
It looks like he's delivering something.
Let's go.
Yang Menglin,
Zhang Jingwen.
Here are your snacks.
Here.
Here you go.
Here's yours.
How much are they?
Three plus five plus eight...
We haven't worked out
the total cost in advance.
Chen Qingqing, you've trapped me.
Situ Feng, you haven't
collected your money!
Are my eyes playing tricks on me?
Situ Feng is now running errands?
It used to be Chen Qingqing, right?
What's going on today?
What's wrong with Situ Feng today?
I want Situ Feng
to run errands for me too.
It feels like
-he's delivering snacks as my boyfriend.
-Yes.
It must have been Chen Qingqing again!
That was quick.
Are you all done?
Here's your money.
That's a lot.
You're worthy of your title
of an idol.
Look how much tips you've got.
That's right.
Great job.
You seem a little weak.
Excuse me?
-Who said I'm weak?
-I'm saying that.
There were only two errands
and you're running out of breath.
I'm not out of breath!
Potato chips as a reward from your boss.
Catch.
Go ahead and eat it.
I shouldn't eat this.
Look how much control other people
are having over your life.
Don't you feel frustrated?
-Give it back if you're not eating it.
-Who said I'm not eating it?
I used to feel frustrated,
but I don't anymore.
That's because feeling angry or frustrated
serves no purpose for me
which is why I've chosen to let go.
Why is having a purpose so important?
Why is it that for everything we do,
we have to define its purpose?
If you're angry, just be angry.
Eat and drink whenever you want.
Eat, drink, play and have fun.
Eating is the most important thing.
Don't you know?
Why think about it so much?
Forget it.
I should say something useful.
One hundred and twenty-five!
Are you going to eat this?
Listen, Situ Feng.
With the calories we consume every day,
as long as you find a way to burn them,
you'll be able to stay in shape.
Keep going!
One hundred and twenty-eight!
One hundred and twenty-nine!
Come on, Situ Feng.
Five.
Don't even think about eating.
I'm not.
Are you still trying to be sneaky?
Focus on height rather than speed.
Continue, higher!
Come on, Situ Feng!
Keep going.
Situ Feng, why are you carrying
huge waterbottles?
It's hot outside!
I'm thirsty!
Situ Feng.
Was it raining outside?
Why are you all wet?
I went skipping.
Oh, skipping.
Skipping?
Chen Qingqing's sorcery is frightening.
Let me join.
Am I hearing this correctly?
Haven't you always said
playing basketball will mess up your hair
which was why you never joined us?
That's in the past. I'm playing today.
Catch this.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, please.
Excuse me. Let me through.
-That's so cool!
-That's amazing!
That suffocating burden
of being an idol...
It's none of your business.
Sorry, excuse me.
Thank you.
Hello?
Yes, speaking.
Tomorrow?
Where is the location?
Ming De College?
Okay, see you.
What am I going to do
if someone recognizes me?
It's you.
Situ Feng.
Now that I look beautiful,
you're trying to make a move.
Chen Qingqing is with me now.
Don't ever sing "Breath" again.
Situ Feng!
Subtitle translation by June Tian