EPISODE 11
Ugly like me?
Don't you have anything nice to say to me?
Fangfang.
What are you looking at?
Zhang Fangfang.
-What is it?
-What are you looking at?
Nothing.
If I'm not mistaken,
this is a man's jacket.
Come on, don't be shy. Just say it.
No, it's nothing.
We have class tomorrow.
You should go to bed now.
Fangfang, you're blushing.
-Hey, Qingqing!
-Yes?
The bonsai I gave you yesterday,
don't water it too much.
Goodness.
You should take care of yourself first.
Can't you be a little nicer?
Sometimes, you're quite interesting.
You can do quite a lot.
Can you just stop pulling that scary face?
You're the scaredy-cat here, Feng.
When I'm a little nicer, you like me.
But when I'm a little rude,
you chicken out right away!
Hey, since when do I like you?
I mean
who gave you the idea to determine
what girls should be like?
If we want to define ourselves,
we've got to be modest and gentle
to everyone else.
What era are we in now?
Actually, that's not what I meant either.
You just need half
of Qingchen's qualities.
Let me ask you this.
Do you know what Qingchen is like?
I see that she has a special place
in your heart.
She's the lead actress of my music video.
Not only she's gorgeous and polite,
but she's also approachable.
You should get to know her
when you get the chance.
You've got a lot to learn from her
to improve yourself.
Right, Gu Nanxi?
Yes.
And she's beautiful.
Her fingers were dancing on the piano keys
just like fairies.
Musical fairies.
Hey! You two rich kids.
Now, I really want to buy a huge mirror
so I can show you
what you really look like.
I want to ask the both of you.
Don't you notice anything strange
about this Qingchen?
She always shows up with a "bang"!
Right in front of you.
Then she goes "bang" again and disappears.
Comes without a shadow,
goes without a trace.
There's more.
Doesn't she always wear a very long dress
every time you meet her?
That's because she has no feet.
And no shadow.
Good point.
Every time I try to call her,
I couldn't get through.
And sometimes,
the number is out of service.
You'd only meet her
at a certain time and in a certain place.
Yet it's not so easy to see her.
Don't tell me
that you've been seeing a ghost?
Look over there!
Chen Qingqing, what are you up to?
Fangfang!
Why did I see you with Lin Yiyang?
No.
My clothes got ripped off.
Then he lent me his jacket.
I was just returning it.
There's nothing between us.
Is that so?
Listen, Fangfang.
You've got to stay away from Yiyang
if you don't need his help.
He's not what he seems to be.
Don't worry, I know that.
-Hello, ma'am.
Fangfang, go back to the dorm.
I'll see you there in a minute.
Bye.
Hi, Ms. Chen.
-What is it?
-I want to ask you.
Is there a great alumnus in our school
that goes by the name of Xiao Jingnan?
Why do you ask?
It's like this.
The Students Council
is now sorting out the archives
of the school's most notable students.
So I'd like to get to learn more
and get to know him better.
He was indeed an excellent person.
Really?
Do you know him?
His data is at the College Archives.
If you want to know more,
you just have to go there.
Is there anything else?
No.
Thank you, ma'am.
May I have your attention, please?
The candidate list
for the school's play has been announced.
Come and see if you've made the cut
to share the stage with the stars!
Excuse me.
May I take a look?
"Instructed by Chen Xiao?" That means...
This is fantastic.
No way!
Even the witch can't keep her day job?
This is really weird.
Qingqing, look.
You made the cut.
I'm at the top of the list!
They really have good a taste.
This is the list of supporting actors.
The main cast is over there.
It's them again!
Do you think you can be the main actress?
-You'd be a laughing stock.
-Yeah.
This opportunity
is certainly made for Xinya.
You should just stick to being an extra.
Yeah.
You two take a good look at the list.
I don't know how many rungs
your names are below mine.
You didn't even make it as extras.
And as for you...
How do I put it?
I've never seen how well you act.
So you want to see
how well I strut my stuff on stage?
Then I'll just have to wait and see.
But you'd better not let me down!
Bring it on.
What's wrong, Feng?
First of all,
congratulations for making the cut
into the Beauty and the Beast lineup.
In the next few hours,
I will conduct the drama class
on behalf of Ms. Wang.
And in two weeks,
we will have a performance.
Gu Nanxi, you managed to come up
with a good plan.
You shall be the director.
Yes, ma'am.
Next, we will assign your roles.
Your rehearsal begins now.
In this scene,
Belle trespasses the West Wing
and then she sees a rose.
The Beast drives her away.
CHIP, MRS POTTS, COGSWORTH, LUMIÈRE
Could it be that no one notices my talent?
I don't think
it's just a matter of talent.
COGSWORTH, LUMIÈRE
Feng.
This is my first stage play,
so I don't have any experience.
Can you give me some advice?
Well, Xinya, you're all good.
I believe in you.
All right.
Ready?
Action!
What are you doing?
Did you touch it?
I'm sorry!
Do you realize
that you could have damned us all?
But I didn't mean any harm.
Get out!
I'm sorry!
Get out of here.
Promise or no promise,
I can't stay here another minute!
Cut! Stop!
Nanxi, how did I do? Did I play it well?
Not...
Not too bad.
It's just that
you need to give your movements
a little restraint.
A little restraint?
Because you moved about so much.
We don't need that.
Got it?
Got it. A little restraint.
Okay, let's do it again.
All right.
Take two. Ready?
Action!
Did you touch it?
I'm sorry!
You could have damned us all!
But I didn't mean any harm!
Get out!
Promise or no promise,
I can't stay here another minute!
One more time!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean any harm.
Get out of here.
-One more time!
-I didn't mean any harm.
Get out!
One more time!
I didn't mean any harm.
Get out!
Promise or no promise,
I can't stay here another minute!
Ms. Chen.
Can I be frank with you?
-Go ahead.
-I think that
if we want to improve the quality
of the play,
I think the role of Belle should go to
Situ Feng!
Qingqing.
You shouldn't joke around all the time.
Ms. Chen, I'm not joking at all.
Gu Nanxi can prove it.
Situ Feng's women's clothes
are really nice.
Yes, they are.
Gu Nanxi!
Are you both pulling a prank on me?
Goodness, seriously.
What I said is all true.
We're praising you,
so don't give me that look.
All right.
I want to tell you the truth too.
You're the best to play the Beast.
Who are you calling the Beast?
Look, your temper is much worse
than a beast.
Situ Feng, do you want me to send you
flying in the air with my spinning kick?
You dare?
Knock it off.
You're Belle
and you're the Beast.
-That'd be perfect.
-No!
At least, I gained something.
You both seem well-coordinated
when you were arguing.
So it'd be nice
for you to take these roles.
But Ms. Chen--
How about this?
Let's call a vote!
Hands up if you don't want Situ Feng
to play Belle!
Wait!
This is not fair.
No one put their hands up.
All right.
I've decided.
Qingqing will be the Beast
and Situ Feng,
you'll play Belle.
Hey, beauty.
As for Lumière,
Xinya will take the role.
Beauty.
Ms. Chen,
if we give Xinya a supporting role,
she won't accept it.
Ms. Chen,
Xinya doesn't think highly
of such petty roles.
How about you cast her as Gaston?
It's a lead role too.
Perhaps.
Sorry.
I was a little engrossed by it.
How did I do? A little better?
In this scene,
Belle trespasses the West Wing
and then she sees a rose.
The Beast drives her away.
They gave Qingqing the lead role.
What's got into that witch's eyes?
What are you doing?
Did you touch it?
No.
I didn't mean any harm.
Do you realize
that you could have damned us all?
I'm sorry.
Get out of here.
Get out!
Hey.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Situ Feng, you're burning up.
Do you have a fever?
You'd better go get some rest.
Ms. Chen.
Situ Feng seems to have a fever.
Feng.
What happened to you?
His head is warm.
Hey, take him to the infirmary now.
Got it.
Take it easy now.
I'm going with him.
The rest should stay here.
You'll take his place.
-You'll act with Qingqing, okay?
-Okay.
Gu Nanxi.
Qingqing.
How's Situ Feng now?
He got a fever because of his cold.
He's resting at home now.
Maybe he caught a cold
when he fell into the pool
during his last photo shoot?
What?
-He fell into the water?
-Yes.
Now I get it.
What do you get?
Is he so afraid of water?
Yes.
You're kidding me, right?
He's such a big boy!
It looks like you're concerned about him.
Am I?
Of course, classmates have
to look out for each other.
We often ask about each other, right?
We often do that, right?
-Really?
-Yeah!
I care about you too.
It's always like that.
It always is.
Qingqing, I heard Feng is sick.
Aren't you his assistant?
-Well, I--
-Can you help us
send our little kind regards to him?
-Me too!
Settle down!
One by one.
-Thank you!
-That's great!
Qingqing.
It looks like you can't leave your job
as his assistant.
Why do I have to do
something like this for them?
Hello.
Welcome to the Situ Residence.
And you are?
I'm Situ Feng's assistant.
-Come on in.
-Thank you.
Hello.
Who are you?
Hello, sir.
I'm Situ Feng's assistant.
So you're Mei.
Yes, I'm Mei.
That's a lot you're carrying.
Carry them for her.
No. You really don't have to.
These are all from Feng's fans.
I have to bring them up myself.
Thank you, sir.
I'm going upstairs.
-Can you see where you're going?
-Yes, I can!
It looks like he's seriously ill.
Chen Qingqing!
What the hell?
I...
I was just helping you cover up.
You were drooling at my face!
What?
I'm not interested in some guy
who wears childish underwear!
Why you...
Don't tell anybody!
I'm doing some people a favor
by sending you these gifts.
They're here.
I'm leaving now.
Hey, Chen Qingqing!
What now?
Why are you drenched?
Did you get caught in the rain?
Yeah, it was raining.
It was raining heavily.
You better get changed,
or you'll catch a cold.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Those clothes should warm you up.
Feng.
Lan Xinya.
-What is she doing here?
-I don't know!
What should I do now?
-Hide!
-Feng!
No.
She could see you here.
Feng!
No.
That's much worse!
Then tell me where to hide!
I don't know!
Feng!
Xinya.
I was worried sick about you.
Are you feeling better now?
A lot better.
I came right after class.
Let me see.
It looks like you're getting better.
But...
your complexion doesn't look normal.
It doesn't?
Never mind about that.
Today, I'll be taking good care of you.
Please, don't--
Come on in.
You, open the window to let in some air.
You three, make the room completely
clean with detergent.
The nurses are on standby for 24 hours
to monitor Feng's condition at all times.
Okay everyone, move it.
You, change Feng's blanket
to a slightly thinner one.
-See what's over here.
-No.
Put it down.
Feng!
Your blanket is so thick.
-Just change it.
-No, thanks.
The doctor said to use thick blankets when
you have a fever so you'll sweat it out.
-Is that so?
-Yeah.
Get him another blanket.
Here you go.
Allow me.
Gosh, Xinya.
Suddenly, I feel so hot.
Take off my blanket.
Hurry, take it off.
Xinya.
What is it, Feng?
You'd better get going.
I need to get enough rest.
Feng.
But today,
I asked the school for a leave
just to be here with you.
Xinya.
Well, you should go now.
I know your good intentions.
Well, then.
Feng.
Go get your rest.
Okay, don't touch anything.
You can go back.
Go.
-Well, Feng.
-Yes?
-If you'll excuse me.
-Sure.
Leave quickly.
Feng.
What now?
Don't forget to call me.
Yes, I will.
-Feng!
-Yes?
So you have that kind of hobby.
What?
Xinya.
How do I look?
You look great!
-I'm going now.
-Yeah, bye.
Come out.
I was suffocating!
Situ Feng.
-How could you think of this idea?
-What else could I do?
Is that my phone?
It seems like it.
It's Gu Nanxi.
Hello? Gu Nanxi.
I'll go back to school now.
Bye.
What is it?
The witch is calling for a rehearsal,
so I've got to go back to school.
A rehearsal, now?
-But it's so late.
-Hey.
Get well soon, okay?
Once you're better,
I'll wait for you to come back
and play on stage.
Hey, are you nuts?
I'm so tired.
We've been rehearsing all day.
That was completely inhumane.
Yeah.
This is clearly not her day job,
but she set her heart on it.
You know that witch is a workaholic.
Hey, you!
Are you done chatting?
Don't just sit there! Back to rehearsal!
Knock it off!
Come on.
I'll show you to your room.
My room?
But I thought...
Do you want to stay in the dungeon?
No one makes slick and quick moves
Like Gaston does
No one shines in the midsummer
You make me tremble
When I stand beside you
-Oh my, Gaston is so perfect!
Stop!
You're such a nuisance.
Can you please rehearse somewhere else?
No one's slick as Gaston
No one's quick as Gaston
In a spitting match
Nobody spits like Gaston
And I'm so good at spitting!
Cut it out, Xinya.
We'll move on to the next act.
You guys go rest.
-Not me--
-Come on.
Move it!
THE BEAST
Qingqing, let's do Act Six.
-The one with the piano.
-Okay.
They'll dub the music,
so you take it easy.
Go on.
I'll take it easy.
It's such a piece of cake,
yet she had to show off like that.
That silhouette...
Where have I seen it before?
Qingchen
is Chen Qingqing!
But why?
Why did you disguise yourself?
What are you trying to hide from us?
Thank you for seeing me
although you're sick.
No need to thank me.
We're best buddies.
You
are the only friend I have left.
Hey, Gu Nanxi.
Aren't you the good boy
who always goes to bed early?
Why are you up late now?
And you're sharing a cola!
What?
Can't I just chat with you for a minute?
It looks like
you've got a lot on your mind.
Say it. I'll straighten it out.
Oh, come on!
I can really tell.
You like Qingchen, right?
Cut it out!
You can't hide your thoughts from me.
So you like Chen Qingqing?
Hey, cut the crap.
Who'd be unlucky enough to like her?
Hey, we have never fought at all, right?
What?
Do you want to fight?
I mean,
if someday,
we end up fighting,
what would be the reason?
No matter what,
I'll never hurt my own friend.
Gu Nanxi.
What's up with you today?
Hold on, I need to get this.
-Hello?
-My little master.
I've got to tell you something,
but you've got to brace yourself.
What is it?
Someone hacked our computers.
They uploaded the video for "Breath."
What?
How did you get hacked?
I can only say that the fans are
going all crazy by now!
But don't you worry.
We haven't announced anything.
And it hasn't spread far.
I hope it doesn't cause you trouble.
Okay.
I hope it's all good.
All right.
You may go back to rest now.
I'll be here to see
how the situation unfolds.
Okay, bye.
What's wrong?
Why do you look so serious?
Nothing, it's just the agency.
Hey.
It looks like you're all better.
A little game is all it takes!
You keep saying I'm so weak.
No, I didn't!
You're all okay now,
-shall we rehearse?
-Sure.
I've got it all down.
Come on.
Come on! I'll show you to your room.
My room?
Go on!
Situ Feng!
Don't blame me for being mean to you.
Is he using me to threaten you?
You and Lin Yiyang...
That bitch Qingqing is about
to take Feng away from you.
Feng is mine!
Are you in love with her?
I heard that Situ Feng took
the female lead in Beauty and the Beast.
This photo was taken
when your parents first met.
Youyou, will you marry me?
I will.
Subtitle translation by CL Tan