EPISODE 12
Go on!
Situ Feng!
What's going on?
Sorry, it was an accident.
"Accident"?
How can there be so many accidents?
Hey, Lin Yiyang!
Some fans hacked the agency's computers,
so the music video got leaked.
-I just found out too.
-Situ Feng, can you please
come up with a better excuse next time?
Are you taking me for a fool?
Lin Yiyang!
You've known me for so long.
You should know me by now.
It's because I know you too well.
So everything you do makes me really sick.
Okay.
I assure you
that I, Situ Feng won't sing
that song again.
I don't want to hear any more
of your promises, Situ Feng.
I thought you wouldn't sing that song
for the sake of Qingqing.
Look at what happened.
You're two-faced.
Okay.
I'm not buying any more of your promises.
You're out of chances.
Don't blame me for being mean to you.
Situ Feng.
Did you make a deal with Yiyang
not to sing "Breath"
because he kidnapped me?
Is he using me to threaten you?
It's nothing.
Just let it be.
-But I just heard him say--
-Shall we rehearse?
Sir.
He's drinking so much.
Is he okay?
He's often like that.
He drinks until he passes out every day.
And he ordered us to leave him alone.
-But he--
-Don't worry.
He'll leave once he's sober.
Li Yiyang.
Yiyang.
Are you okay?
Xinyu.
Don't go.
I feel terrible.
HAVE SOME PORRIDGE. TOO MUCH
ALCOHOL IS BAD FOR YOU - FANGFANG
You've got to be there this afternoon,
or I'll be nervous.
And I assure you, you'll see
the world's most handsome beast...
Situ Feng is not here.
Is this yours?
Thanks.
Do you and Yiyang don't have
enough clothes to wear?
Why do you have to exchange them so often?
Aren't you supposed to go
to the meeting for the play?
Hurry.
You and Lin Yiyang...
You're going to be late, Qingqing.
Students.
Without sacrifice, you won't succeed.
The road uphill is the toughest of all.
And you all
have passed it through without a hitch.
Today,
as long as you have total faith
in yourselves
to bring out the very best
of your abilities,
you'll surely make this play a success.
Did I make myself clear?
-Yes!
Good.
The event is in a few hours.
Let's seize the moment
to do the last rehearsal.
Xinya.
Look.
That bitch Qingqing is about
to take Feng away from you.
Baby, I'm here to check on you.
Munian, you're here!
The setup is really nice.
Not bad, right?
Situ Feng.
I heard you will be wearing
women's clothing.
You guys are so creative!
-Really--
-Qingqing.
I have a problem.
What problem?
The moves.
What's wrong with your moves? That's...
Qingqing.
Why don't we rehearse together?
Sure.
-Kill the beast!
Take whatever booty you can find.
But remember,
the beast is mine!
-Kill the beast!
Gaston, no!
Belle!
What's the matter, Beast?
Are you in love with her?
Don't you know how ugly you are?
How can she possibly like you?
Die, Beast!
Feng is mine!
Your emotions aren't bad,
but those aren't the lines. Do it again.
I heard that Situ Feng took the
female lead in Beauty and the Beast
and Chen Qingqing took the male.
-Hurry, let's go and see!
-Let's check it out!
Yes, finally.
It's so crowded.
Yeah.
Ms. Chen.
Good job.
We should hold more events like this.
Little Town
is a small, quiet town.
Every day, just like
the days before today,
the dawn rises in Little Town.
Every morning, we all say...
-Good morning!
Look.
And this is what the baker sent us.
Wheat bread.
Ever since we moved here,
Little Town hardly changed.
Mr. Jean.
Good morning.
Good morning, Belle.
Did you lose something again?
I believe I have.
Don't you think this pose looks familiar?
-Where have I seen it?
Yeah.
I want to return a book.
-Look at that.
-It's about two lovers
in the beautiful Verona.
Qingqing.
You're up next.
In your final act,
do your best.
-Go for it.
-I will.
Go.
Chen Qingqing.
You've got to make the audience
see your talent!
-What the--
-Why did you drink my alcohol?
Alcohol?
This isn't a prop?
Yeah, this alcohol is for props.
Alcohol for props?
Stop drinking it.
If this is alcohol, what is this?
No one makes slick and quick moves
Like Gaston does
No one shines in the midsummer
You make me tremble
When I stand beside you
-Oh, my, Gaston is so perfect!
Kill the beast!
Remember.
Take whatever booty you can find.
But the Beast is mine!
Oh, no!
We're under attack!
Hurry, warn the Master!
Full force!
-We're not afraid of anything!
-We'll fight them to the end!
Master, the castle is under attack!
Just let them come.
I don't care.
Hello, there.
Beast.
I'm Gaston.
Belle sent me.
Are you in love with her?
Did you honestly think
that she'll love you?
No, Gaston!
Don't hurt him!
Belle!
When we return to the village,
you will marry me.
And that beast's head
will hang on our wall.
I beg you, Beast.
Please let me go!
I'll do anything.
-Please.
-Get out.
Get out of my castle!
Belle.
Are you all right?
You came back.
I told you,
I'll be back.
I'm afraid
it's my turn to leave.
No!
You're going to be fine.
But...
At least I got
to see you again
for one last time.
No.
After what we went through,
we're finally together.
You're going to be fine.
I love you.
I love you too.
Qingqing.
The show is over.
Did you drink?
-Fangfang.
-You're awake.
How did I get here?
You were drunk during the play.
You just woke up.
How could I have missed
the applause and cheers of the audience?
Who told you to drink?
What time is it?
It's four o'clock. Why?
Isn't it that witch's class now?
We're too late now.
Ms. Chen took a sick leave,
so she asked us to have our own revision.
Is she sick?
She said she was worn out.
Perhaps from all the rehearsals.
Is she seriously ill?
Shall we go see her?
We just went there.
It's not that serious.
That's good.
If you're still worried,
you can drop by at her place.
Good point.
NO. 2, SPRING GARDEN, BACK STREET
Ms. Chen.
Chen Qingqing.
I'm here to visit you.
Come in.
Thank you.
Ms. Chen.
You shouldn't overwork like that
after this.
Your health is the most important thing.
I'm just slightly ill.
As long as the play went smoothly,
I felt really pleased.
It was all thanks to you.
If it wasn't for your supervision,
we wouldn't have been able to pull it off.
Actually, for all this while, we've all
misunderstood you.
It's okay.
There's no need to blame yourself.
I just hope that I could see
each and every one of you improve.
And for this performance,
each and every one of you did a great job.
I'll get you some fruits.
No, it's okay.
You should get some rest.
It's okay, I'll be fine.
-It'll take just a minute.
-Okay.
Chen Qingqing.
What's wrong?
Do you know them?
Actually...
Actually, Xiao Jingnan
is my dad.
What about Chen Youyou?
Chen Youyou
is my mom.
Qingqing.
You really turned out to be
exactly like Youyou.
No wonder when I heard you play the piano,
I had
a strong sense of déjà vu.
This is who I am, more or less.
By the way, I'm Chen Xiao.
I look forward to working with you.
Hey.
Newcomers should tell us
their vital stats, right?
-Vital stats!
What's going on here?
I could hear your commotion from outside.
Don't bully our new friend.
I brought you some drinks today.
Come take them, they are for everyone.
-All right!
For you.
What's your name?
Chen Xiao.
My name is Chen too.
I'm Chen Youyou.
Hello.
It's so good to know you,
my little sister.
Guys.
From now on,
Chen Xiao is now my little sister.
Whoever bullies her
is going to get it from me, okay?
My mom was so domineering.
Come to think of it,
the first time I saw you,
you looked kind of familiar.
Your mom was like a hero.
Ever since I got to know her,
she has been helping me, caring for me
and a lot more.
She may not remember,
but I will always remember.
By the way, how are your parents?
My mom passed away many years ago.
And I don't know where my dad is.
I came to this school
just to find out more about my parents.
They're...
Ms. Chen.
It's been almost 20 years.
I've not kept in touch with them.
Ms. Chen.
Can you tell me
what my dad was like?
Because every time
I asked my grandpa,
he'd always flip out.
He always said that my dad
abandoned my mom.
Then he never came back to see me.
Is my dad really that bad?
Did he really love my mom?
Jingnan is not a bad person.
And the person he loved the most
was Youyou.
He loved Mom the most?
Just a moment, Qingqing.
I need to show you something.
This photo was taken
when your parents first met.
Youyou, why are you so calm?
Your dance partner stood you up.
What are you going to do?
It's okay.
I'll just have to forfeit.
You can't pull out like that.
You're really great at dancing.
Wouldn't it be a waste to forfeit?
Then what should I do?
I think we'll just have
to join the audience after this.
Youyou, look.
That guy over there dressed up so weirdly.
He's walking toward us.
Do you know him, Youyou?
I don't.
Hello, are you Miss Chen Youyou?
I'm so sorry that my friend
is giving you such a hard time.
But he had something urgent
to attend to today,
so I'll take his place.
I'm Xiao Jingnan.
Hello.
Can you dance?
Just a little bit.
It's still early before the dance.
Shall we practice?
Sure.
I'll get going.
-Let's try.
-Okay.
Sorry.
Sorry. I'm so sorry!
I can't really dance.
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
I just stepped on your foot.
Why don't we take a break?
Sure.
Youyou.
Can I call you this?
We're in the same grade, right?
I see that you're a bit nervous.
I don't know why either.
Perhaps it's because the dance
is about to start soon.
So I'll get a little bit nervous.
Although I can't dance,
but I think
dancing doesn't matter so much.
What matters is that you enjoy the music.
You have to control the rhythm,
not let the rhythm control you.
Xiao Jingnan.
I didn't think you could comfort anyone,
but it's just the same.
Are you still nervous?
I'm much better.
When I saw them dance, I was stunned.
I had a strong feeling
that I should keep watching.
As time slowly passed,
looking at them
was like gazing at happiness.
And then?
What happened next?
Then,
they danced by controlling the rhythm
like your dad said
and won the event as prom king and queen.
Really?
Xiao Jingnan joined the Student Council
just to be with Youyou.
Then he became the president.
Is it this picture?
Two people who really love each other
will surely outdo themselves
for one another.
Ms. Chen, do you know
what happened to my mom and dad
after graduation?
The last time I saw them
was when Xiao Jingnan proposed to Youyou.
Youyou.
Do you remember this song?
They played this during the dance
when we first met.
Time flies so fast.
We're about to graduate.
I remember
the first time we held hands.
I want to keep holding them.
The lecturers always said
that graduation means separation.
But I don't think so.
I think that graduation to us
can be another new beginning.
Youyou, will you marry me?
I will.
And then,
I heard that Xiao Jingnan and Youyou
went to work in Jincheng.
And then,
I went on with my life.
Studying, graduating
and looking for a job...
I slowly lost touch with them.
Qingqing, don't cry.
Ms. Chen.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for telling me so much
about them.
This is the first time
I heard anything about my parents.
I'm also happy to be their daughter.
Qingqing, have you found any information
about your dad?
No.
Don't worry, Qingqing.
I'll definitely help you out.
I'm sure you'll hear from your dad soon.
Thank you, Ms. Chen.
Ms. Chen, it's getting late.
I should go back to school.
-But I need you to do me a favor.
-Sure.
I came to Yuncheng
without telling my grandpa.
So once I go back to school,
I still want to continue
presenting myself like I've always been.
So you have to help me keep this secret.
Please, Ms. Chen?
Okay.
That won't be a problem.
I've got to go now, Ms. Chen.
Thank you, Ms. Chen.
Let me send you out.
Like what Ms. Chen just said,
Mom and Dad loved each other.
Then why did Grandpa
say that Dad abandoned Mom?
Did he lie to me?
Then why did he have to lie?
Your phone, sir.
Hello?
Grandpa.
Is that you, Qingqing?
How would I know if
I'm in love with somebody?
Are you okay now?
I realized that
I can be myself in front of her.
It looks like this friend of yours
is more than just a friend.
So what if I'm not myself,
but I've turned into
a completely different person?
Chen Qingqing, what brings you here?
How could you just bring
any ordinary person here?
Miss, may I see your invitation?
We've hated each other since we first met.
And we still do.
-Chen Qingqing.
-Yes?
Can I say what I like about you?
Subtitle translation by CL Tan