EPISODE 10
Thank you, Feng.
What a coincidence.
Well, you're here too.
That's right.
What a coincidence.
Why are you two together?
Chen Qingqing.
Since I have some free time today,
I'll educate you about wine.
Give me the 1978 Burgundy wine.
All right, please wait.
Let me get this straight.
I was the one who invited Gu Nanxi
to dine here today.
-She's going all out.
-That's right.
I wanted to thank Gu Nanxi
because he saved me from being framed.
By the way, Xinya,
I really want to thank you.
Burgundy wine from 1978 is the best.
You should drink a lot.
But it's a pity that
you don't know how to appreciate it.
You're right. 1978 is a great year.
Too bad that it's too old
and causes instability.
If it was up to me,
I would choose the one from 2005.
Wines from that year
are very rich in flavor.
They are highly valued
among all vintage wines.
With their strong density
and great structure,
the wines are of the best quality
in recent years.
How did you know about this?
I was just bluffing.
I don't usually drink on normal days.
You're good at memorizing.
Since you're so knowledgeable,
you should drink more then.
Chen Qingqing, do you know how to drink?
Don't waste it.
It's none of your business.
Qingqing doesn't really drink.
I'll drink for her.
Qingqing, you're so almighty.
Even Gu Nanxi
wants to be your white knight.
Feng.
You need to drink for me.
Cheers! Let's drink.
Here.
Drink two more glasses.
I'm telling all of you.
I'm not drunk.
I can still drink.
It's late.
Let's go home.
Nanxi.
My driver is here.
Why don't I send all of you home?
Xinya.
That's not convenient for you.
I'll take care of Situ Feng.
You can go home first.
All right.
Bye.
If he couldn't drink,
he shouldn't have drunk so much.
Gu Nanxi, I'll go home too.
Look, Qingqing.
I have something that I haven't told you.
What is it?
Actually, Situ Feng was the one who helped
find the surveillance footage.
Really?
It's already late.
You should go home.
I'll take care of him.
Gu Nanxi.
Thanks for telling me.
-I'll go home first. See you tomorrow.
-Okay.
Situ Feng.
Hey.
Where's Qingqing?
She went back to school.
School?
I'll go back to school too.
Hang on, I'll send you.
-There's no need.
-Be careful.
Slow down.
It's already so late.
Shouldn't you go home?
Why did you come here instead?
Gu Nanxi! I demand a duel!
You're already drunk.
Yet, you want a duel.
Cut the crap! Come at me.
Let's have a duel then.
I'm not afraid of you.
Come on.
Let's do it again.
What's wrong with you?
You're so fierce today.
I always told you not to act cool
during the match.
You never listened.
Your performance today was awesome.
Hey.
Hey! Are you asleep?
Where is he?
Chen Qingqing!
Chen Qingqing! Come out!
Situ Feng.
Hello, everyone.
Did anyone see Qingqing?
-No.
Who is it?
It must be a love confession.
Let's go and take a look.
That scared me.
Who is it?
-Is he confessing?
-Am I dreaming?
Isn't that Situ Feng?
-Why is it not working?
-What is he doing?
All right.
Chen Qingqing!
It's that Chen Qingqing again.
Go to him.
Chen Qingqing!
Come over here!
Do you want to die, Situ Feng?
Why did you come here
to scream at me at this hour?
Chen Qingqing.
I'm telling you.
Lower down your voice.
Don't let others know that I'm here!
Lower your voice.
Situ Feng.
Can you cut it out?
What do you want to say?
If you're not saying anything,
I'm leaving.
Chen Qingqing!
Wait up! I have a question to ask you.
What is it?
Chen Qingqing!
What's your relationship with them?
Them? Who are you talking about?
You have Hua Munian and Gu Nanxi.
That was for my errands service business.
They can help my store
and help me earn money.
Money?
I have a lot of money.
Look at this.
I'll give you my wallet.
Hang on.
Here. Five yuan, one yuan
and five mao.
I have coins too.
Three of them.
Situ Feng.
Can you cut it out?
Chen Qingqing.
Don't talk to them anymore, okay?
You're mine.
Situ Feng is going to kiss her.
Situ Feng.
How did he disappear so quickly?
-Gu Nanxi.
-Turns out, he was here.
He fell asleep.
Be careful.
He came to find you at this hour.
Did he have anything important
to tell you?
No.
It's nothing. He didn't say anything.
Bring him back quickly.
All right, have a good rest.
Let's go, Situ Feng.
It's this way.
Goodness.
Wake up.
My tooth hurts.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Sorry for disturbing you.
Let's go to sleep.
Dismiss!
What's wrong?
Fangfang.
Didn't you hear it?
Everyone is talking
about what happened last night.
Look at them.
They are mimicking him.
Gosh, it's so embarrassing.
Situ Feng is here.
He's here.
Qingqing, I'm going
to hand in my assignment.
Fangfang.
If you want to study,
you should clear your mind.
See? You're holding it upside down.
As for you, you're going
to tear up the paper.
Are you thinking about breakfast?
Hurry up.
Study after you finish it.
Thank you.
I'll leave you two to it.
I'm going first.
Why are you looking for me?
Take a look at it.
You're really something.
What is it?
PITIFUL ASSISTANT WAS YELLED AT
This...
What do they mean by "pitiful assistant"?
Why am I pitiful?
Shouldn't they interpret this
as a love confession in the dorm?
I know you two don't like each other.
But can both of you
quarrel at the right place?
You fought in the middle of the night.
-But your appearance--
-What about it?
Nothing, it's great.
There won't be any gossip.
The press has been doubting
your identity as the assistant recently.
Plus, do you know what they will write
about the picture from last night?
But that's not what happened.
At this rate, we might
as well put on a whole show.
Situ Feng has a press conference tomorrow.
The press will be there.
You'll go with him.
Show them that both of you
are having a harmonious friendship.
Everything will be fine
after I send them some news.
Hang on.
Are you asking me
to be his assistant for real?
What else then?
My little master.
I know you want to focus
on producing music.
You don't want to know
about the business side.
But if we don't do any business...
If we don't do movies or commercials,
where can we get the money
to promote your music?
Do you know how much loss
the agency has suffered
because you suddenly wanted to cancel
the release of "Breath"?
The boss is really unhappy now.
He took back the funds for promotion.
I used my own money to promote your music.
Don't you believe me?
Look at this.
All of my credit cards are maxed out.
If it wasn't for the money
I loaned from the 9FBank app,
I would have exploded as well,
just like my credit card.
All right, I understand.
I'll do it, okay?
Tell me. What is it that you want?
The movie tomorrow
is directed by the famous Wang Jingwei.
Plus, Chen Qingqing is willing
to cooperate and be your assistant.
What? Chen Qingqing is coming too?
Don't worry, I'll be there tomorrow.
As long as you cooperate
with your deskmate,
I guarantee that nothing will happen.
All right, I'll go.
I'll go, okay?
Qingqing, you're here.
When we reach there,
you should focus on acting.
You just stay by his side.
If you see the press, both of you
should act nice to each other.
Leave the rest to me.
Hello? Yes, sir.
But I'm going with Situ Feng.
All right, I'll come back now.
-Daniel.
-Yes?
Are you leaving?
There's a problem at the office.
I need to deal with it.
What about us, Daniel?
As long as you don't fight,
you will be fine.
Remember my advice.
Maintain your smile
when you see the press.
Be humble when you meet the director.
Thanks for today, Qingqing.
See. The boss is calling again.
Hello? Yes, sir.
Situ Feng.
Can you hear me?
I can't.
Why did you come to my dorm that night?
You said that I'm yours.
That night, I wanted to say
that you're my assistant.
Don't create any trouble and embarrass me.
You came to my dorm at that hour
just to tell me that?
That's right.
What did you think I wanted to tell you?
Nothing.
I didn't think anything.
What should I say later?
You should just say anything you please.
How do you feel working
with Mr. Wang for the first time?
It's an honor to work with Mr. Wang.
I'll take this opportunity
to learn from him.
There's a rumor
that you bully your assistant.
Regarding the accusation,
what do you have to say?
Hello, fellow reporters.
I'm Situ Feng's assistant.
I'm Chen Qingqing.
Do I look like I'm being bullied?
I'm very close
with His Highness in real life.
It's the truth.
Am I right, Your Highness?
Yes, we're close.
So please stand aside, everyone.
-Please move aside.
-You can't take photos.
Please come here.
Mr. Wang.
Situ Feng is here.
Hello, Mr. Wang.
It's a pleasure to work with you.
-Hello, young talent.
-Thank you, Mr. Wang.
This is my co-director, Li.
He'll explain to you later.
After his explanation,
you'll have to wait.
That's all.
-All right.
-Okay.
Your scenes will be filmed later.
You can wait at the side.
-I'll call you when it's time, okay?
-Okay.
-Please come with me.
This is your script. Please go through it.
-Do you want me to read it?
-You should understand it too.
Situ Feng. When will it be our turn?
I think we have to wait for a while.
Excuse me, Mr. Li.
I'm Situ Feng's assistant.
I want to ask you something.
When will it be our turn?
Take a look. There's a delay.
Both of you still have to wait.
Aren't you playing us for fools?
So what about it?
What I meant to say is
there's no heater here.
Everyone's suffering.
Everyone's working
in the same environment.
Wear thicker clothes if you're cold.
Qingqing.
Don't be angry.
It seems like it'll be a while
before our turn.
Here, wear my jacket.
Don't catch a cold.
If not, the press will say
that I'm torturing my assistant.
Aren't you cold?
Me? I'm fine.
It's your turn, Situ Feng.
You were supposed to talk
by the swimming pool, right?
-Yes.
-There's an extra scene.
You'll have to swim.
What?
Is there a problem?
You didn't say that I had to swim.
Plus, I'm not that good at swimming.
Can you find a substitute?
We're going to start filming now.
Where can I find a substitute for you?
Hurry up and prepare.
The whole world is waiting for you.
Situ Feng.
Is it our turn now?
What's wrong with you?
There's an extra scene.
I need to swim.
Swim?
Can you really not swim?
If the sponsors
didn't insist on hiring him,
do you think Mr. Wang
would use a useless idol like him?
I'm telling you.
He's acting up just because
he has some fans.
Let's show him who's boss
on behalf of Mr. Wang.
For this scene,
both of you will stand here.
After Bao finishes her lines,
she'll push you into the water.
All right, ready.
Three, two, one. Action!
I really don't understand.
Why are you so angry?
Neither do I.
Even though my name means "precious,"
why does nobody treasure me?
Great. Cut!
Situ Feng.
Come up.
Thank you.
Hurry.
How are you?
Was the water too cold?
It was great.
Sir, there was a mistake.
A mistake?
Let's do it again.
Situ Feng.
They're doing it on purpose.
Qingqing, don't create any trouble.
Situ Feng.
You don't look like you can't swim.
Are you afraid of the water?
Mind your own business.
Mr. Wang.
-Mr. Wang.
-What's the matter?
Excuse me.
Can I be Situ Feng's substitute?
You?
Sure.
We'll zoom out.
Are you okay with it?
Thank you, sir.
Let's continue after eating.
I've already informed the director.
I'll be your substitute.
What did you say?
Aren't you afraid of water?
I just learned how to swim,
so I'll replace you.
Chen Qingqing, have you gone mad?
I don't need a girl as a substitute.
The director has agreed to it.
There's nothing you can do.
Everyone, get ready.
Three, two, one. Action.
Why does nobody treasure me?
Let's do it again.
Okay, this is perfect.
Qingqing.
Situ Feng.
Don't come here.
I don't want to see you.
I'll help you.
I'm fine.
Pass me the towel.
My makeup is ruined.
What should I do now?
Qingqing.
Are you crying?
I'm fine.
Hey, beautiful lady. Where are you going?
What's this?
What's wrong? Don't leave.
Where are you going?
Let's have fun.
Come, let's play.
Hey! Stop it.
Who are you?
I'm Lin Yiyang.
Run.
Are you okay?
Why are you here?
I'm about to ask you.
I work here.
-This is my family's restaurant.
-What?
Go home.
Hey.
I'll take you home.
This is my house.
I'm leaving then.
Baby, you're home.
"Baby"?
Who is this?
He's my classmate.
He gave me a ride home.
This is my dad.
He likes to call me "Baby."
Hello, sir.
Hello.
Baby's classmate.
Thank you for giving her a ride home.
It's time for dinner.
Come inside and eat.
It's okay. He's busy.
How can you treat a guest like this?
Since you're here, don't be shy.
Come.
That's right. Come.
Let's eat.
Don't be shy.
Dig in.
Here, dig in.
Thank you, ma'am.
Baby.
Why aren't you eating?
Mom cooked all your favorite dishes today.
Aren't these your favorite too?
Just eat.
What are you so excited about?
Have some water.
-Drink up.
-Have a drink.
Okay.
All right.
Our baby
has always been clumsy.
Thank goodness
she has a friend like you
to take care of her.
Hey, why aren't you eating?
Do you not like the food?
It's not that.
When you're home,
what dishes do your dad
and mom cook for you?
I'll make it for you next time.
They aren't at home most of the time.
Dig in then.
Here, dig in.
Hey.
Why did you ask me to come here
early in the morning?
Don't ask so much.
You suddenly left
after yesterday's filming.
Qingqing.
Are you really okay?
I'm fine.
Well...
Are you not angry anymore?
When did I get angry?
You are weird today.
Could it be...
What?
What do you want to say?
Don't dillydally.
-Let me take you somewhere.
-Where?
Cut the crap.
Follow me.
I can't believe such a place
exists in our school.
I know.
Is it for me?
Yes.
Thank you.
What is it called?
Its name is the same as yours.
It's called Qingqing.
It's called Qingqing too?
Yes.
Do you know why?
It's because it's ugly like you too.
How did you find this place?
I discovered it accidentally.
It was abandoned long ago.
Nobody came at all.
I needed a place to rest
so I cleaned up this place.
You're quite romantic.
Qingqing.
This is the first time
I brought someone here.
-Situ Feng.
-Yes?
Am I the first person
just because
you're thankful
that I became your assistant?
If I do it a few more times,
will you really fall in love with me?
Fall in love with you? It's better for me
to fall in love with the plants.
Today is His Highness's album release day.
Didn't you go to buy his album?
Why do you look like this?
I've already bought them.
But I discovered something odd.
What is it?
Look at the new album's song list.
"Breath" isn't here.
I thought it was hidden earlier.
But I listened to the entire album.
The song is not there.
It's not on the album.
I thought His Highness
wanted to try a new genre.
He even filmed a music video
for this song.
Right, I heard that
the agency went to all the trouble
to release this song.
Why isn't it on the album?
Did the agency stop him from releasing it?
It's possible.
I found it odd.
The agency only wants to earn money.
Why would they let
His Highness easily change his style?
We can't let all the hard work
of His Highness go to waste.
Yes, we must protect our idol!
All right, I hacked into their computer.
Did you find "Breath"?
Hurry, download it.
DOWNLOAD COMPLETE
If I'm not mistaken,
this is a man's jacket.
The candidate list for the school's play
has been announced.
Qingqing, look. You made the cut.
Do you think you can be the main actress?
Feng.
-What?
-What's wrong?
Why do you look so serious?
Nothing, it's just the agency.
Subtitle translation by Michelle Chai