EPISODE 27
Hello, dear audience.
Welcome to Situ Feng's
global press conference
for his upcoming new album.
Let's now give a warm welcome
to His Highness.
Welcome.
-His Highness.
SITU FENG'S 2018 NEW ALBUM
BREAK THROUGH PRESS CONFERENCE
Thank you, everyone.
All right. Situ Feng is here today
to give us the details
of his newest album Break Through.
I would like to ask Your Highness.
What kind of journey did you go through
during the making of this album?
All right.
The name of the album is Break Through.
As its name implies, Break Through means
to overcome an obstacle.
When I was producing this album,
I wanted to make a breakthrough
in both the genres and interpretations
of the songs.
When I was writing the songs...
Why does His Highness
look so haggard today?
I thought so too.
-I think he's wearing a lot of makeup.
-I also continued to...
His voice is also a bit hoarse.
He's perhaps exhausted
from promoting his new album.
Making music is hard work nowadays.
-I hope that he'd be all right.
-There are also elements in the palace.
As we all know, the cover of this album
is a collaboration between Situ Feng
and his number one fan, Chen Qingqing,
who's also known as Hebiancao.
The design of the cover
the lyrics page
and also this handshake voucher
are all very original and unique.
That's right.
We've made a bold attempt on this album.
Every album comes
with an exclusive handshake voucher.
With this voucher, you'll be able
to attend my meet-and-greet
and shake my hand for five seconds.
Not only does it sound
like a great deal to me,
but at the same time,
it's also quite an original idea.
I would like to ask Your Highness.
What was it like collaborating
with Chen Qingqing?
I...
Chen Qingqing and I...
-Come here.
-Xinya...
I'll get going now.
You can't do this to them.
-Be my girlfriend.
-Take care of me forever.
-I'll miss you.
-I'm so happy.
EXCLUSIVE HANDSHAKE WITH HIS HIGHNESS
What's going on?
His Highness looks strange.
Holy Mary Mother of God,
please protect His Highness.
SITU FENG'S 2018 NEW ALBUM
BREAK THROUGH PRESS CONFERENCE
I had a great time...
working with her.
All right, everyone.
This is the end
of today's press conference.
Thank you for coming.
And please show your support
for Situ Feng's newest album.
Thank you, everyone.
Ms. Lan, which gown do you like?
I like a couple of them.
But I feel that they all lack something.
I will try this one and that one.
And that one. Please help me to try it on.
Sure, right away.
Lanting, why don't I postpone
the wedding for a few days?
So I'll have time to design my gown.
Silly. Don't you understand?
Chen Qingqing will be back
after Situ Feng finishes his work.
Will he choose you then?
It will be hard to say.
You should tie the knot
as soon as possible.
Pick your wedding gown.
You'll hold an engagement ceremony
in a few days.
Once you're engaged,
no matter what Chen Qingqing does,
Situ Feng won't be able to back out.
By that time,
Situ Feng will be yours forever.
Baby, what are you doing here?
Hua Munian?
Why are you here?
I'm here to ask some brands
for sponsorships.
We're destined to meet.
-That's right.
-It seems that you're in a good mood.
Why are you checking out wedding gowns?
I'm going to--
I'm in a good mood.
I can shop whatever I want.
I'll leave you two alone.
You're doing the right thing.
Take the long view.
Don't give up on everything else
for one Situ Feng.
Don't do anything silly again.
Let's go.
I'm also in a good mood.
Let's shop together. It's my treat.
I'm busy now.
I can't accompany you.
Why are you busy?
Why do I need to tell you?
Tell me.
Miss, the gowns
that you've chosen are ready now.
You can try them on anytime you want.
Is he your fiancé?
You two look great together.
Of course not.
Fiancé?
What's going on?
I'll tell you.
Feng and I are going to get engaged.
We'll be holding
the engagement ceremony in a few days.
Since you've found out,
you're invited.
ENGAGEMENT PARTY: SITU FENG, LAN XINYA
What?
Isn't Chen Qingqing
the one who Situ Feng likes?
It was just a fling.
He has agreed to marry me.
This proves that he's been in love
with me all along.
Lan Xinya, are you insane?
I want to go home now.
Lanting, let's go.
Please stop provoking her, all right?
Hello, Qingqing.
Hello, Gu Nanxi.
Do you know where Situ Feng is?
I called him several times.
But he didn't pick up my calls.
He...
I'm not sure.
He probably didn't bring
his phone with him.
Can you look for him for me?
I'm worried about him.
Don't worry.
I will go look for him now.
Thank you.
Feng.
You look so handsome.
Don't you think
that we look great together
when we stand side by side?
You two have great taste.
This wedding gown suits you well.
You two are perfect for each other.
Of course.
But I prefer the other one.
Feng, give me a second.
-I'll go and try that one again.
-Okay.
-Hello?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
I overreacted last time.
I should be the one apologizing to you.
No.
I've already made up my mind.
And this decision
might hurt you.
That's why I said
sorry.
What decision have you made?
I...
I can't put Xinya in danger again.
We're going to get engaged.
It's over...
Between us.
-Situ Feng.
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Stop apologizing to me.
If you keep apologizing,
it means...
It means that you're not mature enough.
You've made your decision,
so...
So you should be responsible
for the one you love.
Qingqing.
I don't know what to say anymore.
Just say goodbye then.
Usually,
that's how people end a phone call.
Isn't it?
Goodbye.
Xinya, I'm here. Where are you?
See you later.
Feng, are you all right?
You should get some rest.
Otherwise, you won't look great
on the day of the ceremony.
Nanxi, you're here.
Xinya.
I need to go back to school
to get something.
I'll wear this suit.
I'll ask the driver to take you home.
Okay.
Nanxi, why don't you
accompany Feng to school?
Sure.
That's not necessary.
Excuse me, please help me.
Let me use you. Thanks.
The young master went that way!
I need to use you!
Do you know that it was my...
Hey, why are you bringing me here?
To play basketball?
You could do it like that?
Get out of my way!
-Chen Qingqing.
-Yes?
Can I say what I like about you?
You don't have secrets.
You...
Are you saying that you like me?
-Situ Feng, put me down!
-Look.
We found this kitten together.
We're the mom and dad.
I'm the dad. You're the mom.
Of course it'll take my surname.
Am I right, Kitty Chen?
That's right.
-Hey.
-Yes?
Why are you the dad?
Because I'm domineering.
I can't believe such a place
exists in our school.
Is it for me?
Yes.
Thank you.
What is it called?
Its name is the same as yours.
It's called Qingqing.
It's called Qingqing too?
Grandpa, why did you come downstairs?
Qingqing.
This is the first time I'm feeling scared.
Grandpa.
Don't worry.
I've already decided
to stay and manage our family business.
This is not what I'm afraid of.
I tried to raise you
to be a replica of me.
But you ran away.
You started to live independently.
You've lived your own life.
I've finally realized
that I was wrong.
I shouldn't have imposed
my dreams on you.
But Grandpa,
right now,
I don't have a good excuse
to run away again.
A good excuse?
It's probably the most boring excuse
that people use when making a decision.
After all these years,
if I could go back in time
and deal with your mom again,
guess what I would do?
I think
that you would try everything you could
to stop her from leaving.
That way,
Mom would have avoided the accident.
No.
I would encourage her,
trust her
and be proud of her
for being courageous.
God
has finally given me
a second chance.
Hey, breaking news!
Look, she's asking all the fans
to do this.
What? This is insane.
That's impossible.
If we join hands,
there's nothing impossible in the world.
Although we only have three days,
we must not fail this mission.
We shall only succeed.
-Roger that.
-That's right.
There's no way I'm going to miss out
on such an important moment.
His Highness' business is my business.
Use my credit cards.
Let's get to work.
Miss.
You've maxed out all your cards.
No way.
Are you sure that there's nothing wrong
with your laptop?
Come on.
How could this happen
at this life or death moment?
I need to think of another way.
How can I get more money?
Miss, didn't you mention something
about borrowing money from some card?
That's right. Gosh.
How could I forget about it?
I can use the 9Fbank application.
I've just wired 150,000 yuan. Try again.
-Hurry up.
-Over here.
It's working.
We're gathered here today
in the sight of God
to witness the engagement of Mr. Situ Feng
and Miss Lan Xinya.
Do you, Miss Lan Xinya, take this man,
Mr. Situ Feng, to be your fiancé?
I do.
Do you, Mr. Situ Feng, take this woman,
Miss Lan Xinya, to be your fiancée?
Mr. Situ Feng, do you?
I...
I object!
Chen Qingqing?
What is she doing here?
Chen Qingqing.
How dare you interrupt
my engagement ceremony?
Who do you think you are?
I came here today
to officially introduce myself.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Chen Qingqing.
I am
your "fiancée."
I'm your classmate.
I'm your assistant.
I'm the female lead in your music video.
I'm also your business partner.
And you...
You're mine.
What is he to you?
Why didn't you finish your sentence?
I'm done talking.
You're a psychopath.
Qingqing.
Saying sorry to you is useless,
-but I--
-You don't have to say anything.
I didn't come here
to kidnap the groom.
There's one thing that I need to do.
I will leave afterwards.
This is the handshake voucher
from your new album.
I designed this voucher.
It says that
I can shake your hand for five seconds
with this voucher.
Nice to meet you,
Situ Feng.
Chen Qingqing, don't change the topic.
How could you take this voucher seriously?
Five seconds have passed.
Let go of his hand!
I don't only have one voucher.
I've got two, three
and many more.
Let him go!
Situ Feng.
You must keep your word.
Chen Qingqing.
I won't let go of you this time.
Xinya.
I'm sorry.
The person I love
is Chen Qingqing.
I can't keep lying to myself,
to you and to everyone else.
This ceremony
is called off.
Feng!
You have to fight for what you truly want.
Release Chen Qingqing's information
to the paparazzi.
Hey!
Hey, what are you doing?
Isn't this Zhang Fangfang?
I heard that you're dating Lin Yiyang.
You're a pervert.
Lin Yiyang is dating you just for fun.
Have we all just become lovesick?
His Highness has a girlfriend.
Do you know how much money I spent
to settle this matter?
Subtitle translation by Judy Lu