EPISODE 17
When I was little,
my mom gave me this guitar pick.
I turned it into a necklace,
hoping it'd bring me good luck.
Now, I'm giving it to you.
Thank you, Situ Feng.
I promise to cherish it for you.
Chen Qingqing!
Did you celebrate your birthday
with Feng last night?
So what if I did?
How many times have I warned you?
-Don't seduce Feng anymore!
-Hey, Xinya.
What are you doing?
Hey, what's going on?
What are you looking at me for?
Feng.
Why did you celebrate her birthday
without telling me?
Xinya.
Come on. Qingqing and I--
Stop defending her.
Chen Qingqing.
You're really, really, really annoying!
Xinya.
You've gone too far.
You didn't just say that.
Xinya.
Yiyang.
Xinya, what are you doing here?
I used to come here in the past
to watch you and Feng play basketball.
Here.
You still remember
that I liked to drink this?
Yes.
In glass bottles.
But someone
might've already forgotten about it.
Did someone bully you?
Do you think
Feng doesn't like me anymore?
That's not possible.
Then why does he act so indifferent
toward me?
I won the Miss Campus contest.
He had no intention to celebrate with me.
Instead, he was worried
about Chen Qingqing's birthday.
There's more.
He even scolded me
because of Chen Qingqing.
We grew up together.
But ever since Chen Qingqing showed up,
we've drifted apart.
I feel like I'm such a failure.
Come on, Xinya.
Stop crying.
-We need to get water.
-That's right.
Chen Qingqing!
-Lin Yiyang.
What do you want?
I'm warning you.
Stay away from Situ Feng from now on.
Hey.
Your words were rather confusing.
Why should I stay away from him?
Stop pretending, all right?
Everyone knows that you two are close.
Whatever goes on between us
is none of your business.
Xinya's business is my business.
I'm not going to let her get hurt.
It's about Lan Xinya again.
You guys are so annoying.
I'm not in the mood to deal with her.
Fangfang, let's go.
Hey, Lin Yiyang!
Stop it. This might just
be a misunderstanding.
This is none of your business.
Hey.
Isn't this Situ Feng's necklace?
Why is it with you?
Who says you can touch it?
Hey.
Qingqing!
Qingqing.
-Are you all right?
-My neck.
Let's go to the infirmary.
Fangfang, the necklace.
Goodness.
Is it really that serious?
Do I need to wear this?
Don't touch it.
Just stay here and get some rest.
Don't worry.
I'm all right.
I'll be alive and kicking
after I get this damn thing off tomorrow.
How could you still be laughing
after what happened?
By the way, Fangfang,
you can't let Situ Feng know
about what happened.
More importantly,
you must not let him know
that this has something to do
with Lin Yiyang.
I'm scared that he might start a fight
-We must keep it from him--
-Chen Qingqing.
What happened?
How did you get hurt?
It was an accident.
I fell.
Was it an accident? Look at you.
I really did fall.
Tell me. Was it Lin Yiyang?
No.
This has nothing to do with Lin Yiyang.
I see.
Hey, Situ Feng.
Situ Feng!
Ye Bei, look at this new equipment
that I got.
Dalei.
A petrol tank.
This is dangerous.
Look.
This is helium.
It will create a magical effect
when people inhale it.
What kind of magical effect?
If people inhale this gas,
their voice will sound especially funny.
And they will also feel drowsy.
Who knows what might happen
when people are fuzzy-headed?
Be quiet!
Lin Yiyang!
-Situ Feng, what are you doing here?
-Cut the crap.
Didn't I tell you?
Don't lay your hands on Chen Qingqing.
There's no need to reason
with someone like you.
Is that so?
I'm not going to reason with you either.
Dalei, Yiyang is fighting with Situ Feng.
Should we help him?
Yiyang is strong.
He will definitely
take him down right away.
Yiyang, I've got him.
Hurry up. He's all yours.
I'm the one you want.
Hey, Ye Bei, Dalei!
They must have done something wrong.
How could you say that in front of us?
Can't you speak Mandarin?
What the hell? Let's go.
Hey!
Stop fighting!
Lin Yiyang, knock it off.
Qingqing.
You shouldn't be here.
Your neck is injured.
I'm fine.
Situ Feng.
I'm teaching you a lesson
in front of Qingqing.
Lin Yiyang, you must apologize now.
Apologize? No way!
Qingqing, what's going on?
I have no idea.
I know.
That tank.
That tank is leaking.
It must contain helium.
That's why our voice changed.
Inhaling too much of it
will cause hypoxia.
That's right. What should we do?
Hey, Situ Feng!
Fangfang!
Are you all right, Fangfang?
Situ Feng.
Don't just stand there. Give me a hand.
Fangfang.
What are you waiting for?
Situ Feng!
Fangfang, hang in there.
Zhang Fangfang.
Why did you help me
that time?
Lin Yiyang.
Since you're awake,
would you like something to eat?
No.
Suit yourself.
Qingqing.
Did I wake you up?
It's all right.
What happened?
It's nothing serious.
You hurt your arm.
But don't worry.
The doctor has taken care of it.
All you need to do now
is to get lots of rest
and change the dressing frequently.
You will be fine in two days.
Let me help you get up.
I've bought you something to eat.
Eat slowly.
Don't ever do that again. It's dangerous.
Shouldn't someone show gratitude
to his lifesaver
since she's awake now?
Have some more.
Yiyang, are you all right?
I came here as soon as I heard
that you're in the hospital.
I'm fine. Don't worry.
Why are you two here?
Because we had to rescue Yiyang.
Why don’t you ask him?
Yiyang.
What happened?
It's hard to explain everything now.
Have some more.
Zhang Fangfang, did you do it on purpose?
Does she have a thing for you, Yiyang?
What are you talking about?
Lan Xinya, stop talking nonsense.
Believe it or not, I will throw you out.
Would you hurt yourself
in order to rescue someone?
Well, some poor people
like to extort money from others.
They find wealthy people
and blackmail them.
Just tell us how much money you want.
Stop being pretentious.
-Xinya.
-I'm not.
Lan Xinya, get out now!
Xinya.
Let's go for a walk.
Give me a hand.
Hold on. I'll get a wheelchair.
Fangfang, just ignore her.
How did it go, Gu Nanxi?
Could you get in touch with him?
I've already called him several times.
I couldn't get hold of him.
What happened to Situ Feng today?
Did he merely get into a fight
with Lin Yiyang?
Yes. By the time I got there,
the two of them
had already started fighting.
Then, Fangfang got hurt.
I told him to give me a hand.
Later, I took Fangfang to the hospital.
I tried to contact him afterward,
but I couldn't reach him at all.
So I immediately called you.
When you were there,
did you notice anything unusual?
There was nothing unusual.
There was a lot of helium in the room.
If people breathe in too much helium,
they'll suffer from hypoxia.
-Hypoxia?
-Yes.
That's it.
What is it?
Gu Nanxi.
You know something, don't you?
Tell me.
Qingqing, we need to find Situ Feng
as soon as possible.
This isn't the first time he disappeared.
The last time he disappeared,
He was gone for three days.
We couldn't find him anywhere.
We didn't know what he went through.
He passed out as soon as he came back.
How could that happen?
Me, Situ Feng,
Lin Yiyang...
We were childhood friends.
At that time, we had another friend.
It was Lan Xinya's sister.
Her name was Lan Xinyu.
-Lan Xinyu?
-That's right.
Situ Feng and Lan Xinyu had an accident.
The two of them fell into the water.
Situ Feng was rescued,
but Xinyu wasn't.
Later, Situ Feng disappeared
from Xinyu's funeral.
-You said that he might have hypoxia?
-Yes.
The situation might be similar
to drowning.
It could have reminded him of the trauma.
Would he do something stupid?
We should go look for Situ Feng now.
Do you know where he might go?
-I don't know.
-You two grew up together.
Was there a place where you used to go
all the time?
Think about it really hard.
Situ Feng.
You have to be safe.
Situ Feng, give me a hand.
Qingqing, I...
Gu Nanxi.
-Let's go.
-Not just yet.
Hold on a second.
I've asked a friend to come help us.
It's better to be discreet
about this matter.
I called Hua Munian. He's very reliable.
Baby, I'm here.
I'm sorry.
I take back what I've said.
-Hey.
-Come here.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you bring
that troublemaker with you?
It's not my fault.
She was in the office when you called me.
She threatened to tell everyone.
-There was nothing I could do.
-What the hell?
Don't worry.
I didn't tell anyone.
Feng's business is my business.
I will definitely find him.
All right. Everyone has arrived.
Then I'll start distributing tasks.
Qingqing and I are a team.
Hua Munian, you'll pair up with Xinya.
Let's try to think of all the places
that Situ Feng might go
and notify each other
of the places that we've searched.
This will save us a lot of time.
Do you have any questions?
-No.
Gosh. It's rare that you two
can agree on something.
-We'll go first.
-Okay.
Qingqing, we should get going too.
Just relax.
We will look for him again later.
Did Situ Feng come here often in the past?
This is the only 24-hour coffee shop
in Yuncheng.
My sister liked to come here.
She introduced this place to Feng and me.
Later, Feng,
also took me here.
Situ Feng took you on a date here.
How romantic.
Xinya.
What's the matter? Don't scare me.
I know
that Feng took me here
out of the guilt he felt for my sister.
He wanted to take care of me
for my sister.
It wasn't love.
But I've gotten used
to being taken care of.
I can't let him go.
I want to be with him forever.
It doesn’t matter,
if he doesn’t like me.
Xinya, you...
Be good. Stop crying.
Hello?
We're in a coffee shop.
Where are you?
Not yet.
Hua Munian.
Hurry and finish your drink.
We'll start looking for him again.
Roger that.
Qingqing.
You don't look well.
Should I take you to the hospital?
That's not necessary.
I'm fine.
Why don't I take you back to school?
All right.
Don't worry too much about Situ Feng.
I'll find him for you.
Situ Feng.
Where are you?
Are you all right?
Feng.
Come here.
I'll teach you how to play the piano.
Xinyu!
Where did you go?
Situ Feng.
You really are here.
Did you spend the night here?
Hey, Situ Feng.
You didn't answer my calls
or replied to my messages.
Are you seriously going to ignore me?
If you ignore me,
I'm going to leave.
Qingqing.
Don't go.
Then promise me.
Don't ever disappear again.
Why are your hands so cold?
Here. Drink some hot water.
Qingqing.
I didn't mean to do that.
Fangfang...
How is she?
She's in the hospital now.
She will have to stay there
for a couple of days.
Situ Feng.
When I called for you last night,
why did you run away?
I...
I felt like...
I was drowning.
Then...
I...
I saw...
Lan Xinyu?
When we were looking for you today,
Gu Nanxi told me
about the last time you disappeared.
Last night,
I saw Xinyu.
I was so frightened.
I was the one who hurt her.
It was only an illusion.
You didn't hurt anyone.
It was an accident.
No, it wasn't.
If I didn't try to be a hero,
Xinyu
wouldn't have died.
Feng.
I'm a better driver than you.
I'll drive Xinyu home today.
Yiyang, you're being too subjective
about our driving skills.
Xinyu should be the one who decides.
I can't make a decision.
Why don't you two fight it out?
Whoever wins will drive Xinyu home.
-All right.
-I'll stay with you if I lose.
Sure.
-Let's go.
I won!
Hey!
You played dirty!
Feng, aren't you driving a bit too fast?
It's all right.
There aren't many cars on the road.
Situ Feng.
It was an accident.
You didn't want that to happen either.
I believe that
Lan Xinyu is in heaven now
and would want you to live happily.
She cared so much about you.
She would only want
to leave you with good memories,
not nightmares.
Situ Feng.
You know what?
In my heart,
you're always a very brave person.
You always face difficulties with courage.
So,
stop blaming yourself.
Chen Qingqing.
Will you always stay by my side?
Will you never leave me?
I didn't mean to hurt Fangfang.
She's your best friend.
I'm scared.
I don't want to lose
the most important person to me again.
That scared the hell out of me.
I didn't know what it was.
It probably ran away.
Thank God, it's gone.
-Qingqing.
-Yes?
This place has a lot of tillandsias.
So there are quite
a lot of spiders around.
Do you mind?
What's the meaning of tillandsia?
They are wild plants.
They don't have any meanings.
This kind of plant
who has broken free
from the constraint of soil
deserves a meaning.
For example,
the pursuit of freedom.
-Freedom?
-Yes.
It fits you.
Freedom is wonderful.
We're from two different worlds.
We should stay away from each other.
What's wrong with me?
Can you just turn into a ball? Roll out!
I wouldn't let you go
because I was too stubborn.
He can't even do a commercial.
How can he earn money for the agency?
Ms. Wang.
I will do it.
You'll have to get into the water.
Situ Feng, wake up.
I can't lose you.
Qingqing!
Subtitle translation by Judy Lu