EPISODE 23
-I'm all right.
-Didn't you say you were good at drinking?
Was this what you called good at drinking?
Be careful.
I'll call a cab for you.
Hey. Be careful.
This seat has been reserved for Qingqing.
Is this yours?
I'm sorry.
Stop.
Sit down.
I said sit down.
Why are you crying?
It's nothing.
What can I do for you?
I want to study.
How do you do this?
YOUR DADDY IS HERE, FOOL. BAD.
About last time...
I am sorry.
Hello, Man. What's up?
Guess what I saw yesterday?
Gu Nanxi hugged Chen Qingqing.
What?
I'm still following them.
We're at the zoo.
I've already told Situ Feng.
Let's reveal Chen Qingqing's
true colors to the world.
Okay, I got it.
Hey, Lan Xinya.
Are you heading for revision now?
Let's go together.
Chen Qingqing and Gu Nanxi
are getting all intimate now.
I don't think I'm going to study.
I'm going to show Feng
that Chen Qingqing
doesn't deserve his love.
Wait for me.
Thanks for yesterday.
If it wasn't for you,
I would be on the news today.
"Young Lady Found Naked and Drunk
on the Streets."
Thanks, my friend.
Right, you said you had something
to tell me yesterday.
What was it?
Never mind, it's no big deal.
Come on.
You've already put up
with all my rambling yesterday.
Today is my turn.
Why don't you let me hear you out?
I'm afraid it's not going
to work out for me.
How would you know if you don't tell me?
If I were to tell you
the thing which has been bothering me
is that I like you,
what would you do?
Gu Nanxi.
Stop joking with me.
Do you think...
Do you think I'm still drunk?
I know
the person you like is Situ Feng.
After seeing so many things
happen between the two of you,
I've already let go.
It doesn't matter if you're Qingchen
or Chen Qingqing.
You're one of a kind to me
and you will soon become
my friend, Situ Feng's girlfriend.
Let's give each other a hug as friends.
Thank you, Gu Nanxi.
Was it true
what you just said?
You're actually Qingchen?
-Situ Feng, hear me out--
-You don't need to say anything.
Calm down, Situ Feng.
It's not what you think.
"Not what I think"?
Then what should I think?
All I saw was
my best friend
and the girl I love
treated me like a fool.
Tell me.
-How is it not what I think?
-Situ Feng.
-I didn't--
-Didn't what?
You didn't lie to me?
What should I call you?
Chen Qingqing or Miss Qingchen?
Were you ever honest with me?
Fine.
She's all yours.
Situ Feng, don't go. Listen to me.
I didn't mean to lie to you.
I went to look for Gu Nanxi yesterday
because I wanted to ask him
how should I tell you
about my true identity
so you won't be so angry as you are now.
So that's why you two ended up
hugging each other?
No.
-Situ Feng, let me explain.
-What is there to explain?
Do you mean it was just a casual hug?
That it was difficult for you
and even when everyone knew about it,
I was the only person
who was kept in the dark?
What are they quarreling about?
What true identity?
What do you think?
Chen Qingqing must have been
being a huge flirt and caused this.
Okay, let me explain it.
Gu Nanxi and I, we're just friends.
That hug you saw
was just a hug between friends.
Yes, I did lie to you
and I'm sorry about it.
But Situ Feng, I want to tell you
that you're the person I like
from the very beginning!
Hey.
Chen Qingqing.
Chen Qingqing, you're so shameless.
With all the evidence we have,
how could you carry on lying?
Think about it.
Ever since school started,
you've been involving yourself
with Feng and Nanxi.
Plus Hua Munian and Lin Yiyang too.
Are you playing a game?
Or are you collecting boyfriends?
Hey, my friendship with Qingqing
is as pure as the snow.
Shut up!
Hey, Situ Feng!
Chen Qingqing.
Feng has finally seen your true colors.
If you know the meaning of integrity,
please don't bother Feng anymore.
Qingqing, let's go back first.
Situ Feng needs time to calm down.
I will explain to him.
You're not completely sober
from yesterday.
I'll send you home.
It's okay.
I can go back on my own.
Qingqing, are you not feeling well?
You look tired.
Fangfang, I need to tell you a secret.
What's the secret?
Actually,
I'm Qingchen.
Qingchen is me.
What?
Are you really Qingchen?
My real name is Chen Qingqing.
I was trying to escape
from my grandpa's bodyguards.
That's why I switched my identity.
Fangfang, I lied to you.
Are you mad at me?
Silly girl, of course not.
Fangfang, what a relief!
Actually, I can understand it.
You must have your own reasons.
Thanks for understanding
but some might not take it well
like you, right?
Are you talking about Situ Feng?
Don't worry. He's so fond of you.
I'm sure he'll come around.
Fangfang, what are you talking about?
You think I didn't know
what's up with you and Lin Yiyang?
-We--
-The two of you
have been swapping outfits
all the time.
I've already seen it twice.
-What are you talking about, Qingqing?
-It's true, I saw it with my own eyes!
What's wrong, Chen Qingqing?
Why are you so quiet?
Don't you know how to greet someone?
If I see a decent human being,
I will greet her.
I didn't know you're capable
of being sarcastic.
Tomorrow is the exam.
If you have nothing else to say,
please don't waste my time.
Yes, our examinations
will be starting tomorrow.
Feng will be present as well.
I'm warning you.
Do not disturb him.
Do not talk to him.
Do not affect him during examinations.
I will talk to whoever I want to talk to.
Why should I listen to you?
You should because Situ Feng
and I grew up together
and he promised
to take care of me forever.
What?
Feng promised to take care of me forever.
It's not going to happen
between the two of you.
Lan Xinya, do you think
I will believe you?
It doesn't matter
if you believe me or not.
You're living in a different world
compared to Feng.
It's worlds apart.
Feng is a simple guy.
He's an affectionate person.
People like you
who likes to flirt with every guy...
I hope you'll quickly disappear
from my sight.
Lan Xinya.
Do yourself a favor. Keep your mouth shut.
Wasn't that the case?
First, it was Feng, then Gu Nanxi.
Two-timing in a relationship,
do you think it's charming?
Ugly people like to do strange things.
Listen up.
Feng is an only child.
He should date someone
from a compatible family.
A materialistic person like you,
I beg of you.
Just get lost already.
You know what?
You're right, I am materialistic.
That's why I approached Situ Feng.
How's that? Are you satisfied?
But...
It looks like Situ Feng
would rather fall for me,
someone who's materialistic
than to give a damn about you.
Doesn't it drive you crazy?
Last but not least,
Situ Feng is mine.
Since you've admitted to it,
I have nothing else to say.
Girls, let's go.
Situ Feng,
can we talk?
Talk about what?
Actually...
It was not my intention
to deceive you.
It was because--
You know what?
You're right, I am materialistic.
That's why I approached Situ Feng.
How's that? Are you satisfied?
But...
It looks like Situ Feng
would rather fall for me,
someone who's materialistic
than to give a damn about you.
Doesn't it drive you crazy?
Last but not least,
Situ Feng
is mine.
Situ Feng, don't listen to it.
I said those things because--
Chen Qingqing,
there's nothing else for us to talk about.
I gave you my heart
and you trampled on it.
You made me feel like I'm a joke.
That's why I approached Situ Feng.
How's that? Are you satisfied?
But...
-What are you doing, Hua Munian?
-Get over here.
Gosh, you're hurting me.
You need to apologize
to Chen Qingqing now.
Apologize?
Why should I apologize to her?
She said everything herself.
I'm just letting people know about it.
If it wasn't for you,
would Chen Qingqing say those things?
I don't understand.
What is it about Chen Qingqing?
What did she do to all of you?
Why is everyone siding with her?
Why are you protecting her?
Because she's my friend!
I trust her!
Is that what you think of me?
Am I such a horrible person?
I am horrible.
I did all the bad things.
Are you happy?
If she's your friend,
then what about me?
You're different, you're...
Situ Feng.
Gu Nanxi, let go of me!
Situ Feng, you're not a fool.
Don't believe everything you heard
on the recordings.
Why? Why shouldn't I believe it?
Should I believe you
and Chen Qingqing instead?
You're right, I'm a fool
who's not sure what to believe in.
We didn't lie to you.
Didn't lie to me?
Then tell me.
When did you find out that Chen Qingqing
was Qingchen?
You can't answer me, can you?
Let me guess.
Every time I tried to hook you up
with Qingchen,
I wonder what were you thinking?
Every time when I poured my heart out
for Chen Qingqing,
I wonder what were you thinking?
Gu Nanxi.
I thought you were my best friend!
You are my best friend!
You're not my friend!
Can you wake up, Situ Feng?
I said it's not what you think!
No wonder you used to ask me
if we would end up fighting.
So this was what you meant.
You were preparing yourself
for today, am I right?
I was a fool
because I believed in the two of you!
Situ Feng.
Do you still remember how we met?
I was eight years old
and a transfer student.
Everyone knew I was an illegitimate child.
No one wanted to play with me.
It was the saddest
and loneliest time of my life.
It was you
who came to talk to me first.
You were the first person
who wanted to play with me.
Ever since then, I've always
thought you as my best friend.
I admit.
I did fall for Qingchen,
but after I found out who she really was,
I decided to let go of my feelings
because I would never betray
my best friend!
Do you think everything Chen Qingqing
has done for you were all lies?
That's all I'm going to say.
You can think about the rest yourself.
EXAM RESULTS AND RANKING
Hey, how did you do?
-It was just average.
-Did you make it?
How did you do?
-Look, who's that?
-Me too.
Lin Yiyang? Isn't he the guy
who always failed his exams?
I can't believe he made it
into the top 100.
Could it have been a mistake?
What are you reading?
If you're able to score well
for your exams
and make it into top 100,
I will tell you.
Deal.
Lin Yiyang seems like a different person.
I heard before the exams started,
he studied at the library every day.
Are you sure?
Look, it's Lin Yiyang.
He used to look so fierce
and unapproachable.
I didn't know he was good looking.
Are you interested in him?
Of course not, a guy like him
is too much for me to handle.
It's better for me to look
from a distance.
It's good that you know your limits.
Hi, Hebiancao. I am Situ Feng's manager.
I would like to invite you to take part
in His Highness's next album packaging.
Your comic strips will be included
into the album.
Please let us know.
If Situ Feng finds out
about my third identity,
and finds out that I was the one
who drew those funny things about him...
Wouldn't he kill me?
What should I do?
That's odd. It was such a good offer.
Why hasn't she responded yet?
Were my messages not sent?
Maybe.
Well...
Hey, we managed to solve the case.
Why are you still looking so gloomy?
This new album
is a top-quality production.
It contains comic strips
from your number one supporter
plus the handshake coupon.
It's going to become a hot topic
and it's definitely
going to become a huge hit.
That's right.
During my time, where could you
have found such a great deal?
All right.
Tell me about your plans.
Why don't you personally invite Hebiancao?
What?
Hi, Hebiancao.
I'm Situ Feng.
Thank you for your support.
I hope to be working with you
on my new album.
Please let me know
when you've seen my video.
Situ Feng.
Why are you so persistent?
Why does it feel like a Cinderella story?
I haven't seen Hebiancao online
for several days.
If she heard about this
I'm sure she's going to be overjoyed.
Could it be that something happened?
I'm worried too.
I heard she once mentioned
that her college is in Yuncheng?
Lei, you can check her IP address.
Wow, these people.
Are they trying to drive me to the edge?
If I don't agree to work with Situ Feng,
they're probably going
to find out all of my secrets.
Whatever! We shall wait and see.
Qingqing, why are you up so early?
Fangfang, your happiness
is in your own hands.
Now, I'm going to create my own history.
You have to work hard
to seize your own happiness.
Let's do it!
Are you Hebiancao?
Your Highness!
He's our boss.
Do you think anyone can be his girlfriend?
Why did you jump on the bandwagon?
You're so silly.
Do you know there's a clock tower
in our college?
Legend has it that if you enter
the clock tower
and express your regrets sincerely,
the clock will turn anti-clockwise
if it is touched by your sincerity.
You can talk?
Subtitle translation by June Tian