EPISODE 28
Sir.
Mrs. Lan is not feeling well.
Why don't I take you home first?
We'll take care of Xinya.
You must look after Xinya.
Don't worry.
Gu Nanxi.
I'll leave it to you.
Let's go.
Xinya.
Lanting.
Knife.
Do you have a knife? Do you?
Didn't you say that if I hurt myself,
I could keep Feng by my side?
I'm going to hurt myself.
-Xinya.
-I'll do whatever it takes.
Situ Feng is not going to come back.
Give me the knife. I beg you.
Let me keep him by my side.
Hua Munian, do you have a knife?
-Give me the sleeping pills.
-Xinya, knock it off.
Lanting.
Please help me.
-I beg you. Please help me.
-There's nothing you can do.
Even if you hit your head on the wall,
-Situ Feng wouldn't care.
-I beg you. Please help me.
Gu Nanxi.
Can you drag this crazy woman,
Yang Lanting, out?
Did you call me a crazy woman?
Did you not hear what I said?
Look.
You're a selfish, despicable
and reckless, crazy woman.
You don't understand anything.
I was only helping Xinya--
Helping Xinya?
Look at her right now.
Look at what you've done to her.
You weren't helping her.
This was Chen Qingqing's fault.
This has nothing to do with Chen Qingqing.
You're the one who should be responsible.
If you didn't plot any of those things,
Xinya wouldn't have become this way.
Her parents wouldn't have
to worry about her every day.
Situ Feng and Qingqing
wouldn't have had to endure that.
Today's farce wouldn't have happened.
All right. Stop fighting.
Let Xinya calm down first.
Lanting, come outside with me.
Feng.
Lanting.
Weren't you going too far this time?
You have to fight for what you truly want.
But that doesn’t mean
that you can put a person's life at risk.
You knew that Situ Feng
didn't like Lan Xinya.
How could you help her?
Gu Nanxi.
I'm very disappointed in all of you.
Lanting has left.
Nobody else will help me.
Xinya, if you want,
I can help you.
You?
Xinya.
From now on,
you have to let go of your past
and start a new life.
A new life?
You can't stop thinking
about Situ Feng right now.
But I'm telling you.
In a few days,
a few months or a few years,
you won't think about him anymore.
You will meet a better man.
Don't cry for a man who doesn't love you.
Without Feng,
what else can I do?
You'll definitely meet a man
who's better and more talented
than Situ Feng.
He will at least be ten times
or 100 times better than him.
Don't hurt yourself
for a man who doesn't love you.
It won't be easy to find such a man.
Besides,
I'm not worthy of love.
You are.
Do you want to bet?
You'll definitely find that man.
And...
I...
We can look for him together.
-Hurry, let's go.
-Let's go.
-Qingqing.
-Yes?
Where are we going?
To the airport.
I'm afraid that Lan Xinya
will create more drama.
I'm going to hide you at my house.
Qingqing, I'm sorry.
I don't think I can go with you.
-What?
What do you mean?
Are you going to leave me behind again?
-Seriously?
Qingqing.
You're silly.
I didn't bring my ID.
I can't get on the plane.
That's right.
Qingqing.
I've promised you.
I will never let you go.
That's great.
So...
Where should we go now?
Nowhere.
Sometimes, when I run out of inspiration,
I will hop on a bus
and just wander aimlessly.
The view outside the window
will brighten up my mood.
Then, inspiration will come to me.
What are you doing?
I'm writing down what you said.
I'm making an illustration book
of Situ Feng's best quotes
to give back to my fans.
It's time for me to collect materials.
You're putting pressure on me.
-Situ Feng.
-Yes?
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will become
Hebiancao's source materials.
-Cheers.
Shaofang, hurry up and ask Hebiancao
if she could get me a VIP ticket.
Hey!
Let's make Hebiancao's boyfriend
a resident singer at my place.
He'll sing every song that we request.
Hold on.
Calm down.
Have we all just become lovesick?
His Highness has a girlfriend.
I think that it's wise of him
to date someone like Hebiancao.
That's right. His Highness
has found the right girlfriend.
He has good taste in women.
I think that Hebiancao
will take His Highness's career
to the next level.
It's an honor to worship a star
with all of you.
Cheers to our bond.
-Cheers to our bond.
Lin Yiyang.
Thank you for treating me to a movie.
Don't worry about it.
Fangfang.
I...
What is it?
It's nothing.
The movie was nice.
Did you like the female lead?
Yes, I liked her.
She's pretty. Why wouldn't I like her?
They went through so much in the movie.
They could finally be together.
What a nice ending.
Hey.
I didn't see anything.
You're a pervert.
Hey, I didn't see anything.
I didn't see anything.
I'm going back to the dorm.
So...
Are you going
to the library again tomorrow?
I really didn't see anything.
Stop talking about it.
Guys.
Are you both waiting
for the other person to talk first?
Are you trying to burn my tongue?
My little master, Situ Feng
and Madam Chen Qingqing.
Can you give me a heads-up
before you cause trouble next time?
The press was looking for me.
Do you know how much money I spent
to settle this matter?
By the way, Daniel.
You've maxed out all these cards.
Is there another way to pay?
They're all maxed out?
That's right. It's better to pay in cash.
I've got an idea.
I've borrowed 150,000 yuan from 9Fbank.
Withdraw the money.
Okay.
Well...
I'm sorry, Daniel.
We'll give you a heads-up next time.
There's no next time.
Luckily, the fans reacted positively
to the news of you two dating.
It seems like if you find
the right person to date,
the fans won't overreact.
Let me think of a way
to settle this matter.
By the way, Situ Feng,
have you checked the chart lately?
Your album has remained
among the top five.
The agency thinks very highly
of you and trusts you.
Talented boy, keep up the good work.
But...
Daniel.
-Yes?
-The things between Qingqing and I
may not be so simple.
We've caused
a small problem.
Stop. Let me take a sip of water
before you tell me.
Do you remember Qingchen?
Yes, I do.
Chen Qingqing? Qingchen?
Is she Qingchen?
It's you.
You're also Hebiancao.
You're quite an actress.
Do you want to join showbiz
and help grow the film industry?
I didn't have a choice.
Daniel, would it be a problem
if my fans found out
that Chen Qingqing is Qingchen?
But I shouldn't keep this from them.
I'll draft a news release regarding this.
And make the public
accept the fact step by step.
Can you stop giving me
a challenging problem each day?
I swear.
This is the last problem.
Hey!
Isn't this Zhang Fangfang?
I heard that you're dating Lin Yiyang.
Where is he?
Are you waiting for him?
He will be here soon.
Is there anything you need from him?
Nothing special.
But Zhang Fangfang,
if I remember correctly,
you came to our school
on scholarship, didn't you?
But you're hanging out with Lin Yiyang.
He's a bad influence.
I'm afraid
that you might end up getting
kicked out of school.
Xinyan, what are you talking about?
That will never happen to Fangfang.
And think about it.
If she becomes Lin Yiyang's girlfriend,
she will be able to live a wealthy life.
She won't have to go to school.
However, Lin Yiyang
is just dating you for fun.
I...
Let's go, Fangfang.
Lin Yiyang,
you haven't apologized to me yet.
I'm sorry, Hong Xiaoman.
Let me apologize to you for him.
Why are you apologizing for him?
Do you really think
that you're somebody to him?
I...
Of course she has the right
to apologize for me.
But you don't have the right
to accept her apology.
I heard what you said just now.
But you were wrong about something.
If Fangfang doesn't deserve
to attend this college,
I'm sure that the two of you
would get expelled sooner than her.
How dare you bully us?
Aren't you afraid
of getting kicked out of college?
Did anyone see you getting bullied by me?
But something came to my mind
after seeing you two.
I have a very special hobby lately.
Isn't that right, Fangfang?
Yes.
Lately,
I like to raise scorpions.
A scorpion loves to sting a girl's lips.
If you don't leave Fangfang alone,
I promise
to give scorpions to you as a gift.
Xiaoman, let's go.
Let's go, Fangfang.
Fangfang.
Do you want to be the person
who gets to decide things
for me in the future?
What do you mean?
Why are you so dumb?
Be my girlfriend.
I made a lot of mistakes in the past.
But I really want to be
a part of your world.
I will try to become the person
that you expect me to be.
So...
will you be my girlfriend?
Sir, is there anything you need?
You.
Release Chen Qingqing's information
to the paparazzi.
Sir, but shouldn't we give
Mr. Chen a heads-up?
Don't worry about that old man.
Just listen to me.
Yes, sir.
Every girl tries to dress up,
but you dress down instead.
I don't know what to say to you.
I'm used to this look.
Which version of you do you prefer?
Well,
every girl wants
to look pretty.
Right?
Look at me.
Look at these pair of glasses,
these freckles and this hair.
Come to think of it.
I look
like a combination of SpongeBob and Arale.
Do you think so?
Look.
"Look, Patrick Star.
A cloud has appeared in the clear sky."
"That cloud is really a cloud."
Besides, I'm doing this
because I'm afraid that my grandpa
and Lu Jingyang will catch me.
Therefore, I have to act like Spider-Man.
This is my mask.
But you don't have to be afraid anymore.
You don't need the makeup now.
You're right.
Today's the first day of school.
Why don't you go to school looking pretty
and see how everyone will react?
Really?
But I'm used to this look.
If I become pretty all of a sudden,
I will be making a counterattack.
-You will become the campus beauty.
-Really?
The Goddess will become a joke.
They've always been a joke in my eyes
The biggest joke ever
Chen Qingqing?
She's so pretty.
Isn't she Qingchen?
I can't stop drooling over her.
She's so pretty.
There are two good-looking people
in the class.
You must feel really lucky.
That's right.
Zhang Fangfang is also very pretty.
We're really lucky.
That's right. We're aware
that we'll never get
to date girls like them.
Therefore, I'm happy
to just be able to look at them.
That’s true.
-Chen Qingqing is so beautiful.
Please don't go away.
-So pretty.
Situ Feng.
Do you notice anything different
about me today?
No, I don't.
You didn't wear your glasses.
Even if you walk on the streets like this,
no one will take a glance at you.
What are you looking at?
Don't you need to study?
You only care about your appearances.
You should be embarrassed of yourselves.
Have you solved the permutations
and combinations on the blackboard?
Turn around.
-Chen Qingqing.
-Yes?
Teach me.
But Your Highness,
this is the Chemistry textbook.
Are permutations
and combinations not Chemistry?
Yes.
You're close.
Nanxi.
Over there.
Right there.
Who's looking at you?
Why were you trying
to act cool all of a sudden?
The word is out.
My fans have come here.
Fans?
Where?
Ten o'clock.
Hello. So you've found out
where I go to school.
Situ Feng, are you a student here too?
That's right. Do you want my autograph
or do you want to take a photo with me?
We're looking
for the famous Chen Qingqing.
We heard that she goes to this school.
She's a wealthy girl,
but she chose to live like a commoner.
We're really inspired by her.
Can you give her
these flowers and letters?
-Thank you.
-Okay.
Thank you.
Actually, I can give you my autograph.
Well,
I went to your signing event once.
I've already got your autograph.
But thank you.
Can you tell us the progress
of your latest comic book?
Hey!
-Show me the characters.
-Move.
Hey, what are you doing?
She's pretty, but it doesn't mean
that you can harass her.
Also, stop giving her gifts.
Can you not be so shallow?
We represent
the Ballet Academy of Yuncheng.
Miss Chen Qingqing's ballet technique
has reached the realm of the fairies.
We really hope to witness
your performance.
Thank you.
We're from the Comics Club.
Goddess Chen Qingqing's drawings remind me
of several pioneer cartoonists from Japan.
I hope to directly learn from her.
We're from the Piano Association.
Miss Chen Qingqing's music
has cleansed our souls.
Just the thought of it
makes me want to cry.
You're exaggerating.
It's true.
After seeing the video
of Goddess Chen Qingqing,
we were all shocked.
And it's unbelievable
that she's also so pretty.
I'm no match for her.
After hearing your confession,
I'm pretty shocked too.
Mister, please don't block our way.
We're trying to learn from our goddess.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Goddess.
Thank you.
-Miss Chen Qingqing, I worship you.
-Goddess Qingqing, you're amazing.
Hello, Daniel.
Qingqing's gone back to being pretty.
Aren't you going to step in?
Gosh. You've never asked me
to step into anything
since you made your debut.
I...
I'm doing this for her.
Think about it.
Once her looks are exposed,
she will get caught up in scandals.
People might bash her
for hiding her identity
in order to get close to me. Am I right?
It won't be fair to her.
Gosh, Situ Feng.
Give me some advice.
You don't understand the public at all.
The frog became a prince.
The beast also became a prince.
The prince and princess
lived happily ever after.
Did the public get upset by the stories?
They didn't.
The public will be thrilled
to see an ugly girl become pretty.
There won't be any negative coverage.
I think the public
will like Chen Qingqing.
You know what?
She should become a celebrity too.
I think this is a great idea.
What do you think?
Hello?
Situ Feng?
Hey!
Feng.
Hello?
I've done too many stupid things.
For someone who doesn't even love me,
I've forgotten what really matters.
Why are you here?
You don't have to work
in this cafe anymore.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
We're dating. We're not starring
in the drama The President's Lovely Wife.
I have done what you ordered,
Young Master.
This is smart of you.
This couple would not be able
to handle all the negative comments.
Come here.
Tell me. Why did you look at me like that?
I'm trying to drive a wedge between them.
Just wait and see.
Subtitle translation by Judy Lu