Previously on "The Walking Dead"...
Listen to what I say. Now step aside.
♪
[BOTH GRUNT]
[WALKERS SNARLING]
GIRL: Come this way. It's clear.
Go! Go, go, go!
I'm Magna. This is Connie and Kelly.
What's yours?
Judith.
Judith Grimes.
MICHONNE: Hey.
I know you're here.
♪
I'm still here, too.
Maybe you already knew that.
♪
But it hasn't gotten any easier.
Sun keeps rising.
♪
Days keep passing.
World keeps spinning.
♪
Time... it just keeps moving forward.
Weeks, months,
even years go by...
while you try to make sense of it all.
[WALKER GROWLING]
♪
[GRUNTING]
_
♪
Try to find where you belong.
Try to look ahead to a better future.
[HOOVES CLOPPING]
But the truth is...
♪
...the path ahead has only grown darker.
[BRANCHES SNAP]
It's harder to see.
♪
You can feel so lost...
so alone...
♪
...so desperate for something,
anything that might show you the way.
♪
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
But even now,
after all this time,
surrounded by darkness...
♪
...there are still flashes of light...
...tiny beacons that shine out,
calling to us.
♪
It's not enough to light the way ahead,
but it's enough to keep going.
[WALKER GROWLING]
♪
Keep trying. Keep fighting.
[BIRDS CHIRPING, GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪
Keep dreaming.
So that's what I do
every second of every day...
♪
...for you, for us.
I haven't given up,
and I never will.
♪
[HORSE SNORTING SOFTLY]
[WATER TRICKLING]
Come on.
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[LEAVES CRUNCHING, RUSTLING]
Judith!
Jude!
JUDITH: I'm here!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Are you okay?
[PERSON WHIMPERS]
I heard them calling.
They needed our help.
[PEOPLE BREATHING HEAVILY]
Our rig... It got overrun
by sickos.
We owe our lives to Miss Grimes here.
They still need our help.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GULPING]
[WATER SLOSHES, WOMAN COUGHS]
We can't. You know that.
But...
Hey, uh, I dabbled
in the culinary arts, uh,
- once upon a time ago, and, uh...
- Luke.
...you know, with a little bit of help,
I can help whip this buck
into a mighty fine osso buco.
EUGENE: Stew.
We make stew.
More mileage for the masses.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
There are more of you?
- [WALKERS GROWLING]
- Way more, with walls and...
- Judith.
- Jude.
_
KELLY: Incoming.
♪
[GRUNTS]
[BODY THUDS]
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪
- [BODY THUDS]
- There's more on the way.
We gotta get outta here.
[WALKERS GROWLING IN DISTANCE]
They need food and water and medicine.
♪
If they don't go, I don't go.
Come on.
LUKE: Yeah? [CHUCKLES]
Come on. Come on.
- [GRUNTS]
- [INHALES SHARPLY, COUGHS]
[GASPING]
♪
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
JERRY: It'll grow back.
♪
Is there any part of this
place that's not falling apart?
Our loyalty to you, my queen.
[GOAT BLEATS]
- Jerry.
- What?
Married to the king,
mother to the prince...
gonna have to accept it at some point.
[HORSE WHINNIES, HAMMER POUNDING]
If I haven't after all these years,
it's probably not gonna happen.
[METAL CLANKS, GROANS]
- [TOOL CLATTERS]
- Oh, no.
[STEAM HISSING]
[MACHINERY RUMBLING]
Henry.
Need to get out of here.
Not going anywhere, dude.
Someone hand me the tape?
You hold, I'll wrap.
[HISSING FADES]
[RUMBLING STOPS]
[MACHINERY HUMMING]
[TAPE CRINKLING]
Jerry, how we doing?
In the clear.
[TAPE RIPS]
Nice work, dude.
Is everyone all right?
[SIGHS] Another pipe went.
- [TAPE CLATTERS]
- Henry fixed it.
With these meager provisions.
Well done, my boy.
Dad, we're holding things
together with plastic and tape.
- But we are holding things together.
- We need better tools.
Someone who's trained to use them.
Henry, we've discussed this.
No, you've discussed it.
I'll be late for supper.
Don't wait for me.
Henry, I appreciate your
passion and your honesty,
but you had best watch your tone, son.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
[GRUNTS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[TOOLS CLACKING]
He's not wrong.
[GOAT BLEATS]
This place is getting older.
He's getting older.
I know.
[HORSE WHINNIES]
But surely, there are others
who'd gladly train
with Earl Sutton of Hilltop,
assuming he's not retired by now.
We'll figure it out.
This is his home. He wants to fix it.
[SIGHS]
But the fair's right around the corner.
We need him here.
You need him here.
And after the fair, you'll
need him for something else
and then something else after that.
You'll always need him.
I just... [SIGHS]
I want him safe.
[HORSE WHINNIES]
Hilltop feels so distant.
More distant than it's ever been.
- Hasn't been the same since...
- I know.
But sometimes you have
to let the cracks happen
to let the light in.
[LAUGHS]
EUGENE: Again, I feel
the need to remind you
that what we are doing is in
direct and flagrant violation
of the current security protocols.
ROSITA: Yeah, we know.
[HORSE SNORTS]
Ohh. [SNIFFS]
Come on.
♪
[GATE SCREECHES]
[GRUNTS]
♪
[GATE THUDS]
_
Can't be worse than Jones Springs.
Just like Jones Springs
couldn't be worse than Coalport.
Oh, God.
Coalport was a fossilized city of shit.
♪
You'll be safe here.
I promise.
♪
_
[HOOVES CLOPPING]
♪
Holy shit.
WOMAN: Want some water?
♪
_
This is Alexandria.
This is home.
♪
[TOOLS CLACKING]
[METAL SQUEAKING]
♪
- Hi, Daddy!
- Gracie, stay where you are, okay?
♪
There's another one in the wagon.
Female with head
trauma. She's conscious.
♪
Hey. All right.
Alex and the other
nurses are on standby.
I'll take her to the infirmary right now.
I'm coming with her.
♪
[HORSE WHINNIES]
MICHONNE: Whoa.
♪
[GATE CREAKS]
[BAG THUDS]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
You wanna tell me what this is?
Five unknowns... all clean,
one headed to the infirmary.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
All clean? You sure about that?
EUGENE: Indeed.
They're whistle-worthy, clean as a-wise.
They surrendered their weapons willingly
and submitted to
standard frisk procedure.
And why are they here?
AARON: My call.
It's not your call to make.
I decided.
They needed help.
Judith, you know the rules.
You all do.
Thing is, they're here now,
and one of 'em's badly hurt.
Siddiq's checkin' her out, but...
Look, no disrespect,
but maybe their fate is something
we should decide together.
GABRIEL: It'll be dark soon.
First thing tomorrow, we can bring them
before the council for a vote.
[SMACKS LIPS] Okay.
Put them in holding.
_
Come on. Let's go.
♪
That was for the boy.
This is for the man you've become.
You're actin' like we'll
never see each other again.
I'll be back before the
fair starts, all right?
♪
Wouldn't miss it.
As my father said to me once
upon my departure from home,
you be respectful, be responsible,
be kind, and be safe.
I will, Dad. I promise.
♪
I'd still feel better if
Jerry or I came with you.
♪
You need to tend to things here.
This fair is important.
If we could bring the communities
back together as full partners, it would...
It would change everything.
♪
We're gonna be fine.
He's gonna be fine.
♪
He sees the world as it
should be, not as it is.
He's a dreamer.
Hmm.
Wonder where he gets that from.
♪
Nothin' wrong with that.
This world could use
a few more dreamers.
And a few more of those who pull us down
from our flights of fancy back to Earth.
Hmm.
Who at Hilltop will be that for Henry?
I have some ideas.
♪
I'm sure you do, my
queen. I'm sure you do.
♪
GABRIEL: As you can probably
tell from our turnout here,
it's been a long time since we've seen
new faces inside these walls.
We're a fair community
of decent-minded people,
but we are not soft.
And that's not going to change today.
So let's begin.
Which one of you is the leader?
What makes you think we have one?
- Did you know each other before?
- LUKE: No.
It was, uh, Magna and
then Yumiko, uh, first,
and then, uh, Connie and Kelly
and then... and then me
and then Bernie.
[INHALES DEEPLY] Sh...
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry.
[EXHALES SHARPLY] Bernie was
the one that we lost yesterday.
Um...
[SIGHS]
There were others, of course.
But, like Bernie, they just...
♪
[CRYING]
They didn't, uh... They didn't make it.
♪
Who were you before?
Me? Before all this?
[CLAPS HANDS SOFTLY]
[SIGHS] I was a music teacher.
Waited tables at a truck stop.
♪
She says she was a journalist,
but she's just being modest.
She exposed a bunch of
sleazeball politicians
and put them behind bars.
♪
And you?
I was in high school,
stressin' about stupid shit
that felt like the end of the world.
♪
And who are you now?
A fighter.
♪
She says she's my guardian angel,
but, really, it's the other way around.
I guess I'm still a music teacher?
Um, education never ends,
not even in the face
of monsters and mayhem.
♪
What did you do to survive?
What I had to... Anything I had to.
♪
She says she never gave up,
but me, I grew up.
♪
LUKE: [EXHALES SHARPLY]
I don't... I don't...
[STAMMERS]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
I don't think I did anything special.
♪
I-I don't know what I did to deserve it.
Um...
At... At first, I was just lucky.
I was... I was in the right
place at the right time,
and then, uh, I met the right people.
[CHUCKLES]
H-Here's the thing, is that...
It's funny, but [SNIFFS] before all this,
if you saw us all
sittin' at the same table
at, like, a restaurant,
a bar, or something...
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
...you'd say to yourself, "Well, hey,
I don't know. Maybe these
people work together?"
[CHUCKLING] Because
we certainly don't have
anything in common,
except for the fact
that we're breathing.
♪
And that's a lot nowadays, right?
Thank you.
♪
If that's everything, I'd
like to motion for a vote.
I have a question.
GABRIEL: The chair recognizes
our fellow councilperson
and head of security.
[CHAIR SCRAPES]
♪
As a community, we want to be kind.
We want to be generous.
We want to be charitable.
But, as we know,
decisions like the one
we are about to make
can come with a heavy price.
Can you show me your left hand?
Michonne, what are you doing?
[GLOVE THUDS]
You get that at a truck stop?
Screw you.
♪
What is it?
You wanna tell him?
Michonne, if you have
something to say, s...
It's a prison tattoo.
[SPECTATORS GASP, MURMUR]
The four dots are the walls.
The one in the middle is you,
the prisoner.
Hard time.
[SPECTATORS MURMURING]
♪
Look, just because she was a prisoner...
I can explain.
Oh, you wanna tell the truth?
Yes.
- And you have nothing to hide?
- Nothing.
♪
Put the knife on the table.
[MURMURING CONTINUES]
♪
[BELT BUCKLE CLACKS]
[SPECTATORS GASP]
♪
I remember,
and I know that you do, too.
♪
So go ahead. Take your vote.
I second the motion.
MAGNA: Hey!
Can I ask you a question?
MICHONNE: No.
[MURMURING CONTINUES]
[FABRIC THUDS]
[SIGHS]
[STATIC CRACKLING SOFTLY]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
ROSITA: I thought you
gave up on that thing.
I did.
[SWITCHES CLICKING, CRACKLING STOPS]
I just... I keep thinking
that there are still people out there,
people that we don't know about.
Those survivors?
I think Michonne's wrong.
I think they're good people.
Yeah, I mean, prison doesn't mean shit
without knowing the whole
story, and Michonne knows it.
She just got that crowd
riled up on purpose
ever since, you know...
Yeah, I know.
But they're here.
They're here until the one in the infirmary
is back on her feet.
So there's still time for
her to change her mind.
Maybe.
[CHUCKLES]
I was talking to Eugene.
He thinks that if we went further out...
Mm-hmm.
...and set up a remote amplifier,
we could boost the signal.
Yeah, but, you know what
Michonne's gonna say.
Security breach. Yeah, I know.
Plus, trying to find people
and reach out to them with that thing,
it's like stumbling around in the dark.
But think what we might
find, who we might find,
what else might be out there.
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
You stay here,
help with the new
people any way you can.
Me and Eugene,
we'll worry about the relay box.
You sure?
Have I told you lately
how amazing you are?
Yes.
But if you wanna keep
saying it, I won't stop you.
[DOOR OPENS]
- MICHONNE: Thought I was done with this...
- [DOOR CLOSES]
...done with talkin' to you
and never hearing you answer.
But I watched what you
did to protect him...
...how nothing else
mattered except him...
...and I need to be that now for them.
And I know it's not what we planned,
not what we wanted,
but you weren't here.
And neither was he.
- You didn't have to go through the...
- [FLOORBOARD CREAKS]
Judith?
[DOOR CREAKS]
It's almost time for your lesson.
And your homework after that.
Okay, Mom.
[FOOTSTEPS FADE]
[HOOVES CLOPPING, BIRDS CHIRPING]
HENRY: You sure this is right?
Wasn't the turn off to
Hilltop a few miles back?
We're not going to Hilltop. Not yet.
WOMAN: Help!
- Whoa, halt!
- Help! [GRUNTS]
Help! Help!
- Wait. Henry!
- HENRY: She needs help!
Henry, stop!
- Help!
- Shit.
[GRUNTS] Help!
♪
Help!
[GRUNTING]
Get off her!
♪
My hero.
Drop it!
♪
Drop it.
[DOOR CLANKS]
MAN: Now, see, I was
never too good at math,
but I'm pretty sure there's
more of us than you.
♪
Hey there, bosslady.
Comin' up on it soon.
You got those circuits unscrambled yet?
Not yet, but I will
in two armadillo blinks of an eye.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
You must really like Gabriel.
What?
Well, enlisting me as your accomplice
and flouting security
protocol to stand by your man,
well, I take it
as a sign of the seriousness
of your intentions toward him.
Eugene, can we just
focus on what we're doing?
Okeydokey.
Machete-wielding men of the
cloth with zero depth perception
aren't exactly a dime a dozen.
I'll give you that.
But that's not to say
that there aren't other,
more viable selects available to you...
Selects with equally
distinctive qualities
and belief systems firmly
rooted in facts and science
versus fables and fairy tales,
- generally speaking.
- [CHUCKLES]
Anyone specific in mind?
- Generally speaking, as I said.
- Right.
Whoa.
♪
Tracks look fresh.
Maybe hundreds heading east.
♪
Lucky for us, west is
where the deed gets done.
[KNOCKS ON WAGON]
♪
She had a concussion and
she's a little dehydrated,
but she could be back
on her feet by tomorrow.
But should she be?
That's not for me to say.
[WHEEL SQUEAKING]
[GRUNTING]
[WATER RUSHING]
Hey, doc, what's your story?
Were you here from the start?
No, I was a stranger,
someone they took in.
Okay.
But it was different then.
Okay. I-Is there a reason
that things changed?
There's a reason for everything.
♪
Excuse me.
REGINA: For what it's worth,
kid, you didn't stand a chance.
We had you pegged a mile down the road.
JED: [WHISTLES]
[HORSE NEIGHS]
♪
So...
sorry for the inconvenience.
See, this really ain't my bag,
but times have been tough
ever since Sanctuary went bust.
[WALKERS GROWLING]
This is all we have in the world.
We used to have more horses,
but [SCOFFS] we got hungry.
Could've joined one of
the other communities.
♪
[CHUCKLES]
That ain't really my bag, either.
[LAUGHTER]
♪
Listen.
You spared me back in the day,
so I'm gonna offer
you the same courtesy.
Keep your wagon,
your horses, your lives.
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
Shit, you can keep your damn stick.
'Cause what do I need with a stick?
♪
Everything else is ours,
and that'll make us square.
Fine.
Take it and go.
♪
Think I'll have that
rock on your hand, too.
♪
Henry, don't!
HENRY: Come on.
♪
[GRUNTS]
Here.
Take it.
Take it! It's yours!
♪
Pleasure doin' business with ya.
I meant to tell ya,
I really like what you
done with your hair.
♪
JED: [CHUCKLES]
Airplane "A" and airplane
"B" are 1,000 miles apart.
If airplane "A" is flying
east at 500 miles per hour
and airplane "B" is flying west
at 650 miles per hour, how...
You know what?
I would definitely recommend
booking a seat on airplane "C,"
because that is shaping up
to be one hell of a mid-air collision.
You gonna help me or what?
[CHUCKLES]
All right. Let me ask you somethin'.
You ever seen an airplane fly
in any direction at any speed?
No.
Do you think you ever will?
Probably not.
So what the hell
difference does it make?
See, math problems are supposed
to apply to the real world.
You want my help?
Give me a question or a problem
from right here, right now.
[TOOLS CLACKING]
You know the strangers
we brought here yesterday?
My mom's gonna make them leave.
Well, no, I didn't
know, but let me guess.
You being you, you wanna help 'em.
I found 'em. I brought 'em here.
Lemme tell you something.
When I was about your age, I
used to bring home stray dogs.
My mom, she hated it.
I never understood why.
They always seemed
so friendly and grateful.
Till one day I brought
home the wrong dog.
What happened?
Did it bite you?
Not me.
That dog killed all the other strays,
chewed off half my mom's ear
when she tried to stop it.
The thing is,
that dog seemed just as friendly
and grateful as the rest of 'em.
And what about after that?
You ever bring home another dog?
Well, hell no. I wised my ass up.
Yeah.
[BOOK THUDS]
And look how great
everything turned out for you.
Wait a minute. Where you going?
I thought you wanted my help.
I do, but just with math.
Why just math?
Because it doesn't
matter if you're a good
or bad person on the inside.
The numbers don't care.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[GRUNTS]
[SWITCHES CLICK]
[STATIC HISSES]
Lookin' good, Eugene!
EUGENE: I'm comin' down.
Okay.
[SIGHS]
Slow and steady. Easy peasy.
[GRUNTS]
[WALKERS GROWLING]
[WIND HOWLS]
♪
Sweet sassy molassy.
Ro! Herd!
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪
Get your ass down! Now!
[HORSES NEIGHING]
♪
Shit.
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
♪
[GRUNTS]
EUGENE: [SCREAMS]
Ohh!
Eugene!
♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY] My knee.
Can you put weight on it?
That's a seriously painful negative.
[PANTING]
Herd musta flipped
a hardcore "U" on the DL.
♪
Aah.
Use this as a crutch. We gotta go.
[GRUNTS]
♪
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
[CLICKS TONGUE]
I don't get it.
You didn't even try.
There's no point.
- That's bullshit.
- Henry.
No, there's right, and there's wrong.
You stand up for what's right,
and you fight what's wrong.
You taught me that.
And I remember when you did.
What happened?
You.
♪
Some day, you'll understand.
MAGNA: I'm sorry.
That Michonne set me up.
_
You screwed up, Magna.
We didn't know how things
were gonna play out.
I wanted us to have options.
Hand it over.
What?
Yumiko's necklace. Come on.
Yeah, we noticed. Hand it over.
[SIGHS]
[NECKLACE CLACKS]
We can't just go back out there.
Without horses, our rig,
supplies, how long do we last?
- _
- For as long as we can, minute by minute,
day by day, ride or die, right?
Same as always.
Right.
MAGNA: Yeah.
That worked out great for Bernie, right?
_
If Bernie could see this place,
see what life we could live,
you know he wanted us to have it, right?
We don't have a choice.
We fight, as always.
We fight.
_
She says...
I know.
We need this.
Everything Miko talks about.
Listen to her, okay?
She's right.
They got little kids here.
You wanna fight debate style? Cool.
Or you wanna fight-fight?
I say let's save it for
somebody who deserves it, right?
Yes? I get a yes vote on that?
Yes.
Kelly.
Yes. Majority rules.
Hand it over now.
- Come on.
- Please.
[NECKLACE CLACKS]
Sleep on it, all right? [SCOFFS]
You'll feel better about
it in the light of day.
♪
- Wait.
- The ring, I could let go.
But that stuff belonged
to people I knew,
people who went out and never came back.
We found that stuff.
We didn't do anything.
You hurt my son.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I swear you'll never see us again.
♪
I know.
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
MARAUDERS: [SCREAMING]
♪
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[UTENSILS CLATTERING]
♪
MICHONNE: RJ!
RJ: [LAUGHS]
Oh, my God.
What are you doing awake?
- Mommy, I'm tired.
- You sleepy?
- Why did you...?
- Mm-hmm.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
♪
You missed one.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
Thank you.
You were right about me.
I've done things. Terrible things.
If I had all this,
I wouldn't trust me, either.
We've all done things.
Or else we wouldn't be here.
It isn't always that easy to live with.
It's better than losing everything.
♪
Judith Grimes.
You said Dad would've
wanted me to have it
to protect myself and the people I love.
Yeah, he would have, but I'm the one
who's supposed to be protecting you.
Is that why you're kicking them out?
'Cause I think Dad would've wanted me
to do what I did yesterday, too.
♪
He would've been proud.
Your brother, too.
♪
Then why won't you help them?
You'll understand someday.
♪
I know you talk to him sometimes.
To Carl, too.
♪
I'm starting to forget their voices.
I'm not trying to, but
they keep fading away.
♪
I hope you can still hear them.
RJ: Mama, I'm hungry now.
[LAUGHS]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
♪
[PANTING]
Come on!
[WALKERS GROWLING]
♪
Damn it. They just keep coming.
[PANTING]
They're catching up. Let's go.
- Eugene!
- I'm holding you back.
And I cannot keep on keepin' on.
I'll gladly distract the...
The dead while you vamoose,
but... there's somethin'
I've been working up
the testicular gravitas to tell you,
somethin' I've been holdin' inside of me
- for a really long time.
- Shut up!
Don't make this weird. We are making it.
Come on. Now.
[WALKERS GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
♪
Mom?
Yeah?
I'm sorry about what I said last night.
And thank you.
It's okay.
You're safe, and that's all that matters.
♪
[SMOOCHES]
Where are you taking us?
Seems like we've gone clear off the map.
You keep your eyes on the road, mister.
I know where I'm going.
I know, but...
Whoa.
♪
Need a ride, stranger?
[SIGHS]
♪
[DOORS CREAK]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
♪
MAN: [SIGHS]
Sorry, guys. [GRUNTS]
If I knew we were gonna be
booted as soon as I recovered,
I would've hit my head a bit harder.
You know, it's not too late.
_
LUKE: Doc.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hospitality.
[SIGHS]
Especially you.
Thank you.
[CLAPS HANDS]
[SIGHS]
[HORSE WHINNIES]
[HOOVES CLOPPING]
Change of plans.
There's a place a lot like this one.
The leader might take you in.
I'll escort you personally, talk to her.
You're gonna take them to Hilltop?
With you.
You gotta keep an eye on your
patient till we get there.
_
♪
Good luck.
[CHUCKLES]
I'll work on it.
♪
[GROANS]
Over.
[PANTING]
[WALKERS GROWLING]
♪
WALKER: Where... are... they?
WALKER #2: They must be close.
WALKER #3: Don't let them get away.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --