ANNOUNCER:
Previously, on "The Walking Dead"...
It's Jadis.
Whatever this is,
I can't do it.
I have to tell Rick.
(GRUNTS)
It kind of looks like
an arrow hit him.
You really think I did it?
Did you take out Justin
with that thing?
He killed my husband.
It's good you're leaving
this place.
With you.
NEGAN: You're not saving
the world, Rick.
You're just getting it
ready for me.
- It's time to see Negan.
- All right.
(EXHALING SHARPLY)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(WALKERS GROWLING)
(BANGING)
(WALKER GROWLING)
(GRUNTS)
(WALKERS GROWLING)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(WALKER GROWLING)
Improved By: FidelPerez
Sub Upload Date: October 30, 2018
Is that a goat?
(HERSHEL COOS)
And all those people?
(SMOOCHES)
(HERSHEL COOING)
Hi.
Good morning, Hershel.
Oh, who's my big boy?
(HAMMERS CLANGING IN DISTANCE)
(CLANGS)
JESUS: Maggie.
Didn't realize you
were back from the camp.
Just came in this morning.
Another letter from
Georgie just came in.
I was gonna put it on your desk,
but here you are.
Will you put it
in the drawer for me
with the others?
I'll read it later.
Sure.
You're headed back already?
I just came to pick up
a few things.
That crowbar
being one of them?
You've done a good job
taking care of things here.
I'm gonna need you to keep
doing that.
While you're someplace
other than the camp.
I'm gonna make things right.
Like we talked about.
Like you did with Gregory.
Only, we never talked
about that.
I'm not asking you
to agree with me.
There was a time I did.
Look, Negan deserved
to die when it ended.
Rick was wrong because
he made a call
that wasn't his to make.
I just want to be sure
that you're not wrong
in the same way that he was.
And I want you to be sure.
DIANNE: Maggie?
You ready?
I am.
I'll be back when it's done.
(HORSES WHINNY)
(WATER RUSHING)
EUGENE:
I gather you've gandered
- the now rushing river under the bridge?
- I have.
Seems Mother Nature served us up
a serious bowl of whoop-ass
in the form of an overnight deluge,
effectively annihilating
the upstream levee.
What are the chances the bridge'll hold?
Well, factoring in the undue stress
of the rapid current
against the supports,
plus the added weight
from the construction
materials and whatnot,
I take no pleasure in saying that,
in the long term, it's bad.
I'm sorry.
- There's gotta be a way.
- I wish there were.
But it's simply not safe
to keep on keepin' on
with the project, as it were,
not with the numbers we currently have.
- There is a small silver lining.
- Yeah?
What's that?
The two nearby herds
we've been tracking,
one Tybalt and Cordelia,
are running parallel, as expected,
but, luckily, show no signs of merging,
which is first-rate news,
not only for the camp's safety
but because, once merged,
neither Tordelia nor Cordalt
had a particularly good ring to them.
The herd monikers
are from the great book...
of plays.
They're a starter set
of dead Shakespearean characters.
Needed an endless pool.
Thanks, Eugene.
I am truly very sorry I didn't do more.
Maybe if I'd just,
well, read more books...
Engineering, motivational,
or otherwise...
Maybe we would've...
Maybe we could've...
Don't do that.
What?
You're not just a guy
who read some books.
You made something. You got us here.
After everything...
that's everything.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
RICK: Hey.
Hey.
You leaving, too?
Yeah.
I'm taking my people home.
To the Kingdom.
You've seen it out there, Rick.
What about the Sanctuary?
I sent Alden to head off the group
and lead 'em back.
They need to try standing on their own.
What if they can't? What if it...
What if it goes down
the same way it did here?
Then what?
Then that's on them.
They don't want us there anymore.
But I know they don't
want Negan anymore, either.
Not most of 'em, anyway.
So it's up to them
to figure out who they want to be.
Like you did.
Like we all did.
I don't know if we're
doing the right thing here.
I really don't.
But if anyone gives me hope
for how things can turn out,
it's you.
You know that, right?
I'm still trying to figure things out.
Just like everybody else.
I am sorry, Rick.
I really wanted it to work.
I really did.
I know.
Get outta here.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
Got somethin' for you, jefe.
What is it?
Maggie's running down to Alexandria.
Jesus thought you should know pronto.
- When did she leave?
- Dunno.
Call just came in
from the Hilltop relay.
Did he say anything else?
Just that you'd know what that means.
Sorry, man, that's all I got.
No. No.
Thanks, Jerry.
Alexandria Relay One,
this is Rick Grimes.
Come in, please.
FEMALE VOICE: Go for AR One.
AR One, I need you to get an
urgent message to Alexandria...
If Maggie Rhee shows
up, delay her at the gate
and alert Michonne right away.
Do not... repeat...
Do not let her in without an escort.
- Over.
- Copy that, Rick.
Will relay your message right now.
Over.
And, Maggie, if you're listening...
let's talk.
I think she's done talkin'.
Hey.
What's goin' on?
Maggie's headed to Alexandria.
She's about do something
she might regret.
Hop on. I'll take you.
- You sure? We got enough fuel?
- Yeah.
We'll get there quicker.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(ENGINE REVS)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
(SIGHS)
I'll be right back, baby.
Morning, Nora.
Is it that time already?
NORA: Don't sound so excited.
It's not always all bad news.
I'm sorry.
What kind of day is it gonna be?
- Mostly bad.
- (CHUCKLES)
We've given up about a
fourth of our tomato crops
to the crows.
Need to plant more stakes and flags.
We could. There's just too many of 'em.
Seems like one of those things
where the world's starting
to have an edge over us.
Once we get the windmill up and running,
it'll help.
And I'll talk to Eugene
when he gets back.
- All right.
- What else?
Negan.
Scott tried to feed him this morning.
He won't eat.
He wouldn't eat yesterday, either.
I was gonna try at lunch...
That's okay.
I'll handle it.
You sure? 'Cause I don't...
No, no. It's my responsibility.
I'm sure.
But thank you, Nora.
Just doing my job.
(GATE CLOSES)
(ENGINE REVS)
That was the way, back there.
Pull over.
I... Pull over!
(ENGINE SHUTS OFF)
What is this?
You know exactly what this is.
I already called it in.
Maggie's not making
it through those gates.
Yeah, that message didn't go through.
You messed with the relay?
This time, man,
it's gonna go the way
it was supposed to.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(BOTH BREATHING SHARPLY)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(PLATE CLATTERS)
The hunger strike ends today.
(GRUNTS)
I'm not on strike.
Then what is this?
This is me not in the mood to eat.
But it's nice to know that you care.
We're keeping you alive,
and the living eat.
So eat, Negan.
It's a nice day.
(CHUCKLES)
I'll be back in an hour.
I want that gone.
Is that all you got?
I got better things to do.
You want me to eat?
Well, I want you to stay and talk to me.
I mean, I... I'm proof
that you're making a
civilization, right?
I mean, that's what your boyfriend says,
so hard to be that
if I'm dead from starvation.
I thought you said
you weren't on strike.
I'm not if you stay and talk to me.
I'd say it's about 20 minutes
before the sun hits that bar.
That's all you get.
Then, you're gonna eat every last bite.
You wanna talk?
(STOOL CLATTERS)
Let's talk.
Those roots...
they're the only way we're getting out.
DARYL: Too high up, though.
(GRUNTS)
God damn it!
You set that up that, too?
Man, you're really layin' this on me?
You're the one that had
to go chasin' after her.
Couldn't just let things be, huh?
You know what keeping
Negan alive means to us.
Ah.
I know what seein'
him dead means to her.
Daryl, I get why she
can't accept it, I do.
- Do you?
- Her never coming to Alexandria,
her hanging Gregory the way she did?
I know. I'm not blind.
Well, you sure as hell
been acting like it.
Man, your ass wouldn't even be alive
if it wasn't for Glenn.
You wouldn't have found Lori,
you wouldn't have found Carl.
And you sure as...
wouldn't have found any of us.
He did that.
Or did you forget?
Of course not.
I think about it every damn day.
And Maggie, I hate what I did to her,
what I took from her,
but it's what I had to do.
She's doing what she has to do.
What? You're okay with that?
Why the hell wouldn't I be?!
You spared Dwight.
After Denise, after what he did to you.
(SCOFFS) What do you mean?
Lockin' me in a damn closet?
Paradin' me around
so I couldn't say nothin'?
Man, you got that guy sitting in a cell
like a damn symbol to all them assholes
who can't wait to see things
- go back to the way that they were.
- Keeping him alive
is how we make sure it won't!
No.
Keeping him alive is givin'
'em hope that it will.
Michonne talked to her.
She came to the camp.
She was coming around.
Yeah, well, she was tryin'.
The truth is, she just
couldn't live with it.
Just like Oceanside.
Oceanside?
You saying Oceanside
killed those Saviors?
Arat?
I'm sayin' they got what they deserved.
You knew,
and you didn't say anything?
Truth is,
I couldn't live with it, either.
If this doesn't work,
if she kills Negan,
he becomes a martyr.
The war was for nothing.
Every person who's
died, died for nothing.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Carl... Carl died for nothing.
What about the rest of us?
You don't think after all
the shit we've been through,
we couldn't handle it?
Man, you keep askin' us
to have faith in all these other people.
Truth is, you don't
have enough faith in us.
You know that's... That's not true.
I'd die for you.
And I would've died for Carl.
You know that.
But you gotta hear me.
You're chasin' somethin' for him
that ain't meant to be, man.
You just got to let him go.
Let him go.
I never... I never asked
anyone to follow me.
I know.
But maybe you should've.
NEGAN: Damn.
That sounds more boring than my day.
You're the one
that's stuck in here with the C team
while Rick and his merry
band of bridge-builders
are out there.
Why is that?
You think I'm stuck?
I think that I'm not meant
to be rotting in this cell,
just like I think the warrior in you
is not meant to be planting kale
and kissing boo-boos.
You think that's all this is?
We're reordering the world.
Rebuilding government and creating laws.
We're at the start of everything.
And nothing is holding us back.
While you're rotting
in here with nothing.
I am, uh...
I am grateful my wife
didn't have to see me like this.
What do you mean?
As opposed to the asshole
that you were before?
God, she was...
She was an angel.
She deserved better than she got.
What happened to her?
(SIGHS)
What used to happen.
Cancer.
We would've loved to have had a kid.
We would've loved to
had a kid like Carl.
You were lucky.
I think about him every damn day.
But he's still here.
In everything we do.
I look around, and...
I see him everywhere.
Do you see him in this cell?
Everywhere.
Carl wasn't your first, was he?
I'd say you have about 10
minutes to clear this tray,
and then I'm gone.
How did he die?
It was a "he," wasn't it?
Did he have your eyes?
His name was Andre.
And he just didn't make it.
I'm sorry.
I've made my peace with it.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
You know...
you ask me,
it's better this way.
And how the hell exactly is that?
My wife...
she wasn't made for this.
She was weak when she died.
There was a part of
me that was relieved.
And now I know...
I know she made me...
not weak.
And with you...
With you, it's the same.
- We are not the same.
- We were built for more.
We still are, Michonne.
Behind walls and bars, we die.
But, see, out there...
it's like an addiction.
(CUP CLATTERS)
I know that you know
what I'm talking about.
(SIGHS)
And that is why you're grateful, too.
Grateful for what?
That Andre's gone.
Because you know
all he would've done is make you weak.
(TRAY CLATTERS)
(DOOR OPENS, CREAKS)
(WALKER GROWLING)
(GRUNTS)
Anne... please.
You don't have to do this.
Yes. I do.
There's only one place
left for me to go.
And you're the price of admission.
You don't want to.
I know you, Anne.
You're afraid, but you don't have to be.
You've changed.
I wanted to.
I tried.
But I'm not like you, Gabriel.
You moved on from your past.
You opened your heart, let people in.
But don't you see?
I didn't make it that way.
Others did.
You did.
I'm a better person because of you.
Then I'm sorry...
it was all for nothing.
(WALKER GROWLING)
What you're about to do, it's my fault.
I'm sorry.
You asked me for help...
and I failed you.
I pushed you away
because I was afraid, too.
I see that now.
But the beauty of God's
love and forgiveness
is that it is bountiful.
And I hope you can forgive me someday,
just like I forgive you.
I forgive you, Anne,
whatever you have to do.
(WALKER GROWLING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(GRUNTING)
JERRY: Everything okay?
Take these trunks
- and lock them in the medical tent now.
- On it, Boss.
If we hurry, we can make it
to the Kingdom by nightfall.
(HORSES WHINNYING)
Where'd you get the gun, Jed?
JED: Alden wasn't as quick as you.
Surprised me, too.
How about we all lower our weapons.
Nobody gets hurt today.
That's right.
Listen to the woman.
Drop your guns. Party's over.
See, uh, I took the scenic route,
but I figured it out.
Oceanside's killing us.
So now, being that it's war,
they're gonna get what's comin' to 'em.
Stop it, Jed.
You're gonna get everybody killed.
Excuse me, Carol.
You ain't bosslady no more.
You're a weak little woman
who got in a lucky shot.
And now...
...listen to what I say.
(GUN COCKS)
Now, step aside.
(KEYS RATTLING)
JED: Aah! Aah!
CAROL: No!
(GUNSHOTS IN DISTANCE)
That's back at the camp.
It's gonna draw those herds.
(GUNFIRE, ALL SHOUTING)
Come on.
All right.
1, 2, 3.
(BOTH GRUNT)
Shit!
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Here we go. We got this.
Come on. Ready?
We got this.
1, 2, 3!
(GRUNTING)
Yep.
Why did you say those things?
I wasn't trying to piss you off.
You should know that.
Why do you care what I think?
'Cause you never come down here.
It's always Rick or someone else.
So tell me why that matters.
(SIGHS)
I shouldn't have brought up your son.
You weren't ready to hear it.
Hear what?
That we're the same.
All or nothing.
You are trapped, same as me.
You're connected to the dead same as me.
We are the same,
and you can't stand that we're the same.
No.
We're not.
Yeah, we do what we
need to to get shit done.
But you get a kick out of it.
Me?
I'm trying every day
to make things better,
thinking of ways to
bring people together,
not pitting them against each other.
I sacrifice, and I compromise.
And, yeah, I do get
strength from the dead,
but I live for the living,
and I make no apologies for that.
My sons are gone,
but this world is going to
be better for my daughter
and for every other
child that comes into it.
Oh.
You're not scared that you're like me.
You're scared that you're
gonna end up like me...
With everything and everyone
that you love gone.
You're desperately
trying to connect with me.
Because there is nothing
worse than nothing.
Long as you're still breathing,
it's not nothing.
Time's up.
Eat, Negan.
One way or another,
you're gonna have to.
(GRUNTS)
Wait.
What?
Before you go,
there is something I want to ask you.
(SIGHS)
There are things in this world that...
That we desperately hold on to
when there's nothing left.
This whole time,
you thought I was
your last, best chance.
(CHUCKLING) Oh, God.
I... I wanna see her.
- I need to see her.
- No.
Please.
Negan, we don't have your bat.
Where...
Where is she? What did you do with her?
Still out there.
No.
(VOICE BREAKING) No.
Eat, Negan.
Food's good.
I am gonna see my Lucille.
(NORMAL VOICE) Damn it.
Damn!
(GRUNTING)
(WALKER GROWLING)
Look out!
DARYL: (PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
- You okay?
- RICK: Yeah.
Yeah. There's more coming!
Think you can get to this one?
(PANTING) Yeah.
(GRUNTING)
Heads up!
(WALKER GROWLING)
(WALKERS GROWLING)
(GROWLING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTING)
Daryl, you gotta hurry.
- DARYL: I'm hurryin'!
- (WALKERS GROWLING)
(BREATHING SHARPLY)
Take my hand.
(GRUNTS)
You're almost there.
Come on!
(WALKERS GROWLING)
You're almost there.
Brother...
Brother... take my hand.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (WALKERS GROWLING)
- Heads up!
Come on.
(HORSE SNORTING)
(WALKERS GROWLING)
- (HORSE NEIGHS)
- DARYL: Come on.
- Let's go.
- Wait.
I'm gonna stay back, lead
'em away from the camp.
- What?
- I'm staying.
No, man!
I'm not giving up on it, not yet.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
The river. Take 'em to the bridge.
It ain't ever gonna hold,
- and they'll get washed out to sea.
- No, man, I'm not sacrificing the bridge.
I'll find another way.
There ain't no other way, man!
I'm not destroying the bridge.
We need it.
Fine.
Hey.
Be safe.
You too.
(GRUNTS)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(METAL CLATTERING)
Anne!
ANNE: If you want to go fast, go alone.
If you want to go far, go together.
I need to go fast.
(CRYING)
"Game day was finally here.
The boys and girls were so excited.
They washed their faces,
they brushed their teeth,
and they put on fresh, clean uniforms.
They grabbed their gear,
and then, they made
their way to the field."
The end.
Can I get a kiss right here?
Mwah! Thank you, baby girl.
(SIGHS)
(HORSE SNORTING)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(WALKERS GROWLING)
RICK: Whoa. Easy, easy.
Easy.
(WALKERS GROWLING)
Damn it. Whoa!
(HORSE WHINNIES)
Whoa. Whoa! Whoa!
(HORSE SNORTS)
Damn it!
Aah! Aaaaah!
(GRUNTING)
(WALKERS GROWLING)
(SCREAMS)
Improved By: FidelPerez
Sub Upload Date: October 30, 2018