[Heart monitor beeping]
Rick:
Wake up.
[Beeping continues]
It's time to go.
Wake up.
[Beeping continues]
[Helicopter blades whirring]
Morgan:
What is your wound?
[Sighs]
[Beeping continues]
Rick:
Wake up.
[Chuckles]
Yeah, wake up, asshole.
[Gasps, breathes shakily]
[Walkers growling]
[Groans]
[Screaming]
[Neighs]
Aah, aah!
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Grunting]
[Screaming]
♪♪
[Growling continues]
[Horse neighs]
♪♪
[Engine sputtering]
[Grunts]
Man: Jadis,
confirm location.
Confirm location
and status of your "A."
I'm in a clearing.
East bank
of the Accotink.
1.6 miles due north
of the junkyard.
You have the "A"?
I have the "A,"
and it's ready
for transport.
We hadn't heard from you
since the aborted pickup.
We know your group
vacated the landfill.
If this is a trick,
there can still
be consequences.
It's not a trick.
If I need evacuation,
you know
that I'm desperate.
I need
to leave this place.
You know
where to find me.
[Walkie-talkie clicks]
♪♪
[Walkie-talkie clicks]And I'll be ready.
[Walkie-talkie clicks]
[Horse neighs]
[Breathing heavily]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
I need to keep 'em safe.
I need to stay awake. [Wheezes]
♪♪
Lead 'em away. Some...
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Horse neighing]
[Growling continues]
[Grunts]
[Grunting]
Easy.
[Groans]
♪♪
[Walker growling]
Whoa.
Gimme a minute.
[Growling continues]
[Growling stops]
[Horse snorts]
[Breathing heavily]
We can go now.
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Panting]
Hey! Hey!
♪♪
[Horse whinnies]
Easy. Whoa. Whoa.
Whoa, whoa.
[Grunts]
[Wheezing]
[Breathing heavily]
[Grunts]
[Flies buzzing]
[Insects chirping]
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
Rick:
I'm looking for my family.
Lori:
What's your wound?
♪♪
God damn, cowboy.
Look like shit.
♪♪
Rick:
So, what is this?
What is this?
Come on, Rick. Look around.
You know
what this is.
Are those the idiots
we were chasin'?
Attaboy.
Dispatch said there was
two suspects, right?
Oh,
there's a third man.
Yes,
there was.
That third man
changed everything, didn't he?
[Sighs]
I'm looking
for my family.
Oh, is that
what you're doing,
looking for
yourfamily, huh?
Mm-hmm.
Well, see,
that's not entirely true.
One could argue
it's myfamily
you're lookin' for, right?
[Chuckles]
How is my baby girl,
by the way?
Got my eyes,
doesn't she?
Mm.
She hasn't got
your nose.
[Laughs]
Good thing
she ain't got my ears, man.
[Both laugh]
Ah, you're --
you're such an asshole.
Oh, yes, I am,
yes, I am.
I am
theasshole.
Hm.
Same as you,
really.
Oh, you think
I'm an asshole?
I don't thinka thing, man.
I knowyou're an asshole.
I like to take credit
for that, actually, Rick,
when I think
about it.
I mean, I'm sure
others did influence you,
but I'd like
to take full credit.
I didn't want it.
You know that.
But you took it,
right?
Boy,
that shit you did in that field,
just you and me,
man, you took a page
out of my book, Rick.
You know,
I'm glad you did it.
You stepped up,
brother.
It had to be me.
Still has to be me.
Yeah, see, Rick, yeah,
I think
that's where you're wrong.
Has to be me.
You?That's right.
The only way
this gets done, Rick.
I want you
to think about
how you bit that piece of shit's
throat out.
Asshole in the church
with the red machete.
That is what
I'm talkin' 'bout.
That's the shit
that I need from you
that I always knew
you had in you.
I knew you had it in you, Rick,
and it is time.
You want answers?
You wanna know
what this is all about,
this right here, you and me?I asked you, didn't I?
Yeah, you did ask,
so now I'm gonna tell ya,
and I want you
to listen carefully.
You got it?Mm.
It's time.
Kneel down.
Dig deep.
Find it, Rick --
the rage, the hatred.
Find it. The loyalty
that's in there, find it.
It's in there,
Rick.
It's the only way
that this gets done,
and this
has to get done.
You understand me?
It has to.
You can do it,
brother.
♪♪
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
for what I did to you.
You need
to forget that shit.
♪♪
You know somethin',
Rick?
Wake up!
[Walker growling]
[Grunts]
♪♪
[Grunting]
[Growling continues]
[Grunts]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Horse neighs]
What are you makin'?
A bracelet.
Oh,
with the shells?Mm-hmm.
That's gonna be pretty.
A creature used to live
in this one?
Yeah,
all of them.
This one?Yep.
[Sighs]
[Scoffs]
[Knock on door]
Hey.
Hope I'm not --
No, no.
Come on in.
[Sighs]
What's goin' on?
Maggie's here.
Aunt Maggie.
One of the guys at the gate
told me she just came in.
What?
[Birds chirping]
Maggie?
Get out of my way.
You're willing to turn this
into something else?
For him?
Not for him,
for me.
For others.
For Glenn.
Negan should've died
under that tree.
But he didn't die,
Maggie.
It's done.
Because Rick decided
it was?
Step...back.
You were there,
Michonne.
You saw
what Negan did.
You think
Glenn would want this?
For you to go through me
to get to him?
I dunno
what he'd want.
I dunno, because I never
got to say goodbye.
He wouldn't want it,
Maggie.
Your father
wouldn't want this.
You know this.
The only thing I had,
the one thing I had
was knowing I was gonna see
Glenn's murderer die,
and you took it
from me.
So takin' it back,
what the hell
is that gonna do?
It's gonna
start things over.No.
start something else.
If he'd butchered Rick in
front of you instead of Glenn --
Mm, Maggie.
If you had a child
to raise alone because of him,
he would've been dead
a long time ago,
and you know it.
So stop actin' like
this is a choice.
Stop actin' like
I can just turn it off.
Because it has been
a year and a half,
and I can't.
[Sighs]
You're gonna have to
find a way.
Tell me how.
[Sighs]
If there is something else
that I can do, Michonne.
Because I can't keep
livin' like this.
I...
I can't.
'Cause there's nothin'
you can say.
There's only
what you do.
And you can live
with what comes after?
Have to.
Can't live
with it now.
[Keys rattle]
[Door opens]
[Door creaks]
[Door closes]
[Negan chuckles]
Aw, she just gave up
the keys, huh?
It's a shame.
She got the blade,
but you --
you got the fire.
My money
was on you.
So you remember me.
'Course I do.
It's why I thought
you were gonna win.
Good.
Get on your knees.
[Sighs]
[Inhales deeply]
You know, I remember you
screamin' in that clearing.
I remember
how much I broke you
breakin' open
your husband's head like I did.
Glenn.
His name was Glenn.
So now what?
You finally come for...
revenge?
Justice.Damn.
Thought you'd do this
a hell of a lot sooner.
It take you this long
to work up your nerve?
I was always
gonna settle this,
what you did
to my husband.
Get on your knees.
What I did to him?
You mean
how I cracked open his skull
and popped out
his goddamn eyeball?
How I bashed his big,
beautiful brains into the ground
over and over while you
and his little friends watched?
Is that
what you mean?
Ah, I used to say
that I didn't enjoy killin'.
That was a lie.
Your old man...
Christ,
I forgot his name again.
But he was different.
Killin' him
the way I did,
ooh, now,
that was fun.
[Breathing shakily]
[Sighs]
Get to it.
Have your justice.
Kill me.
It was worth it.
Lemme see you
in the light.
Come on.
Kill me.[Lock clanks]
You not
have it in you?
Don't you punk out
like Rick.
Come into the light.
Kill me.
This is
what you came here for!
You kill me!
Move into the light.
[Crying] Kill me.
[Crying]
[Grunts]
Please. Please.
Please kill me.
Why?You have to.
Just do it.You tell me why!
Tell me!
Why should I?!
So I can be
with my wife!
with Lucille!
[Crying]
♪♪
I should be dead.
I have to be dead.
And it's supposed to
be you.
It has to be you,
because I can't do it.
I can't do it.
I've tried.
I can't.
I can't be like this.
Please, please don't make me
stay like this.
It's -- Settle it.
Settle me.
Kill me.
Please.
[Sobs]
Get back
in your cell.
No.
No. Why?
I came
to kill Negan,
and you're already
worse than dead.
♪♪
That settles it.
Go.
[Crying]
It wasn't supposed to
be like this.
[Crying]
[Lock clanks]
[Crying continues]
Maggie, Michonne,
somethin's up at the camp.
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
[Panting]
♪♪
I need to lead 'em.
Gotta find my family.
[Growling continues]
♪♪
Woman:
What's your wound?
♪♪
Hey, Rick.
Here.
Look at this.
[Sighs]
This place.
It's beautiful.
It is something,
isn't it?
♪♪
I'm so sorry
for what happened to you.
To Beth and Glenn.
For everything
Maggie's lost.
Rick.
Maybe if
I tried harder,
done things different,
listened more --
My girl,
she's strong,
and my grandson,
he'll only make her stronger.
You ain't
gotta worry about her.
♪♪
I need
to find my family.
to keep 'em together.
No,
you don't.
You only think
you do.
I know
it's been hard.
It has.
What you wanted for me,
for Carl,
it hasn't been easy.
♪♪
We've been tryin' --But we'll get there.
All of us.
I'm tired, Hershel.
♪♪
My family...
Maybe I can
find 'em here.
No, Rick.
You have to wake up.
[Horse neighing]
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
[Horse neighing]
♪♪
[Growling continues]
[Electricity buzzing]
♪♪
[Panting]
Abraham:
What's your wound?
[Panting continues]
[Board clatters]
[Door creaks]
[Panting continues]
♪♪
[Rick exhales sharply]
They...
They're all dead.
Yeah.
I know.
And it's okay.
How can it be okay?
How -- How can this
be okay?
'Cause you did
your part,
like I did mine,
like the others did
before us.
How?
They give us the strength
that we needed
to do what we had to do
for the others,
and the others
draw strength from us.
We change each other.
We help each other.
We make
each other better.
And it never ends.
It feels like
it's ending.
Little things
do end,
but it's never
the end of everything,
because we don't die.
It's not about you or me
or any one of us.
It's about
all of us.
And I don't think
it just evens out.
I think it always crosses over
toward the good,
toward the brave,
toward love.
♪♪
Your family...
You're not gonna find them,
because they're not lost.
♪♪
And you are not lost.
What you need to do
is wake up.
♪♪
[Grunts][Horse neighs]
[Gasps]
[Grunting]
♪♪
[Groans]
No.
[Panting]
[Walker growling]
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
[Groans]
No.
[Wheezes, grunting]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Grunts, wheezes]
[Panting]
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
[Grunting]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Panting]
[Walkers growling in distance]
♪♪
Daryl: Rick.
Rick!
♪♪
[Growling continues]
It's okay.
♪♪
We're gonna get you
out of here, okay?
No,
you take care of them.
I can't.
You will.
It's not over.
We don't die.
[Panting]
♪♪
You wanna know
why I fell in love with you?
Because you're
a fighter,
and you never give up.
So fight, Rick.
Fight for me.
Fight for all of us.
♪♪
You're my family.
[Sighs]
I found you.
You did.
♪♪
But this...
This isn't real.
Yes, it is.
♪♪
Now wake up.
[Breathing shakily]
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
[Panting]
♪♪
[Growling continues]
[Panting continues]
♪♪
No. No.
It's gonna hold.
♪♪
I can't.
[Gasps]
[Walker growling]
♪♪
Maggie:
What is he doing?!
Michonne: He's hurt!
Daryl: That herd that
went right through Hilltop.
He's trying
to bring down the bridge.
No.
We turn them around.
Fight 'em back.
Carol:
Fire your guns.
Try to divert them.
♪♪
Rick: No, don't do it,
not for me.
It's too many.
No.
It's not working!
Keep trying.
[Growling continues]
[Panting]
♪♪
[Growling continues]
Rick!
I found 'em.
♪♪
[Static]
Man:
What was that?
Was that the bridge?
Man #2: Rick! He blew it
to stop the herd!
[Static]
Woman: Move north,
break up the rest.
Bring some guns.
[Helicopter blades whirring]
[Gun clicks]
I have a "B."
Not an "A."
I never had an "A."
He's hurt,
but he's strong.
Can you help him?
Man: I warned you
there'd be consequences
if you tried something.
It's not a trick,
not anymore.
I'm trying
to save a friend --
a friend
who saved me.
I have something
for you now.
We have a deal?
Do we have a deal?
["Space Junk" plays]
♪♪
♪ Yeah
♪ Ooh
You're still here.
You're gonna be okay.
I'm gonna save you.
♪♪
♪ Driftin' on the spaceway
♪ By the Betelgeuse Hotel
♪ Mappin' out constellations
♪ Of the place I know so well
♪ Siftin' through the system
♪ For the beast
that knows my name ♪
♪ Endlessly I list them
♪ In the master game
♪ Welcome to my world
♪ Welcome to my only world
♪ It is full of space junk
♪♪
[Birds chirping]
[Walkers growling]
[Grunting]
Run!
[Growling continues]
[Grunts]
[Grunting]
[ Groans ]
This is it. Stand me up.
We need to fight.
Walking's not
gonna do it.
Okay, shit.
Okay.
Mag,
what do we do?We circle up.
Knives up. We fight.
No, let's just
open up a seam, okay?
Okay.
[Walkers growling]
[Gunshots]
Girl: C'mon this way!
It's clear!
Go!
Go, go, go!
[Growling continues]
[Panting]
♪♪
You got names?
I'm Magna.
This is Connie and Kelly
and Yumiko and Luke.
What's yours?
♪♪
Judith.
Judith Grimes.
♪♪