Previously on
"The Walking Dead"...
Dad, we're holding things together with
plastic and tape. We need better tools.
Someone who's trained to use them.
There's a place a lot like this one.
The leader might take you in.
You're gonna take them to Hilltop?
With you.
Carol: Whoa.
You need a ride, stranger?
♪ ♪
[Walkers snarl]
Walker: [Raspy] Where... are... they?
[Walkers growling]
[Panting]
Walker: She's dead.
Walker #2: But we're getting closer to her.
[Panting continues]
♪ ♪
Don't let her get away.
[Grunts]
[Indistinct whispering]
[Walkers growling]
[Panting]
[Whispering continues]
Get her!
[Gasping]
♪ ♪
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne == https://subscene.com ==
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
♪ ♪
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne == https://subscene.com ==
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
[Birds chirping]
Careful.
Traps everywhere.
[Birds chirping]
You didn't fix the boat
since last time?
[Dog panting]
Good dog.
Carol: When was the last time you ate?
Dog ate yesterday.
I'm not talking about the dog.
How much further
have the patrols cleared?
'Til the Route D river bend.
Their rig's about
five miles past that.
If their story checks out.
You'd feel better
if you just say it.
What makes you think
I want to say something?
I'm not hearing you deny it.
I was gonna tell you
that I'm glad you
changed your mind about them.
[Horse neighs softly]
But you think I should've
let them stay in Alexandria.
Well, you're going pretty far
out of your way not to.
Considering.
Considering what?
That you like these guys.
Really?
That's what I think?
Uh-huh.
I mean, I'm not
hearing you deny it.
Doesn't mean I trust them.
What do I always say
about having options, huh?
Us not being defenseless
out in the open
because you gave them a reason
not to trust us...
I choose that option.
Except, oh, wait.
Guys. Chill.
We can roll with this
a little while longer.
Cool?
No, no.
It's not cool.
I want my damn knives.
Look, I'm sorry about Magna.
She can be a bit hotheaded.
That's one word for it.
She's been on edge
since we lost Bernie.
Was he with you long?
Long enough.
He loved
getting under Magna's skin.
He, um, used to wear
this absolutely horrid shirt.
It was like looking into
creation itself.
In paisley.
God, it was horrendous.
But Magna hated it.
She said just looking at it
gave her a migraine.
So Bernie wore it
every day for a week.
Honestly, I think
she came around on the shirt.
Just like
she came around on him.
Like family.
This place...
Hilltop.
It's safe?
It is.
What's it like?
It's been a while
since I've been there.
Then how do you know it's safe?
I promised my daughter
that I would get you there,
and I will.
You're just
gonna have to trust me.
[The Jesus and Mary Chain's
"April Skies" plays]
♪ Hey, honey,
what you trying to say? ♪
♪ As I stand here,
don't you walk away ♪
♪ And the world
comes tumbling down ♪
[Chicken clucking]
♪ ♪
♪ Hand in hand
in a violent life ♪
- ♪ Making love on the edge of a knife ♪
- Oh, hey, can you let him know
that I still need more room
in the garden?
On it.
♪ And the world
comes tumbling down ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And it's hard for me to say ♪
♪ And it's hard for me to stay ♪
♪ I'm going down
to be by myself ♪
♪ I'm going back
for the good of my health ♪
Oh, Tara, I'll have
the ag output to you
in a couple of hours. Awesome.
Thanks, Oscar.
♪ And there's one thing
I couldn't do ♪
- ♪ Sacrifice myself to you ♪
-  She's doing great.
And added one more recruit,
so that makes three total
this month.
- Okay. Awesome.
- ♪ Sacrifice ♪
♪ ♪
[Music continues softly]
[Music stops, record needle scratches lightly]
Hey.
You're spending a lot of time
with Georgie's records.
It's a good collection.
I appreciate the gift.
Maggie send another letter?
Yeah. The twins dropped it off
this morning.
She's good.
Happy.
What's up?
Got a list of people
that want to talk to you.
I'm sure you do.
Fine. I'll just leave this here
and you can deal with it.
Very funny.
Sit.
I'm listening.
I have 20 minutes before I have
to be back to the infirmary.
Hit me.
Okay.
Mm.
Okay, Tammy Rose wants
to expand the crop fields,
but she needs to see
how far she can cultivate.
Um, Enid still needs
more room in the garden
for medicinal herbs.
Um, Alden also needs your okay
to send another team out
for scrap metal.
There's a noise complaint
from trailer 7.
And...
Why did you give that kid
a kazoo?
You... You find a kazoo,
you give it to a kid.
I'll deal with it.
And there's this.
Congrats on being
re-elected leader of Hilltop.
Yeah, well, a win is a given
when no one runs against you.
You could at least
pretend to be happy.
Thank you, Tara.
This place is a mess.
Just take Maggie's office.
She'd want you to have it.
It's fine.
I don't need it.
'Cause you still think
this is temporary?
I'm gonna go check on
those crop fields for Tammy.
What? Now?
I-I have a list of things
that I have to go over.
And you can ask me them
when I get back.
Seriously?
[Walker growling]
[Grunts]
[Growls]
♪ ♪
[Breathes sharply]
You just going to
leave him there?
Yeah.
Keeps the animals away.
You've been out here longer
than I thought you'd be.
Longer than you said you'd be.
[Breathes sharply]
Yeah, I like it.
It's quiet.
[Insects buzzing]
How's the King?
He's having a hard time
letting go.
I'm taking Henry to the Hilltop.
He wants to apprentice
at the smithy.
[Grunts lightly]
Well, I appreciate your visit.
You seem real good.
[Grunts]
You gonna tell me
why you're really here?
♪ ♪
I want you to come with us.
I can't stay at Hilltop.
We've got problems of our own
at the Kingdom,
and I'd just feel
really a lot better
if you were there with him.
You want me to babysit your boy?
It's not like that.
How is it?
Henry's an idealist,
just like Ezekiel.
I love that about him. I do.
It's important.
But it can be dangerous, too.
No.
He's gonna have to learn,
just like everybody else.
Just like you and I did.
♪ ♪
Luke: Oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
Sickos tore the damn place up.
Look at this place.
Yumiko: I didn't think
it would be this bad.
[Sighs]
Is this all that's left?
Hey, whoa.
[Horse neighs]
♪ ♪
[Horses neighing]
Michonne: The herd you ran from
did all this?
Magna: No. A bigger one
must've come through here.
[Walker growling in distance]
♪ ♪
[Sighs]
[Walker growling]
♪ ♪
[Walkers growling]
[Both grunting]
[Growling stops]
Shit. Shit.
You should take
something of his with us.
Why would I do that?
To remember him.
This is the first instrument
I ever played as a kid.
My aunt got it for me
for my birthday,
and I had it a whole week
before my mom decided,
for her own sanity,
that I liked painting better.
Well...
Oh, maybe for my sanity, you don't.
[Chuckles]
Luke: It has to be here.
It's... It's just got to be here.
What's going on?
[Scoffs]
No, I'm not telling him that.
Yes, I have a love
of the musical arts,
but Connie here
does not appreciate my...
[Laughs]
No, it is not a fetish.
Not a fetish.
It's not a fetish.
Can you please
just help me find it?
Please?
Thank you.
Michonne: DJ, collect all their weapons.
Hell, no.
We're taking what's ours.
Michonne: No.
I'm not letting my men
take five armed strangers
into Hilltop.
Your men?
What about you?
I came to see
if your story checks out.
It does.
Siddiq and DJ will take you
the rest of the way.
So not only
have you not been to this place
in who knows how long,
you aren't coming with us
and we can't have our weapons?
You want your weapons,
take them.
Then you're on your own
out here.
Michonne...
You want an escort to Hilltop,
a chance at something better,
they stay with us.
I vote for the second one.
Magna: So we're just
supposed to trust her
if she doesn't even trust us?
I mean, guys,
we... we made it this long.
I-I say we take our chances
out there.
Nope.
Second one.
You with me?
Second one?
Yumiko: Stop it.
Luke's right.
They wouldn't
put us back together
just to pull us apart again.
They wouldn't.
You said we'd be there
by morning?
That's right.
Look, I know
you don't like her rules...
I don't, either.
But we made it out here
a long time on our own,
with less than this.
So, for a real chance
for a safe place to live,
we can make it a few more hours.
Okay?
Sun'll be down soon.
We should find shelter.
[Grunting]
♪ ♪
[Breathing heavily]
Jesus: Rule number one.
"Always be mindful
of your surroundings."
Actually, rule number one is...
"Don't forget
to look up."
♪ ♪
[Laughs]
Ow!
♪ ♪
Not bad.
[Both grunting]
♪ ♪
Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
You okay?
[Both grunting]
[Laughs]
♪ ♪
[Breathing heavily]
You heard me coming again.
[Chuckles]
[Groans]
You're still a little heavy
on your left foot.
Wasn't today Election Day?
Or Re-election Day, as it were?
That's why I was late.
Partly.
It's been harder and harder
to get away.
Tara can't cover for you?
If she knew
I've been coming this far out
without a security detail...
As it is, she wants to have me
tried for dereliction of duty.
If Michonne knew I was
violating protocol like this?
[Sighs] Same boat, my friend.
I don't suppose she's
changed her mind about the fair?
Now you're kidding, right?
[Chuckles]
No.
She won't even
put it to a revote.
Not since she tanked
the first one with council.
Just like she did
with the new people.
Yeah...
The fair's important, Aaron.
Not just for the Kingdom,
for all of us.
We have to come back together.
I know.
But Michonne...
she doesn't even
know about Maggie.
[Horse neighs]
♪ ♪
There.
Rosita?
Rosita, you okay?
Hey, hey, hey.
What happened?
You all right?
Aaron? What are you...?
Where's Eugene?
I saw you two leave together.
Where is he?
I-I left him...
in the barn.
What barn?
I don't know.
Jesus: Aaron...
I-I left him.
[Walkers growling]
We have to get her
back to Hilltop.
Eugene's still out here.
It'll be dark soon.
Whichever barn he's in,
we have to hope he'll be safe
there till tomorrow.
Let's go.
[Birds chirping]
Your dog always do that?
Well, he's got his reasons.
[Grunts]
[Sizzling]
I'm impressed.
[Clears throat]
This is really nice...
You cooking for us.
You... You're good at this.
I'm sure there's people
at Hilltop who know how to cook.
Wait.
Is this why we came here?
'Cause you think
I need a chaperone?
And this is the guy?
Henry.
I can handle myself.
I never said you couldn't.
About 30 minutes,
and the food will be ready.
Well, good.
That's just enough time.
Time for what?
[Insects chirping]
[Dog panting]
[Dog barking]
[Fire crackling]
Look, I know you think
I'm still lookin' for him.
♪ ♪
Are you?
I never found the body.
Ever.
After a while,
it just got easier
to stay out here.
♪ ♪
You have to let that go.
There.
That's better.
♪ ♪
Come on.
Dinner's ready.
♪ ♪
[Slurps]
How'd you get the scar, anyway?
♪ ♪
Where's that dog?
His food's getting cold.
Dog!
♪ ♪
[Dish clatters]
Dog!
♪ ♪
[Whistling]
[Horse snorts in distance]
♪ ♪
Drop it.
And turn around slow.
♪ ♪
I can't.
It... It'll...
I said drop it.
Mm.
Y-You don't understand...
Aah! No!
♪ ♪
The hell is going on?
Wh...
[Breathing heavily]
Daryl?
[Walker growling]
[Grunts]
♪ ♪
You following me?
What're you doing out here?
Turn it off.
Go back to camp.
[Growling continues]
[Thud]
♪ ♪
[Dog barking]
Daryl: Dammit.
What's wrong?
[Barking continues]
[Walkers growling]
♪ ♪
Stay here.
[Barking continues]
[Growling continues]
Shh! Come on.
I got you.
I got you, pup.
[Barks]
[Growling]
♪ ♪
Ohh!
Daryl!
Stay back!
[Growling continues]
[Barking continues]
♪ ♪
Ohh!
[Grunts]
♪ ♪
[Barking continues]
[Growling continues]
[Breathing quickly]
♪ ♪
[Growling]
[Dog whimpers]
♪ ♪
[Grunting]
Be careful... careful, care...
You got it?
It's just a scrape.
[Breathing heavily]
I told you to stay back.
Yeah, you're welcome.
[Sighs]
[Grunts]
♪ ♪
How is she?
Any change?
No, she's still out.
But she's gonna be okay.
She's just dehydrated.
Enid has her on an IV.
[Sighs]
It was weird...
seeing her after all this time...
Aaron, too.
What were you guys
doing out there?
I've been training him.
Talking to him.
Keeping the lines
of communication open.
Making sure they're still alive.
To avoid being here?
To try and get Alexandria
on board with the fair.
They won't.
I can't accept that.
You shouldn't, either.
It's important.
Listen, everybody here
is starting to notice
how much you're gone.
The fair is important
to all of us,
but we need you here.
Why?
Because they made you our leader.
Well, maybe they shouldn't have.
Well, Jesus...
Look, I know you think
you're just keeping a promise to Maggie,
but you took this job.
So stop pretending
it's just for now.
She's not here.
You are.
Your people are counting on you.
Maggie is counting on you.
I'm counting on you.
♪ ♪
I came... I came to tell you
that I'm going out in
the morning to look for Eugene.
You need to stay here,
keep this place together.
[Footsteps depart]
[Insects chirping]
♪ ♪
Here.
Use that.
It's good for the infection.
Ohh.
Hi, Dog. Dog.
[Dog panting]
The dog checks the traps,
lets me know
if I have a walker problem.
Never got stuck before, though.
Anyway...
thank you for your help.
Oh, it's no problem.
Thanks for, uh, saving me.
Can you not tell my mom
about that, though?
[Smooches]
Dog, hey.
Go, Dog!
You know, the traps...
They're not for animals.
That's... That's no way to die,
slow and painful like that.
I just want to keep the walkers out.
But there seems to be more
and more of 'em lately.
[Clears throat]
You know, my mom...
She says you're her best friend.
The one who's always had her back,
no matter what.
She misses you.
She worries about you.
You can...
You can see that, right?
Well...
she knows where I'm at.
She knows how to find me.
She shouldn't have to.
Is that what you want?
Me looking over your shoulder
all the time?
It isn't just about me.
Luke: T-This is...
This is unbelievable.
It's utterly unbelievable.
[Scoffs]
Listen, I...
Mnh-mnh-mnh-mnh.
Do you...
Do you know what this is?
This is... This is
an original Stradivarius,
- circa 1725.
- Circa 1725.
He found it in a mansion
outside of Philadelphia
before it was overrun by sickos.
[Sighs]
In the kid's room,
of all places.
Like the kid was gonna miss it.
[Chuckles]
What?
Oh, so you've been traveling
with a... a collection
of instruments
all this time?
Why?
It's art.
Here we go.
Look, for a very long time,
historians and archeologists
have wondered
how did ancient humans
survive the Neanderthals?
Okay?
How did we defeat them
when they were bigger
and they were smarter
and they were stronger, faster?
They had better tools than us.
So why are we still here
and they're not?
[Inhales sharply]
And then they found a cave.
Okay?
And in that cave,
they found
a 40,000-year-old flute.
A flute?
Yes.
A flute.
[Chuckling] Yeah.
And then they realized
that maybe ancient humans
didn't defeat Neanderthal.
Not in the way that we think
of the word "defeat," okay?
They came together
as an answer to defeat.
They sat around a campfire.
They shared their stories
with each other
in the form of music.
And paintings.
And... And they created
a... a common identity.
And then they, you know,
they... they built communities,
and they grew.
And... And then, as they grew,
Neanderthal retreated,
and then, after a while,
they just died out.
So this, yeah.
This. This.
This is the one thing
that separates us
from the animals.
For better or for worse,
it brings us together.
And if we're trying
to rebuild something,
you can't ignore that.
After everything
you've seen and done,
you still believe
that's all it'll take?
Yeah.
It's survival of the fittest.
Sharing with each other...
that's part
of what makes us stronger.
Michonne: I'll probably reach Alexandria
before you get back to Hilltop,
so if you need any supplies,
you should take them.
Siddiq: I'd rather have the
company, [Chuckling] honestly.
Come with us.
It's the least you could do
after murdering Luke's violin
last night.
[Chuckles]
It's for the best.
You know that.
You don't have to worry
about Maggie.
We can't take the risk.
I don't know what she'll do
if she sees me.
Michonne, Maggie's gone.
Took Hershel with her.
Jesus runs Hilltop now.
♪ ♪
Where is she?
And how do you know?
Michonne.
What is it?
Walkers!
Let's move!
Magna: Grab your stuff.
Let's go.
Yumiko: Michonne, DJ needs
to give us our weapons.
DJ: Michonne!
Yo, hey!
Kelly: How are we
supposed to fight?
Michonne!
We need our weapons!
[Walkers growling]
[Grunts]
[Horse neighs in distance]
♪ ♪
Michonne!
[Walkers growling]
[Grunts]
Ohh!
Yumiko: DJ!
[Walkers growling]
♪ ♪
[Horse neighs in distance]
[Growling continues]
Shit. We can't circle up, so we split up.
Luke, you're with Siddiq and DJ.
The rest of us follow her.
Okay.
[Horse neighing]
[Growling continues]
♪ ♪
[Laughs]
[Grunts]
[Growling continues]
Get back!
♪ ♪
[Horse neighs]
[Walker growling]
♪ ♪
That's the same herd
that attacked your rig.
How do you know?
[Growling]
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
[Thumps softly]
♪ ♪
Michonne!
Let's go!
We have to go.
Michonne.
[Growling continues]
♪ ♪
[Birds chirping]
- Hey.
How'd you sleep?
Good.
Good. You?
Real good.
Good.
Be ready to go
in about 10 minutes.
[Frog croaking]
[Dog barks]
Michonne: I know what it's like...
to worry about your family.
To carry the burden
of protecting them.
To feel guilt when they suffer.
She'll be fine.
[Sniffles]
We all will.
Because you have to be.
I would know.
I just want us to have a home,
you know?
Somewhere safe.
You will.
This is as far as I go.
I should've told you
about Maggie sooner.
I'm sorry.
Where is she?
With Georgie.
Someplace far.
Helping her with some new community.
That's all I know.
Mm.
I wanted to say something sooner,
but I promised someone
I wouldn't.
So I didn't.
This means you can come with us to Hilltop.
You should.
No.
I'm needed back home.
I kept my promise to Judith.
What about Carl?
What about your promise to him?
It's not that simple.
[Hoofbeats]
♪ ♪
Those spears.
You from Hilltop?
We are.
You?
Alexandria.
We're headed there now.
We have a message.
We have one of yours, Rosita Espinosa.
She's been injured.
♪ ♪
Let them know
Michonne and the others
are headed to Hilltop.
Tell them we're safe.
[Horse neighs]
♪ ♪
Yumiko: Connie?
What is it?
DJ: [Clicks tongue] Come on.
DJ, hold up.
Hold up.
Do you see something?
Siddiq: What is it?
♪ ♪
She says it's nothing.
Let's go.
[Smooches]
[Horse neighs]
[Dog barking]
[Engine rumbling]
Henry: So, Enid's still here,
right?
Carol: Far as I know.
Why?
Wonder if she'll recognize me.
It's been a while,
and I'm taller.
Like, bigger.
You know?
You're adorable.
No, I'm not.
Unless Enid likes adorable.
This is a pleasant surprise.
What brings you all the way out here?
Henry.
He's taken a stubborn interest
in blacksmithing.
Oh. We might be able to help with that.
Thought I heard a bike.
Oh. Good to see you, man.
Daryl: What you doin' here?
Something up?
[Horse snorts]
We found Rosita
outside the walls yesterday.
She's pretty banged up.
Is she here?
Yeah.
And, uh, Eugene's missing.
We're headed out to go find him.
Could use a good tracker.
Yeah.
Of course.
Go.
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Then I'm going, too.
No.
Mom, but...
No, come on.
Let's get you settled.
♪ ♪
[Horse snorts]
I know the terrain.
I know where we should start looking.
I should go out with you guys.
♪ ♪
Well, somebody's got to
make this place run.
So I'll stay.
But the next time I hear
a complaint about a kazoo...
I'll deal with it.
I promise.
[Engine starts]
Dog!
[Dog barking]
♪ ♪
[Barking continues]
Whoo!
♪ ♪
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne == https://subscene.com ==
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44