[English subtitles are available]
[Director Yoo Seon Dong]
[Writer Kim Sae Bom]
[Lee Dong Wook]
[Wi Ha Jun]
[Han Ji Eun]
[Cha Hak Yeon]
[Bad, Evil, Crazy]
[Bad and Crazy]
[All characters, places, groups, events,
and organizations are fictional.]
Darn you. Hey.
Hey, you piece of...
What is this place?
You owe O Gyeong Tae an apology.
O Gyeong Tae?
Apologize to him before you go.
Apologize?
You psycho. What do you mean...
Darn it!
Hey, Officer O.
Wake up.
O Gyeong Tae. Wake up!
You psycho!
We'll all die at this rate.
What will you do now?
What are you waiting for?
What?
What do you want me to do? You psycho!
-This idiot.
-Oh, he woke up!
-He woke up!
-Hey! Why would you jump in there?
-Who do you think you are?
-Gosh, ma'am.
He just woke up. Don't smack him so hard.
He saved a life. He's a hero.
What? A hero, my foot.
Hey, who do you think you are?
You're no hero.
-Why would you do such a thing?
-Mom!
-It's so unlike you.
-It hurts!
-Why would you do that?
-It hurts.
-Mom! You're hurting him.
-Gosh, seriously.
Let's go. That's enough.
Goodness gracious.
-Are you all right?
-Hey, what happened?
Why am I here?
That's what I want to ask you.
What on earth happened?
-Hey, help me up.
-Are you okay?
Gosh... Why am I lying down here?
Exactly, why are you lying down here?
I have no idea what happened.
What's going on?
[Monitoring]
Who threw you into blazing flames?
Who is this scumbag?
[Episode 2]
Well, just some psycho.
There's this lunatic but...
Hey, this is not the time
to go on about some lunatic.
This is serious, okay?
Hey, they're saying
Gyeong Tae tried to take his own life
because you had been
covertly watching him.
They're making stuff up
to get our team in trouble.
Those rats...
The more I think about it,
the angrier I get.
Are we everyone's enemy or what?
We're cops too, you know.
The jerks who are supposed
to be our colleagues are even worse.
Darn it.
Maybe we should track down that lunatic.
Hey, who called it in first?
Last night, I was suddenly so hungry.
So I ordered some jokbal
and came out to have a smoke...
I mean, I came out to get some fresh air.
But it was raining so hard.
That moment,
I saw a handsome guy on his motorcycle.
I was going to say hi to him,
but I suddenly heard a loud boom
and saw smoke coming out of that house.
So I panicked
and called the police right away.
Then this guy and someone else
suddenly fell, like you see in movies.
Hey, that's enough.
Did you see a guy wearing a helmet?
A black helmet.
-A black helmet?
-Yes.
No, I didn't.
She didn't see him. The lady
at the corner store said the same thing.
You said he was here.
Maybe you were confused.
Does everyone here
walk around with their eyes closed?
Are you really the guy
that fell from the window?
What kind of workout do you do?
I thought you died on the spot.
I go fishing. Hey, let's go.
You should quit jokbal.
Bye.
[Jeong In Seon!]
[Happy birthday.]
[Isn't this teddy bear so cute?]
[So stop bringing home
those ugly toys now.]
[Take good care of this from now on.]
[I'm going to watch you
and see what you do all day.]
[Okay, sweetie?]
-A video message?
-Yes.
She had a daughter, you know.
There was nothing else?
-Are you sure?
-Yes, I'm sure.
Because of this stupid video,
we went through all the trouble.
Hey, this video message...
What about Ryu Su Yeol?
I haven't really heard anything from him,
so I don't think he did it
knowing the situation.
It seems like the higher-ups want to
reprimand him for excessive investigation.
What about that officer?
He's still unconscious. The chances of him
regaining consciousness are slim.
Didn't you say
he saw your face?
Yes.
-Hey, In Beom.
-Yes.
-In Beom.
We have to get this sorted out.
If you're charged with attempted murder,
even the President can't save you.
Okay.
[Officer O attempted suicide
because of a senior inspector.]
"The cops in this country
embarrass me so much."
Do you have to read it out loud
right in front of me?
[Officer O is innocent.
Bring him back to life!]
"Senior Inspector Ryu,
you should've been the one to die."
-What kind of scumbag...
-Hey.
My, the number of views
keeps going up at the speed of light.
At this rate,
this will soon reach the Blue House.
What the heck are you up to? You idiot!
Someone had beaten him up to a pulp.
I found him collapsed on the floor.
I mean, sir. I saved his life.
You saved him? Hey, Su Yeol.
You'd never save anyone
if there was nothing in it for you.
-We both know that.
-What happened was...
-Bong Pil, seriously.
-I clearly told you
to stay out of trouble
until the evaluation was over.
But you voluntarily got yourself
into trouble,
which tells me that
you don't want the promotion. Am I right?
What does that have to do with this?
Why would I not want the promotion?
What? You don't want to give up?
Then what will you do about this?
These jerks are running their mouths
nonstop right now.
Do you actually think
you can be promoted this time?
-Whatever. Stop reading that.
-Hey!
Okay, fine. I'll go get it all sorted out.
[Subsection Chief Gwak Bong Pil]
Jae Seon, hey.
That crazy fool.
I thought you'd finally get a promotion
by screwing O Gyeong Tae over.
But all of that has gone down the drain
because you saved him.
Shut it. It's not over yet.
It's not over yet? Then what?
What will you do? Will you track down
the one who beat him up?
Gosh, that punk...
I swear,
that jerk with the helmet saw it too.
That darn helmet...
Stop talking about the helmet, will you?
Jeez.
No one saw him.
If anyone else heard it,
they'd flat out say you're lying.
I'm only listening to this nonsense
because I'm very patient.
Have you totally lost your mind or what?
How do you think I feel right now?
Having to explain it
when I know it makes no sense!
I definitely saw him.
He was right there with me. What?
Should I lie and say he wasn't?
Okay. I heard you. Come on.
Why did you spit all over my food? Jeez.
Wait.
Seeing how he knew
where O Gyeong Tae lived,
maybe, they knew each other.
Are they friends?
Then is he friends with the guy
that beat him up?
Wait. The guy who beat up O Gyeong Tae
is friends with the helmet guy?
Is this a school reunion?
This is it. You need to get
some counseling. You need therapy.
Hey, have you lost your mind?
You want me to start seeing a shrink now?
So I can lose my badge?
Exactly. You should go see a shrink
before you completely lose it!
I know a good doctor.
You trust me, don't you?
I'm your guy, Yang Jae Seon.
Geun Su. Yeom Geun Su.
[Munyang Market]
[Heart Mender]
All right. I met Inspector Yang Jae Seon
about five years ago.
The illegal distribution of mental health
medication brought us together.
Ever since then,
we have kept a very nice relationship.
I guess you can say we're good friends.
You know?
Have the drink,
and feel free to talk to me.
I know that opening up to someone
for the first time is very difficult.
Just think of me as your mother.
Please relax.
You know,
I keep seeing this crazy guy lately.
Pardon?
But that guy shows up out of nowhere
and starts attacking me.
You're a cop. You can arrest him yourself.
What's the problem?
No, listen. The thing is...
I don't know who he is.
He's always wearing a helmet.
So I've never seen his face.
He shows up out of the blue
and vanishes into thin air.
But what drives me crazy is
that no one has seen him other than me.
So no one will believe me.
This is really driving me insane.
[Yeom Geun Su]
Listen. I told you. Didn't I?
He goes around wearing that helmet.
But no one has seen him.
[It's a big one. You're not coming today?]
[Of course, I'm coming.]
I'm always the only one who sees him.
That drives me crazy.
[-Bring a lot of cash.]
-Why am I the only one?
[When can you come?]
[I'll be late.
I need to listen to this lunatic.]
It's so frustrating.
You made me tell this frustrating story
again. This is more frustrating!
After going through a traumatic incident,
people start talking nonsense
and seeing things.
No. I saw him even before my accident.
Right. You start to confuse the timeline,
think you saw someone when you didn't,
and feel as if you experienced something
that you never did. That happens.
You just need to get a lot of sleep
and rest. Doctor's order. Okay?
That's easy for you to say.
You think this is some flu?
Accepting your condition
is the first step in any treatment plan.
Once you give in and think
what I'm telling you is true,
you will be able to relax,
and the world will start to look
like a beautiful place.
It has nothing to do with my accident.
That wasn't the first time I saw him.
When did you see him first then?
You look like a smart guy.
What's wrong with you?
How is it possible that no one saw a guy
with a helmet in a sauna?
Doesn't it sound odd to you?
Exactly!
I often go to saunas myself, so I know
it's so easy to fall asleep there!
Then are you saying that was a dream too?
Yes!
What about the wound?
He beat me up pretty hard.
When people fall off while sleeping,
they easily get hurt. You know?
Are you getting any sleep?
You need to get a lot of sleep and rest.
All right.
Why don't you go and get some sleep?
What do you need? Sleeping pills?
[Sleeping pills]
Right. That apartment unit
with blue lights was super vivid.
[Jae Seon]
Hey, what did the people
at the substation say?
Who could have a grudge against that guy?
[Sohyang Police Substation]
Couldn't you tell
O Gyeong Tae was such a saint?
He looks just like me ten years ago.
Did you look into his whereabouts
on the day of the accident?
He came here again. Why?
Probably because of Jeong Yu Na.
Look.
He called her here
in the middle of the night.
He was never going to give up.
No.
Do In Beom told me that they found
some activity that proved she was...
Her credit card transaction?
I actually looked into that
before coming here.
She didn't use the credit card.
Her friend from the bar took
the credit card when she dropped it.
She was cash-strapped, so she used it.
She was going to pay Jeong back.
Then...
The case was closed at Munyang Station.
And Jeong Yu Na is still missing.
Gosh. Where did you go, Jeong Yu Na?
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
When did you start the construction?
Gosh, come on. Are you serious?
Who are you guys now?
Why are so many people so nosy
about what I do with the house?
Get out.
-Come on.
-Hey. We're not being nosy.
We're cops.
We're on official business here.
Was this guy being nosy then?
-Yes. He was looking for something.
-He was looking for something? What?
I don't know.
He said something about a doll. Jeez.
What?
Sir, did you throw out
all the stuff that was in this unit?
I threw them out long ago.
You came too late.
I definitely saw tangled hair
that was covered in blood.
Gosh.
These are all bloodstains, aren't they?
You... You're... You jerk!
[That can't be. That wasn't a dream?]
The apartment unit
where O Gyeong Tae saw bloodstains
could be the crime scene. But
they're already done with remodeling it.
O Gyeong Tae must have found a clue
about Jeong Yu Na before the incident.
And what if there are people
who need to cover up whatever he found?
They would've done something to him.
Wait. Then what about Do In Beom?
He already beat O Gyeong Tae up before.
Gosh. I know.
But that's all circumstantial.
True.
Should we look for Jeong Yu Na first?
Darn it. O Gyeong Tae.
He's going to make me
look for Jeong Yu Na.
Jeez. My head hurts.
Really?
I told you to go get that checked out.
Hey, I'm done for the day.
Meet with the security guard.
And get the security footage from the day
when she stopped using her phone
until she was reported missing.
-Okay. You just take care of yourself.
-Gosh.
[Pharmacy]
[Missing Person Jeong Yu Na]
[Please help me find my mother.
Name: Jeong Yu Na, Age, 31]
Hey, Jae Seon. Tell me about her family.
Jeez. Oh, my head.
-Hello.
Hey, little munchkin.
Excuse me.
You can't take this down!
Gosh. You can't just put up posters there.
Step aside, please.
Stop it!
-Gosh. You're a strong girl. Stop that.
-You can't take that down.
Don't be so stubborn. Step aside.
[Missing Person Jeong Yu Na]
-Gosh.
-Hey.
-Don't rip my mother's poster!
-Come on.
Hey, give me that.
-Hello.
-Thank you for your service.
Sure. What in the world...
Are you In Seon?
[Civil Servant ID Card, Ryu Su Yeol]
Are you really a police officer?
Then do you think
all cops look like thugs?
You don't believe me even with the ID?
Forget about that.
Have your ice cream.
Well, you know... About your mom.
Did you
find my mom?
No, it's not that.
Then,
did my mom run away?
It's okay. You can tell me now.
Could you make sure
the police officer at the substation
gets this?
I promised him
that I'd make him a new one,
but I couldn't find
another four-leaf clover.
[Munyang Police Agency]
[I collected all the camera footage
from the vicinity of Jeong's apartment.]
[March 21, 2021, Camera 07]
[Enter, Exit, Car Plate Numbers]
This apartment complex has too many exits
and entrances. Darn it.
[Enter, Exit, Car Plate Numbers]
Gosh.
-Did you stay up all night?
-What? Yes.
Why are you working so hard?
Take it easy, man.
I'll decide what to do.
Mind your own business.
-What is it?
-I've never seen a car like this.
-Come take a look.
-What is it?
Look. There's something fishy
about this car. Right here.
Look, a van with a stovepipe.
Have you seen a van like this?
Yes, I have.
For real? A car like this actually exists?
When my dog died,
Dong Yeol made a big fuss
about holding a funeral for the dog.
That's when I saw one.
-But this was well after midnight.
-Right.
The problem is, this is illegal.
Hey, what's the phone number?
-It's 1533... 8572.
-Okay.
Let's see.
[The number you have dialed...]
I knew it. The number does not exist.
There's no point running the plate.
-Let's check the footage and track it.
-Something's very fishy here.
Go straight?
Obviously. Keep going straight
unless I tell you otherwise.
Where are we right now?
Darn it. How far did this car go?
-Oh, make a right!
-Make a right?
-Yes, right here.
-Okay, got it.
The route we got off the footage
ends here.
-I see something over there.
-Hey, look!
-Over there!
-That van right there.
-That's it, right?
-Yes. These punks... You're so dead.
-Look, this is it.
-Yes, this is the one.
[Mobile Funeral Home, Rainbow Bridge]
-What?
-I can't see the inside. Darn it.
Look at these heavily tinted windows.
Hey, look.
[Mobile Funeral Home, Rainbow Bridge]
So your boss owns that black van outside?
Yes, it's from his old business.
Do you make business signs here?
My boss will be here soon.
What's up there? I'll go check it out.
Do you want some coffee?
Sure.
Don't be so rude.
I feel like you're belittling me.
I refuse to put up with this.
I'll make your coffee after I pee.
What's his deal?
-Hey! He's getting away!
-What?
Hey, no!
-Get him. Jae Seon, get him!
-Hey, stop!
-Hey!
-Stop right there, you punk!
Hey!
Hey, Jae Seon. Inspector Yang, this van!
Should we put in a request for a warrant?
No. Hey, there's a crack.
[Mobile Funeral Home, Rainbow Bridge]
What? Where?
-The window's cracked.
-Where?
Just tell me to break it,
for goodness' sake.
Nice, you're so strong.
You smashed it with just one punch.
You're here. I was going to...
Hey! Back off!
-Ouch!
-You little...
What happened?
They suddenly barged in
and took everything, even the ashes.
What was I supposed to do?
Thank goodness my boy who was there
managed to run away.
Leave the country for a while.
Both you and him.
Take all your boys with you.
You see, I want to.
But look. How many are there?
If I have to take all of them with me,
it'll cost me a lot of money.
This is the last time.
Leave the country and lie low
unless you want to die.
Yes, sir.
[National Forensic Service]
[Restricted Area]
Yes, we did find some human ashes.
It's a small amount, but we did find some.
So? You want a DNA analysis done, right?
Okay, all done.
So it's done?
Yes, thank you for your cooperation.
Wait, sir.
Yes.
My sister had life insurance
with her daughter as the beneficiary.
This means we can now get
the insurance payout, right?
Are you serious right now?
Sorry? Why?
We can't get it?
You can only get the payout
if your sister is dead.
Right, so if she is dead...
Is that more important to you right now?
Are you praying that
your sister is dead or what?
Hey, calm down.
Is her daughter the beneficiary
of her life insurance policy?
Yes.
Then first, make sure
you get custody of the child.
With that, you'll gain the right
to manage the payout.
But you see,
the money is hers. If you mess
with the money or spend it all,
you will end up in jail.
Mister.
I'm...
Yes?
My mom.
Is she dead?
We don't know yet.
Then is she not dead?
I told you
that it's fine.
I don't have to
find my mom.
So you can now
stop looking for my mom.
Ma'am, you'll get rid of
this water tank too, right?
Yes, I should.
-Okay.
-Goodness.
One, two.
Hang on. Put it down for a second.
What's this?
Hey, Jae Seon.
[Hey, Su Yeol. I just heard from NFS
with the results.]
[It is Jeong Yu Na.]
[And I've put out an APB
on those foreigners. I'll rush back now.]
[Okay, all right.]
So you were right, after all.
-Hey.
-Yes?
How would you define life?
-Not sure.
-When I make pizza, I think that life is
a lot like pizza toppings.
You're my dough,
-and I'm your pizza toppings.
-My gosh.
-I'm the cheese on your pizza.
-Hey!
I'll melt your heart!
Gosh, hey. I'll tell you
what you can call me from now on.
Repeat after me. "Babe."
-Babe...
-Come on, say it!
-My gosh, I love your outfit today.
-Come on. Say it. "Babe."
Gosh, I can't say it.
-Babe. I mean, the police, right?
-My gosh.
I'm calling to report trespassing.
-Who's that guy?
-This guy is my little brother.
Brother, shouldn't you be at work now?
What are you doing here?
The address is 110 Lexi Apartments
in Munmi-dong. The unit number is 1523.
Get out now. I mean, please leave.
Babe, get out.
Why do you keep saying 13?
It's 23. Unit 1523.
No, 34! Get it right. It's 34!
-Get out.
-Are you deaf?
Hey, are you not going to leave?
I'm not in a good mood.
Leave when I'm asking nicely.
Put out the candles, will you?
I didn't even know that they were lit.
Oh, that lady said she was hungry,
so I ordered some jokbal.
Jokbal, my foot.
-It's 35,000 won, right?
-Yes, here you go.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you. Drive safely.
[But it was raining so hard.]
That moment,
I saw a handsome guy on his motorcycle.
Hey, Jae Seon.
You have that student's number, right?
Gyeong Tae's witness.
[The Delivery Crew]
Hang on.
[See? I told you. He's a total nutcase.]
Hey. Can't you tell
that jerk is a total attention-seeker
who wants to be a hero?
Jeong Yu Na's credit card was used
yesterday.
Do you believe me now?
This scumbag...
I knew it! It can't be a coincidence.
He beat up Gyeong Tae
at Jeong Yu Na's place
with a plan from the get-go.
[He killed her.
But Gyeong Tae kept on digging,]
[so he tried to kill him too.]
I was suspicious of Do In Beom,
but he's a real scumbag.
Go to Munyang Police Agency now.
We'll lock him up if we need to, okay?
[Police]
Well, where do I begin
so I can make sure I don't have to see
your shameless face anymore,
Assistant Inspector Do?
If you've got something to say,
say it and go home.
That's one way of doing it.
Why did you go to O Gyeong Tae's place
last Wednesday night?
What? Were you relieved because
the cameras in the area weren't working?
There are dashcams everywhere, you know.
-What's your problem?
-You stay out of this.
I was wondering what this was about.
I went to see him because I felt bad.
I was thinking
maybe he just wanted to do his best
and that I was too harsh on him.
But back then, I really didn't know
that he was such a scary jerk.
Had I known, I would've caught him
right then and there, no matter what.
What? What are you talking about?
What?
You haven't heard yet?
He killed Jeong Yu Na.
-What?
-Who killed whom?
This morning,
[a knife was found under the water tank
at O Gyeong Tae's place.]
[On the knife, they found his fingerprint
as well as Jeong Yu Na's blood.]
We just got back
from the National Forensic Service.
You scumbag.
Cut the nonsense.
-Hey, calm down.
-Have you no manners?
I have no respect for a scumbag like you.
Hey!
You killed Jeong Yu Na.
You killed her.
Then you planted evidence at his place
to frame him, you scumbag!
Calm down! And you, get off of him.
What?
They found what?
O Gyeong Tae's print
and Jeong Yu Na's blood? On the knife?
What kind of idiot
would hide such evidence at his place?
My point, exactly.
But such an idiot actually exists.
And that idiot tried to kill himself
because he was scared.
-You scumbag!
-Hey, let go!
-Hey!
-I will kill that jerk today and quit.
-Hey, you!
-You're dead meat.
-Bring it on.
-Hey.
-You little...
-Hey!
-Break it up!
[Kind Munyang Police,
Always There for the Citizens]
I don't even get angry anymore.
Trust me. It's not O Gyeong Tae.
They found Jeong Yu Na's blood
and his fingerprint on the knife.
What's your problem? You're the only one
who believes that it wasn't him.
It was Do In Beom. I'm sure of it.
He killed Jeong Yu Na
and even tried to kill Gyeong Tae.
Listen, I know that you're being like this
because of Assemblyman Do.
He wouldn't want to have anything to do
with a murderer.
You know me. Obviously,
I've already thought this through.
We can clean up the mess
before Assemblyman Do is affected by...
She's estimated to have been killed
on the 25th of last month,
right?
Yes.
Assemblyman Do called earlier.
He said he was with Do In Beom that day.
What?
Assemblyman Do said that? Why is he lying?
Clearly, it's not a lie!
What?
Will you go fight with him
and insist that he's lying?
[To Be Promoted: Ryu Su Yeol]
[Senior Inspector to Superintendent]
O Gyeong Tae being the killer
[Ryu Su Yeol]
will help you out too.
Don't you realize that?
Don't do anything stupid.
Don't ruin things, okay?
And that fool, Jae Seon.
Make sure he behaves himself!
Goodness.
[The police officer]
[pending internal investigation]
[who tried to take his own life
has now become a murder suspect.]
[Munyang General Hospital]
[The entire nation is in shock.]
[Officer O, murdered Jeong,
a woman who had been reported missing]
[Officer O Charged With Murder
of Missing Person]
[in Munyang.]
Sir, let's go grab a bite to eat.
[The late Jeong Yu Na]
[The fact that he exposed the police
corruption when he was a prosecutor]
[-and his slogan for clean politics]
-Jeez.
[have won over the public.]
[On top of this,
his image as an approachable candidate]
[seemed to have helped win over the people
who are not interested in politics.]
[Clean and just politics!]
[We shall make it happen again!]
[Candidate Do's Ratings Doubles]
[-Number Two Do Yu Gon!
-Number Two Do Yu Gon!]
[-Vote for Do Yu Gon!
-Vote for Do Yu Gon!]
What's that? You keep fidgeting with that.
She's got dexterous hands.
My kids can't make anything
with their hands.
Su Yeol.
I know I shouldn't have lost
my temper that day.
I know I shouldn't have...
But...
If we stop here,
that will make us scumbags.
Right?
[From the 11th Graduating Class
of Munyang High School]
[Congratulations on your promotion.
From Style]
[Captain Ryu Su Yeol]
Hello, sir.
Good for him and his promotion.
Hey, Jae Seon.
Why aren't you pestering me
to treat you to a meal?
I have to go home early
to look after the kids.
Should I buy meat and come over today?
It's been a while.
I can take all of us out to...
There's a fly here.
No. Nothing to see here.
[Captain Ryu Su Yeol]
You did it.
That's why you were waiting out here?
At this hour?
Let's talk.
Come on. Don't slam the door.
My car isn't in...
So you had O Gyeong Tae's case.
How did you know that?
Why did O Gyeong Tae kill Jeong Yu Na?
-What?
-I looked into it.
They didn't have any connections
until she was reported missing.
Are you sure
O Gyeong Tae killed Jeong Yu Na?
Isn't it odd?
We have the evidence. The knife.
They found the knife at his house.
That's definitive proof. Isn't it?
You didn't even figure out his motive.
Someone could have framed him.
So what? What's your point?
Jeong Yu Na.
She was Min Su's confidential informant.
[Tak Min Su]
What?
It's been a while, Jeong Hyeon Su.
You know something about Min Su,
don't you?
Isn't that why you've been hiding?
So this is the place?
Min Su got you to make a spy cam
and deliver it here.
Yes. I put it in a necklace.
But the problem is the woman
from this apartment died.
What? She's dead?
Min Su died
when he was going after someone.
And Min Su's informant,
Jeong Yu Na, died too.
This
might not be a simple murder case.
Have you seen a necklace like this?
Come on. Take a look at it again. Please.
Jeong Yu Na had this.
There's a camera inside.
I have to find this first.
I've never seen a necklace like that.
And that's not my case anymore.
So stop pestering me. Go to the Violent
Crimes Unit at Munyang Station.
-Get out.
-Su Yeol.
Get out of my car now. Come on.
Darn it.
Hey! Come on. The door!
Fine! I will do it then!
[Gate 3]
[Exit, Parking]
Gosh. Come on.
You've got to be kidding me.
[Hello. This is the maintenance office.]
Hello. The elevator stopped.
I'm in elevator three.
I'm stuck
between the 13th and 14th floors.
[Under Maintenance]
Please hurry.
Are you sure
O Gyeong Tae killed Jeong Yu Na?
You didn't even figure out his motive.
[Someone could have framed him.]
Not again. Come on. Don't do this.
Hey.
Hello? Sir?
[Elevator Three]
Hey. Hello?
Come on! Answer me!
Let me see.
My phone isn't working.
This is driving me crazy.
Hey! Please!
Hey! Help me!
Sir, what took you so long?
Please help me.
Peekaboo.
-Are you that happy to see me?
-You jerk.
Hey! We could've fallen. Why did you jump?
-Don't come near me.
-Didn't you miss me? I missed you so much!
You crazy jerk. Get away from me.
What? What's going on?
What is this? What are you going to do?
Stop that! You lunatic! Stop!
Stop jumping!
You crazy jerk. Stop!
-Let's go!
-Stop that!
Stop that.
Stop!
You psycho!
What's going on?
You... What are you doing?
-Bless you.
-No. Don't do it!
Stop!
I told you to stop that, you jerk!
What...
[You are in Basement Level 1.]
Stop that!
Where am I? Why...
Not the stairs! Stay on the flat surface!
No, not the stairs.
Move!
Get out of our way.
Gosh.
What the...
You psycho.
Hey, I'm about to fall off. Hey, no!
Darn it. You lunatic!
Stop!
Watch out!
What? You stopped?
Why? Hey, this is scaring me even more.
Why did you stop?
Hey, how do I unfasten this?
Hey. You psycho...
What's your deal?
You were driving like a total lunatic.
Why stop now...
Hey!
Be gentle, will you?
That thing costs more than your life.
I've always known this about you,
but you're so brave, Boss.
What? You think it's because I'm drunk?
By the way,
your Korean has improved so much.
Staying here makes me anxious.
You said that the cop gave you money
for us to flee the country.
I'm afraid the other cops
would raid this place again.
Hey, was I supposed to say no
when he was offering money?
We need to get rid of the things here
before we flee.
Still, if they find out
that we're still here,
they'll all raid us!
Hey, no one would even think
that we'd come back here.
Think about it, you idiot.
SU JAN.
Just go upstairs and keep an eye on them.
Make sure they don't slack off.
Okay.
Hurry up, SU JAN.
Who are you?
Hey, what are you doing?
The chicken is already here?
No, I'm not...
Tell him he'd better tell the truth
if he wants to live.
-What?
-Is it the fried chicken?
-No, I'm not...
-And tell him
he'll get punched
every time he talks nonsense.
You punk, who are you...
Boys! This guy punched me!
Hey, why are there so many of you?
Hey, why...
-Where did they all come from?
-One, two, three, four...
Get him!
Hey!
Have you seen a necklace like this?
Jeong Yu Na had this.
There's a camera inside.
[I have to find this first.]
Gosh, fine.
It's not like I've never done this before.
You little...
Oh, my. This feels nice.
What's he doing?
-No!
-Please, no!
I'm not doing it, you idiots!
Hey! Get him.
Get him!
Catch him!
Hey, boys!
SU JAN!
Hey, pig. Get down.
Sorry sir, getting down!
-My apologies.
-Good!
One.
[-All right.
-Two!]
[I'm sorry. We'll leave.
We'll leave right away.]
[We really will.]
[I told you not to use your phone
when I'm here.]
[Who knows? Maybe you're taking]
[photos of me to blackmail me later on.]
[Hey, are you dead?]
[Listen up, even if you're dead.]
You brought this upon yourself.
You got that?
You deserved to die!
Why did you have to die? Why drop dead?
[Assemblyman Do called earlier.]
He said he was with Do In Beom that day.
Will you go fight with him
[and insist that he's lying?]
You punk! Hey!
That little...
Hey, stop!
You psycho! You piece of...
No! Stop!
Hey! What are you doing? What the...
Hey, stop!
You crazy jerk!
This is attempted murder!
Will this end with Min Su?
Didn't you see this coming
when you fled on your own?
Anyway... What's this?
Give me the necklace.
You have no idea what that is.
Who are you?
Who the heck are you?
Who are you
and why are you doing this to me?
Me?
Hero.
What?
To punish those trash-like rotten punks.
The last of this era!
The hero.
You're one crazy idiot, aren't you?
You...
You still don't get who I am, do you?
Watch closely from now on.
About who I am.
Hey!
What?
What is this?
[Assemblyman Do Yu Gon
has been re-elected.]
[Voting Booth]
[Do Yu Gon Re-elected
With 30 Percent of Popular Vote]
[Formerly a prosecutor,
Assemblyman Do Yu Gon]
[got into politics at a young age]
[after exposing
the corruption in the prosecution...]
[Munyang Police Agency]
Hey.
Come on in, Senior Inspector Ryu.
He's Superintendent Ryu now.
Oh, that's right. Superintendent Ryu.
-Hello, sir.
-Things are happening for you, it seems.
My gosh, thank you. I'll work harder.
Oh, there he is.
It's been a while, Superintendent Ryu.
Hello, sir.
There are many competent officers
in Munyang.
It's all thanks to you,
our competent commissioner.
My gosh, thank you. I'm flattered.
Superintendent Ryu.
This is just between us,
but your promotion wouldn't have happened
without Assemblyman Do's help.
Right.
Ryu Su Yeol. Are you nervous?
What are you waiting for?
You should thank him.
-Thank you, sir.
-Don't mention it.
Assemblyman Do would like to have a meal
with all of us.
What do you say? Are you busy today?
No, of course not. I made sure
to leave my schedule wide open.
Good, that's great.
There's a good Chinese restaurant
across the street. Let's go there.
-Let's go.
Shoot.
[Munyang Police Agency]
Are you all right?
Yes. I'll use the restroom
and meet you there, sir.
All right. Let's go.
Darn it.
Get it together, Ryu Su Yeol.
Do better.
Do better? On what?
I watched the clip on the flash drive.
That punk...
What?
Where is he?
Where did he go?
Hey.
That little...
[Stairs]
That jerk...
Hey! Darn you!
What? Where's he going?
Hey! You!
Hey! Stop!
Do Yu Gon!
No...
No, don't.
No!
[You still don't get it?]
[Now, do you see]
[who I am?]
You lunatic!
[Bad, Evil, Crazy]
[Bad and Crazy]
-That punk.
-Hey, Ryu Su Yeol! Get him!
What the heck did you do to me?
-Get him!
-Darn it.
[This wouldn't have happened
had you told me what was going on.]
You'll die at this rate.
-Hey!
[-I told you it wasn't a dream.]
-He's not real!
No...
You're that cop, aren't you?
You lunatics!
[If you indeed caught a shark,]
it'll sink the boat you're on.
Don't you know that?
[Who brought Jeong Yu Na's corpse here?]