[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode 15]
Xu Qian is from Northern Zhou.
Northern Zhou?
This is what I ignored.
The characters on the bamboo table
looked like they were written with great force
and carelessly.
It was definitely not carved by Miss Zhang.
If it was a Han person who wrote it,
the strokes wouldn't have been like that.
The angle of the knife shows that it was not written with the right hand,
but the left hand.
And the knife found in Xu Qian's mansion
is a typical Northern Zhou short knife.
The Northern Zhou people hold a long knife with the right hand,
and a short knife with the left hand.
So,
for effortless things like writing,
they usually use their left hand.
So that's what you were thinking last night?
I thought it was an urgent matter.
Is it really worth it
to wake us up so early in the morning for this?
I see.
The most beautiful house according to Miss Zhang
is the style of Northern Zhou architecture.
She and Xu Qian were deeply in love.
During this period,
Xu Qianji might have taken her to Northern Zhou.
Why didn't Mr. Zhang mention it before?
Because the Zhang family really cares about its reputation.
They didn't want to tell outsiders
about Miss Zhang's eloping.
Besides, the person she loves
is from Northern Zhou.
Even if we asked them,
they wouldn't admit it anyway.
Is she really
so obsessed with Northern Zhou architecture?
Northern Zhou architecture?
Who has ever seen it before?
Although I'm a martial artist,
I've never been to Northern Zhou.
I've only heard that those from Northern Zhou are good at riding horses.
They're nomadic people
and live on grasslands.
They usually stay in yurts.
As for what exactly yurts look like,
I have no idea.
We can’t just sit here and do nothing.
Since you have found an important clue, Qingfeng,
I'll go to the street
to see if anyone knows people from Northern Zhou.
As long as we find Northern Zhou people to help us,
we can build the yurt.
Now the two states are at odds
and spies are everywhere.
It's not easy
to find Northern Zhou people on the street.
We have to find a way.
If you know friends from Northern Zhou,
bring them to Wood Feather House
so that Mr. Luo doesn't have to look for them.
Miss Chen,
tell me
about what you know of the Northern Zhou yurt.
The nomadic people don't have a fixed place to live.
They move on horses all the time.
That's why they prefer yurts.
The style of yurts is very different from the residence in Jiangnan and Central Plain.
Look.
No stone wall and no wood celing.
Only yurts are used to provide protection from wind and rain
so that they're ready to move at any time.
Inside a yurt,
how big is the space?
How many pillars are there?
What's its floor made of?
How do I know that?
I just heard it from my brother.
Does your brother know how to build a yurt?
Why?
If he knows the details,
I'd like to visit your family
and talk to your brother.
Well...
I don't think you can.
Why?
My brother doesn't live in the family mansion.
Is it because he's not in the house
or you don't want me to go there again?
What do you mean?
Li Qingfeng, just say it.
I don’t want to talk about it.
All I want now is to know how to build a Northern Zhou yurt.
What do you mean?
Are you suspecting me?
You suspect that I’m engaged with Mr. He,
so you want to confirm it with my brother.
You'd rather believe him
than me.
Do you trust me then?
If you trust me,
you won't fend off my questions.
you wouldn't have
kept anything about your family from me.
Li Qingfeng.
Master, Li Qingfeng.
Somebody from Northern Zhou is here.
We're so lucky.
As soon as we went out to look for the Northern Zhou people,
we met Mr. He who came to visit us.
He brought milk wine
and dried beef.
He is actually from Northern Zhou.
Is Mr. He your friend?
To put it more precisely,
he's a friend of Miss Chen.
Yes, he's my friend.
I'm here to bring some specialties
from my hometown to Miss Chen.
Miss Chen, since you need my help,
why didn't you tell me earlier?
I will do my best to help.
It's very kind of you.
But we don't want to bother you
about the building of the yurt.
Please do bother me.
Mr. He, we need your help.
Will you help me?
It's my honor
to be at your service, Miss Chen.
He!
Do all Northern Zhou people
stare at girls like you do?
Please forgive me.
Miss Chen is so beautiful
that I couldn't take my eyes off her.
My apologies.
You think I'm beautiful?
Of course you are.
Your stunning beauty
amazed me when we first met.
Mr. He,
since you promise to help,
let's get to the point.
Please tell us how to build a yurt.
Okay.
But I have a request.
I hope Miss Chen
will be in charge of the draft.
You don't have to worry about
the division of work in Wood Feather House.
I think you didn't hear me clearly.
I said
I'll only help
if Miss Chen is in charge of the draft.
Understand?
Don't worry, Mr. He.
I'll do the draft.
OK.
Are you free now?
I still have things to attend to today.
I'll come back tomorrow, OK?
OK, deal.
See you tomorrow.
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
Mr. Li.
Luo.
My lady said she couldn’t finish the food alone,
so she asked me to share it with you.
Thank you.
I thought you would refuse.
Why would I?
My lady is not interested in Mr. He at all.
I can tell that
she’s just mad at you.
Thank you, Luo.
Well,
another thing.
Go ahead.
My lady is very upset.
As a man,
maybe you should try to
have a better understanding of women.
Did your lady tell you to say that?
No, no, no.
I said it
because I hate to see
my lady be so depressed.
I feel sorry for her.
Sorry for making you worry, Luo.
Sorry.
Mr. Li, don't say sorry.
I’m off.
Luo.
Master.
[Thorough survey of curves and lines]
What are you doing?
My lady asked me
to share with everyone the food from Northern Zhou.
I'm going to take yours.
What's so good about food in Northern Zhou?
I need to ask you something very serious.
Please go ahead.
Do you think
He Zhigu has a crush on Master?
I'm afraid
everybody can clearly see that.
How dare that Northern Zhou barbarian
try to hit on our Princess?
Should I send some people to warn him
and tell him to behave?
It's all in your head, sir.
There must be plenty of men out there
who find my lady
attractive.
How can we blame them?
What matters is who she likes.
That makes sense.
But look at Li Qingfeng.
He's an idiot.
He should have made it clear that he's the one that Master likes.
Are you taking his side now?
No, I'm not.
I just think
Li Qingfeng
is better than He Zhigu.
Don't worry.
My lady will never like somebody like Mr. He.
That’s true.
But I’m afraid that idiot Li Qingfeng
would make himself look bad compared with He Zhigu.
Stop.
Who hasn’t got it?
I’ll help you deliver the food.
Don’t bother.
Be good.
What the hell is this? It's so hard.
It's gonna break my teeth!
What? Are you going to close the door?
We are men.
Why do you have to close the door?
Forget it.
What's wrong?
Can't you tell that He Zhigu
fancies Master?
So what?
I'll give you a chance.
When you finish work here,
I'll bring my kung fu coach
to teach that guy a lesson.
And you'll be very lucky
to be the first one to do it.
What do you think?
How will you teach Mr. He a lesson?
I'll beat him up.
Why don't you just kill him?
Li Qingfeng,
I underestimated you.
But,
that's a terrible idea.
Li Qingfeng, are you kidding me?
I just don’t know
why you have to teach Mr. He a lesson.
Don't play dumb with me.
You know exactly what I'm talking about!
I don't have time for that.
Just ask
someone else.
You are not honest to yourself.
No wonder you always make Master angry.
I see
what happened today.
Although you upset Master,
I'm happy.
Because now,
Master won't be
fooled by your hypocrisy.
That's good.
When you see me and Miss Chen
work together,
how do you feel?
Why didn't you just ask
how it makes me feel
to see you two
being lovey-dovey together?
To be honest,
I used to think
Master was way out of your league.
So I was furious whenever I saw you and her together.
But then...
Anyway, I'm fine now.
As the saying goes,
distance tests the strength of a horse,
and time reveals the true character of a person.
Let's wait and see.
We're different.
Is Miss Chen the love of your life?
I...
Luo.
Luo!
Luo! Luo!
What’s going on?
Mr. He, please.
So this is where you work.
It's where I work with Architect Li.
Do you two work together?
Yes.
In that case,
Mr. Li,
I really envy you.
Don't move.
Mr. Li doesn't like other people to touch his stuff.
But he makes an exception for you, right?
Yes.
That's right.
Mr. He, shall we start now?
Of course.
Please.
I'm good at swordsmanship,
but I don't know anything about painting.
Miss Chen, please.
You'll do the draft and I'll describe it.
OK?
Alright. Thank you, Mr. He.
Do you have to observe here?
I'm an architect.
Even though I'm not in charge of the draft,
it's my job to supervise here.
It doesn't matter.
Let's get started.
The Northern Zhou yurt is composed of four parts,
including a door, Hana, Oni and a round skylight.
[The Northern Zhou yurt is composed of]
Besides, there are willow rafters,
leather ropes and mane ropes.
A big yurt is round.
A small one is one and a half zhang in its diameter.
Miss Chen.
This is not right.
Let me help you.
Like this. Look.
It should be like this.
Mr. He.
Li Qingfeng, what are you doing?
Look, now I have to redraw it.
Let me do it.
It doesn't look round now.
Miss Chen, please make another draft.
I'll do it.
It doesn't really matter.
Let me do it.
Mr. Li, it looks like you don't really care about
the accuracy of the draft.
I don’t think it’s necessary for me to stay. Goodbye.
Mr. He.
Wait for me.
Mr. He, wait for me.
Wait.
Miss Chen, I'm willing to help you.
But Architect Li seems to hold grudges against me.
With him here,
I'm afraid the draft can't be completed today.
I know.
That's the way he is.
Just ignore him.
How about we get the paper and ink brush
and go to the meeting hall to finish the draft?
Miss Chen.
To be honest,
I really don't feel comfortable in Wood Feather House.
So you mean...
How about this?
Let's find a quiet place
so that no one will disturb us
and I'll be able to explain the details of the yurt.
What do you think?
Well...
You don't want to?
No, no, no.
I would love to.
Then let's go to Yi Mu Restaurant.
I'll get the tools. Wait for me.
OK.
What are you going to do?
To do the draft at Yi Mu Restaurant.
Why do you have to go there?
It's all your fault!
If you hadn't irritated He Zhigu,
I wouldn't have had to go there.
Don't go.
How can I make the draft if I don't?
How can we build the yurt without a draft?
I don’t think
we can't find another person from Northern Zhou to help us
in Lin'an.
Li Qingfeng,
are you worried about me?
I...
Not at all!
OK. If you don't want me to go,
apologize to me.
Then I'll refuse Mr. He.
Apologize?
Why should I apologize?
What do you think?
I think you should give me an explanation.
OK. Wait for it then.
Mr. He, let’s go.
Here.
Thank you.
Miss Chen, why do you look so upset
all of a sudden?
That's Li Qingfeng’s special talent I guess.
Forget it.
He's ridiculous.
I'll leave him alone.
Let's go.
[Yi Mu Restaurant]
Miss Chen.
Speaking of Xiao,
there are only two things that attract me the most.
The first thing is the delicious food.
Food here
is so delicious wherever I go.
What's the second one?
The second one is
the beautiful and elegant Jiangnan girls like you, Miss Chen.
Mr. He, you're wrong.
Jiangnan girls are indeed beautiful and elegant.
But
I'm not one of those girls.
My personality
is more like men.
Miss Chen, your personality
is a combination of the gentleness of Jiangnan
and the roughness of Northern Zhou.
So I think
you're supposed to live in Northern Zhou.
I don't think so.
This place is called Yi Mu Restaurant.
It's quiet and elegant.
I will remember this place.
This is where our first date takes place.
It means a lot to me.
It means nothing...
Miss Chen...
Don't get me wrong.
I was talking about Li Qingfeng.
You mean...
Well,
Li Qingfeng brought me here before.
Interesting.
I thought Mr. Li was talented,
but didn't know how to enjoy life.
I didn't expect him to come here at leisure.
At leisure...
When he
is alone,
he enjoys himself by playing instruments, chess, doing calligraphy, painting, reciting poetry, and drinking wine and tea.
But when he's with other people,
he's always a boring guy.
Selfish.
-Do you think I... -Besides,
he's arrogant.
and infuriating.
When he upset people,
he blames others first.
That's ridiculous, right?
Yes.
By the way,
I drew a painting with him.
Please tell me who draws better.
You...Miss Chen.
Sit down.
Let's make the draft.
I almost forgot.
OK. Let's do it.
Don't worry.
I don't know Miss Chen as well as you do,
but I'm sure
she just wants to do the job well.
I know.
But you don't look like you know.
Sometimes you
don't mince your words and upset other people.
But sometimes,
you prefer to keep to yourself.
Miss Zhao,
can I ask you a somewhat offensive question?
This is not your style.
Go ahead.
On the day I first visited your family‘s mansion,
you didn't even know me.
Why did you like me?
There's a difference between liking someone
and understanding someone.
It takes time to understand another person.
But I like you
because I just knew you were the one the moment I saw you.
That feeling
is very precious.
What if
two people are in love,
but one of them is hiding something from the other?
What should be done in that case?
If it's for the sake of their relationship,
I don't think that's an inappropriate thing to do.
Besides,
truth will come to light sooner or later.
Nothing
can be hidden forever.
You'll know the truth eventually.
Is Miss Chen hiding something from you?
No.
I don't think so, either.
Miss Chen is also very straightforward.
On the contrary, you tend to keep to yourself
and it's more likely that you hide things from her.
Miss Zhao.
Miss Chen, we were talking about you.
It must be something bad.
You two
are exactly the same.
OK, I won't bother you.
I’m off.
By the way,
I've never seen a Northern Zhou yurt.
If you don't mind,
take me with you when you're at work.
No problem, Miss Zhao.
OK.
Goodbye.
What?
Are you waiting for me?
I'm waiting for the draft.
Come and have a look.
My draft is very detailed.
Leave it here.
What?
You demanded supervision during the day.
Now
I've finished the draft,
but you don't even want to have a look!
This is a draft that you and Mr. He
spent a whole day on.
It must be very detailed.
I don't need to see it.
Somebody's jealous here, huh?
I can feel it in the air.
Why are you staring at me?
You keep staring at me.
Are you trying to eat me?
What are you doing?
Did you do anything else
besides making the draft with He Zhigu?
Do you care?
Yes.
Then apologize to me.
Or I won't tell you.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Then go away.
No.
Go away!
How dare you!
You deserve it.
-It's raining. -Right.
Mr. Li.
I'm not sure
whether you can
build the most beautiful house in the world or not.
But
we can have a try.
Fu had a seizure several times after she came back.
We can’t get her worked up again.
If you are not completely sure about it,
forget it.
Mr. Zhang,
I think we should give it a try.
We can’t see Fu
live in hysteria for the rest of her life.
But she can't afford to get worked up again.
Mr. Zhang,
we'll cover the house with curtains.
If the new house
is not the most beautiful one according to her,
then we'll just demolish it.
OK.
But Mr. Li,
I'm curious.
What kind of house are you going to build?
Why there are only pillars without stone bricks?
You'll see.
Don't worry, Mr. Zhang.
OK. Thank you.
Mr. Zhang.
Miss Zhao.
What are you doing here?
Just for fun.
Since I can't help much with your work,
I’m here to take a look.
I have nothing better to do now.
Are you free to go to my archery room
to see my new bows and arrows?
OK.
Please.
How is it, Miss Zhao?
Is my archery room good?
Did you make this yourself?
Yes.
You let me win on purpose in the hunting field before.
My eyes were following you
and I was distracted.
Follow me?
Yes.
You're very straightforward.
One shouldn’t hesitate
in face of love.
I like you the way you like Architect Li.
Your sincerity
has impressed me a lot.
You know I like Architect Li,
so why did you still say that?
Because I'm in love.
And I want to be honest with you.
In that case,
we're very much alike.
We can be friends.
I’m happy
to be your friend.
Isn't it painful
to only be friends with the one you like?
If I can't even be friends with the girl I like,
it would be even more painful.
I can't believe it's more difficult to build pillars than stacking up stones.
Thank you, guys.
Go to bed early tonight.
Tomorrow's work will be more difficult.
You are exploiting us.
I thought you were going to
find more craftsmen tomorrow.
None of the workers in Lin'an
has done this before.
We need to help them one by one if we hire them.
The more craftsmen, the more tiring the work will be.
Exactly.
I went to the Ministry of Works to register for this work.
Even the Minister
had never seen a yurt draft before.
Well,
we should thank Miss Chen and Mr. He.
If they hadn't
made the draft so carefully,
we couldn't have worked in such a smooth way.
Actually,
the architecture plan was adjusted
by Architect Li.
Lin'an is different from Northern Zhou.
The weather here is wetter and less windy.
If we do it
strictly according to the hurt in Northern Zhou,
it would be too stuffy inside.
But
based on his adjustment,
we put air holes in the yurt
and also change the sewing method of the blanket.
It's more comfortable to live in the yurt.
You're really a genius, Architect Li.
Even though you've never seen the yurt before,
you can adjust it according to the local conditions.
When will they come back?
You're back from work!
Miss Zhao.
Why are you still here?
I'm waiting for you to have some midnight snacks.
Miss Zhao, are you going to
treat us?
It's Mr. Zhang who wants to treat you.
You've worked so hard on your first day of work.
Thank you.
Forget it.
Treat us when it's all completed.
I'm already exhausted.
We appreciate your offer.
But we still have to work tomorrow.
We're off.
Alright.
I'll leave too.
[Zhang's Mansion]
Miss Chen.
You just can't leave her alone, huh?
Mr. He.
Miss Chen, I have something to tell you.
Are you available now?
Mr. He, please go ahead.
Here is the thing.
It suddenly occurred to me last night that
although the draft
of the yurt was finished,
I haven't told you
the details of the interior of the yurt,
which is very different
from what you have here.
I'm afraid if I don't tell you about it,
you may make an awkwardly-decorated yurt.
Thank you, Mr. He.
How about this?
Please come back here tomorrow
and tell us what to do on site.
I have a lot of work to deal with tomorrow.
That's why I came here late at night.
Well,
why don't you go back to Wood Feather House with us?
You know
I don't feel comfortable there.
Shall we go to Yi Mu Restaurant instead?
OK.
Mr. Li, we...
In that case,
I’ll leave now.
OK, let’s go to Yi Mu Restaurant.
Luo, none of you should go with me.
I’ll go alone.
Let's go.
Master!
My lady! I told you
none of you should go with me.
[Wood Feather House]
How about us going to Yi Mu Restaurant together?
No.
Calm down.
Think twice.
If you don't go tonight,
I'm afraid Miss Chen will blame you for the rest of your life.
[Wood Feather House]
Qingfeng, where are you going?
I'm taking a walk.
Qingfeng.
You…
Luo.
I'm going to Yi Mu Restaurant.
It's late at night and they're together.
What if that barbarian is up to something?
Master will be in danger.
Don’t worry.
She'll be fine.
Mr. He, please don't drink.
Tell me
about the interior of the yurt.
It's already very late now.
And you still have work to do tomorrow.
I'm going to the palace to see His Majesty.
Miss Chen,
will you go back with me?
Brother will go with you.
You two can talk about national affairs.
I won't go back.
OK.
In a few days,
after I finish this,
I'm going back to Northern Zhou.
I really don't want to leave
this beautiful and bustling Lin'an city.
Our two states have been doing business for years.
You can come back anytime you want to.
Will you be happy to see me again?
Of course I will.
Here.
Miss Chen.
Thank you for everything.
I'd like to propose a toast to you.
[Yi Mu Restaurant]
Have a drink with me.
Like this?
Miss Chen, you're really good.
You described it very well.
Drink the wine and air your grievances.
Come on.
Miss Chen is in the opposite private room.
You can see her anytime.
Li Qingfeng,
I don’t know if it’s the best time,
but I want to tell you that,
actually,
I haven't really gotten over you.
Maybe
it's really inappropriate
and indecent for me to say it at this moment.
But I swear this is the last time I say it.
Since you showed up in my family's mansion
and got my embroidered ball,
I couldn't help falling in love.
I like you.
I don't care about your background.
I like you for what you are.
Even if my father
and my brothers object,
I don't care.
I only care about you.
I don't know architecture.
I can't work with you like Miss Chen.
Maybe
I don't really know how to love someone.
and did many things that you hate.
But from the very beginning,
I've been in love with you.
After you rejected me
and decided to be with Miss Chen,
I felt so painful.
But I still can't get over you.
Can you understand that?
If you love Miss Chen,
I hope you're the one who's loved.
If you two break up,
I hope
you'll let me be the one who loves you.
Li Qingfeng.
I will never like anybody else so much
in my life.
I want to ask you one last question.
Do I
still have a chance?
Cheers.
Miss Chen, you're really good at drinking.
I'm not.
Not as good as Li Qingfeng.
We're talking here,
but you keep mentioning Li Qingfeng.
Aren’t you afraid that I'll be upset by that?
Do I?
Then forget about him.
I’m still mad at him.
Come on.
Cheers.
You...
What are you doing?
I...
Li Qingfeng.
What are you doing here? Don't disturb me.
Miss Chen and I were just drinking and chatting.
Why did you come here without invitation?
Cheers.
OK.
Let's drink.
Cheers!
What are you doing?
Don't use my cup.
Very good.
I've said what I should say.
I'm taking her back to Wood Feather House.
Miss Chen,
I'll take my leave.
See you.
Take care.
You came to pick me up?
Why did you bring him here?
For the draft.
What else can we do here?
Draft?
Then why did you drink?
You're so boring.
Why couldn't we drink?
You always come here to drink.
Why can't I?
Do you know what he's up to?
Aren’t you afraid?
Mr. He is not a bad guy.
How do you know he is not?
I...
I just know.
You
must be jealous
because I'm close to him.
You know I’m jealous.
Then why did you still bring him here?
♫When I miss you during the night♫
I...
♫I call you while I'm dreaming♫
You care about me so much.
Why don't you admit your mistakes and apologize?
You're so proud and never give in.
♫I feel so relieved♫
♫You are all in my dreams♫
You don't know that
women's heart is like the West Lake.
♫How many times have I been back to the past?♫
♫I just want to meet you again♫
♫I'm so lucky♫
♫There's someone who didn't give up♫
♫You'll ride on the colorful clouds♫
♫And take me to see the world♫
♫Put on my wedding dress for you♫
♫I want to become a butterfly♫
♫Flying around♫
You...
Don't ask me
why I lied to you.
♫Flying to your arms♫
OK?
♫Ask your heart♫
♫Even if there's only♫
I won't.
Really?
♫Very little left♫
But you said that
♫Only death will do us apart♫
if you didn't understand me,
♫Yes I do♫
you wouldn't have been getting close to me.
I just tried it.
♫I want to become a butterfly♫
I think it works.
♫Flying around♫
Womanizer.
♫Flying to your arms ♫
♫Ask your heart♫
From now on,
♫Even if there's only♫
I won't be out of line.
♫Very little left♫
♫Only death will do us apart♫
From now on...
♫Yes I do♫