You came to see Sarawat again.
Why are you two always together lately?
So the rumor saying Sarawat likes Tine is true?
True.
You can compete for anything with anyone
but you can’t beat Sarawat when it comes to love
You agreed to flirt because you wanted some experience to write a song?
I am telling you. Flirting with me is quite special
1 or 2?
1.
2. means I’m hitting on you
1. means you will be hit on…by me.
Both 1 and 2 mean I like you
If you listen to Scrubb’s songs when you are happy, you will be even happier
If you listen when you are in love, you will be more deeply in love
If you listen to their songs when you are sad, you will feel better
It’s like someone is comforting you
Do you remember that I like Scrubb?
One of my favorite songs is called Everything.
And why are you telling me this?
Can you play Everything for me tomorrow?
Music Club is having a music show called Altermajeeb this Saturday.
Please come and join us.
Why does Mr.Chic have to do anything like this?
It’s exhausting and hot
I am freaking thirsty.
Stop messing things and stop complaining.
Tine.
I need to go to guitar practice
Take care of the rest.
Do it yourself.
You are ungrateful.
I just helped flirt with you in front of Green the other day.
Can’t you help me with this?
Oh please!
Your fandom set the price for my head all over social media
Your friends told them it was a joke and saved my ass
You don’t have to go so big next time
You talk too much
If I made you blush too much, just say it.
Sarawat!
Saraleo!
Thank you, Tine.
Pear, you remember my name.
Of course I do. You taught me a chord.
You are in the Faculty of Laws, aren’t you?
That’s right.
I have a friend in that Faculty too.
Seriously?
What is your friend’s name? I might know her.
Her name is Baifern.
Baifern?
So how is your guitar lesson going?
Not so bad.
It’s okay. I guess.
I will teach you, okay?
Sure. Thank you so much.
Why do you have so many flyers left?
Sarawat left me with these.
Why such a good mood?
Not your business.
I guess your practice is over since you have time to bug me here
Yes.
I asked to leave early.
I need to refurnish my room
That’s good.
Your room is like a haunted house
Help me!
In your dreams
I have a motto ‘Say No to Work. Say Yes to Boobs.’
When you have big boobs, give me a call.
If you help me clean up my room, I will let you grab my boobs
No.
I have to meet Pear this afternoon
I will take her to buy Scrubb’s CDs.
I am a good Scrubb’s missioner
She is one of Scrubb’s apostles now
How about evening?
This evening?
I have a cheerleading practice
If you need help, ask your fans
You have an army.
Bye.
Damn you!
My boobs are not big enough, are they?
Ready!
Ready! 3 4.
Keep them up.
Don’t be so flabby.
We won’t win the competition with this performance
Have I not told you…
that you need to turn your phones off in practice?
Tine’s phone
Sarawat is calling
Tine!
I am so sorry.
Pick up your phone quickly.
Don’t keep Sarawat waiting.
Hello
Are you done practicing?
Eyes on me, everyone.
Come help me with my room.
Can you stop dreaming?
I am still in practice
And I am so freaking starving.
What do you want to eat?
What?
Are you buying me snacks?
Did I say I would?
I freaking hate you!
Let’s do this.
If you bring me snacks, I will let you grab my boobs.
Hello!
What…
Break for 15 minutes.
Take a break, guys.
Sarawat, you brought us snacks?
I told him to.
I saw that everyone was so tired, so I told him to buy us snacks
Don’t fight over them, guys.
You can be kind too.
Sorry I call you asshole sometimes.
Can I grab your boobs now?
Boobs what?
Now you’re being an asshole again.
I was just joking.
But I am being serious
Stop.
STOP IT!
Damn you!
Hey! Seniors want to know if you have a girlfriend.
They see that you’re on Instagram, but you don’t fol anyone
What did you say?
Fol?
Yes. Fol.
What is fol?
My bad.
I forgot that you just exposed to the social media world
Fol as in follow
It’s when you follow someone on IG.
You follow people whom you are interested in
You basically snoop around their Instagram.
Are you listening to me?
Is this how you follow?
Did you even hear my question?
Do you have eyes for someone right now?
I told you I would hit on you. How can I have eyes for someone else?
Fake flirting doesn’t count. Give me the real answer.
Do you like anyone right now?
Hey!
Why are you following me?
I am telling you…
the one I’m following is the one I like
When will you stop messing with me?
Guys, let’s get back to work!
I have to go back to practice
Thank you so much for the snacks.
Don’t forget to follow other people.
Bye.
Get some rest.
Who are you looking for?
Sarawat went home already
But…
He left this for you, Tine
A spare key to my room
Meet me at 7 and help me clean up
Do not bail!
Wat!
Wake up!
Why did you tell me to come so early if you want to sleep in?
Wat!
Wat! Wake up!
You…
HOLY SHIT!
You’re here?
You are not…
You are not wearing…
What?
Look!
Why did you sleep naked?
You should have worn an underwear at least
I didn’t wear anything?
That means…
You saw everything in Sarawat Expo?
Stop it.
Aren’t you ashamed at all?
Why do you seem so proud?
I am not talking to you
What do you want me to do?
Look at my room.
Help me clean up.
Clean up what?
Everything.
Start with the shoes.
It’s not even messy.
Do you call it clean then?
Can I just let you grab my boobs and then I go?
Seriously?
I was kidding
I was just playing
I will do it now.
Where do you want them?
On your head?
Sorry!
You have many pairs of shoes.
They all new…
except…
this pair.
Why?
They are comfortable.
Comfortable?
This worn out?
If your fans know about this, they will buy you new pairs for sure
I won’t wear anything that other people buy for me
But if you do, I might.
Me?
And why would I do that?
Where do you want it?
Here.
Help me change the bed sheet.
I’m tired of black.
The Altermajeeb event tomorrow,
what songs are you guys playing?
Why?
Do you remember that I like Scrubb?
One of my favorite songs is called Everything.
And why are you telling me this?
Can you play Everything for me tomorrow?
Sorry.
The seniors have their songs listed
Can you ask them to change?
Convince them.
Please.
They made up their minds, Tine.
Just help me!
I want to hear it live.
Try to talk to them please
Put the sheet on.
I won’t do it then.
Alright. I will talk to them
Make the bed first.
It looks good
Test it.
It is so soft.
- I think it is soft too.
- Hey!
What are you doing?
This bed is so nice
I am checking the sheet
I should have changed it ages ago
Why did I put up with black?
Don’t have to check it right here.
I need to check here because I sleep right here.
Wat, I bought you…
Is this Sarawat’s brother?
You look hot like your brother.
Can you please get lost for an hour or two?
If you take my brother with you, I’ll ask the seniors to play a Scrubb’s song.