I’m refurnishing my room.
Good.
Your room is like a haunted house.
Wat! Wake up!
Why did you sleep naked?
I didn’t wear anything?
So you saw everything in Sarawat Expo?
Your girlfriend said it?
Your University will have an Open House tomorrow
Take Phukong with you so he can observe the Faculty he likes
If you listen to Scrubb’s songs when you are happy, you will be even happier
If you listen when you are in love, you will be more deeply in love.
I get it now.
My seniors’ band will perform at Faculty of Accountancy next week.
They are playing Scrubb songs.
You can take Pear to see
I’ll think about it.
Why?
I don’t know.
I like it better when you play guitar
It sounds perfect for Scrubb songs.
I’m not so sure about other bands.
But…
I won’t ask you to play Scrubb songs for Pear again
I feel bad
Asking you to fake flirting with me bothers you enough already
It’s good that you know
I’ll just see you off here
I need to help them clean up
See you later.
Who is that?
A kid from Music Club maybe
Why?
Sarawat won’t take his eyes off you, Tine.
Are you guys a thing?
Is that for me?
Of course not.
I am just scratching my cheek
I have a homework for you.
Last time, you guys recorded a video individually
This time, you will record and turn in the video in pair
If you got your mate already, inform Air
and go home.
Tine.
Who said we would pair up?
We are both beginners.
We will go down in flames.
I’m going to ask Pear.
She is a beginner too.
She is not even here today
Plus, she must have a partner already
What should we do?
Hurry up!
I want to go home
Have you paired up with anyone?
No.
Pair with me then
No need to ask. I have been waiting for you here
Hi guys. I am Tine, Mr. Chic
The person next to me is…
Tine’s boyfriend.
Hi guys. I am Tine, Mr. Chic
The person next to me is…
Tine’s HUSBAND!
I’ll smack your freaking head!
Can you be serious here?
I am being serious.
Hi guys. I am Tine, Mr. Chic.
The person next to me is Sarawat.
What song are we playing today?
I lost the chords.
That’s right! We are playing I Lost the Chords
Can you stop playing?
Playing what?
I seriously can’t find the chord sheet
I just gave it to you
It’s here.
♪ I never thought I would have such a great day with you by my side like this ♫
♪ I instantly felt it the second we first met ♫
♪ It’s like there was something ♫
Shit!
My nails are too short
I can’t play.
Can I borrow that thing?
It’s called a pick
And I have only one.
Just put up with it a little longer.
Stingy much?
Give it here
What do you think you’re doing?
Hey!!
Tine!!
What the heck did you just do?
Who taught you that a pick could be cut in half?
Here.
Now we have two
You think this is funny?
One pick per person!
We can’t share it. It can’t be used anymore.
Oh what?
I didn’t know
Then…
Let’s call it a day.
We will record again another time
My Faculty football team is playing.
Cheerleaders must be there.
They are playing today?
That means your Faculty plays against mine.
Cheer for me
Are you crazy?
I have to be on the Law side
What is with you?
I helped flirt with you to get rid of Green and just now you cut my pick in half
You can’t do this little thing for me?
Come on. You can’t seriously be upset
Fine.
I will be on the Law side
but cheer for you inside. Okay?
Fine.
It’s good enough knowing that you’re there
You mean on my Faculty side?
No.
In my heart
I will be going now.
See you soon, nuisance.
What?
Are we so close that he can pat my head?
Oops!
5 6 7 8.
Sarawat!
You came to the wrong side.
It’s for Law team here.
I am thirsty.
Thirsty?
Tell the staff on your side.
Who did the makeup for you?
You’re performing Chinese opera or what?
It’s the way cheerleaders do.
If you don’t like it, tell the makeup artist
If you don’t like it, tell the makeup artist.
Hold this.
Bye.
What about your jersey?
Wash it for me
Tine!
What’s up?
Bad news.
What?
Hey! That’s the cheerleaders.
It’s Fong.
What’s wrong with Fong?
Come here.
She dumped me.
I saw her with some yellow-haired, motorbike dude.
They might be just friends
She tried on a freaking wedding gown.
calm down
I don’t want to calm down
I’ll kick his fu*king ass.
In this condition, he will kick your ass first.
Ohm, go get his shoe
Don’t stop me.
Do you want a problem?
[L Co Hol]
What a small world!
My name is Man. People call me Man-Oh-Hum
Oh Ho!
I don’t know how it became Oh Hum
And this is…
Boss,
a warm guy with a sexy body
And that is…
You all know his name.
Sarawat.
If you want to know more about him, you can ask Tine
What the heck!
This is Fong, Phuak, and Ohm
Fong is going through a heartbreak
so we brought him here to console him.
A broken heart is no problem at all compared to a lover with small boobs
Don’t get yourself attached to just one person
Right, Mr. Sarawat?
It’s my business.
Great talk, Man.
To Man!
Cheers!
Cheer.
That was an awesome speech, Man.
Cheers!
I am Tine
Man is right there
and he hasn’t said anything for a while now
Tine.
What?
Are you drunk?
Can I touch your boobs?
What!?!
Are you crazy?
What a pervert!
Be careful.
Fong!
Hold it until you get home
You can’t pee there.
Do it here!
Your car is parked over there. This is not yours
I’ll drive.
Tine!
Give it here.
Tine.
Big boobbies!
Am I in the car?
Let me get you home
- Let's get them home.
- That's Tine.
Where are we?
Your dorm
Fong.
We are here.
Motherfu*ker!
Do you want to have a problem?
That’s Tine.
Fong!
Come get your friend
Let me help.
Let me go.
- I'll kick his ass.
- That's Tine.
Calm down
Let me go. I'm not drunk.
Are you all right?
Hell no
I’m completely sober because of Fong’s foot
Are you all right?
Wat, are you coming?
I will look after Tine.
Take care of Boss
See yah!
See you.
Aren’t you going?
I am walking a nuisance to his room
You don’t have to.
My room is just here.
I can walk myself there
I left my car at the bar
I can’t go home.
Then hurry up and catch up with your friends
They left just now.
Call them.
The battery just died.
Let me see.
The battery died
Let me crash here tonight
Here?
Let me sleep in your room tonight
What kind of person do you like?
Do you like the weird one?
If I hear that you hit on her once, I’ll grab your boobs once