Why are you checking it so closely?
Is that Sarawat?
No.
You’re mistaken.
He is.
Sara…
Pear, look.
This case is so beautiful.
Touch it.
What?
It’s so beautiful.
Look.
Aren’t they all the same?
No.
Never mind.
Tine, thank you for helping me choose the guitar and waiting for my mom with me
It’s my pleasure.
Thank you
Should we do some other heavenly thing together?
I just realized I got something to do
If you want to go home, you can
See you later.
Sir, this seat is already taken.
I think he already left.
Left?
Yes.
Someone dropped this.
I think it belongs to him.
Thank you.
Here you are.
Looking for me?
I just want to see if Law cheerleaders can beat Political Science cheerleaders
Who are you looking for?
Wat can’t be here. He has guitar practice
Who told you I was looking for him?
I’m looking for my friends
Since we are here, let’s take a photo and capture the moment.
Your skin is so bright.
Send it to me.
Okay.
Good luck and see you.
I hope you’re qualified.
Your friends said you had guitar practice.
I bailed on it
How did you know that I’m here?
[Here to see U Cheerleader qualification. Law is the best]
I knew it
A bunch of girls here but they wanted to take a photo with me
Those guys were just messing with me.
Messing with you or with me exactly?
What do you mean?
Forget it.
Why don’t you clean your face?
I want to but the makeup is waterproof.
It won’t come out.
You go around with a makeup remover in your bag?
It is for you.
Can you be gentle? You’re plucking my eyebrows.
Did you hit on anyone when I wasn’t around?
No.
Of course not.
Who would I hit on?
The names of our University Cheerleaders are out!
Tine, you are enlisted.
I am?
Yep!
I am tired. I don’t want to practice for the U Cheerleader.
Isn’t it good?
You will get to wear makeup more often
Sarcastic much?
Give me the remover.
I can use it next time
No. It’s mine.
Why are you being stingy?
You’re such a hog.
I’ll clean the makeup for you after every show, all right
Now stop complaining.
You’re annoying.
Face up.
Turn this way.
Done.
A thank you would be nice.
THANK YOU!
My hubby, Sarawat.
Your wifey has brought you snacks.
What possessed you? Why did you bring me snacks?
And when did I become your husband?
I brought you snacks to say sorry.
Sorry that I teased you before.
Teased me what?
I think I just found the one.
Now I know how it feels to meet the person we like
But I don’t know who he is or where he lives
I don’t even know his name
I don’t know if I ever get to see him again
What do you think I should do?
Should I give up?
If you really are my best friend, you know the answer
Give me my snacks.
[Club Rooms]
Thank you for helping me with the guitar and for making the video with me.
If my friend was available, I wouldn’t have to bother you this much.
Don’t mention it.
It’s my pleasure to help you, Pear.
Is there anything going on between you and Sarawat?
Are you crazy?
What does he mean by this message?
[Time for revenge. I am gonna post all the pics in his phone.]