[Political Science VS Engineering]
Nervous?
Have you prepared to lose?
Who in here is nervous?
People here are happy for my friend because he’s about to be taken
Let me tell you something.
My friend doesn’t even need to come watch.
You guys will lose no matter what.
Right?
Are you dreaming?
My friend will give everything. Losing is not in his dictionary.
Just watch.
We will watch every action
He is looking fiercely.
[Super Bright]
Whose jersey are you wearing?
Are you taking the game seriously?
I’ve been listening for quite some time
I don’t want to brag
I have eight-year training at Old Trafford
How can you still calm?
Or are you preparing yourself for the defeat?
Sure.
Of course
Goal!
Engineering holds a one-nil lead.
That goal was brilliant.
Engineering has the ball again.
Will Political Science stand a chance?
Super Bright!
Hey! Why are you here?
Why aren’t you studying with Wan?
Tine!
What is happening?
This last minute, Super Bright got the ball inside the penalty area
Will he make it?
Sarawat goals!
That was brilliant.
Foul!
The referee calls a foul.
Political Science didn’t score.
That goal doesn’t count.
It was a hard tackle there.
Engineering player was injured.
And that is the time.
Engineering, the former champion beats Political Science one-nil
They are to defend their title again
If you guys win, my friend will post a love confession to your friend
If you lose, Sarawat will have to leave my friend alone
Deal?
Political science will have to fight for the second runner up title with Architecture
Great job!
Great job, referee.
What a pleasant result!
Your plan to come and distract him last minute was awesome.
He can't bother you anymore.
We need to celebrate.
I already booked a table for us.
You guys go ahead.
I’ll catch up with you later
Why?
Are you…
going to change first?
That’s great.
It’s a jersey of a loser
Hurry up and meet us at the bar
Hey!
If you lose, you need to leave me alone.
It doesn’t mean I need to leave you alone
Whenever I’m down, Scrubb songs are my therapy
Just listen.
♪ Look up to the sky of a new day with a blank mind ♫
♪ Forget about bad days ♫
♪ Sad days that passed ♫
♪ We take on a journey ♫
♪ We’ve been through things together ♫
♪ Sometimes we make mistakes ♫
♪ When I feel discouraged, you are here comforting me ♫
♪ I know ♫
♪ I can give you anything ♫
♪ As long as I have you on this journey ♫
♪ No matter how long ♫
♪ I am right here ♫
♪ But there is more ♫
♪ More good things are coming our way ♫
♪ And it’s not just that ♫
♪ I want you to be sure ♫
♪ More good things are coming our way ♫
♪ And it’s not just that ♫
♪ I want you to be sure ♫
♪ Today you have me ♫
♪ I don’t care about anybody else ♫
♪ Please know that ♫
♪ There will be just the two of us ♫
When is your next match?
Why are you asking?
You can’t come cheering anyway.
I watched the playback.
That was not a foul.
The referee made a mistake.
Let’s not count this match.
You still have one more game to fight.
Super Bright?
Whose jersey are you wearing?
Teammates challenged me to screen physical appearance of the one I like.
The one with super bright skin is not me.
It’s you.
Little buffalo.
Why don’t you just call me an albino buffalo then?
I’m gonna go now.
Albino buffalo!
Where are you going?
Thank you.
Wait!
It’s mine.
You’re still sick.
You are so mean.
I have to go.
I will give a comment on your work tomorrow
Damn it!
What is wrong now?
I’m dizzy
I’m about to faint.
I think you need to drive me home
I don’t think I can drive
It’s your car. You drive.
I can’t, seriously.
You must do it.
I think I’m gonna pass out.
Fine.
You are such a baby.
Give me your car key.
Thanks a lot.
What?
I forgot my headphones
I think I left them on the football field.
I’m gonna go back and get them.
Okie Dokie!
Dickhead!
You said you felt dizzy.
How about you drive yourself home?
Here.
Nope!
I got a headache
Asshole.
I’ll be right back.
Headache. Headache.
Hey!
Was it you who messed with my friend?
What the f*ck are you guys doing?
Watch it!
Directed by Weerachit Thongjila
Why is Sarawat, a Political Science star player sitting on a bench?
Is he injured?
Do you think he was one of the Architecture students that hurt you yesterday?
What happened to your hand?
I don’t mind fighting.
Just feel pity for those who backbite.
I’m so on for a real fight.
I can’t let you go up on stage like this
Will my show be good enough to substitute Control S?
Since you gave me this guitar, I haven’t named it yet.
Stay with me tonight.
Sure.