I think we should split up here.
I’m going to the bathroom and then head back
See you.
Bye.
Hey!
Wat!
What happened to you?
Damn!
Can you get up?
It hurts.
Just hang in there.
Who did this to you?
The same group.
Just because their girlfriends liked my IG posts.
What a stupid reason!
Hey!
You got beaten up before?
Why haven’t you told me?
Screw it.
I didn’t want you to worry
Who is worried about you?
I’m just afraid you will die young. That’s all.
From now on, you have to tell me when you have a problem
Do you get it?
Got it.
Face up.
You can stop.
It’s not that bad
It’s way better like this
The pain is gone
What’s with you?
Hey!
What did you just do?
You just healed me.
You are such a pervert.
Now I don’t mind getting beaten up more often.
What if I get ambushed on the way back?
Can you sleepover at my place tonight?
Take me home
How old are you, three?
You get scared too easily.
I don’t have anything with me.
How can I crash at your place?
I’ve prepared everything you need
You can even use my toothbrush. I don’t mind.
But I do.
I will be off now
What?
Go with me.
I said I didn’t have my stuff with me.
I said use mine. I don’t care.
But I do!
Don't forget to use a cold pack
Yes.
Let’s go.
Go to my room.
I go back to my room. You go back to your room
I go back to my room. You go back to my room
You go back to your room. I go back to my room.
Come on
Hey!
What?
Do you still have my football jersey?
Yes.
I will give it back before the game starts
I don’t want you to return it to me.
I have another one
But can you wear my jersey
And come cheer for me when I play?
If you come wearing that jersey and football shorts
It will give me the ultimate power to beat Engineering.
Why do I need to wear your jersey?
Should we go back now?
Let’s go.
Would you have mercy for an injured guy here?
And you forgot your tissue.
Man!
You pretended to be me to chat with someone?
Yes.
He talked and agreed to meet up.
All these because of your beauty.
Thanks but you need to delete my photo now!
Come on
I’m confessing my crime here because I need your help
Can you go meet him for me?
No way.
You dream about it.
No.
Please.
Just once.
No.
Take my picture out.
Please.
No.
Up to you then.
I thought I would give you Ed Sheeran concert ticket if you said yes.
I know you love him
The tickets are already sold out now.
What ticket again?
Ed Sheeran
Are you Earn?
Yes.
Please have a seat P’Tan.
I am Type
Sorry
My tongue twisted.
Please have a seat P’Type.
Thank you so much for helping with my report
No problem.
Which subject is this report for again?
Introduction to Economics.
That’s why I need some thoughts from someone who attends so many business seminars
Before we start, let me record this interview.
Sure.
Economics.
Why do you need this note?
It’s…
What are you playing?
I knew it.
I knew it was weird
We greeted and you suddenly asked to meet.
What do you really want from me?
It’s not what you think.
You’re misunderstanding
It’s…
What?
Never mind.
I don’t want to know.
But don’t ever do this to me again.
Otherwise, I will call the police.
Got it?
Got it.
What do you think I should do?
Should I give up?
What a shame! Man
You’ve come this far.
Why didn’t you return it yourself?
Excuse me.
Is this your pen?
You must have dropped it.
It’s easier said than done
If he knew the truth, he might hate me.
It might be better to not knowing each other and let things carry on like this
Man.
Don’t forget my concert ticket
Can you wear my jersey…
and come cheer for me when I play?
If you come wearing that jersey and football shorts,
It will give me the ultimate power to beat Engineering
Something just comes up with family.
I don’t think I can study with you guys
You all can still use my place to study with Wan.
I will leave the key at the lobby.
You can’t!
We chose your place just for you to spend special time with Wan
We are all at the football field.
What?
We don’t want to bother you.
Go get your prey, Tiger.
Have fun
When is the next game?
Why are you asking?
You can’t come cheering anyway
Hey!
Was it you who just messed with my friend?