Really?
Open it.
P’Dim!
Are you Green’s boyfriend?
Ex-boyfriend.
When did we break up, Green?
On that day.
We broke up for 2 minutes and then made love in bed
Is this what you call a breakup?
Why do you think I brought Green who can’t play any musical instrument into Music Club?
Of course, I needed to keep an eye on him.
I just didn’t think that his new lover is in the club too.
It’s not that.
You’re misunderstanding.
Step aside if you don’t want to get hurt
No.
You might be his boyfriend, but you have no right to hurt him.
I said step aside!
Green, I am sorry.
I am sorry I hurt you
I know how you feel now.
It hurts me so bad to see you with someone else.
Aren’t you here to yell at me?
No.
I came to apologize
and tell him something.
If you hurt Green, prepare to get hurt even more
P’Dim.
Let me see.
Does it hurt?
It did
but the pain is gone now
Will you forgive me?
I can never be angry with you.
Come on. Let’s go home
Tine.
I am sorry.
I won’t be bothering you again.
I hope you and Sarawat are together forever.
Let’s go home.
Someone dropped this.
I think it is his
People normally come here to escape from heartbreaks or unfortunate situations
Thank you.
Excuse me
Have you seen the guy sleeping next to me last night?
He went home.
How can I help?
Can I have his number, please?
I can’t give you that. It’s personal information
Go back to your meditation, please
Please. At least tell me his name.
I really can’t
Please, pretty lady.
The young man who went home forget to take his phone
I’ll just leave it here.
I will call someone to pick it up later
Sarawat.
Yesterday, Green was…
Good timing.
Try this.
What are you playing now?
What kind of person do you think I am?
This is good and I want to share it with you.
Hasn’t it ever occurred to you…
that when you see something nice, you want to share it with me?
No?
I don’t know
What kind of question is this?
Do you want to try?
Try to get to know each other.
You don’t have to like me very much.
Just keep your heart open for me.
CUT!
Was it good?
Did you just practice your lines with me?
Do you think I just confessed my love to you?
What a relief!
Sorry.
My class finished later than expected.
Did they start with the makeup yet?
No one is here yet.
That’s great.
Sarawat, have you seen the new playlist?
Well.
How about we play Desktop Error song?
It’s really difficult.
I am trying to transcribe it.
The Connect is also interesting.
See? I included their songs here.
I know you so well, don’t I?
Are you guys trying to pick a song?
Let me help you.
You don’t know any bands besides Scrubb
Stay out of it.
I just heard this song the other day
It is super awesome.
Just listen.
If it’s great, we can include this one instead
Right!
I heard it and thought of you
Hey!
It’s good.
I am gonna go get us some drinks.
It’s awesome.
Include it on the list.
It’s a good choice.
That’s why I want you to hear it.
I liked it the first time I heard.
it’s cool.
Earn, let’s go get changed
Do you want to try?
Try to get to know each other.
- You don’t have to like me very much
- I…
Just keep your heart open for me
Sarawat just posted a picture.
I don’t give a sh*t!
Tine.
Just tell me what is wrong