Looking for me?
Hey!
How can you still stand?
Didn’t you break your leg?
I just got a little scrape from a wrong tackle
When did I break my leg?
Man posted on his IG that your leg is broken
Man was just being Man. You believe him?
It’s good you’re here though.
So I don’t need to do it myself.
Why would I?
Do it yourself.
My energy ran out.
Bandage me, please.
Tine, be gentle.
Why are your hands shaking so much?
I…
I am afraid of blood.
I guess I am too
Because I am all shaking here.
I meant my heart
Uh…
I got some work to do.
I will be off now
Hey!! We won!
I told you
8 years in practice at Old Trafford
You’re here too?
That’s great. We are celebrating.
Come with us.
Uh…
Come on. Come with us!
Your friends are coming too
Especially Phuak
He said he had stories to tell
Let’s go.
To Political Science victory!
Cheers!
To 10 points for our presentation!
To the parking spot that we fought for this morning!
Cheers!
Bottoms up.
See? I drink it all.
Drink up, Tine.
Why do you guys keep celebrating?
It’s like you’re trying to get me drunk.
And why are you avoiding my eye contact?
Don’t tell me that you want them to get me drunk
Huh?
He was just playing.
You’re overthinking it
I am envious
You have someone so cute to play with.
What about the one you met at the seminar?
Go play with him.
I don’t even know what his name is
It’s no problem. Just look for him then.
Go to every freaking seminar.
Right, inspector?
Copy that, sergeant!
You guys talk too much.
To us for being lucky enough to get this table!
Cheers!
Enough already.
Where are all my friends?
Why did they leave me to get drunk alone?
To your friends that are missing!
Cheers!
My beloved friend, Tine.
To the Line ID I got from a hot girl there!
Cheers!
Great!
How was your night?
They got me so drunk I passed out.
Which one of you got me home last night?
Don’t tell me you still haven’t seen it on your IG
- IG?
- Yes.
Where is your room key?
What are you trying to grab?
Stay still.
It was fun though
- Do it one more time
- No.
Hey! What are you doing?
I’m taking them off so you will be comfortable
Take them all off.
[tine_chic : I am reserved.]
SARALEO!!
Between Green and Sarawat, I can’t even tell who is more dangerous at this point.
I’d say Sarawat.
He found a way to your room
I won’t be surprised if you become his one day
By the way, Green is not bothering you anymore
When will you tell Sarawat to stop with this fake flirting thing?
Right.
Right
A hundred drawings as promised.
It’s your turn to keep your promise.
He has done a great job
If you say no,
you’re a loser
Sure.
I will be your tutor.
Are you happy?
Tine.
Green.
Why are you here?
I know everything
You asked Sarawat to fake flirting with you.
No.
What are you talking about?
Why did you lie to me?
I heard you and your friends talking in the bathroom
I know it was all your plan
Why did you have to be so harsh?
I didn’t mean to be harsh.
But…
I just…
Tine, I know that I’m not good enough for you.
But please…
Give me one more chance
Who said I flirted with him just to get rid of you?
I did everything
because I genuinely like Tine.
I don’t believe you.
I know that everything is just a plan.
It was a plan at first
But then I realized…
I really like Tine
I will never believe that
You don’t?
Do you want us to kiss and prove?
This song is for someone so silly who didn’t get to hear it when I played the first time.
Do you want to grab something to eat?
You want to eat with me. It’s weird.