You don’t believe me?
Do you want us to kiss and prove?
That’s enough.
That’s enough
Fine. I believe you.
I believe that Sarawat really likes Tine
That was close
How did you know he was coming?
He’s been following you since you’re in the University
I knew something was happening
If green didn’t stop you, would you really kiss me?
Do you really think I would kiss you?
I said it because I knew Green couldn’t take it.
Who would kiss you?
Drink up.
This meal, my treat.
What’s got into you?
I am just bored.
And I haven’t sat down and eaten with all of you for quite some time
Come on. Drink while they’re still cold.
Since we are all here…
I have…
You have something to ask
How did you know?
Whenever you said it’s your treat, you always need help
What is your problem this time?
The thing is…
I have a friend from Music Club
He is worried and wondering if his friend…
Let’s do this.
Let’s call that guy ‘A.’
He is wondering if A likes me…
No!!
He is wondering if A likes him. I meant my friend.
So…
Who is this guy A anyway?
I can hack into his Facebook account.
Let’s not go to that.
How about this?
Get him drunk
I am sure he will confess everything
That method works only for you.
I must be out of my mind asking you guys
I know a way.
Make him jealous.
Why?
No matter how good people are at keeping it inside
jealousy always shows when they see someone else approaching the ones they like
If your friend wants to know if A likes him, try to make A jealous
I’m here because I want to get better at time management
Sawasdee Krub.
I don’t think you need to know my name
I am here just to look for someone.
But it doesn’t seem like…
he is here.
So I’m just gonna go.
Thank you very much.
Don’t give up just yet
There are plenty of seminars for you to look
He must be at one of them.
Do you want to hear the event list that I went to?
I went to all academic seminars,
both direct and indirect sales meetings, online marketing classes
and leadership camps.
Only Dharma camp that I haven’t been to
That is old people community
Your darling won’t be there
Dang it! He’s here.
I gotta go
Sir, may I see your pass, please?
It is with my friend. The one that just went in there
I’ll go get it for you.
Can you call him to bring it out instead?
Look!
Sir, you can’t get in.
Please wait outside.
He was just right there.
Wait outside, please.
Wat!
Are you done practicing?
Do you want to grab something to eat?
What’s wrong?
You got plan already?
No.
You just asked me to eat with you. It’s weird.
Don’t think too much.
Sarawat, my dear friend.
Go out and have a drink with me tonight
Please.
OK.
My band is playing at L Co Hol tonight
It’s like a big rehearsal for the opening act for Scrubb this Saturday
Meet me there.
We are playing Scrubb songs. You will love it
OK
See you at L Co Hol
L Co Hol! See you there.
What’s wrong with him?
And why am I taking a detour?
It’s really you
Do you remember me?
You found my friend’s pen at the seminar last week.
That’s right.
He is here too. He sat beside me.
He even invited me to an event but I’m not sure I can make it
What kind of event? Can I join?
Here. He left me a brochure
Meditation retreat for 2 nights?
Exactly! It’s perfect for someone like you
Perfect for someone like me?
A meditation retreat?
Thank you.
So when a guy named Sarawat walks in, I need to act like your girlfriend and make him jealous?
That’s correct.
If you did great, I’ll reward you with extra tips, Nancy
Let’s practice then
Practice?
Babe, where should we go after this?
Hey!!
This is too much.
- Too much?
- Make it less obvious.
Do it naturally.
How about this?
Hi baby. Do you want some snack?
Sarawat is here.
Aww!! He is so hot!
Nuisance, have you been waiting for long?
Not long but I’m leaving.
I have something else to do
Sit!
Sit right here.
I will pay.
Watch me play first.
Wait here.
Nan…
Thanks for absolutely nothing
Hi guys.
We’ve prepared a special song for you tonight.
One of our members requested it actually.
He even wants to sing it himself.
Give our guitarist a big hand, guys!
This song…
is for someone so silly who didn’t get to hear it when I played the first time
This song is called Everything.
♪ I will do everything ♫
♪ I will try every possible way ♫
♪ I know how it is going to be ♫
♪ It doesn’t matter who you like ♫
♪ Just look at me ♫
♪ That’s it ♫
♪ That’s all it takes to make me happy ♫
♪ I don’t care who you like ♫
♪ It doesn’t matter what the reality is ♫
♪ All I know is that you are the one in my heart ♫
Tine, I want to take a picture with Sarawat.
Can you ask him for me?
Please.
Ask him yourself.
Why are you upset?
Are you his boyfriend or something?
No matter how good people are at keeping it inside
jealousy always shows when they see someone else approaching the ones they like.
I am sorry.
It’s OK, Tine
You know my name?
A University cheerleader. Of course, I do
Ah! That’s right.
Sorry again about that.
Wait up.
I won’t get mad for bumping me if I get just one selfie with you
Thanks.
What the heck is wrong with you?
Why did you take a photo with him?
It’s none of your business.
I didn’t say anything when those girls handed you drinks and hugged you
I didn’t touch their drinks and hug anyone.
Think twice of what you saw.
Yeah?
Tine! What is your problem exactly?
Let go of me
I won’t!
Unless you tell me.
I am jealous, all right.
You happy now?
I drank a little too much last night.
I watched you play and…
We’ve come to the end of the show.
This song is for everyone here