Do you still have a stomachache?
Yeah.
I feel a bit queasy inside.
I want to throw up, but I can’t
How about you take some rest today?
You didn’t get enough sleep last night
How did you know?
I know you listened to music all night.
Do you want to eat anything?
How about congee?
No.
I am OK.
Just go take a shower. You’re late
I can skip one day to take care of you.
It’s just a flatulence, not an appendicitis.
Just go.
But I’m worried.
I am OK.
You can go.
Are you sure?
Yes.
So my friend needs to watch out for his boyfriend’s first love, right?
His first love came back and took back what was hers?
Well, not really.
Just tell your friend to ask his boyfriend frankly.
If he asks and it turns out to be nothing, then my friend is a fool.
But if he keeps it inside, his brain will explode.
If someone doesn’t love us anymore, that person will leave whether we ask the question or not.
Why are you calling me?
Why did you come back early?
I ditched the rehearsal
I am worried about you.
I bought you a congee.
Don’t worry about the band. They are all OK.
What is it?
Is Pam your first love?
Do you think someone who has never been in love can write a love song?
Are you writing a love song?
I am so excited.
I want to hear the song you wrote for me.