Is Tine here?
What are you doing here?
Can I…
Can I have my guitar back?
Sorry.
I didn’t mean to keep it.
I was going to return it to you.
That’s OK.
I’m just borrowing it for the contest.
You will get it back.
Come and support me.
I…
I will wait for you.
Well well.
It doesn’t seem like an end for you two.
The food is here.
Finally.
I’m so hungry I could eat a horse.
It has your name on it.
I didn’t order crispy pork with Chinese broccoli.
I just don’t want to owe you anything.
Did I ever say you owe me anything?
Did you challenge my brother that
if you win, you will take P’Tine out?
Yeah.
What if you lose?
If I lose,
what do you want me to do?
Tine, I think
you should give Sarawat one more chance.
He must be really remorseful.
But I don’t think you should go.
Once a glass is broken, it’ll never be the same.
Nothing in this whole world can stay the same.
Even if you leave the glass untouched, it can get old.
Stop arguing.
He has decided not to go.
We better go.
Is this a music contest or a beauty contest?
Do you have to look like an idol?
Well, I want to be a net idol too.
In case my band wins,
I must look hot when we receive the winner cup.
Good idea.
Can I borrow your beauty item?
I want to look good too.
The door is here.
Sawasdee Krub.
Wat, how are you?
We are the last to perform.
Wait for me.
Don’t worry.
Go kill it, man.
I brought my boyfriend to see too.
And Tine?
Is he coming?
Should I call him?
No.
He will come.
Don’t you know where he is?
You’re the one in relationship with him.
Just listen to it and you will know.
I don’t know if you are listening.
I want you to know this.