Can I grab your boobs?
Are you insane?
Go take a shower.
Can I borrow this?
Last time, you recorded a video individually
This time you will pair up
Have you paired up with anyone?
No.
Pair with me then?
No need to ask. I have been waiting for you here
You go around with a makeup remover in your bag?
It is for you.
What kind of person do you like? That was almost every kind
Do you like the weird one?
Is there anything going on between you and Sarawat?
Promise me that you will not cheat on me or talk to anyone when I’m not around
Cheat on?
We are not dating
I will seriously be hitting on Pear.
Did you hear what I said?
I said I will seriously hit on Pear
You will hit on her
So I’m just your secret lover?
Wait!
Should I act heartbroken?
Should I cry?
Hey!
What is wrong with you?
I just want to have a girlfriend. Why are you…
You are reserved.
Don’t ever hit on anyone
Hey!
Wat!
Sarawat!
Saraleo!! What did you just do?
Get up and talk to me.
Let go of my hand.
Tine!
Tine! Are you dead in there?
Tine
What are you up to?
Why haven’t you taken a shower yet?
Come on. I am hungry.
Hey!
A new wallet?
I haven’t seen you used this one
That’s my brother’s!
He didn’t just forget his wallet.
He forgot his phone too
That also belongs to my brother
Hold on.
He uses your picture as his lock screen wallpaper
Of course
It’s normal. We are brothers
It’s not normal because it’s a picture of you and Sarawat.
It’s…
Enough already
I know Sarawat slept here last night
‘I didn’t want to wake you.’
‘I am off for music practice.’
He left a note for you.
So you guys moved in together already?
Are you crazy?
He came to record a video for Music Club.
By the time we’re done recording, it was really late.
So, I let him crash here.
But he was gone when I woke up.
And have you asked him how he feels for you yet?
You are reserved.
Don’t ever hit on anyone
Uh…
I have.
He said he was just messing with Green’s head.
He was playing.
It’s nothing, guys.
It’s late. Let me go take a shower.
Quickly.
I am hungry.
Tine, what’s wrong?
You seem really distracted today
I am sorry.
We can leave it here for today
Don’t forget to practice at home.
These are yours.
You forgot them
Thanks.
You’re welcome
I’m gonna go now.
Tine.
Tine!
Why are you mad?
Don’t you think I should be mad at what you did to me?
I am sorry.
I was in a rush this morning.
I didn’t wait until you woke up
I am not talking about this morning
I am talking about last night.
Last night?
Don’t you remember what you did to me at all?
I did something to you?
What?
I was drunk last night.
We recorded a video in your room
And then…
Then you…
Forget it.
I’m gonna go now
Wait!
I’m not done talking to you
I have a football match this Saturday
Come and cheer for me.
I don’t think so
University cheerleaders are not assigned for this match
Screw U-cheerleaders.
I just want you to cheer for me
Fine.
I’ll think about it
I actually have to help Phuak with his food review page
I will be off now.
Any of you who wants to attend an intensive course for Faculty of Architecture
register right here with me, P’Chat, your handsome tutor.
Can I ask you something?
P’Mil, a senior who played guitar at the Open House, will he be a tutor too?
And does he have a girlfriend?
Am I his type?
They are all here because of you.
Why don’t you tutor them?
I am sure our Faculty welcomes the biggest number of freshmen this year
Really?
Yes.
I am sorry, guys.
I dedicate my time for music practice
I am afraid I won’t have enough time to take care of you guys.
I don’t think I can tutor you
How about just one student?
Are you here for the Open House?
What Faculty are you enrolling in?
I don’t know yet
Yeah?
Let me give you advice.
Enroll for any Faculty but Architecture
The workload is crazy.
I told you Architecture is not easy
That’s why I need a great tutor…
…like you.
But I don’t need a troll student like you
See you.
Wait!
Register first.
Mil will be back.
Hand it to your friends too.
Hi guys. I am admin Phuak from page ‘Gross But Cheap So We Gotta Eat.’
I am taking you to a hot pot restaurant near University
It’s cheap but the taste is horrible.
Fits for our concept
Damn it! Phuak!
Did you have to say ‘horrible’ so loud?
They will kick us out.
[Sarawat: The game is about to start. Where are you?]
Tine, taste it and review
What kind of soup is this? It burns my throat.
Of course it does.
They put Thai herbal liquor in it. It’s a special recipe.
Prepare to get drunk.
Guys can’t take girlfriends here then.
Why not?
People always speak the truth when drunk
If you’re hiding secrets from your girlfriend
you will spill it all out after having this soup
Come on. Drink up.
It’s really great.
Cheers!
Drink it all.
Drink up.
Is it true…
that when people are drunk, they speak the truth?
Of course not.
Ohm was just saying
There is something I’ve always wanted to tell you though
What?
Do you remember your phone with a cracked screen?
You didn’t sit on it. Ohm dropped it and blamed it on you.
Shut the front door, Phuak!!
Don’t listen to him. He’s drunk.
I am not. I remember all of it.
As for Fong,
he used your Facebook account to register a porn website.
It’s OK guys.
Let’s have more soup.
Cheers!
Come on.
Is this the end of the world?
My husband shows up here and helps out
I have to.
My car broke down.
I need some money to fix it
Be a tutor and make some money then
I heard that many girls wanted to be your students
Little girls have nothing on a real deal like you, Jae Tun.
What a sweet talker!
I can’t raise the wage for you though
If you want more money, do the OT in my room
Here.
What is this?
P’Chat told me to draw Kon (person), Rod (car, watering) and Ton Mai (tree)
I’ve finished it and I want to hear your opinion.
If I give you a comment, will you leave me alone?
You’ll never know.
Once you see my drawing, you might want to be my tutor.
Here it is.
A person watering a tree.
Can you just go and be a troll somewhere else?
I am your customer.
You can’t shoo me away.
I’ll report this to Jae Tun
Jae…
What do you want? Just order
Quickly.
Honey toast
100 honey toasts
You order for the whole freaking universe?
I’m not doing it.
Jae Tun…
What do you want?
If you agree to be my tutor, I will be a good boy
I will stop bugging you.
Fine.
Draw a person, a car, and a tree and hand them in to me tomorrow morning.
I’ll be your tutor then.
You don’t need to wait till tomorrow
I can finish it right now.
100 drawings altogether
If you can’t do it, get out of my sight completely
Go now.
You’re running out of time.
Let’s go to the next restaurant
I’m not going
What is happening?
[Man: RIP Sarawat’s knee.]
Bandage me, please.
Why are you shaking so much?
Don’t tell me you still haven’t seen it on your IG