Wait!
I have something to talk to you.
But I don’t
If you are in the same club he is in, you will see him more often
Before you become our club members
you need to go through our special welcoming ceremony
Did Sarawat agree to help you or not?
Don’t worry. It’s easy to see him now.
I will ask him for his help
Okay.
Okay what?
Okay. I will be your fake boyfriend.
He is taken
So you will help me?
Cheers!
Tine, what did you do to make Sarawat help you?
You gave him some kind of special service?
You are gross!
I have no idea.
He changed his mind all of a sudden.
He might think being flirtatious in front of Green is not going to ruin his reputation.
It’s not like he has to flirt in front of his fans.
I guess so.
I need you guys to help me with something
Sarawat will be at his Faculty tomorrow morning.
You guys need to tell Green that I will be there
Tine!
Your friends told me someone’s been hitting on you. Is that true?
True.
Sarawat.
A guitar is for you to play…
…but I am for you to love
You can compete for anything with anyone
but you can’t beat Sarawat when it comes to love.
No!!!
That’s not true.
There?
There where?
In front of his Faculty.
Where exactly?
In front of his Faculty building where there is a parking lot.
Then there is a road
When you cross it, you’ll see his Faculty building.
Ah!! The parking lot.
Right.
Isn’t that at the back though?
I will share you guys the exact location
Can you do it now?
I want to see where
Damn it!!
You pieces of dumb shit!
5 4 3 2 1…
Tine!
Good morning…
Where is Tine?
He is where his heart belongs.
Wait!
You said the same thing at the same time?
Is this some kind of a plan?
It’s not a plan!
Really!
So where is Tine?
Tine!
Your friends told me someone has been hitting on you. Is that true?
You can see for yourself.
Sarawat.
Hey!
Tine…
Are you trying to make me jealous?
God! You are such a cutie.
Don’t worry
I won’t be jealous because I know you belong to mine
Come on. Let’s go.
Sorry.
I didn’t know you wanted me to start being flirtatious already.
I didn’t pay attention
Because of you, Green was stalking me for almost an hour
It was hard to sneak away.
So what do you need me to do?
You just don’t know anything, do you?
Do it like when you hit on girls
Buy me snacks and drinks. Take care of me.
Something like that.
Got it.
What?
Green is not here.
Just freakin’ take it.
Someone bought it for me.
I will have it all then.
Your fans are so kind and caring
Are you Tine?
Where is Wat? I saw you two talking just now
He went that way.
Thanks.
His fans bought him lots of ice-creams
Do you want one?
That’s okay.
He just gave me a snack from his fans
That can’t be right
He bought that from a shop himself.
You’re mistaken.
I have to go before these ice-creams melt.
No snacks!
Food first.
Why are you here?
To have lunch with you.
I skip my Faculty event just to come to see you
Faculty of Humanities is having an event?
Yes.
There is a charity auction on used stuff from hot girls from my Faculty.
The event is about to start.
You guys can go. I can stay with Tine
You don’t have to.
My friends might be jerks, but they won’t leave me for those girls
Hey!!
I made you a lunchbox.
I put all the efforts I have into this.
Look how cute it is.
Oh my god!
I am so surprised I can even do this.
Sarawat.
Don’t go.
Do you understand my signal?
Help me.
Sarawat!
Help!
Don’t leave me.
Let’s try it.
Come on.
Open your mouth.
Here is your lunch
Can I have this?
I already drank it
So?
You were exaggerating it
Green thought that you were just pretending
It didn’t look real
It was how people flirted in the series I saw.
What do you want me to do?
What series do you possibly think we are in?
The Nuisance…
…and the Handsome Prince.
I was just being sarcastic
You are so dull at flirting.
Haven’t you been in love with anyone before?
Are we all here?
Go back to your professional zone
This zone is for new waves only
Where have you been?
We have fewer members now so we will all practice together
Be focused and don’t let your weird music distract me
I need to rehearse.
Weird music?
I don’t play weird anymore.
You think?
That’s wrong
You need to press harder.
My fingers can’t press any harder.
Do you have a guitar with less stiff strings?
You need to put up with it for now
When we get the new allowance, we will buy a new one
Do you have any recommendations for guitar strings?
I will change them for the time being.
If you prefer a clear sound, I recommend Elixir.
If you prefer a soft and deep sound, go for D'Addario
Da…what?
D'Addario.
D'Ad…da…ri…o
Got it.
Guys.
Before you leave, I need to inform you of two things
Firstly, our club will have a music show called Altermajeeb
You need to advertise that.
Many cool bands will perform in this event,
especially the band called Sunshine, Daisies, Butter Mellow
That’s a band name?
It sounds like an essay topic
That’s my band.
Do you have a problem?
I don’t.
Secondly,
there will be a small evaluation for those who are in guitar class.
Skillful players record yourselves playing a song.
Beginners record yourselves playing basic chords and send it to me
Sucky players will be criticized on social media.
If you don’t turn in the video, you will be kicked out of this club
If you get it, now go home.
Play it like I taught you, Tine.
Keep fighting.
Wat, where are you going after this?
Why?
Are you asking me on a date?
No.
Can you go buy D'Addario strings with me?
I think maybe the flirting was awkward because we are not close enough
We might need to spend more time together
So you’re asking me on a date in a guitar shop
No need to beat around the bush.
A date is a date.
Sorry though
Shops around here don’t have the strings you want.
They don’t?
What should I do? I need to practice.
I have a guitar with soft strings that I don’t play very often
Seriously?
Can I borrow that one to record a video?
Sure, on one condition
What is it?
Sarawat, what brings you to the Faculty of Laws?
I came to see Tine.
Are you sure this is not a haunted house?