Actually…
It should be your song as promised, Pam
But I can’t write one for you anyway.
I tried.
No matter how hard I tried,
the lyrics wouldn’t come out.
I don’t know why.
All I know is that...
the only one I want to write a song for is Tine.
Though he doesn’t want to hear it anymore.
Thanks, guys.
Here comes the last song from us.
I’m gonna let someone perfect for the song
take over my job.
Tine.
I don’t know if you are listening.
I want you to know this.
Ever since I knew you,
this song has been stuck in my head.
Sometimes it sounds nice.
Sometimes it sounds weird.
But the song really makes me happy.
You know?
I never confessed to Pam,
because I just knew what love is when I met you.
This song is called ‘Tine.’
Give him support, guys!
♪ It’s probably normal that you are nice to everyone ♫
♪ It’s not like I am special ♫
♪ It’s funny how I take it too far ♫
♪ You must be so annoyed by me, right? ♫
♪ I apologize for misinterpreting ♫
♪ Can you please answer this one question from me? ♫
♪ All these times, I just imagine all the things? ♫
♪ It’s all in my head? ♫
♪ I thought we were in love ♫
♪ Just tell me. I’m willing to accept it ♫
♪ Just tell me you never love me ♫
Will you trust me again?
Please.
Tine, get up.
I’ll take you home.
Face up.
Turn this way.
Hold on to me so you won’t fall.
What are you doing?
I’m afraid you would fall.
What the heck are you doing?
I said I would flirt with you.
I will flirt
until you agree to be my boyfriend.
I will do it now.
Sorry.
Just a bit more.
No one has ever plastered me before in my life.
And do you think I have done this for anyone?
Don’t afraid you will fall
because I’m going to hug you like this all night.
Okay?
Here. Let me share the pillow.
I will find you a fan or something.
Ouch!
Hey!
Your leg!
I am fine.
Don’t worry about me.
Worry about yourself.
I am OK.
Are you alright?
Come on.
Get up.
I am not so sure
you can take care of my little brother.
I won’t ask you to believe me, but I will show you.
Who said I hit on him just to get rid of you?
I did it because I genuinely like Tine.
Just so you know.
The only one I’ve always had feelings for…
…is you, Tine.
I like you.
I’ve liked you since the second I saw you.
Do you really think we will last 10 years?
I want to be with you more than that.
For me…
Tine is a living thing…
that I want to call ‘nuisance’ for the rest of my life.
I just want to be with you.
If it is our movie, you can choose…
whether...
you want it to end
with tragedy
Or end with happiness.
What do you say?
What will you choose?
Will you trust me again?
I wouldn’t be here if I don’t trust you, would I?
Don’t ever take it off again.
Save your voices for later, guys.
That just made my heart bloom.
Oh yeah!
How are you feeling, Air?
I am so happy right now.
You guys too, right?
It’s time everyone here has waited for.
I have the contest result in my hand.
Which band do you think will win this?
Scream the band you are rooting for, guys.
Come on.
And the winner of 2020 Music Contest goes to…
To…
The winner is…
Who?
Ctrl S.
Congratulations!
The joy hasn’t ended yet.
We have a big surprise for you.
We have a special live show
from a special band for everyone in here.
Please welcome Scrubb!
We see each other every year.
Congratulations…what’s the name again?
Ctrl S.
Right. Ctrl S.
This song is for those
who are meant to be together.
♪ I walk past and see strangers ♫
♪ My life is in the same loop ♫
♪ I always feel the same ♫
Have you ever wondered
why we are in pairs?
If you love someone, don’t be quiet about it.
Tell that person right away.
Be quiet.
Don’t be quiet about it.
But read it quietly.
The book you gave me is telling me not to.
I told you to be quiet.
Before I will be quiet,
can I tell you something?
I freaking like you.
I FREAKING LIKE YOU!
That’s enough. I know.
Maybe...
being together kills the loneliness.
and…
…makes us happy.
You lost. Don’t forget to keep the promise.
You will keep your heart open for me.
Welcome all the freshmen to this Faculty.
Anyone wants me to sign,
just move to the line right here.
Come one. Don’t be shy.
Come on.
Just come.
Fine.
Hey!
You two!
P’Mil, will you sign this for me, please?
My signature is crap.
Can I not sign it?
You can’t?
It is really crappy.
How about you sign it just for me?
I didn’t fail like the first exam.
For some couple,
being together gives them
challenges and liveliness.
For some couple, they fulfill each other.
♪ Someone who can make us smile ♫
♪  though how sad we are ♫
This year,
[One Year Later]
our club has many more members
than we’re allowed to.
So we are going to have a little test.
If you are beginners, don’t worry.
We had a beginner who practiced for the test
and passed last year.
Do you want to know how he did it?
Please welcome P’Tine upfront
to share his experience.
Sawasdee Krub.
I couldn’t play any musical instrument.
I even practiced on a guitar app for that test
because I didn’t have a guitar of my own.
I cheated at first,
but I got caught.
So I had to play it with a little ability I got.
When I was done,
the club president asked me about music.
I couldn’t answer any of them.
What?
How did you pass?
For the last question,
he asked me if I knew anything about music at all.
Back then, I had a friend in this club.
So I said I didn’t know anything about music.
But I knew a friend named Sarawat.
He was the reason I wanted to play guitar.
Do you want to know who Sarawat is?
Please welcome P’Sarawat here
to teach you guys guitar.
Where are you going?
Come help me.
What do you want me to do?
Be my student.
Pick up the guitar!
Stand here.
Start with the basic chords.
C chord.
Wrong!
The way to place your fingers is wrong.
Press harder and play.
Wrong!
A year has passed and your fingers are still weak.
Have you been practicing?
Wrong!
Aren’t you embarrassed?
A member can’t play a basic chord.
Who would trust our club?
Stop teasing him!
Tine is about to cry.
Guys, don’t be frightened.
P’Sarawat always teases his boyfriend like this.
Oh! You were teasing me?
I pretended to yell
but you really played it wrong.
That’s it.
Good job.
As for our couple,
I am not so sure what the reason is.
What I know is that when we are together,
we are the couple people are jealous of the most.
That’s how we teach.
If you can’t take it, you can withdraw.
It’s still hot.
You don’t have to do it.
Eat more.
Just stay put.
Let’s go see a movie.
How about we have dinner after the movie?
What is your stomach made of?
Your shirt is so cool.
Man!
Yes!
[Your P’Mil]
Damn it!
Fine.
I surrender.
Don’t!
Look at you.
You’re playing it right. What’s left to teach?
We are done with basic chords.
Let me teach you the harder ones.
Point finger on the fifth string.
This on the second string.
This on the fourth and this on the third.
Ten years from now or even more,
Our couple
will be just you and me.
The Nuisance
and the Handsome Prince.
Directed by Weerachit Thongjila
I am sorry.
Win stepped on it and broke them into pieces.
Did it break when you picked it up?
Definitely into pieces. Win did it!
OK. Let’s start over.
My friend is a gentleman.
Damn you!
I just can’t.
All over my face.
I am sorry.
It’s almost done.
I am so sorry.
Start from the beginning.
‘Your brother is drunk’
Ready?
My friend might be foul-mouthed,
but he is a gentleman.
Action!
Sarawat, take the photo from him
No pocket.
Why did you agree to take a photo with Kao*? (*A cute way to say ‘me/people’)
What?
Kao my ass!
You’re giving me goosebumps.
What’s the right script?
I meant taking photos with other people.
Come on.
Cover his mouth.
♪ Someone who can make us smile ♫
♪  though how sad we are ♫
♪ You have changed my definition of love ♫