Sarawat, the Political Science star player is sitting on the bench.
Is he injured?
Is he…
one of the Architecture students that hurt you yesterday?
What happened to your hand?
I am not afraid of other people
Just worried about a dog that backbites
I am up for a real fight too
I can’t let you perform in this condition
Will my show be good enough to substitute Control S?
Just ask him already.
If you don’t, I will freaking hit on him myself
Tine.
I am so done flirting.
Will you be my boyfriend?
How are you shippers doing?
You are all squealing.
Even I was shipping them.
And that was a surprise show from our Music Club.
Now let them take a break backstage.
Give them a big hand, guys!
It’s all ruined.
How could he say it was just a show?
If he didn’t say that, the rest of them wouldn’t get to perform.
Yeah yeah! Hero!
We won’t help you ever again.
We are off now.
So that was just part of the show?
I’m relieved then.
I was in shock for a moment
Are you really happy that it wasn’t real?
Yes.
If it was real,
I would feel really bad.
I thought I could do this one thing for you
but I completely failed
You told me that…
it was supposed to be the happy ending scene in the movie.
I ruined it
though I had practiced really hard for it.
Maybe…
I am not the protagonist in your movie
That scene doesn’t have to be the end of it.
You can still give it a happy ending.
How?
If it is our movie,
you can choose…
whether you want it to end with tragedy
Or end with happiness
Just be my boyfriend now.
Quit playing already.
I am asking you for real
What do you say?
What will you choose?
What are you playing, Tine?
I hate movies with sad endings.
Yes
Yes?
Yes. I am your boyfriend now.
[Sarawat already has a boyfriend. His name is Tine.]
You…
You are so damn cute!
Ouch!
My leg!
Sorry.
Tine!
What?
We wanted to know if Sarawat asking you to be his boyfriend in the concert was a real thing
Uh…
It’s…
You know what?
Fong thinks it’s real.
And he thinks you already said yes to him.
Right.
Tine curses Sarawat three times a day.
If he ends up being Sarawat’s boyfriend, then he is a loser
Loser?
Exactly.
So Tine?
Is it real or not?
Real.
Real my ass!
You know that he likes to tease me.
I am going to get a coffee.
Slow down.
What now?
Have you told your friends that we are together?
I haven’t
You told me you would tell everyone here today
Change of plan.
Can we tell them later?
I need more time.
They are so ready to tease me.
What is wrong?
Are you mad?
No.
I…
want to grab your boobs.
WHAT?
I want to grab your boobs.
Now?
Can I?
Yes but just once.
And don’t tell your friends that we are dating yet.
Can I squeeze?
Hell no!
That’s enough.
That’s all you got.
I just forgot about you
What were you two whispering about?
Did you just stop Sarawat from telling us that you’re together?
What?
We were talking about the Music Club.
Guys, I just won a lotto. This table eats for free.
Are you serious?
Of course.
On one condition though.
Let me kiss Sarawat on the cheek.
What will my friend get then?
OK.
Everyone here eats for free then.
Kiss him!
Do you see the guy in this picture?
I do
He is my boyfriend
- Who?
- I can’t let you kiss me
Damn it!
You said you wouldn’t tell our friends.
I wasn’t telling them.
I was telling the one hitting on me.
So they are boyfriends now.
What are you waiting for, guys?
Give them a round of applause!
Keep on clapping.
The exams are finally over.
Right.
I was about to ask you to celebrate with us.
But someone is already here picking you up.
See you later.
See you.
Are you done with your exams?
Yes.
Should we go out and celebrate?
Exams are over and you are walking like a pro again.
It still hurts.
I think…
I need to ride on your back on the way to dinner.
I wish…
it really hurts.
You are in pain forever.
But If I’m in pain and you take care of me,
I’m OK with that
You’re such a…
Come on.
I need to go somewhere before dinner
Wow!
This room is way better than my dorm.
It’s beautiful.
You like it?
I do!
Let’s go upstairs.
Whose room is it anyway?
I am thinking…
it can be our room.
What?
I’ve been thinking about this for a while now
I want to see you before I close my eyes to sleep.
And I want to see you first thing after I wake up.
Move in with me?
Stay with me tonight?
Fine!
Yes! It’s our love lair.
Come here!
Should we put our clothes together in the same basket?
Why?
Come on.
No. We need to separate them.
I want some.
Don’t spill it.
Why did you bring a ball with you?
What?
It is clean.
Hey!
Tine, don’t!
You like to bug me, don’t you?
Okay. You can have some.
Where are you putting it?
Don’t know.
Put it right here.
Dipshit!
I can’t.
Help me
Oh!
I am trying to pick a song to play at the contest.
Play a Scrubb song.
I knew it.
I will…
if you let me kiss you on the cheek.
No way!
No?
No.
Just one kiss?
Fine then.
A Scrubb song will be played
Here it is.
A housewarming gift for you two.
Thanks, bro.
Wait!
What kind of flower are these wrapped in plastic?
Holy shit!!
They are condoms.
For a newly wedded couple.
Why are you guys turning red?
Is it hot in here?
No. It’s cool.
Are you turning red because of the condom bouquet?
We are interrupting their sweet moment.
We will be out of your hair now.
Right. Just go already.
But we just got here.
120 condoms in there.
Be careful with those.
Didn’t you lock the door? How did they get in?
I don’t know.
What a gross bouquet!
Besides Man and Boss’s, there’s another gift too.
Ah huh.
Are you more interested in your phone than me?
Hey!
I am sorry.
What did you just say?
Forget it.
You can continue playing on your phone.
I am sorry.
I didn’t ignore you.
You can see it for yourself.
[I like Sarawat.]
You promised to post a love confession to me.
Are you still mad, sir?
I am
I’m mad at myself for not being able to be mad at you, little buffalo!
What were you talking about just now?
I have something for you too.
Thank you for moving in with me
Wait!
It’s the pick I cut in half.
You kept it
I keep everything about you
If I could, I would keep you locked up in there
So the two of us can stay together forever.
Hey!
It could be my mom
She might be wondering about the new place
I’m gonna talk to her for a bit.
[Who the hell is Sarawat?]
[Why is he with my boy?]
Tine is my boyfriend. F*ck off!
Tine!
Who the hell is this guy?
What?
He said you’re his.
Did he ever hit on you or something?
Where?
SHIT!
What?
The one you were talking to is…
Tonight, can I…?
Either you say yes or I continue pouting.
Yes or no?