Man.
This way.
Sure.
Sawasdee Krub.
He woke up and thought I took his clothes off
He punched me in the face.
What?
How could you do that to me?
I was standing there in shock.
I heard you are a Political Science student.
Where will you go for your internship program?
I don’t know yet
Political Science grads now have broader career path than before.
What are you leaning to?
I haven’t thought about that yet
I am just a first-year student.
People here usually plan ahead since high school
You should start thinking about it.
The competitions are high these days.
Well, I do plan my future.
I will graduate and ask P’Type to be my boyfriend.
Seriously?
But you have no clue about your job.
Type gets paid really well.
Will you be able to take care of him?
Of course, I will.
I might not have a lot of money
But I have a heart of a fighter.
A heart, he said.
A heart of a fighter.
Let’s stop teasing him.
He is still young.
I don’t have money
Can I pay with my heart?
I will pay for P’Type and me.
Don’t worry about that.
It’s my treat.
Please don’t. I will pay.
Up to you then
I was joking.
Give it back here.
Keep your money for the tuition. Let me take care of this meal
See you guys
Get home safe.
Didn’t you drive here?
Come on. I’ll give you a ride.
That’s ok.
Come on. I had only soda.
You’re safe.
Type, get in.
You can just go. I will give P’Type a ride home.
Did you ask him if he wanted to ride on your aged motorbike?
P’Type, are you coming with me?
Take your pick.
If you want to ride comfortably, come with me
But if you want to experience a tough life full of smoke and sweat, go with him
You!
Man, stop!
Stop.
Just stop.
P’Beam, I’ll go with you.
Come on. Let’s go.
Please.
Thank you.
But I think I better go with him
All these times,
I thought we got along pretty well.
Good luck to you then.
What are you doing?
You seem drowsy.
Are you sick?
No. I am fine.
Really?
Actually, it’s bloating up in my stomach
Phuak took us to 4 restaurants.
OK. Just a sec.
Here.
Take one pill at a time.
Next time, you can just say it.
Got it?
I’ll turn off the light.
Hey!
We haven’t had a music clip together for quite some time
How about we record one tonight?
It is late, and you are not well.
Let’s do it later, OK?
Get some sleep
Goodnight.
♪ In my memory ♫
♪ I am standing there when we say the word ♫
♪ The word that is stuck in my mind ♫
♪ Days have passed ♫
♪ Every time I wake up ♫
It’s good.
Yeah?
Yes.
I can’t play.
♪ I still think of that word ♫
♪ The word in my heart ♫
Is it cute?
You can be cheesy too.
What? No one can do it like me.
♪ All the pain I’ve been through ♫
♪ I am escaping ♫
♪ I am leaving the reality behind because it hurts me so bad ♫
♪ It can wait ♫
♪ I just want to close my eyes ♫
I feel a bit queasy inside.
I want to throw up, but I can’t.
How about you take some rest today?
You didn’t get enough sleep last night.
How did you know?