P’Dim.
Will my show be good enough to substitute Control S?
What’s got into your head?
I am not as good as Sarawat
But I can perform by myself.
Great!
I will perform a guitar solo after Tine’s show
Me too.
Us too.
It doesn’t sound so bad.
We give this stage to newbies.
It might motivate more people to step up and join the contest
Do you all know that...
when you are on stage,
you carry the club reputation with you?
I do
This club accepted me and taught me guitar lessons
It’s time for me to repay it.
P’Dim is crazy enough to let Tine perform
Fong.
Talk to him. He only listens to you.
Try to change his mind.
What’s wrong with him playing for the club?
He is a newbie.
He doesn’t have enough time to practice
First time on stage is tough.
I don’t want him to fail.
Do you know why Tine hasn’t said yes to your confession?
How does that have to do with anything here?
Tine was always the one taking care of his ex.
But now he is the one being taken care of.
I guess he is not used to it.
He might want to prove that he is good enough to be with you
Don’t be happy just yet.
If he fails this time, he might get too discouraged.
He might withdraw himself from a relationship with you forever.
Thanks.
Your food is right here
I’m gonna go practice now.
Hey!
I hurt my knee, not my eyes
You can practice here.
I can be your mentor
Fine.
I will get you a chair
What are you looking at?
I’m just thinking…
ever since you gave me this guitar,
I haven’t named it yet
What?
Is it the right time to name a guitar?
I am serious here.
If you were a guitar, you would want to play for the owner who gave you a nice name
Up to you then.
What kind of name do you like then?
Something that describes me
Ringworm.
Just call yourself that.
Scrubb?
Yes.
Don’t you feel pity for them at all?
Don’t ruin their band by naming your guitar that
What name do you want then?
Just pick one already, nuisance.
Stop being picky and practice.
Nuisance!
That’s right.
Freaking right for my guitar.
You are awesome!
You are clever.
Let me see your music chords.
Are you playing a Scrubb song?
Yes. Why?
The first time having a girlfriend,
the first heartbreak,
the first music video recording
Scrubb songs took parts in all of them.
This will be my first time on stage.
How can I play a song from other bands?
You’re right.
I am jealous of Scrubb
They are your first of many things.
I want to be Scrubb
Why?
So that I can be with you both when you’re happy and sad
I want to be Scrubb.
Cheesy!
Let me practice already.
Otherwise, the true sadness will come if I can't play
Wrong.
Press harder.
Press more firmly.
Isn’t this firm enough?
If it’s firmly enough, it won’t sound wrong.
Wrong. Press harder.
Here.
Press harder.
Now play.
This is called right.
Memorize it.
Give me the pick.
Nobody holds a pick as you do.
Look.
Use your point finger like this.
Spare the edge.
Grab it together with your thumb.
And you strum it.
Give me your hand.
Put a pick on your point finger.
Leave the edge
Press it with your thumb.
Tine.
Will you marry me?
What the hell?
You’re teaching me to hold a pick, not putting on a wedding ring.
Okay. Keep going!
Why are you smiling?
Who is?
Does it hurt your fingers?
Stop.
Let me see
All of them hurt?
Yes.
Just take a break.
If you practice too hard and hurt your fingers, you can’t perform anyway
Let me have a look.
See? Your fingers are about to bleed.
You have to be able to play when the day comes.
I’m trying to be gentle, but this is hard.
Sorry.
You know what.
No one has ever plastered me before in my life.
And do you think I have done this for anyone?
Marry me?
Again? Stop it!
It’s done.
Thank you.
Take a break for a while until your fingers heal.
Listen to the song in the meantime.
I said no practice.
Put it down.
[To help you see the chords more clearly.]
Good timing.
We are teaming up.
This game, I will play for your opponent
What?
Be my guest. Play for the team you want.
What the heck is your problem?
That was one hell of a tackle.
Ouch!
Shit!
What are you playing?
I’m doing what you did to my brother.
Yes!
I am Sarawat’s brother!
F*ck you!
You have an appointment for the x-ray tomorrow.
I am not available tomorrow morning
Can we postpone it for later?
Your doctor is free only tomorrow morning.
After that, he is fully booked.
We can’t postpone it.
Wat.
What is on your mind?
Nothing.
The nurse told me you have to come for an x-ray tomorrow
Just come.
I will be fine.
But you are performing.
Do you think I went through all the practice just to bother you at the end?
Can you take me somewhere today?
Where?
Welcome everyone to our Music Club shows.
My name is…
You OK?
Keep fighting!