Are you here hoping to see Sarawat?
No.
I just…
come to reminisce it one last time.
The place where everything started.
Unlike me.
I came to recall my old Sarawat.
His eyes
before they laid on you.
I had always liked him.
And I thought he felt the same way.
I kept waiting.
I waited for him to confess his feeling.
Until that day,
we came here for the concert.
And he met you, Tine.
From then on,
his eyes have changed.
I learned the truth long ago.
That’s why I went to a different University.
I thought I could forget about him.
But one day, he posted your photo on his IG.
And, everyone can see.
He didn’t have the guts to say he liked me,
but he told every on social media about you.
That made me wonder if I came back,
would things be different?
But no.
How do you know?
I think he still loves you.
Answer me!
Pam!
I am sorry.
I can’t love you.
He tried to hide it
but I knew he was writing a love song for you.
He told you so
because he felt guilty towards me.
About the song…
Give it a try.
Why do I have to?
Just listen to it and you will know.
What a nice weather!
May I sit here and read with you?
Do whatever you want.
Just don’t bother me.
Loving you is kind of bothering?
I will haunt you every day.
I will stick with you no matter what.
I can follow you for the rest of my life.
Did you ask me if I wanted to be followed?
We will see about that.
You gotta miss me if I don’t show up one day.
Excuse me.
Your friend came here the other day.
He asked me to return this to you.
Thank you.
I have been looking for you everywhere.
What a surprise you are Tine’s brother.
Do I know you?
You don’t remember me?
No.
You are never in my memories.
And I don’t think
I ever associated with someone like you.
This side.
Man.
Man!
Sorry.
I thought you were my friend.
Pass me the ball.
Who is he anyway?
He comes to play with us every day.
I don’t know.
I guess he doesn’t have any friends.
What is wrong with you?
The contest is about to happen.
Why aren’t you in practice?
Why do you care?
It’s none of your business.
Fine.
I will play with you.
That’s two.
Two what?
It was the first goal.
Two times you’ve lost to me.
One for football and
one for Tine.
And when did I lose Tine to you?
Just look at yourself now!
If my band wins the contest this year,
I’ll ask Tine out.
And if you can’t take it,
don’t dare show your face at the contest.
I am warning you.
You must treat me BBQ pork this time.
You bailed on me last time.
Trust me on this. I won’t bail this time.
We’ll see about that.
Come on. I won’t ditch you.
Come on.
Hey!
Man.
Man!
Why are you avoiding me?
I am not.
Are you still mad about what P’Beam said?
Hell yes.
I am mad because I was insulted.
I am mad because you didn’t try to protect me a bit.
I am mad at myself the most
because I suck just like they said.
You know what?
I promised myself
I won’t see you again until I am more mature.
I don’t know if I can ever be mature in this life.
You cannot.
You can’t even keep your promise.
What promise?
You promised to come and see me every day.
You came into my life,
followed me around every day.
And now you want to disappear on me?
All you can do is talk.
But you already have P’Beam.
Who told you that?
I don’t want a luxurious life.
I just want a simple life.
Are you OK with this?
I have nothing for you.
I am not.
You said you would take care of me.
Find a way to do it.
If you can pester me everywhere,
taking care of me won’t be so hard.
I guess so.
Will you take me home today?
No.
What?
Just joking.
Sure.
Didn’t you drive here?
I did.
But I want to ride through smoke and dust with you.
Dust?
That’s unexpected.
It’s not nice and clean.
Will you take me home or not?
It’s hot out there.
I know.
Of course, I will.
I won’t let you go home alone.
So…
Are we cool now?
Um.
Then…
Can I hug you?
No.
Come on.
There is no one around.
Give me a hug.
Fine.
BBQ pork.
BBQ pork my ass!
Don’t mind him.
Let go.
What?
Do you want to eat BBQ pork?
No.
Why not?
Are you on a diet?
I want to go home.
BBQ pork and dessert.
No. I want to go home.
It won’t take that long.
What will you do at home?
I just want to go home.
Fine.
I’ll take you home.
But let me hug you again.
Cheer up, guys.
Sorry I am late.
Hurry!
I have set up the guitar for you.
Thanks.
Why do you have to look so nice and bright?
Ah!
It’s the Music Contest tomorrow.
It’s just routine.
You know I have nothing to do with Sarawat anymore.
Yeah?
And this guitar?
Why haven’t you returned it to him?
I just…
I will...
I will but I need to take my name tag off first.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Stop talking about this.
Must be Ohm.
Hide it.
If he sees it, he will definitely tease you.
Hide?
Yes.
Wat.
He has decided not to go.