Hey!
When did my friend say he would post a love confession to your friend?
I didn’t mention any names in the post
What makes you think I was talking about your friend?
We don’t know that.
But what we know for sure is that your friend is hitting on my friend here
Don’t mess with his head like that.
Who is messing with his head?
No one is.
I posted it because I am very sure that we will win
You can’t be too confident
Your opponent holds six championship cups.
So?
We are going to break that record.
If you don’t think we can, you don’t need to panic
Fine.
If you guys win, my friend will post a love confession to your friend.
If you lose, Sarawat will have to leave my friend alone
Deal?
I think…
your friend here is gonna have to prepare a sweet love confession for me
Hello?
Chat told me you are sick
Yes.
I can’t attend the tutoring class with you for a while.
That’s okay.
Chat told me your address.
He got it from your application.
I will meet you there and assign you some homework.
You don’t have to
I’m almost there.
What?
See you.
What a coincidence!
Someone I hate lives around here too.
His name is Sarawat.
Do you know him?
I don’t
I don’t come here very often.
Whose football jersey is this?
My brother’s.
What Faculty is he in?
The Faculty of…
He wears number 12.
It reminds me of that jerk Sarawat.
The Faculty of…
- Poli…
- Political Science?
No.12 from Political Science is Sarawat.
How are you related to Sarawat?
The thing is…
my brother is having a football match against Political Science
So I tried to find Political Science football jersey to burn just to jinx them
You are such a great little brother.
You picked the right number
Anything that belongs to Sarawat should be burned to the ground.
That’s right.
Burn them all.
We are at the checkpoint.
Stop and boost your energy, guys.
- Thank you.
- Me too.
That’s not refreshing enough.
Try this.
Man!
You did it again!
Refreshing, isn’t it?
It’s sticky
That girl is cute
Don’t look at him.
Don’t let him mess with your head.
Go.
They scream for you again.
I did this once
Taking off your shirt?
Yes.
Girls screamed their lungs out for me
Don’t play it again.
What? It was fun.
Your trick to get Tine confess is superb
Why can’t you apply that to your love life?
Do you want to get beaten up?
My own plan is in progress
I got my hand on his phone
Now I have both his number and Line ID.
There is one problem though
He is not single?
I’m not brave enough to call.
If I were a cute little girl, I wouldn’t worry
I am a handsome young man. I’m sure he would freak out if I called.
Not a problem.
Just create a fake Line account.
Fake Line account?
Make it up?
Yep!
Good idea.
Who should I be?
It’s brilliant, Boss!!
Thank you so much.
If it wasn’t for you, I wouldn’t know who I should pretend to be
You are super clever, my friend!
I know now who I’m going to be.
Are you pretending to be Wat?
Wat My Ass!!
Great plan!
She is so cute.
If I were him, I would definitely want to talk to her
You want to talk to every cute girl.
Let’s see if he’s easily deceived like you.
I’m going to start now.
Sawasdee Ka.
Are you P’Type, the one who likes to go to business seminars?
How do you spell ‘Ka’?
K and A.
Yes.
Who is this?
He replied so quickly.
My name is Earn. I am a freshman
I see you at several seminars so I think it would be great if we can exchange knowledge
Sure.
I am happy to help If I can
I told you he is friendly
Right? Earn is pretty.
If I were him, I would be friendly too
What’s next?
I need some information for my report.
Can I have an interview with you..?
Wait!
You talk to him for 5 minutes and now you want to see him?
Is it weird?
Of course.
Okay. I’m going to delete it then
Delete.
Shit!
I just hit send!
Can I unsend it now?
No!
He read it! He is quick!
What do I do, Boss?
Shit!
This can go in two directions.
He might answer that question.
Or he blocks your account completely
Block?
You sound like a pervert
Damn it!
Let me see her picture again
Knock it off.
So Tine isn’t Sarawat’s boyfriend?
Sarawat is going after him but he doesn’t care, right?
Is that so?
I’ve been misunderstanding.
That’s why I didn’t reach out to you.
I was afraid Sarawat would get jealous.
Don’t be afraid.
My friend likes a cute little girl with fair skin just like you
The library will be closed this Saturday.
Where should we study?
How about Tine’s room?
It’s available.
He lives alone
We can study as long as we like.
Study?
Sounds good.
This Saturday, I have to go watch…
Education is more important, right?
We should study.
See you guys at Tine’s place on Saturday then
My room?
Yep!
I told you to deactivate your IG
Why is it still there?
What if I get ambushed on the way back?
Will you spend the night at my place?