The test will be on Friday. Don’t forget to practice
Tine, you’re still here.
Yeah. I don’t have a guitar of my own.
So I think I will play on a bit more.
You guys can go.
I like your determination.
But what you play is still wrong
Thank you for your advice
Enjoy your snacks. From Team Sarawat’s Wives.
I am not stealing.
I am just protecting your snacks from anyone who wants to steal them
Wrong!
Can your fingers work properly?
Press harder
Wrong!
I can’t press any harder
Here.
What?
My guitar.
Its strings are better
Try it.
It’s okay.
Just take it.
Now play it.
It’s right this time.
Does it hurt your fingers?
No.
That’s good.
Keep practicing.
Now try chord E.
How do you do chord E?
Move over.
Your middle finger on the second fret, fifth string
Your ring finger on the second fret, fourth string.
Your point finger on the first fret, third string.
Now play it.
Memorize it so I don’t have to teach you again.
Play on.
What are you looking at?
I'm just wondering why you aren't in the Faculty of Music since you're so good.
I play because I enjoy it
I’m afraid that if I actually learn it,
it won’t give me pleasure anymore.
I do what I like by heart, not by duty
What are you still looking at?
I’m begging you.
Please help me.
Just pretend that you like me.
So you’re in this club because of this?
It’s not like that.
It’s…
Yes! I admit it.
Now that you know it, please help to be my fake boyfriend
Are you saying yes or no?
[Faculty Building]
Sarawat is here.
Record a video.
Let’s take a selfie.
Sarawat…
Have you seen a guy who comes to practice here every day?
I haven’t seen him
He might be finding himself a new club.
I don’t think he will pass the test.
P’Dim wants to see you in the storage room but I have no idea why.
Is that you, nuisance?!?
Do you think I will give up that easily?
If you want to get out, you have to be my fake boyfriend.
Deal with your own problem.
Let me out.
Up to you then.
Sleep tight in there tonight.
Are you threatening me?
Do you want to get hurt?
Do you think I’m afraid?
Tine!!
Are you in here? I think I just saw you.
You won’t get out of Music Club because you’re afraid of your seniors. Am I right?
Don’t be. I have friends from Bodybuilder Club just to help you.
Let me deal with the seniors for you
Open, please
Tine.
You don’t want to be in that club.
Just resign and join Cooking Club with me.
I know that someone is in there
If you don’t open the door, I will.
What are you doing here so loud?
I was sleeping in there?
Who are you here for?
In there?
Yeah, why?
I’m looking for Tine. Have you seen him?
Tine?
No.
Really?
I’m going to continue my sleep.
Anything else?
Nope.
Sleeping in a cupboard?
Sorry for bothering.
Bye bye.
Tine!
Come out, nuisance
That was close.
Thank you so much.
I didn’t want to help you.
I just didn’t want to get involved in your business.
It’s a good idea to change the club.
You won’t pass a test for Music Club.
What if I pass?
If I pass, you have to be my fake boyfriend.
Deal?
If you do, I’ll help you.
But if you fail, you have to leave me alone
Deal.
The result is out.
We don’t pass.