(Episode 5)
Who is it this early in the morning?
I'm meeting a client,
so I'll be an hour late today.
Okay, noted.
It's chilly today, so bundle up.
Did I go too far?
(You should bundle up too.)
You should bundle up too.
He emphasized that I
should bundle up today,
so that is what I'll do.
Pink is always right.
It's so pretty.
The doors are closing.
Wait a second! Gosh, thank you.
Oh, it's you, Mr. Kwon.
The doors are closing.
Like always, I meet you in the elevator...
even though I'm coming in an hour
late after meeting a client.
Anyone who hears you might assume that...
I wait for you at the
elevator every morning.
I'm coming in late
because of a meeting too.
- By the way, I have good news.
- I don't want to know.
I've never been delighted by
your so-called good news before.
It's for real this time.
I have two incredibly exciting news.
Which would you like to hear first?
One's only slightly good while
the other is a true delight.
Okay, we men should play on a large scale,
so I'll start with the big news.
Always Law Firm...
might take on a big case.
I'm 99 percent certain. Once we take it on,
we'll be at the center of attention.
What's the case?
That's a secret.
I'll move onto the small news now.
The firm's going out to dinner today.
Mr. Kwon! Why aren't you answering me?
We're all going out for dinner.
I will not be attending.
You never do.
Why can't you enjoy the fun
when it's brought to your lap?
Sorry for being late.
Good morning.
What's all this?
Aren't they pretty?
Spring is right around the corner,
so I decorated my desk
in the shade of pink.
It may be spring soon,
but a law firm office...
shouldn't be pink.
Are you saying that this isn't allowed?
Are you aware that you're
in violation of...
one's right to pursue happiness
and the right to free will?
How did you know that?
You said so at the drive-in theater.
I have a good memory,
so I recall everything.
All right then. Do as you wish.
What's all this?
I thought it was rude
to only revamp my desk.
Still, I prefer black to pink.
Even though you're fond of black,
a splash of pink here and there...
will elevate your mood.
My right to pursue happiness
and the right to free will...
should be assured too.
All right. I'll get rid of them.
A strawberry?
Wait.
- Take these too.
- Keep those at least.
When I'm not in my seat, you can write...
notes for me and stick them on my desk.
That way, we won't forget.
Then...
Right.
What?
Yes.
I'll send the content
certification right away.
Sure.
♫ You and I, this moment right here ♫
♫ I'm going to cherish it deep in my heart ♫
(Please put together the content
certification for Ms. Jung.)
Please put together the content
certification for Ms. Jung.
(Sure.)
♫ It's so precious ♫
♫ So make it count ♫
Come in.
♫ Remember this day ♫
♫ When the gentle breeze blows
and flowers bloom ♫
♫ Each minute, each second, make it count ♫
♫ Then I'll be forever ♫
♫ Gathering all the moments,
I'll give it to you ♫
Sure thing.
She could've just said it.
♫ La la la la ♫
♫ I really hope we make it count ♫
♫ I'm laying on a bench,
using your lap as a pillow ♫
(Please apply for Mr. Park's hearing
to be moved to next Tuesday.)
♫ I'm laying on a bench,
using your lap as a pillow ♫
Please apply for Mr. Park's hearing...
to be moved to next Tuesday.
♫ The gravity is twice as strong here ♫
(It's been moved to 3pm on February 26.)
It's been moved to 3pm on February 26.
Apply for commission of documents...
regarding Mr. Baek's case...
at the Cheongju District
Prosecutor's Office.
Done and done.
Check Mr. Han's deadline for
an appeal and notify him.
The deadline is the 27th,
and he will appeal.
Good job. I'm sorry
I gave you too many tasks.
It's all right. Please let me know
if there's anything else I can do.
(It's all right. Please let me know
if there's anything else I can do.)
♫ Gathering all the moments,
I'll give it to you ♫
♫ Stick close to me
so I can't even miss you ♫
♫ I really hope we make it count ♫
Hi, is this Thunder Express?
This is Dan Moon Hee of Always Law Firm.
That's right.
I need a parcel delivered by courier.
Sure, I'll be waiting.
I wonder what he thinks of me.
Does he like me?
Does he not?
Does he like me or does he not?
Likes me or not.
- He...
- He likes you!
I'm sure that he likes you too.
I've seen people tell
fortunes with petals before,
but not with tangerines.
It's a first for me too.
I just don't know what he thinks of me.
What is he like?
Is it still just a one-sided love?
I'm not sure.
I do think that he's interested in me too.
Would you like to hear me out?
Sure, I'm curious to know.
He works at the courier service
our law firm often calls.
His tone changes when only addressing me.
He keeps his voice low with others,
but takes on a higher tone with me.
He must be thrilled to see me, right?
That's not all though.
The company gives out a key ring...
after five deliveries,
but even though I only called
the service four times,
I was given this key ring for free.
We all wish to go all out
for the ones we love.
It's pretty.
He must truly be into you.
Really?
You're a woman with a lot
of relationship experience,
so your words seem trustworthy.
I actually haven't dated much.
Oh, right. I read it in an interview.
You've never had a boyfriend before.
I may not be experienced
with romantic relationships,
but I give out great advice.
Don't you remember?
I hosted that TV dating show.
From what I can tell,
this is for sure.
My gosh! Nice!
- It's a secret though.
- Sure.
My gosh. She must really like him.
Do tangerines actually work though?
Maybe I should try it too.
He likes me.
He likes me not.
He likes me,
he likes me not...
(He likes me, he likes me not,
he likes me, he likes me not...)
He likes me!
Ms. Oh, it's time to go to the trial.
Okay. I'm on my way.
After questioning the witness,
the defendant's alibi...
and the fact that he was not at the
scene has been proved clearly.
Therefore, I request you to...
sentence him as not guilty.
Mr. Kwon, it seems like
we'll win the trial, right?
Yes, maybe we will.
Come on, stop being so modest.
From the smile on your face,
it seems like you're confident.
You get so happy whenever you win.
You're a natural-born attorney.
By the way, why did you become an attorney?
I heard that your friends from
college all became prosecutors.
Attorneys make more money.
What? He became an attorney
because of money?
He's even a sincere guy.
The more I get to know him,
the more charming he seems.
It's almost time for lunch.
Why don't we go eat something?
Sure.
Wait. Oh, right.
What if she wants to drink coffee again?
No. Since it's lunch time,
she might want to have lunch together.
Aren't you coming?
I'm coming. Come on, let's go! Hurry!
Jung Rok.
- A UFO!
- What?
It went that way!
Hurry up. Come on, let's go already.
- Hurry!
- Jung Rok.
Hey.
- Were you here for a trial?
- Yes.
I see you often lately.
So? You don't like it?
You came too, Ms. Oh.
Yes, I did.
If you have time, how about lunch?
Does pasta sound good?
Pasta?
Actually, I have something to tell you.
- Is it important?
- Yes. It's extremely important.
It's also kind of a secret.
I'm sorry, but can you go
back to the office first?
What?
Go back first?
He promised to eat with me first
and just broke it.
Do you know how much I like...
pasta?
So, what is this important
and secret thing about?
- Do you know the Im Yun Hee Case?
- Yes.
I'm in charge of that case.
She was assaulted by her
husband for years...
and while she was being beaten,
she killed her husband with a knife.
Is this murder or self-defense?
What do you think?
But once self-defense
is accepted at a trial,
it becomes a difficult matter
for the prosecutor in charge,
and all the other suspects will
start to claim self-defense.
The attorneys will mention previous cases
and claim self-defense too.
It's a sensitive matter for us.
It's hard to make a clear decision
for situations like this.
I know.
I didn't expect you to give me an answer.
At first, I said I'd take
this case confidently,
but I'm sort of in a pickle.
Do you want to go for some coffee?
No, I have to go back now.
Why? Don't you still have some time left?
I have work to do. I'll see you next time.
What's keeping him so busy?
- Why are you standing there?
- I'm taking these away.
You're not qualified to have these notes.
Do I need to be qualified to have notes?
Why? Didn't you say you
didn't want them before?
Are you having second thoughts?
No, but I'm just wondering
why you'd take them back.
I can do whatever I want.
If you're offended, you can sue me.
There's no need for that.
We still have 20 minutes left.
Let's go out and have lunch.
I don't want to eat anything!
Why do you keep glaring at me like that?
I'm not. I often hear
that I have blazing eyes.
An actress must have eyes that
can mesmerize the camera.
- Okay. Have a good day.
- Excuse me.
Yes? Is there something you want to say?
This may sound random, but do you
want to have dinner with me someday?
- Sorry?
- How about tomorrow?
Do you want to go eat
something tasty tomorrow?
I don't think I'll be hungry tomorrow.
Then let's watch a movie.
Do you like romance?
How about "Love in Titicaca"?
- I saw it yesterday.
- It opens in theaters tomorrow.
I see.
Well... I'll just be
straightforward with you.
I like you too, Chan Sung.
Too?
So I want to watch a movie with you...
and have dinner and get to know you more.
I'm sorry, but this is so out of the blue.
Can you give me some time to think it over?
Of course I can.
- For how long?
- About... 10 years?
Have a good day.
I'll meet with a client
and go straight home.
Okay.
Are you upset with me over something?
If it's because I didn't keep my promise...
to have lunch with you...
No way, it's not because of that.
Then what is it?
Do I have to explain
everything to you in detail?
Don't you know the constitution
states freedom to one's privacy?
Did I teach you that too?
No, I learned about that myself.
It's article 17 of the constitution.
That's not what's important right now.
Okay. I will respect
your freedom to your privacy.
But...
Let me ask you something.
Between "Avatar" that you saw in 2009,
and "What's Wrong With That Lawyer"
we saw last week,
which one did you like better?
What?
Which one was better, and which
remains more in your memory?
"Avatar" was interesting
because of the unique content,
and I enjoyed relating to
"What's Wrong With That Lawyer".
Does that mean you liked both of them?
You can't give up both?
You're so mean, Mr. Kwon!
I'll see you on the day of the trial.
Okay. Contact me if there are
any other documents you need.
- Good day, sir.
- Okay.
Contact the witness who will
come to the hearing next week,
confirm whether he will come or not,
and send him the location.
She sent two O's?
What is wrong with her?
Welcome.
Maybe I should've reserved
someplace with a private room.
Yun Seo, is it okay to eat
at an open place like this?
No problem. I'll just sit
in a corner like this.
Mr. Kwon isn't coming again tonight?
Did you ever see him coming
voluntarily to a team dinner?
Over there.
He has participated voluntarily.
- Cheers.
It's been a while since we all gathered.
Ms. Dan, why are you drinking so hurriedly?
She was rejected again.
You know, that guy
from the Thunder Express.
Really?
Gosh, you fell for him
quick as a lightning bolt,
and got rejected even more quickly.
You must be so busy, Ms. Dan.
Since you get dumped regularly once a week.
What did you say?
By the way, what happened?
This morning, you said
you weren't going to come.
What changed your mind?
Well...
Why are you looking at Yun Seo?
Is she the reason why you're here?
Yes, I came to see Ms. Oh.
Gosh, that was so straightforward.
Do you guys have feelings for each other?
We don't have feelings for each other.
That's absurd.
- You're totally mistaken.
- Then...
why did he just make such
a suspicious comment?
There's nothing to be suspicious of.
I'm really just here to see Ms. Oh.
I wanted to ask her something.
What do you need to ask?
Lately, she's been working hard and
studying law in her spare time.
She was very enthusiastic.
But today, for some reason,
she was very insincere with her work
and kept being frustrated with me.
I figured she'd have a good reason,
so I came to resolve whatever
misunderstanding she might have.
Ms. Oh, can you tell me why
you're so angry at me?
You're asking me that in front of everyone?
Yes, I'd like to hear everyone's opinion.
If a majority of people
think I'm the one at fault,
I'm willing to fix what I did wrong.
So don't feel pressured,
and tell me what's bothering you.
You said it wasn't because
I didn't eat lunch with you.
Then by any chance, are you angry
because I didn't let you...
decorate my office in pink?
- Stop it.
- What's he saying?
Well, the thing is, I like pink.
Yes, I like pink.
And I decorated Mr. Kwon's office...
with some pink ornaments,
but he didn't like them.
So I just... But that's not why I'm angry.
Then are you angry because I
gave you a lot of work today?
Was it because I kept giving you
memo pads written with stuff to do?
You're so inhumane.
You should've gone up to her and
asked her politely face to face.
Even I'd feel upset if you just
wrote something on a memo pad...
and threw it on my desk.
- Right?
- No.
That's not why I'm angry. It's not...
To be honest, I didn't really
have a reasonable reason.
I think I ended up reacting sensitively...
because I was hungry.
Yes, that's right.
I'm sorry for causing a misunderstanding,
Mr. Kwon.
No, it's okay. I'm glad we
resolved our misunderstanding.
Gosh, it was nothing serious.
Now that you've reconciled,
you guys should clink glasses.
No, that's not necessary.
He must feel at ease now that you
guys resolved your misunderstanding.
Go on.
Cheers.
Goodness, this is nice.
Eat up.
Okay.
Mr. Kwon.
I'd like to have a word with you.
Sure.
I thought we were all good.
What more is there to talk about?
Why did you do that?
Why did you have to do that?
- What do you mean?
- It was our personal issue.
It should've stayed between the two of us.
Why did you have to blab
about it to everyone?
"Blab"?
As I told you earlier, I wanted to hear...
everyone's opinion.
And if a majority of people...
Do you think this is a trial?
The act of checking who's right and
who's wrong in front of everyone...
is no different from a trial.
I'm sorry if it offended you.
But we managed to resolve
our misunderstandings...
Do you really think we resolved
our misunderstandings?
Nothing's resolved between us.
Do you know why?
It's because there's another reason why...
I'm angry at you.
What do you mean?
Why did you eat pasta without me?
Why didn't you take me with you?
I wanted to have pasta as well!
Are you saying you were upset all day...
because I didn't take you
with me to eat pasta?
Let's eat pasta tomorrow.
- Pasta...
- Why did you do that?
Why did you have pasta...
with someone else?
I'm so annoyed.
It's so annoying.
Gosh, I'm so upset.
I wanted to eat pasta too.
Hey, you're home.
Hey.
By the way, Joo Won told me
that he saw you earlier.
I heard you ate pasta with Yeo Reum today.
- Is pasta the problem again?
- What do you mean "again"?
It's my first time mentioning it.
So what about it? What about pasta?
What's so wrong about eating pasta?
I'm jealous.
What? You're jealous?
Of course. I may have
broken up with Yeo Reum,
but that doesn't mean I'm over her.
So it's very natural to get angry
at the fact that the girl I like...
had pasta with someone else.
If someone gets angry at you for
eating pasta with someone else,
does that mean that person likes you?
What?
She likes me?
Hyuk Joon.
Should we go to the beach?
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
You need to go to work.
Yes, I need to go to work.
Did you get drunk yesterday
and make a mistake again?
I wonder who invented alcohol.
I guess you did make a mistake.
I'm the one who's curious.
Who in the world...
is responsible for making you
get in trouble all the time?
What did you do this time?
- I don't know.
- Just tell me what happened.
I need to know in order to help
you get out of whatever you did.
I don't know, okay?
I just want to be alone!
Here?
We're almost there.
Already? We're here already?
What am I going to do?
What am I going to say to him?
Hello.
Yes, good morning.
Ms. Oh.
- Yes?
- Please check if the sentencing...
of yesterday's trial got delivered to us.
And please check if the court filed...
the petition of appeal for
case number 2018G-327.
Okay.
Hey, Mr. Kwon.
Well...
About what I said to you yesterday...
Yes? Which part?
Well...
I asked you why you ate
pasta with someone else...
instead of eating it with me.
I only said that as a friend.
- A friend?
- Yes.
Women tend to be like that.
For example, when your best friend
at school leaves you out...
and eats tteokbokki with another friend,
it makes you feel really
left out and upset.
It makes you feel as if you
lost your best friend.
And to be frank, the two of us...
are like best friends at the firm.
- Best friends?
- Yes.
We're totally best friends.
We work so close to each other,
we eat together,
and we handle cases together.
I mean, how much closer can we get?
But I felt a bit upset...
when it seemed as though...
you were closer with someone else.
It's childish, isn't it?
Not only do I look young on the outside,
but I also have a very young mindset.
So please forget about
what happened yesterday.
- Okay?
- Yes, okay.
Mr. Kwon, Mr. Yeon wishes to see you.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
What on earth is wrong with you?
- So what do you want to say?
- Didn't I mention it yesterday?
I did, didn't I?
I said that we had some good news.
Our law firm will take
on a high-profile case.
Has it been decided then?
Well, you know...
Give this a read.
This too.
Isn't this the Im Yun Hee Case?
It's the hottest case right now.
Take the case and have it
declared self-defense.
- I can't.
- What? Why not?
You should be grateful for such a big case,
not refuse it.
It's not that. I just don't have the time.
I'm currently working on a total 32 cases.
Still.
You can't pass up on an
opportunity like this.
If that's the case, take it yourself.
You're not exactly busy these days.
You won't be asked on more TV shows anyway.
Please don't bring that up.
I'll be declining them anyway.
I now have PTSD.
I was only under the weather,
but I got some mean comments.
"Did he really pass the bar?"
"Did you see him tremble?"
"Maybe he's not really a lawyer."
I couldn't be more humiliated,
so don't mention TV shows to me ever again.
Mr. Yeon, the...
Don't ever mention it again.
- The...
- Stop it!
The sitting cushion.
This isn't what you sit on.
It's a blanket.
Anyway, you're taking the case.
It must be because you
advocate public interest.
The women's organization
specifically wants you on the case.
("From Victim of Domestic Violence
to Murder Suspect")
("Former Husband Died
in a Fire 5 Years Ago")
Read these and find any
articles related to the case.
Sure.
I saw this on the news.
Are you the lead attorney on this?
Yes, so it seems.
That's great.
If someone as talented as you defends her,
her claims of self-defense will be proved.
Do you think that this was self-defense?
Yes.
Her husband beat her badly,
so she reacted in the spur of the moment.
It's not simple though.
Also, there are preconditions needed
for this to have been self-defense.
Preconditions?
(Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum)
Ms. Yoo, Ms. Im Yun Hee will be here soon.
All right. We're keeping it simple today.
She's here!
In order for it to have been self-defense,
an attack must've been made
against her or a third-party.
Also, that attack must have
happened in front of her.
Lastly, even if it were to protect herself,
she shouldn't have used excessive force.
Simply speaking, she can't
have crossed the line...
even if it were to save herself.
For instance, let's say
someone slapped you.
You can't retaliate with a weapon.
The force used wasn't reasonable,
so it isn't self-defense.
There were many cases like this before,
but the Supreme Court ruled
against self-defense.
The prosecution will use
that as precedence.
Then you can set a new precedent...
by having it ruled as self-defense.
She could've intentionally
killed her husband.
Anyway, please search for more articles.
Sure.
Ms. Im.
I will now call you a suspect.
You have the right to remain silent...
and refuse to answer any questions.
Choosing to keep silent
won't be used against you,
and you may have a lawyer
present at these interviews.
Do you understand these rights?
Will you have a lawyer present...
or shall we begin the questioning?
Why did you want to see me again?
Are you busy?
I was studying up on Ms. Im's case.
- Do you see any holes?
- I'm not sure.
I think I should meet her
and talk to her first.
Once a case becomes yours,
you always do your best.
Did you call me here to check on...
whether I was doing my best?
Oh, please.
Why would that have been my intention?
Can you pick out a tie for me?
This makes me look sexy...
while this makes me look young and dandy.
Which is better?
What on earth are you doing?
I've been asked on a TV show.
I'm having an interview here at the firm.
Didn't you just tell me that
you were too traumatized...
to be on TV anymore?
Confucius said...
that our greatest glory
is not in never failing,
but in rising every time we fail.
I failed my first TV show
because of the nerves,
but I will rise despite that failure.
Even if I fail again, I will rise again.
I'll get going then.
I'm too exhausted and in need of caffeine.
I'll take mine strong. Hold on.
What about Ms. Oh?
What do we do?
The interview crew has a busy schedule...
and doesn't know
when exactly it'll be here.
Being spotted by the crew will
only put her on the spot.
We can't ask her to spend all
day at a coffee shop though.
I guess it'll all work out, right?
I'm sure there's a place for
her to hide in this firm.
Mr. Sexy?
Mr. Fresh?
Is this better?
- Go with sexy.
- Mr. Sexy it is.
This is much better.
Would you like a cup of coffee too?
No, I'll get my own.
Ms. Oh Jin Sim,
I'm going to the detention center
to meet Ms. Im tomorrow.
Would you like to come too?
- Me too?
- Yes.
Only lawyers are allowed to talk to her,
but being there...
will help you with your career in law.
Of course. It'll be better
than never visiting it.
Thank you for being so thoughtful.
We should drink our coffee.
The detention center? Doesn't that mean...
a decently long car ride?
Then, the two of us...
It'll be a fairly long ride,
so I had better be prepared.
I'm going there to work.
What should I wear tomorrow?
Hold on. A bad outfit
will lower my spirits.
I won't be able to focus on work properly.
I won't be able to focus on work...
if my skin is too dry either.
I must be such a workaholic.
♫ Yes, everything is so new for me ♫
♫ Something that has a feeling, you know? ♫
♫ Whatever it is, make it hip and elegant ♫
♫ I'm pretty picky ♫
♫ I'm good at pretending I don't know ♫
♫ Don't be discouraged, be careful ♫
♫ Yes, I'm like thunder ♫
♫ I shine ♫
♫ Look out for me, it's about to get noisy (say) ♫
♫ Hi lovely! We're beautiful,
no matter how we doodley ♫
♫ It's too hard, tell me with easier words ♫
♫ Can you see my heart? (Hey!) ♫
Good morning, Mr. Kwon.
That neck-tie...
looks good on you.
Your necklace is pretty too.
♫ Don't act like you don't know ♫
It's cold, so let's get in.
♫ So what you gonna do?
What you gonna do? Woo hoo! ♫
It feels nice to be out on a drive.
It's not a drive. We're going
to the detention center.
We're in the car, so it's a drive.
Yes, this is Kwon Jung Rok.
Yes, I understand.
That was a call from the detention center.
Visiting hours has been
postponed for two hours.
Really?
It's almost time for lunch,
so let's drop by somewhere and eat.
Actually, I...
made some lunch boxes.
Lunch boxes?
It's a waste of time looking
for restaurants anyway.
We can save time and focus more on work.
It's also my dream to eat
a lunch box outside...
while enjoying a beautiful view.
Well, since we have a lot
of time, let's go then.
I have it.
Shall we just go inside and eat?
I'll just eat here.
Why? It's so cold out here.
You said it's your dream.
Your cooking is better than I thought.
How bad did you think I was?
I once shot a drama as
a chef of Korean food.
I learned from an expert back then...
and I can make Korean food like
this even with my eyes closed.
As an actress, you must experience
living as various types of people.
It sounds very interesting.
Back then, I was really happy.
When do you feel that you're happy?
When I get my paycheck?
Goodness. You said you became
an attorney because of the money.
You really love money, don't you?
It's too cold. Let's go inside.
If you catch a cold
or something, it's my loss.
What?
Why is it your loss?
You're the star of our law firm.
If you catch a cold from this
picnic and don't come to work,
can you imagine how sorry I would feel?
I'm saying, it's an extremely
huge loss for our law firm.
- Can you hand me that?
- Okay.
If you're cold, there are
always pockets to keep you warm.
Really?
- Thank you.
- No, wait.
I meant, put your hands
inside your pockets.
I'm sorry.
Where are my pockets again?
Se Won, isn't it uncomfortable
staying at your friend's home?
It is. He's a total cranky guy.
It must be uncomfortable staying
with him over the weekend.
How about watching a movie with me?
That sounds more uncomfortable.
It's Prosecutor Yoo Yeo Reum.
Ms. Yoo must be pretty frustrated lately...
because of the Im Yun Hee Case.
Why? Is something not going well?
I heard Mr. Im really wanted to
take on the Im Yun Hee Case,
but it went to Ms. Yoo.
I heard Mr. Im has a huge grudge
and is giving her a hard time.
Is she the newbie who is
working with Se Won now?
Why do they look so close?
Are they dating?
I heard her dad is a high-ranking
official at the Blue House.
The son of a hospital owner and
a daughter of a Blue House official.
They sound like the perfect match.
Don't you think?
I guess.
Doesn't Se Won and that newbie
look good together?
They're both from rich families.
It's better than...
the son of a hospital owner and
a daughter of a suspect for fraud.
That's just absurd.
Come to think of it,
you're truly something.
Your dad was suspected of committing fraud,
but your ex-boyfriend didn't indict him...
and ended up being kicked
out to the countryside.
But how could you be so brazen about this?
If I were you, I won't last a second here.
What's your point?
We all have our own place in this world.
No matter how hard you try,
you won't become more than
an ordinary prosecutor.
I know you're trying so desperately
because you know that too.
You want to do whatever it
takes to be successful.
- That's enough.
- Do you think...
the chief prosecutor gave
you the Im Yun Hee Case...
because you're competent?
It's because you're a woman...
and he knows there's a way he can use you.
If you understand, stop acting up so much.
Do you want to wait in the car?
No. I'll take a look around too.
As I told you, you can't come
with me to the meeting room.
I told you, I already know that.
Are people detained in here
all waiting for trials...
like Im Yun Hee?
That's not always the case.
Some have already been sentenced...
and some are in the process
of a trial or waiting for it.
Oh, my. It's two o'clock.
You should get going.
It's cold. You should just wait in the car.
Why? Are you worried?
Yes. I'm worried.
If you catch a cold,
it's a loss for me as well.
What? Why?
If you catch a cold, there
will be a delay in work,
and I'll eventually have
more work on my shoulders.
And if you happen to pass
on your cold to me...
Gosh. Seriously, you're so mean.
Satisfied?
It's very cold outside.
Stop being stubborn. Take a quick
look around, and wait in the car.
What was that?
Was he just worried about me?
What was that? What?
Ms. Im.
Can you tell me...
what happened that day in detail?
I know it's hard to bring back that memory,
but you must tell me
everything that happened...
that day without leaving anything out.
Do you admit to the charges...
of you murdering your husband?
Do you have regrets for...
what you did?.
I'm very well aware that you've been
a victim of domestic violence...
for so many years.
However, that alone is not enough...
to justify your murder.
Then...
what do you think I should've done?
Should I have died instead?
(Prosecutor: Yoon Yeo Reum)
(Im Yun Hee, Murder)
I really think she was only
trying to defend herself.
What do you think? It was an
act of self-defense, right?
I don't think I should
jump to conclusions yet.
I guess you feel more confused now
that you've met her in person.
Then how about this? While you drive,
I'll read this more meticulously.
If I read it thoroughly enough,
I might find a breakthrough.
Trust me.
Okay.
♫ Left home, out on my own ♫
♫ Had to leave 'cause I had no choice ♫
I thought she was going
to find a breakthrough.
♫ To find what I've lost through the years ♫
♫ Through all the noise, yeah ♫
♫ I see it clear ♫
♫ Naming lights is the life I live ♫
♫ Sing my song for a thousand loud ♫
My goodness.
I just wanted to think for a little while,
but I guess I ended up dozing off.
You should've woken me up when we got here.
I felt sorry to wake you up
because you were so sound asleep.
- Did you wait a long time?
- No.
Did I make any mistakes while I was asleep?
I'm not really sure
if I can call this a mistake.
But you did snore a lot.
I snored? Me?
Goodness, there's no way. I don't snore.
I was joking.
Why would you make a
joke looking so serious?
But is snoring that big of a deal?
Of course.
I only want you to think I'm pretty and...
You want me to think that?
Yes, because...
It's because you're so strict.
I feel like you'll criticize
me if I loosen up too much.
I'll be off now.
Go home safely.
I must've been crazy. Why would
I say something like that?
Hey, Mr. Lee. Yes.
I urgently need you to look
into something for me.
Im Yun Hee lived with her
dad ever since her mom...
ran away from home because
her dad was very abusive.
But her dad disappeared 10 years
ago and has been MIA ever since.
It's been 10 years since
her dad disappeared?
Then he must already be registered as dead.
Yes.
Her mom ran away from home.
Her dad disappeared and
is assumed to be dead.
Her ex-husband died in a fire.
And the husband she remarried...
What a terrible life.
Yes.
After she graduated high
school, she made a living...
by working as a cashier,
a saleswoman at a mall, and so on.
She also worked in insurance.
Did you just say "insurance"?
Do you think she'll be
able to get acquitted?
I'm not sure. The main issue will be
whether the murder was accidental...
or planned with a means
to get insurance money.
Ms. Im used to work in insurance,
so they'll be suspicious of that.
But about Ms. Im...
The report said her ex-husband had
a record of having committed violence.
So why do you think she ended
up remarrying a guy...
who was also very violent?
One would think she'd avoid men like that.
I once appeared on a drama
as a psychotherapist.
And there was a woman who habitually...
forgave her violent husband every
time he begged and apologized.
I heard that's also a
psychological problem.
I already requested a doctor...
to conduct a psychiatric evaluation on her.
(Yoo Yeo Reum)
I'm quite taken aback.
You already know how important
this case is to me.
Do you really have to stand
on the opposite side?
It's against the ethics of
an attorney to turn down...
a client's request.
If I start being picky
about every single case,
I won't be able to defend anyone.
Yes, I know that. But there's
something you should know.
The court has never acknowledged
any form of murder...
as self-defense.
That's not important.
I'm going to do my best to
reveal what really happened.
I'll make sure she only gets
punished for what she deserves.
And if she's innocent, I'm going
to make sure she gets acquitted.
That's my job.
She'll never be able to get acquitted.
Because that's my job.
- The prosecution is wrong!
- Today is Im Yun Hee's first trial.
It is known that she accidentally
ended up murdering him...
while she was trying to
stop her husband's assault.
However, the prosecution indicted her...
for murder instead of
involuntary manslaughter.
The defendant, Im Yun Hee,
was legally married to
the victim, Kim Yeong Tae.
And on January 21, 2019,
while she was getting assaulted...
by the victim in her house,
she used a kitchen knife to
threaten Kim Yeong Tae...
and murdered him by stabbing him
in the stomach and chest.
The late victim habitually
committed domestic violence,
so this might seem as an
act of self-defense...
assuming that the victim could no
longer put up with the assault.
However, if you take a look
at the autopsy result,
you'll be able to realize that
this was a planned murder.
How much of a possibility
is there for her...
to coincidentally stab her
husband right in the vital spot?
This is why the prosecution wishes
to indict the defendant for murder.
Attorney, please state your opinion
regarding the charges.
According to the paramedic
that was at the scene,
the defendant had broken two of her ribs...
and was injured enough to be
hospitalized for nine weeks.
Even if she did intend on murdering him,
how much of a possibility is there
for a small woman like her...
to stab him right in his vital
spot considering the fact...
that she was also severely injured?
Thus, I request that the
defendant gets acquitted...
by claiming that it was
an act of self-defense.
The only will that existed
at the crime scene...
was the defendant's will to survive.
She had no other will or
intention behind what happened.
From what I heard, your mother
ran away from home when you were 10.
May I ask you why?
She was getting beaten up by my drunk dad,
and she ended up hitting
her head on the floor.
She bled a lot,
and while my dad started looking
for something to hit my mom with,
she ran away.
She probably just wanted to stay alive.
After that incident,
I heard your dad started
beating you up as well.
Is that correct?
Yes. That's right.
Her father and her deceased husband...
were both violent men.
Your father must've been
tough for you to endure,
so why meet and marry men...
that were as violent as him?
Your Honor,
I bring a psychiatrist to the stand...
to better explain my client's situation.
At a glance, it may be hard to understand.
However, we become
accustomed to situations...
if we're in them long enough.
Could you explain that in detail?
Children who were abused at a young age...
can't properly tell that
it's not acceptable.
Naturally, they end up
picking up the habit too.
Also, if children aren't
in same situations,
they experience anxiety and stress.
And so the vicious cycle continues.
Here is the assessment you made
of Ms. Im's mental state.
"The subject, from a young age,"
"was exposed to a life
of physical violence."
"Therefore, it can't be said
that she is of sound mind."
That is what you wrote. Is this right?
Yes, that's my assessment.
So in your professional opinion,
Ms. Im might have not
been in her right mind...
at the time of this incident.
Am I safe to say that?
Yes.
That is all, Your Honor.
Prosecution, will you redirect?
Yes, Your Honor.
Ms. Im,
these are the bills...
of your first husband's
life insurance policy...
as well as the one of your father's
who disappeared 10 years ago.
Did you apply for them yourself?
Yes, that's right.
Your deceased husband Kim Yeong Tae...
also had a life insurance policy.
You knew that, right?
- Yes.
- Do you know for how much?
I don't.
Kim Yeong Tae has
a life insurance policy...
of 4.94 million dollars.
It's a large amount of money
for you to not have known.
That is all.
You're arguing insanity?
I get it. Even though she's
charged with murder,
she could get a reduced
sentence with an insanity plea.
That's a win for an attorney, isn't it?
Don't say that.
Both self-defense and
an insanity plea are...
written in the book of criminal law.
I won't let you win with an insanity plea,
so don't even bother trying.
This isn't a case that you can win.
Why are you obsessed with this case?
Because this is the only way.
You were born with a silver spoon,
so you'll never understand it.
- You're back.
- Welcome back.
Hello, everyone.
Ms. Oh, where's Mr. Kwon?
He stayed to talk to the
lead prosecutor on the case.
I was asked to head back alone.
How did the trial go?
Articles have been exploding online.
You don't look so happy.
Did it go badly for our side?
Yes, although...
we were doing all right when Mr. Kwon...
argued the insanity defense.
However, the life insurance
policy of the deceased husband...
swayed a lot of the votes.
Just how much would she receive?
4.9 million dollars.
4.9 million dollars?
No wonder everyone stirred.
Tell me about it. Even I'm wondering...
if she did it for the money.
Poor Mr. Kwon.
The news is all over this case.
Losing it will put a big
dent in his career.
Don't say that when
the verdict is still out.
Mr. Kwon.
I'm back.
Excuse me, Mr. Kwon.
Don't take what the others
said too seriously.
I don't.
Anyone would think so
after today's outcome.
Right.
Still,
I think that you'll win this case.
To be honest, I thought that...
people who are stiff and logical...
were the type to become lawyers.
I now think it's more for the warm-hearted.
For someone like you.
Despite what many think,
you have a warm heart...
and you're very thoughtful.
There was a time when I felt like...
I was alone in this world.
I had no one taking my side back then.
Life seemed impossible.
Back then,
if I had someone like you in my life,
it would've been better.
That's what I've been thinking.
That's how great of a lawyer you are,
so I trust that you'll find
a solution for this case.
Look at the time.
Why are you still here?
I was looking up precedents
regarding self-defense.
I wanted to be of help somehow.
Would you like to have dinner with me?
Sure. I was actually starving.
Then let's head out.
You know,
I became a lawyer...
because I wanted to...
take people's sides instead
of punishing them.
Then why did you say before...
that it was to earn a lot of money?
I felt too embarrassed
to tell you the truth...
back then.
Then why are you being honest with me now?
Because...
what you said made me want to be honest.
Thank you for saying
that you believe in me.
Also, if there comes a time...
when you feel like you're
alone in this world...
and that there's no one
to take your side again,
I'll be there for you.
♫ So much that I don't know ♫
Mr. Kwon.
♫ Honestly, it's hard ♫
♫ I don't know the right timing ♫
♫ Why do things keep messing up? ♫
There's something I want to say to you.
♫ My heart has slow footsteps ♫
But...
♫ So with all my strength, I chased after you ♫
I won't say it right now.
However,
I will someday tell you...
the exact emotions...
that I'm feeling right this moment.
Ms. Oh Jin Sim.
Do you...
like me?
What?
♫ You're probably my ♫
♫ One, one, one, my one ♫
♫ The only one, one, one, you are ♫
♫ If this is love, love, love, if love ♫
♫ What should I do, what should I do?
What if this is the love ♫
♫ I'm looking at you for a while ♫
♫ Wondering if you feel the same way ♫
♫ Of course, I really don't know ♫
♫ It's still so hard ♫
(Touch Your Heart)
A modern woman who works.
I look like a workaholic,
and it's really sexy.
Don't you think you're making
my Yun Seo work too hard?
Your Yun Seo?
- Stop it.
- It's because I care.
He cares?
Would you like a cup of coffee?
He told me not to make you work too hard.
Your boyfriend.
You've never dated anyone, have you?
You don't seem to bright
when it comes to women.
Someone told me that I'm
going to win no matter what.
So believe in me and wait until I win.
It's going to take a new turn.
He could be the only witness of this case.
But he could also be another suspect.
♫ What do I do? What if love? ♫
♫ You're probably my ♫
♫ One, one, one, my one ♫