(Episode 14)
Wait.
Mr. Kwon? He's not in his office right now.
There's nothing I can say on his behalf.
I'm sorry.
It's a new day, but we're still
getting a bunch of calls.
I wonder if we'll end up
spending the entire day...
answering calls again.
Our law firm homepage is frozen.
People might even present a petition
to the government at this rate.
What are we going to do?
On top of that, we've been getting
a lot fewer clients lately.
We haven't gotten a client
ever since what happened.
- Here's this week's schedule.
- Thanks.
- Mr. Yeon.
- Yes?
Don't you think you should
make up with Mr. Kwon now?
- What?
- He took the case already.
It's too late for him to turn back.
He already has a lot of
people demotivating him.
If you add onto that,
it'll only give him a hard time.
What about me?
How do you think I feel having
to go through all this?
Gosh, he really is a stubborn one.
It was exactly the same five years ago...
Never mind.
Anyway, he should be the one
approaching me to apologize.
Why should I reach out to him...
after what he's done?
You should get back to work.
(Attorney, Kwon Jung Rok)
(Who Is the Culprit?
Im Yun Hee or Park Su Myeong?)
What is it?
I have something to tell you.
You acted like you were never
going to talk to me again.
What is it?
What's this? Is it an apology letter?
It's my resignation letter.
What did you just say?
A resignation letter?
I feel like I've caused a lot
of damage to our firm...
after having decided to
defend Park Su Myeong.
So I think I should quit in
order to minimize the damage...
So you're just going to quit?
Do you think it'll all be
fine if you just run away?
Is that what you really think?
Do you really think quitting
is the best decision?
I'll leave after I'm done
with all the cases...
- I'm currently in charge of.
- Hey.
This really isn't the way to go.
You can't do this to me.
I never once...
thought of you as my employee.
To me, you were a precious friend
and a trustworthy brother.
I thought of you more
dearly than my own family.
But on top of having taken such
a huge case without telling me,
you're now going to quit?
The law firm is receiving
unnecessary criticism because of me.
No one can work properly
because people keep calling us,
and we haven't even been
getting any new clients.
But even so, I must defend this case.
I might've ruined someone's life.
I need to do what I can to
put things back to normal.
This is the best I can do.
Okay, fine. Do as you please!
I don't need an irresponsible
person like you.
So just do as you please.
You can defend whomever you want.
And you also go ahead and quit.
The defendant, Hong Jung Su,
is a self-made CEO...
who has about five million dollars.
He's been refusing to get divorced
because he doesn't wish...
to divide his property with his wife...
Let me repeat that. He's been refusing...
He's been...
He's been refusing to get divorced...
My wish is for you to
stay steady as a rock.
Just like you have been so far,
I believe that you'll serve justice.
Hey, Mr. Park.
Did you call because I asked
you to recommend an attorney?
Yes, did you find anyone?
Gosh, I don't care about how good they are.
They just need to be responsible.
It's fine as long as they
don't suddenly hand in...
a resignation letter out of the blue.
Yes.
Mr. Yeon, that's my cell phone.
Yes, I know that.
What are we going to do about the mood?
(Five Days Left Until
Park Su Myeong's Appeal)
(Does His Attorney, Kwon Jung Rok,
Not Have Any Countermeasures?)
I wonder if he's okay.
There's no one I can ask about him.
I think I saved his number last time.
(Prosecutor Kim Se Won)
(Kim Se Won)
- Hey.
- Where are you?
Let's have a drink.
No, I'm tired.
The thing is, someone wants to see you.
This person's having a
hard time letting you go.
What's that supposed to mean?
Hey, over here.
What are you doing? Get over here.
Sit down.
I was really surprised
when I got a call from Joon Gyu.
You're not students anymore.
Why are you guys fighting like kids?
Jung Rok, I heard you even
wrote a resignation letter.
I mean, I understand that you want
to quit because you don't want...
to cause trouble to the firm.
But you should've made
amends with Joon Gyu first.
How can you just hand in your resignation?
And from what I can gather,
Joon Gyu isn't wrong.
Not to gamble on uncertainty
is solid advice.
Your boss has a right to say that.
Must you be so petty?
Come to think of it,
I was a little hard on him.
I said that he'd be
branded as an attorney...
who takes on cases for a show.
A show? That is a bit harsh.
Were you always this cruel?
Se Won, that's enough.
It's my fault for taking a
case without his approval.
You took a case without
your boss' approval?
Do you not respect your superiors?
It must've been because I'm stubborn.
You know how cautious Mr. Kwon is.
Why tell him to drop the case
when you know him so well?
Are you kidding me?
Are you trying to help
us or make us angrier?
Pick a plan and stick to it.
Were my actions weird just now?
Yes.
Anyway, from what I can tell,
you both were wrong in this case.
Let's just say that you're
equally responsible.
Here.
Here you go.
So... Take this.
Anyway, let's bury the hatchet now.
Come on.
Darn it.
All right then. I'll leave you two alone...
to talk this out.
- This isn't a blind date you know.
- Can't you just stay?
Let go of me.
I don't care how you do it.
Just talk it out.
I'll get going then.
Stay.
Stay a little longer.
He can't just ask me here and leave.
Darn.
Why did he have to do this?
Darn it.
Prosecutor Kim,
thank you for helping me
with my case before.
I can't believe it took
me so long to thank you.
Anyway, that being said,
how is Mr. Kwon doing?
(Anyway, that being said,
how is Mr. Kwon doing?)
No, that's too obvious.
Anyone can tell that I'm anxious to ask...
how Mr. Kwon's doing.
Also, I've already asked the people
at the law firm too many times.
Mr. Kwon.
I mean, Jung Rok.
Don't you know me?
Did you think that I wouldn't
understand your wishes...
and really fire you?
Has our time together...
been nothing more than a thin relationship?
I'm sorry.
You asked...
whether or not I had responsibility
or a sense of belonging...
regarding our law firm.
What you said is right.
From start to finish, I've been nothing...
but selfish and opinionated.
I took this case to ease my mind...
and not be embarrassed by myself.
That's why I thought I should
endure the criticism alone.
I didn't want to cause
trouble to you or the firm,
and resigning was the best way...
to achieve that.
I know.
I know that.
I know why you chose to resign.
Still,
I can't see you get hurt anymore.
I know this will hurt you
like it did five years ago,
so I can't...
sit back and watch it eat you up alive.
Jung Rok...
Do you know what I regret most in my life?
I think we must stand with the victims.
What the victims are saying is true.
I'm certain of the germicide's harmfulness.
I checked the report that said it was safe.
It turns out that the lab
fabricated the conditions...
in order to get the results they wanted.
Wait...
Still, you're representing
Sejong Chemicals.
Does your boss know about this?
I think my boss...
was in on the fabricated report too.
Hey.
Are you trying to blow the whistle?
You're not, right?
No, of course not.
This resulted in 250 victims.
Even though I'm representing the defendant,
I still can have a conscience, can't I?
Jung Rok, are you insane?
Cut this nonsense out.
You know how powerful Daehan Law Firm is.
A whistleblower, you say?
If you do, they'll bury you as an attorney.
I'm scared too.
However, I can't turn
a blind eye and cover my ears.
Once becomes twice,
and I might end up...
becoming a monster with no conscience.
That is what I'm more scared of.
I will ask the bar association...
for the nullification of your law license.
Violation of attorney-client privilege.
That seems like a good enough reason.
Article 2 Section 3 of the
Attorneys' Code of Ethics...
states that attorneys must not
commit an act of misconduct...
and always have the
public's interest at heart.
I will live my life as an attorney...
that at least has a shred of conscience.
Jung Rok, you crazy idiot.
I can't believe you.
You insane jerk.
(Yeram Law Firm)
Hello, sir.
I'm Yeon Joon Gyu, an attorney
of the 32nd group of graduates.
He's a kindhearted and talented attorney.
I can't have him be crushed
by Daehan Law Firm.
How can I reject when you're
the one who's asking?
Thank you, sir.
I will never forget this.
Thank you.
The biggest regret in my life...
is not stopping you five years ago.
I had to watch you crumble...
before my very eyes.
Still, what is the best
thing I've done though?
I'm glad I saved you five years ago.
You joined my law firm not long after,
and we powered through
tough times together.
We may not have long conversations,
but we've become friends
who count on one another.
That's who you are to me.
So you resigning from the firm like that...
made me rethink my life.
So let's do this together.
I can't...
just let you crumble like this.
So even though we have
our work cut out for us,
we'll push through together.
Now...
I won't waver.
Will it be like walking
on thin ice again today?
I know, it's so uncomfortable.
- Good morning.
- Hello.
- Ms. Dan, Mr. Lee.
We'll hold an emergency meeting
in five minutes, so get ready.
- Pil Gi, go tell Mr. Choi.
- Okay.
An emergency meeting? What is it about?
It's just about saving someone.
- Saving someone? Who?
- Who else?
It's Mr. Kwon, the nation's most-hated man.
- The nation's most-hated man?
- That's right.
With all those calls of complaint
and malicious comments,
you really are the nation's most-hated man.
- Get ready, then.
- Okay.
Thank you, guys.
What happened?
Until last night, they acted like
they'd never see each other.
I know.
I wonder what happened
to melt their hearts...
that were frozen solid.
They probably had a drink and made up.
Well, get ready!
Cue!
Cut! Okay.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
- Great job, everyone.
- Good job.
- Good job, Yun Seo.
Thank you, everyone.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Good job.
Good job, Ms. Oh Jin Sim.
- Yun Seo, what's wrong?
- I'm just...
thinking of Mr. Kwon.
This is where he and I used to walk.
Hold on, Hyuk Joon.
Excuse me, Prosecutor Kim!
Ms. Oh. What brings you here?
I was shooting a drama.
How could we bump into
each other like this?
I was actually thinking of contacting you.
Me? About what?
Well... Last time,
since you took care of the
stalking case for me,
I wanted to thank you.
Because of that?
And also...
Just tell me honestly.
You want to ask about Jung Rok, right?
You catch on quite quick.
So how is...
Mr. Kwon doing?
The public seems to be
criticizing him heavily.
- Is he doing okay?
- Of course not.
After he took that case,
he hasn't even been eating properly.
I'm afraid he might faint
or something soon.
Yun Seo, we should get going now.
You're going to be late for your schedule.
- I should go now.
- Okay.
Please take good care of...
Mr. Kwon.
Maybe I shouldn't have said that.
She seems very worried.
Well, I told her to make her worried.
On January 21, 2019,
while being assaulted by
her husband, Kim Yeong Tae,
Im Yun Hee was indicted on
the charges of stabbing...
her husband two times.
Im Yun Hee's father went missing
and was presumed dead,
and her former husband
also died from a fire,
which raised suspicion
from the prosecution.
It's because immediately after
their death, Im Yun Hee...
received a large insurance
payout under their names.
The court sentenced Park Su Myeong...
to 20 years in prison,
and Im Yun Hee was released on bail.
Currently, Im Yun Hee has
received 2.73 million dollars...
out of the total 4.49 million,
and has disappeared.
She disappeared?
Why was she in such a hurry when
she didn't receive the whole payout?
This definitely seems fishy.
But Park Su Myeong is claiming
something different suddenly.
That he only stabbed him once.
If he really stabbed him just
once like Park Su Myeong said,
there might be another culprit,
or an accomplice.
Do you have any leads?
While I was looking into
Im Yun Hee's whereabouts,
a witness stated that Im Yun Hee...
came to receive the insurance
payout with an unknown man.
Currently, Im Yun Hee has no
family members that are known of.
Then who was it?
It hasn't been long since
her husband died. She already...
No. It might've been a relationship
that started before his death.
As you all know, for cases
related to affairs and divorces,
I'm one of the nation's number one experts.
My gut tells me they were having an affair.
Time out.
You said Im Yun Hee's former husband
also died from a fire 5 years ago.
Then there might be a possibility
that Im Yun Hee and that man...
schemed it together for the money.
It's quite convincing.
As for now, it's just an assumption.
First, our priority is to identify
the man in the surveillance camera.
Okay. Mr. Lee, you should...
look into Im Yun Hee's whereabouts
after she was released.
And also search all the surveillance
cameras near that area.
I'm certain the two of them must've
been caught on camera together.
Okay.
By the way, Mr. Yeon. It's been
a while since you sent out...
that vibe as a real attorney.
I agree. I forgot for a moment...
that you were an attorney.
Attorney Yeon.
Why does that sound insulting?
Attorney Yeon?
Do you know why I received a
loan to open this law firm?
Prosecutor Yeon, Judge Yeon.
It sounds really natural.
But if you match up Yeon
with 'Attorney', what is it?
Attorney Yeon.
Attorney Yeon, doesn't it
sound kind of lame?
I hate it when a title sounds lame. So...
That's why I became CEO Yeon
instead of Attorney Yeon.
- Attorney Yeon.
- Hey.
Anyway, if you have any more
opinions, let's talk again.
- Okay.
- Great job.
- Mr. Kwon,
if you need any help,
you can ask me anytime.
Sure. Thank you.
It'd be nice if he had a personal
secretary like Yun Seo right now.
Shall we hire a secretary for him?
But Ms. Hwang will be returning
soon from her maternity leave,
so it's not the right time
to choose another secretary.
I guess so. Then what should we do?
What about letting one of the
interns be Mr. Kwon's secretary...
Pick me! I can do a much
better job than Jong Hwa.
Please give me an opportunity.
I will not miss this kind of
rare chance that will never...
- come back again.
- Sure, do it.
We're choosing one person,
and you're the only one who applied.
You went through some tough competition.
Congratulations. Get ready then.
Yes, sir.
I was looking for
precedents on self-defense.
I wanted to be of help to you in any way.
Who knows? I might be able to see...
something that you missed.
I want to support you in any way I can.
- Yes?
- Hey.
As of today, Pil Gi will...
support you as your personal assistant.
I'm Kim Pil Gi.
I'll become an ace intern that
will be the perfect match for you.
I look forward to working with you.
He tends to overreact, but he's competent.
- Get to it then.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Kwon, what do you want
me to do from now on?
If you want me to find precedents,
I'll find them until I pull all
the ligaments in my wrists.
All right. Like you just said,
go look for some precedents.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Kwon, do you need any help?
- No, I'm good.
- Yes, sir.
Where are you going, Mr. Kwon?
I need to copy some files.
- There's something I have to see.
- Okay.
- I'll show you the way.
- No.
That's fine. If someone calls,
please write down a memo.
There's a diary inside the drawer.
You can read that and
get used to your work.
Okay. By the way, Mr. Kwon.
It's lunchtime soon.
What do you want to eat?
Shall I go to buy something for you?
No, thanks. I'll take care
of it on my own. Bye.
Okay. Goodbye, sir.
No matter how cornered it gets,
a tiger is still a tiger.
I'm going to see how Mr. Kwon...
overcomes this difficulty
with my own two eyes...
and take in and acquire
all his knowledge and tactics.
Oh, right. The diary.
This belongs to Ms. Oh.
After he took that case, he
hasn't even been eating properly.
I'm afraid he might faint
or something soon.
Why did you just sigh?
Are you having trouble
memorizing your lines?
No, I'm just a little tired. That's all.
You must be pretty exhausted.
But you're done for the day once
you finish shooting this scene.
So you can go home and get some rest.
Okay.
I'm getting a call from the law firm.
Yes, this is Oh Yun Seo.
Hi, Pil Gi.
- What brings you to call me?
- Well, the thing is,
I'll be assisting Mr. Kwon
starting from today.
And when I opened the drawer of the desk,
I noticed that you left behind...
your pen.
And I just wanted to ask...
if I could keep the pen as a memento.
Sure.
No, wait.
Yes, Mr. Lee.
I asked around about the
screenshot of the CCTV footage.
But I couldn't get anything new.
Okay, that will do for now.
Bye.
You're back, Mr. Kwon.
Yes.
Did you get any calls?
No, not really.
But you do have a guest.
The thing is,
I found Ms. Oh's pen in the drawer.
So I called and told her about it,
and she came to take it back.
I kept offering to send it to her...
via courier,
but she said she'll come
and get it herself...
because it's very important to her.
And she came as soon as she could.
Mr. Yeon asked me to come to his office,
so I'll be back a little later.
Well...
I came for my pen.
And I thought I'd say hello.
I'm the one who left that
document there, you know.
Yes, I know.
Gosh, you knew that,
but you never contacted me to thank me?
You should've thanked me after you got it.
I demand compensation.
It's only right that you
compensate me in return...
for such high-quality resource.
Article 734 of the Civil Act.
"A person who manages affairs
on behalf of another..."
"without being bound to do so..."
"shall conduct that management..."
"in the manner most advantageous
to his or herself."
You know that, right?
So as a means for compensating me,
you should treat me to a meal.
Or...
should I treat you to a meal?
Come to think of it, I did something
you never asked me to do,
so I'm pretty sure I made
you feel uncomfortable.
So let me treat you to a meal...
as a means to apologize.
What should we eat?
Let's eat something healthy.
Ms. Oh Jin Sim.
Did you forget...
that we broke up?
How could I forget?
Yes, I know that. But the thing is,
I'm worried about you.
You're going through a lot these days.
It hurt me a lot after I
saw the news articles.
Back when I used to have a hard time,
you were always there for me by my side.
But I can't do that for you...
because we're no longer a couple.
But I still came anyway.
"What if he's not happy to see me?"
"What if I only make him
feel uncomfortable?"
I was really worried, but I came anyway...
because I wanted to eat with you.
I was worried you might faint...
for working too hard without
even eating anything.
You don't need to worry
about stuff like that.
- Pardon?
- Like you just said,
we're not a couple anymore.
Mr. Kwon.
So don't worry about me...
and just focus on your career.
And forget about all the memories
you made while you were here.
♫ Don't leave yet, don't let go ♫
♫ That song is playing in my ears ♫
♫ Don't stop, there's still so much ♫
♫ I haven't told you yet ♫
♫ I can't let go of your small hand ♫
♫ That touched my left hand ♫
♫ When we looked into each other's eyes ♫
♫ I can't forget that moment ♫
♫ Hold my hand ♫
You were home? Why didn't
you open the door for me?
Yun Seo, I got you
a restorative beverage...
and some abalone soup for your health.
What's wrong? Is there something wrong?
All the sticky notes were gone.
- What?
- I heard Mr. Kwon...
is having a hard time these days.
So I visited him today...
because I got really worried.
But he didn't look at
me the way he used to.
And he also got rid of
all the sticky notes...
that I wrote for him.
I guess...
he's completely over me now.
I don't know how I'm
going to cope with that.
By the way, do you know
why Yun Seo came earlier?
She left behind a pen,
so she came to get it.
She came here to get her pen
amid her busy schedule?
That pen must really mean a lot to her.
I think I kind of get what that is.
There are things that
are precious to you...
although they might not seem
that way to other people.
Back when I was in elementary school,
I picked up a leaf bookmark on
my way to my grandma's house.
I think...
I'll feel really sad if I lose this.
Right.
Mr. Kwon?
I've been checking other CCTVs,
but nothing stands out.
I contacted those I know from my
detective days, so don't worry.
What's wrong?
The photograph of this evidence is weird.
In what way?
The blood splattered
everywhere in the attack,
but Park Su Myeong's
jacket seems almost clean.
The jacket you see is the
one the defendant...
wore on the day of the murder.
According to the lab result,
only a small amount...
of the suspect's blood
was found on the sleeve.
While it proves that...
my client attacked the victim,
it also can indicate that he
only stabbed the victim once.
(Prosecutor)
The fatal wound...
was the second stab to the victim's chest.
The knife ruptured an artery
connected to the heart...
and the victim died of excessive bleeding.
As you can see, the floor and
the walls are covered in blood.
It's because when the killer
pulled out the knife,
his blood sprayed like water
coming from a faucet.
So for the killer to have...
close to no blood on his clothes...
seems implausible.
Also, Im Yun Hee, who was
granted bail by the court,
recently cashed in only
half of her husband's...
4.93 million-dollar life insurance
and she is nowhere to be found.
Why did she go into hiding...
after giving up over two million dollars?
With all these facts combined,
can you still be sure...
that the prosecution proved
my client's guilt...
beyond a reasonable doubt?
(Judge)
Will the prosecution like to add anything?
Your Honor, I'd like to call
a witness to the stand.
The sole witness of this crime.
Here is Im Yun Hee.
Yun Hee!
(Witness)
Witness,
can I ask why you've been off the grid?
I needed to clear my head,
so I went on a vacation.
I see.
You were once the suspect of this murder...
and now you're the sole witness,
so let me ask you this.
The victim, Kim Yeong Tae.
Who stabbed him twice and killed him?
Yun Hee!
Su Myeong.
I'm sorry, Su Myeong.
Yun Hee, don't cry!
Yun Hee...
Witness, I ask you again.
Once in the abdomen and once in the chest.
Is Park Su Myeong who's
sitting over there...
the man who stabbed your husband
twice and killed him?
Yes, he is.
That is all.
But Yun Hee...
Yun Hee...
- Ms. Im!
- Mr. Kwon!
You claimed that she had vanished,
but she showed up today.
- What are your thoughts on that?
- Do you still think...
that the real killer is out there?
Many are criticizing
your choice to defend Mr. Park...
What happened?
What do you think happened?
It was a clean win.
I'm glad I got in touch
with Ms. Im when I did.
If not, it would've been a disaster.
By the way, how did we
get in contact with her?
Well, she called in person
and asked to be a witness.
("The Park Su Myeong Case:
Who Is the Real Killer?")
What on earth happened?
I thought that we had solid evidence.
Tell me about it.
I had no idea that Im Yun Hee...
would appear in court.
What do you think is the truth?
Do you believe her innocence?
She wouldn't have come
to court if she weren't.
I don't know what's happening,
but the public now
hates Mr. Kwon even more.
("Im Yun Hee's Testimony
Corners Attorney Kwon")
Yun Seo, stop reading that.
Reading it will only upset you more.
I can't take this anymore.
Yun Seo, can you start by...
just slapping me really hard?
What on earth are you doing?
No, I deserve it.
I deserve a slap from you.
Attorney Kwon...
didn't break up with you
because he doesn't like you.
Yes, Mr. Lee.
I have the CCTV footage.
It's near the bank where she
received the insurance money.
February 27, 3pm. It's that day.
It's the clearest video I could find,
but it's still tricky to identify anyone.
What is it?
There isn't one that shows his face.
But look at this though.
Can I get a fingerprint of it?
I have a feeling that it's possible.
I think it is too.
He didn't break up with you
because he doesn't like you.
He did so because he adores you that much.
We...
should break up.
Do you suddenly feel betrayed
now that you think about it?
Do you feel pressured
because of all the attention...
I'm getting?
Because of all the reasons
you just mentioned,
I've come to a conclusion that we
shouldn't date each other anymore.
So I think it would be
best that we break up.
He didn't mean it.
♫ So much that I don't know ♫
♫ Honestly, it's hard ♫
♫ I don't know the right timing ♫
♫ Why do things keep messing up? ♫
Are you off to work?
- What are you doing here?
- I packed you a meal.
Here.
Please enjoy.
♫ Each step you take ♫
Don't skip your meals.
- Ms. Oh...
- Filming will start soon,
so I should get going.
I hope it gives you energy
to kick butt at court today.
Make sure you eat it all.
♫ Oh love, what do I do? What if love? ♫
♫ You're probably my ♫
♫ One, one, one, my one ♫
♫ The only one, one, one, you are ♫
Mr. Kwon, would you like
to have dinner with me?
I know a restaurant that's secluded.
Let's go there.
♫ What if this is the love ♫
Why are you doing this?
If you keep coming like this,
someone might take a picture,
and you might be caught in a scandal.
Like I told you,
- you should forget about...
- I don't want to forget.
I'll decide whether I'll forget or not.
I'll do what I want to do,
and not forget you.
I'll long for you...
and come to see you if I'm worried,
and come see you...
when I miss you.
Su Myeong.
Is it tough in there?
I'm sorry, Su Myeong.
Don't cry, Yun Hee. Don't cry.
Don't cry, Yun Hee.
Su Myeong, all you did was to save me.
Su Myeong.
That day when you came to my house.
- Do you remember?
- I stabbed him.
I saved you. I stabbed him.
You're right.
You saved me.
But Su Myeong. Don't you remember...
stabbing him two times?
No, Yun Hee. I stabbed him once.
I stabbed him once.
No.
You stabbed him twice.
You killed him.
(Yeo Reum)
Yes, Yeo Reum.
I checked the identity
through the fingerprints.
But something's strange.
The fingerprints belong to a dead person.
What?
A dead person's fingerprints?
Choi Sang Ho.
He was arrested three times
for violence and once for fraud.
Choi Sang Ho?
- He is...
- That's right.
He's Im Yun Hee's ex-husband.
Do you mean her ex-husband is alive?
Yes. The bodies have been switched.
The person who died from
a fire wasn't Choi Sang Ho.
We've requested an arrest warrant
for Im Yun Hee and Choi Sang Ho.
Let's watch the video.
The man you see in this video
is the man who took...
the insurance payout with Im Yun Hee.
We were able to obtain his
fingerprints from this glass wall,
and after fingerprint analysis,
we found out his identity.
This man is...
Im Yun Hee's dead ex-husband, Choi Sang Ho.
How could this be possible?
How could a dead man...
be walking on the streets?
Choi Sang Ho, who was
supposedly dead due to a fire,
was in fact alive,
and he was an accomplice
to Im Yun Hee's crime.
Further, in order to check...
the identity of the man who
died in the fire accident,
I compared the dental records
of the corpse with...
Im Yun Hee's acquaintances,
and I was able to confirm the
real identity of the corpse.
It was Im Yun Hee's father,
who was known to have
been missing, Mr. Im Oh Joong.
Mr. Choi Sang Ho.
Is that your name?
You know you're the prime suspect
of the Kim Yeong Tae Case, right?
You have the right to take the Fifth,
but if you don't say anything,
you will take the full blame...
for everything.
Im Yun Hee is claiming...
you're the one who is solely
responsible for this crime.
No, that brat...
That brat made me do it. I'm a victim too.
Then, shall we begin with
the Kim Yeong Tae Murder Case?
Tell me what happened.
Yun Hee!
One week before the incident,
Yun Hee kept calling Park Su Myeong
to her house for a delivery.
Thank you for coming again.
She showed herself after being assaulted,
and brainwashed him with the same words.
I wish...
someone would kill him for me.
That jerk!
She kept saying she wished
someone could kill him for her.
Su Myeong.
Su Myeong, snap back into it.
- Yun Hee.
- Listen to me carefully.
Today, you weren't here.
You didn't see anything...
and didn't do anything, okay?
Don't tell anyone about this.
Can you promise me?
- Yes.
- Okay?
Go. Go now.
It's over. Come out.
What are you doing?
If you used him to kill him,
you should call the police.
Are you mad?
The police will suspect me too then.
Don't you know I'll become a
suspect if I'm at the scene?
First, I'll confess...
and when they find out
he's the real culprit later,
I'll receive sympathy...
and get rid of any suspicions
that this was insurance fraud.
We're done here, so get lost.
I called you just in case,
but I didn't need you.
Okay.
Give it to me.
I'll take care of this, so don't
come near here from now on.
Don't call me either.
Im Yun Hee, who was on trial
for the murder of her husband,
has been arrested for
conspiracy to commit murder...
and murder by the prosecution.
Ms. Im schemed with her
former husband, and conspired to...
murder her ex-husband Kim Yeong Tae.
She also murdered her father and
disguised it as a fire accident.
Afterwards, she made the corpse
look like her ex-husband's,
and illegally received the insurance
payout of her father and ex-husband.
Okay.
So her father wasn't missing,
but murdered...
and her ex-husband
didn't die from a fire...
but they disguised the corpse of
her father to look like his, right?
That's how they received the
insurance payout for two people.
They used up all that money on gambling,
and they approached another man
and killed him for more money.
How could a human being
commit such an atrocity?
Anyway, it's been revealed that
Im Yun Hee is the worst evil ever,
and I'm so glad.
Mr. Kwon, who exposed
the truth became a star.
Tell me about it.
Mr. Kwon eventually succeeded.
Wait. Where is Mr. Yeon?
He's busy doing interviews over the phone.
Interviews?
Yes, I am...
I'm Kwon Jung Rok's spiritual
leader and role model.
I'm Yeon Joon Gyu,
the CEO of Always Law Firm.
There we go.
Oh, yes. Kwon Jung Rok...
is an excellent attorney and colleague...
who's doing a great job in
following my footsteps...
of righteousness and honesty.
By having taken this case,
it shows that Kwon Jung Rok fully
understands our firm's motto.
And that personally makes
me feel very proud of him.
The motto of Always Law Firm is...
"Pursue the truth and achieve justice."
And of course, I was the one
who came up with that motto.
Oh, is this all you need?
Well, I still have a lot more
I'd like to say.
Are you not curious about
my childhood background...
and how I was able to become
such a magnificent CEO?
What about my ideal type of woman
or my future plans to appear on TV?
Hello? Hello?
Why did he hang up?
I don't understand.
I should call him again.
(Record of evidence)
Jung Rok, we should drink
on a day like this.
What do you want to eat?
I'll buy you anything.
Rib eye? Lobster? Perch?
Corn dogs? Just tell me.
I'll buy you everything you want.
Maybe next time. I'm a little tired today.
Yes, I guess you should
go home and get some rest.
You haven't slept for days.
Then let's take a rain check...
and get wasted next time.
I'll see you.
By the way, can I ask you something?
You refused to go to the company dinner...
because you were tired.
So why did you ask me
to drink soju with you?
I just wanted...
to drink with you alone today.
♫ I wish everything would just stop ♫
Mr. Kwon, we should drink tonight.
How about we meet at the pork
back-bone stew restaurant...
that we went to after we
won a case last time?
♫ Those words won't leave my head all day ♫
Two servings of pork
back-bone stew, please.
Okay.
♫ I'm just smiling, not knowing anything ♫
Welcome.
♫ Only deep scars remain ♫
♫ Sorry, I don't know why ♫
Mr. Kwon.
♫ In the photographs in my hands ♫
Can we talk outside for a while?
♫ You're just smiling ♫
♫ But you're never coming back ♫
♫ You're never coming back ♫
Ms. Oh, why are you doing this?
What did I do?
You know we shouldn't be meeting
each other like this anymore.
No, not really.
I don't get why we can't meet.
I heard...
why you decided...
to break up with me.
I had to go through a lot of things,
but you were the reason why I
managed to overcome everything.
And in that process, I became stronger.
I'm more scared about losing you...
than losing an opportunity
in this industry...
because of a scandal.
So...
if you really care about me,
please stay by my side.
Let's start over again.
Are you still not going to hold onto me?
If you let go now,
we'll never get to see each other again.
Ms. Oh Jin Sim.
I love you.
♫ Time is a strange thing ♫
♫ Only after it passes ♫
♫ You long for it ♫
♫ A sweet dream, when you open your eyes ♫
♫ It may still be clear ♫
♫ But soon ♫
♫ It gets far away and disappears lala ♫
♫ You and I ♫
♫ This moment right here ♫
♫ I'm going to cherish it ♫
♫ Deep in my heart,
the soft touch of your hand ♫
♫ Even today's air ♫
♫ I'm gonna remember it all ♫
♫ It's so precious ♫
♫ So make it count ♫
♫ Remember this day ♫
♫ When the gentle breeze blows
and flowers bloom ♫
(Touch Your Heart)
I don't want to go home.
I miss you all the time.
An advisory counsel?
- Is no one interested?
- I'll do it.
What's your problem? You're so annoying.
In order to protect you,
we should be more careful from now on...
so that no one finds out
about our relationship.
We should be more careful from now on?
I get that he's your manager,
but he should respect your privacy.
Yun Seo, I need to use your bathroom.
Hyuk Joon!
How does Yun Seo get along
with the male lead?
"Known for being a great kisser"?
I forgot about the kissing scene
in episode four.
I think the two might start dating
because of this drama.
I'll do my best...
- to help you practice.
- Goodness.
Is this how it's done?
♫ Whisper your heart to me ♫