Are you all right?
Please stay in the car.
What is this?
I just asked you a question.
I guess I mistook her for someone else.
I thought it was someone I knew,
but I guess I was wrong.
Mr. Kwon.
Are you all right?
What did he say?
Why did he follow me?
He said he mistook you for someone else.
He didn't.
He was obviously following me.
- He is...
- I know.
He's the one who made your life difficult.
That's why I didn't want
to just let him leave.
(Text Message)
I felt betrayed to see you happy.
Until next time, Ms. Oh.
Don't, Mr. Kwon.
I don't want to provoke him in any way.
I don't want to be associated with him.
Thank you for driving me home.
Sure.
I'm too worried to let
you be alone tonight.
Would it be okay if I kept you company?
At first,
he approached me as a fan.
Mr. Lee, thank you so much.
I hear that you want Yun Seo
to be the female lead...
in Director Han Sang Cheol's
upcoming blockbuster movie.
That's right.
I'm a fan of Yun Seo,
but that's not the only reason.
I just feel like this movie will suit her.
I'd be a fool not to celebrate then.
Let me pour you a glass.
- Let me pour you one too.
- Sure. It's an honor.
Ms. Oh,
have a glass.
I'm not much of a drinker.
Go on.
Ms. Oh,
are you all right?
Have a drink.
Where am I?
You're awake.
Why the glum face?
For me, it's been a blast.
All night,
I was able to watch my woman.
I should get going.
- Cheers, everyone.
- Cheers!
- Good job.
- Good job, guys.
I've never seen a team work
this well together before.
Ms. Oh, the director is asking for you.
- Really?
- Right now?
- Get going then.
- Sure.
I shouldn't have followed him there.
Director?
What are you doing?
Yun Seo.
I love you.
What are you saying?
What must I do...
to make you realize that?
Why do you seem so startled?
I said I love you.
I love you, darn it!
This is the narcotics division
of Gangnam Police Department.
Lee Gang Joon, you are under arrest...
for the violation of...
the Narcotic Control Act.
What? Yun Seo!
Hey!
- Let go of me!
- Get him out of here.
Yun Seo!
And just like that,
I was also accused of...
taking drugs.
I was let go...
after the drug test came back negative,
but just being there with him...
brought about all kinds of rumors.
I told people my story...
and said he was a stalker.
No matter how hard I tried,
no one would believe me.
Malicious and damaging articles...
continued to be published,
and it was too hard to endure.
I felt like I was going to crumble,
and that's why...
I took some time off.
Back then,
I was scared of him who let this happen,
of the people who turned their backs on me,
and of those who kept making up rumors.
I was scared of and disgusted by them all.
You don't have to say anymore.
It's all right.
I actually...
wanted to...
tell you about it someday.
I didn't want you...
to get the wrong idea of me.
Sure.
I don't think that at all.
Please stop worrying now.
You should go to sleep too.
Sure.
I will after I see you fall asleep.
All this time...
I haven't been able to tell
anyone my side of the story.
But now that I've told you everything,
I feel more comfortable.
Do you remember what I told you before?
People who commit crimes should suffer.
The victims shouldn't suffer instead.
You should forget all your bad memories...
and become happier than anyone else.
Right.
I remember.
I will make that happen.
I'll make you happier than anyone.
So, don't be afraid,
and let's overcome it together.
- You're up, Mr. Kwon.
- Yes.
What are you doing?
What do you think? I'm making breakfast.
You should have breakfast
before you go to work.
Let's see.
I'm making doenjang stew.
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
Do you want to taste it?
Isn't it good?
This place is great at
making doenjang stew, right?
Yes. This place must be
famous for its doenjang stew.
I won't spread any rumors though.
Okay. We should hurry up and eat.
Then we'll drop by your house
so you can change...
and we can go to work together.
Okay.
Now, all I have to do is add tofu.
I will...overcome it.
With you, Mr. Kwon.
As you can see, I'm certain
Jung Ji Ho embezzled funds.
He's pocketing millions of dollars.
If you need more proof...
What about the Bujin Steel Bribe
Case I asked you to look into?
Sir, I can't just let
Jung Ji Ho slide like this.
Didn't you expect this
when you put me on this case?
That I wouldn't give up?
Don't you know who Choi Yoon Su is?
He was the ace of the special
prosecution department.
And he's defending Jung Ji Ho right now.
He probably already bribed
the testifiers or witnesses.
Do you think you'll stand a chance?
Are you afraid of Choi Yoon Su...
or the person who's behind him?
What did you say?
(Evidence Record, Jung Ji Ho,
Embezzlement of funds)
Sir, are we really going
to end it like this?
I don't know when, but we
will reopen this box one day.
Let's make sure we catch him then.
What an unfortunate situation.
You still love your husband,
but you're thinking of divorce.
What's the reason?
Because my husband changed.
He used to tell me...
that he loved me a dozen times a day.
But recently, he makes up
excuses that he's busy...
and only says it twice.
He's saying it 10 times less.
- Sorry?
- That's not it.
My husband knew me better than anyone else.
But a few days ago, he said he
wanted to watch a drama with me...
and bought a chicken on his way home.
Why is that a problem?
We should eat one chicken per person.
When I looked at him tearing
the chicken with his teeth,
it felt like my heart was
being torn apart too.
How could I keep living with him?
We should part ways.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but the reason for your divorce
isn't as serious as I thought.
And there's not enough proof that
your husband really changed.
My husband changed!
He's a mean man who broke my heart.
Of course, a decent man
shouldn't make a woman cry.
Here. Wipe your tears and calm down.
- Thank you.
- You can keep it.
All right, then. Have a good day.
Hi, Mom.
What? Tomorrow is my birthday?
What do I want as a gift?
It's okay.
You gave birth to a perfect son like me,
so I should be the one buying you a gift.
Okay. I'll see you later, Mom. Bye.
Tomorrow is his birthday?
Ms. Dan. Is something bothering you?
Well...
Actually, there is someone
who I've fallen for lately.
Again?
So?
Well, tomorrow is a happy
day for that person...
and I want to congratulate him.
What should I get him as a gift?
If it's a crush,
you should give him something simple
so he doesn't feel pressured.
If you like each other, do something
that can progress your relationship.
- For instance, you can buy dinner.
- The thing is...
It seems like a crush in a way,
but maybe he likes me too.
Do you want to hear about it?
First, he appeared like a prince
when I was in a crisis...
and helped me.
Second, I said I needed something,
and he gave it to me as a gift.
It's okay.
Buy me a drink someday.
A gift?
Maybe you're not mistaken this time.
He seems to like you too.
Really?
He seems genuinely attracted,
so just make the first move.
Ask him out to dinner tomorrow.
- How about a drink?
- Drink?
He told me to buy him
a drink someday first.
That's great. You should dress
up prettier than usual...
and make him fall for you.
But in order to look pretty,
what do I have to wear?
I've never dressed up properly.
Do you know what his
ideal type of woman is?
You should try to look as similar
as possible to his ideal type.
His ideal type of woman?
An ideal type of woman?
- Ms. Dan?
- Yes?
Do you have something to say?
- No. Why do you ask?
- You just looked at me.
That was delicious.
Since we all had a nice lunch,
today's coffee is on me.
I'll take your orders.
I'll have an espresso.
- I'll have a cafe mocha.
- I'll have a latte.
- I'll have a latte too.
- I'm sorry to say this,
but I'll have a latte with an extra shot.
I'll have a strawberry cream frappe...
with extra whipping cream.
Ms. Oh, can you memorize all this?
Don't you have to write it down?
Mr. Yeon will have an espresso,
Ms. Yang will have cafe mocha,
Hae Yeong and Jong Hwa will have lattes.
Pil Gi will have a latte
with an extra shot.
Mr. Lee will have a strawberry cream
frappe with extra whipping cream.
Mr. Kwon, since you like instant coffee,
I'll go inside and make you one.
How did you remember all that?
I have an amazing memory.
I'll go and get your coffee then.
- I'll be back.
- I'll help you. Let's go.
- Me too.
- I'll help you too.
It's an honor to drink coffee bought
by the universe's goddess, Ms. Oh.
Doesn't Ms. Oh seem...
very enthusiastic and bright today?
I love it.
(Lee Gang Joon, Former CEO
of Jeguk Entertainment,)
(Returns as Vice President
of Jeguk Holdings)
(Lee Gang Joon, Former CEO
of Jeguk Entertainment,)
(Returns as Vice President
of Jeguk Holdings)
I guess he's back for good.
Ms. Oh, it's time to go home.
Ms. Oh.
Yes, Mr. Kwon.
It's time to go home now.
Oh, okay. I need to make
a few photocopies first.
(Lee Gang Joon, Former CEO
of Jeguk Entertainment,)
(Returns as Vice President
of Jeguk Holdings)
Ms. Oh.
The Supreme Court unanimously
changed a court precedent recently.
I'll give you the number of the precedent.
Can you print that out for me?
Let's go on a date tonight.
Okay, I'll look for it right now.
Why did you suddenly bring
me to an amusement park?
I watched a few of your dramas
whenever I had time.
And whenever the female
character was having a bad day,
the male character always
tried to cheer her up...
by taking her to either
a beach or an amusement park.
I wondered where I should take you
out of the two places.
And I figured it'd be twice
as fun if I brought you...
to an amusement park that's
located near the beach.
More importantly,
the amusement park is small,
so it's not visited by a lot of people.
So I also thought it'd be
a very reasonable choice.
Thank you for caring about me so much.
You don't need to try so hard.
- What?
- It'll be hard...
to overcome everything overnight.
So let's just take one step at a time.
I'll always stay by your side to support...
and protect you.
I feel so reassured.
- Ms. Oh!
- Goodness, it's okay.
Ms. Oh! Ms. Oh!
Hold on tight.
Ms. Oh.
Don't worry!
Are you okay, Mr. Kwon?
I'll protect you.
Don't worry. I'll protect you.
Try raising your hands.
Ms. Oh!
Please stop!
- Stop!
- Put your hands up.
Mr. Kwon. Mr. Kwon, wake up.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'll protect you.
Stop the ride!
Please! Stop the ride!
I'm okay, Ms. Oh.
Mr. Kwon, I didn't know you were
scared of amusement park rides.
I'm not scared. I just haven't been
on a ride since elementary school,
so it's more adequate to
say that I was nervous...
due to the unfamiliar environment.
And keep in mind that I'm getting
used to it very quickly.
Then how about we ride it one more time?
It'll help you get used to it more quickly.
No, that's... That's okay.
I think I've had enough for today.
Be honest with me.
You were scared, weren't you?
- No.
- Come on.
I know you were scared.
I wasn't scared.
My goodness.
Are you angry? You sound really sensitive.
You just sounded sensitive which
is how you normally talk.
How I normally talk?
No one's ever told me that I'm sensitive.
They all probably say it behind your back.
You're really sensitive.
You really startled me when we first met.
You were the most sensitive
person I had ever met.
But of course,
you're sweet as ever right now.
Come to think of it, you actually...
do look similar.
Look similar?
I sometimes tend to hear that
I look similar to actors.
You're like a hedgehog, Mr. Kwon.
- A hedgehog?
- Yes.
Hedgehogs are known to be...
very sensitive and sharp on the outside.
But once you get to know them,
they're cute.
That's what you're like.
You're a hedgehog.
A hedgehog.
That cotton candy looks really cute.
Did you see it?
Yes, I did.
I'll get one for you.
Sir, I'd like one teddy bear cotton candy.
I'm sorry. I'm done for the day.
What?
Sir, I'm sorry to ask you this,
but can you please make me one?
Your cotton candy might console
and brighten someone's life.
It might also act as a driving
force to overcome their fear.
My cotton candy?
Yes. So please do me a favor.
Okay.
♫ Times when the wind blew ♫
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Ms. Oh.
♫ On that starry night ♫
- I'm sorry.
- My goodness.
♫ I just wanna be your star for you ♫
Gosh.
It was a polar bear earlier.
But now, it's a black bear.
♫ I'll embrace your day ♫
I'm sorry.
I should've been careful of
every single step I took.
Or when I bumped into that guy,
I should've saved the bear
by holding it above my head.
It's okay.
The back is still clean.
Let's eat the back part.
♫ I'll fill up your dark night
with my heart ♫
You should try some as well. Here.
Try it.
Ms. Oh.
What's that?
- Firecrackers?
- Yes.
I also learned about this from one
of the dramas you appeared in.
People always play with firecrackers
every time they come to the beach.
Wait there for a second.
There. You can look forward to it.
I heard there are times
when they don't work.
I... I wonder what's wrong.
I think this one's going to work, right?
Why would they sell something
that doesn't work?
I should file a complaint as
a consumer immediately...
and also put in a claim for damages.
Gosh, it's beautiful.
Mr. Kwon, let's put in a claim
for damages a little later...
and enjoy the fireworks.
But that's not for us.
It will be if we watch it together.
Hurry. Come on.
Gosh, it's so pretty.
I'm sorry, Ms. Oh.
What? For what?
I brought you all the way
here to make you happy.
But I was scared of all the rides,
I ruined the cotton candy
that you wanted to eat,
and the firecrackers didn't even work.
I feel like I ruined everything.
All the male characters in the
dramas you appeared in...
didn't seem to have a
problem making you happy.
I had more fun today than any
of the scenes I appeared in.
It's because...
I'm here this time with someone...
I truly love.
You're my real boyfriend,
and your feelings for me are real.
That's why I've had the best time today.
I swear.
When I'm with you, I feel certain...
that I'll be able to overcome
just about anything.
Will you be able to sleep alone today?
Of course.
Call me if anything happens.
I'll call even if nothing does.
I can't sleep without hearing your voice.
- Drive home safely then.
- Sure.
You didn't have to pick me up.
I hope I didn't cause you
any inconvenience today.
It's all right.
Nothing more will happen now,
so you don't need to worry.
Right.
Mr. Kwon, why are you suddenly speeding up?
No reason.
You should head upstairs first.
I need to make a phone call.
- I'll get going then.
- Sure.
What the...
Who do you think you are?
Taking photos without permission...
can be a violation of
one's portrait rights.
In the case of sexual humiliation,
you may be charged with violation of
the special act on sexual assault.
I wasn't taking photos of you.
No, they were of me.
I'd rather you never do
anything like this again.
Actually, I should tell him that myself.
(Call number)
This is Oh Yun Seo.
Things were too hectic last
night to properly greet you.
I didn't think I'd have
to speak to you again,
but if you keep having people tail me,
we might have to meet...
in court.
You've gotten bolder...
since the last time I saw you.
That's right.
I'm not afraid of you anymore.
I'm taking this with me.
I'll need evidence
if I'm to take him to court.
Darn it.
How did you know?
You kept glancing at the
mirror while driving.
I saw that a car was following us.
You then told me to head upstairs first,
so I knew you were going
to approach the car.
I stayed to call the police
if things got out of hand.
Clever, aren't I?
Are you sure you're all right?
Yes, of course. It's like I said.
We'll get through this together.
Are you actually thinking
about pressing charges?
I don't know.
I gave him a warning,
so we'll wait and see.
To be honest, I don't want...
to be associated with him again.
Aren't Mr. Kwon and Ms. Oh
joining us for coffee?
They seem to be busy.
I don't think I've seen Ms. Dan either.
She said she was stopping
by the court today.
- Everyone, good morning.
- There she is.
I see that you're all here.
Ms. Dan, what's wrong?
Are you protesting because I
told you to up your performance?
If you thought this would
scare me, you were right.
I'm terrified.
Mr. Yeon,
you and your jokes.
I'm sorry for my low-performance level.
Starting today, I,
Dan Moon Hee, will live up...
to your expectations.
I'll do my best.
Did you hear that?
Am I the only one who's scared?
Doesn't this terrify anyone else?
Mr. Yeon, why are you being this way?
I quite like Ms. Dan's new look.
You know what they say.
"There's no fault with
a woman's transformation."
All right then. I'll get...
to work.
Honestly, I'm petrified.
It's not like you to
take her side like that.
It reminded me of the old times.
When I went on a trip to Spain,
I grew sick and tired of my perfect image,
so I dressed like a gypsy
throughout my vacation.
Are you saying her look is
equivalent of your gypsy style?
Not exactly.
However, when you want
to let go of yourself...
but others try to stop you,
it makes you want to act out more.
What are you doing in my office?
Well, there's something I'd like to ask.
Do you have any plans for tonight?
No, I don't have anything special.
Then would you like to have dinner with me?
What?
I'm to thank you for the
ukulele with drinks, remember?
I thought I'd buy some today.
I came across the fact that
it's your birthday today.
So how about a meal and a few drinks?
Is this really a gift?
Sorry?
Why would I have drinks
with you on my birthday?
I have dinner plans with my mother tonight.
Since I'm without a girlfriend this year,
and there's no one I particularly like,
I booked a French restaurant
for me and my mother.
That means I'll have to
take a rain check...
on those drinks.
Please leave now.
Sure.
You little punk.
Is that all you can do?
Tell me!
Mr. Lee.
What is it?
What's that serious face?
You're scaring me.
The thing is... Mr. Yeon.
I'm afraid we won't be able to...
cast Yun Seo for this drama.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry, Mr. Yeon.
There was a company that
promised to invest in us,
but I guess they heard rumors
that Yun Seo was a candidate...
for the female lead of the drama.
And the president of that company said...
he doesn't want Yun Seo to be in the drama.
Why? Because of the scandal?
We're not sure why either.
This is so unfair.
You all know Yun Seo is working
at a law firm as a secretary...
in order to shoot this drama.
We also know that and want to...
go with Yun Seo if possible.
But what choice do we have?
We have to receive the investment...
and make this drama work.
It's been months since an
investor contacted us,
so there is nothing we can do either.
Sir, I'm really sorry...
but can you give me the
number of that investor?
I'll meet him in person
and try to persuade him.
What?
The CEO of an investment company?
So when did you plan on meeting him?
I'll go too then.
I'll go with you and persuade him.
Yes. I'll see you after work.
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
I was mistaken again.
Tell me the truth!
It's a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
My wife told me that you said...
men who make women cry are scumbags...
and told her to split up
with me and get a divorce!
Wait a second. That wasn't
what I meant at all!
On top of that, you gave her
this handkerchief...
and told her to keep it as a gift!
If that's not hitting on someone, what is?
That's just because she blew her nose,
and snot was all over my handkerchief...
Forget it. You're lucky that we made up.
If we didn't, what did you intend to do?
We're you really thinking
of dating my wife?
I thought you were an expert
in handling divorces.
You're just an expert at seducing women!
Watch your mouth.
If you keep this up,
I won't tolerate it any longer.
If you won't, what will you do?
What will you do, you jerk!
- Who are you?
- I'm Attorney Dan Moon Hee.
You seem to be mistaken.
Mr. Choi isn't that kind of person.
He's a very warmhearted and kind man.
He's not someone who hits
on his clients so cheaply.
What do you know to butt in?
I know well enough.
So you should leave now.
If you don't want to be sued for
obstruction of business, slandering,
and even assault.
You didn't forget that this place
is a law firm, did you?
Honey, let's just go.
You shouldn't be seduced by men like him.
All right.
- I'm afraid.
- Don't be.
I'm scared.
Are you okay, Ms. Dan?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
- Why did you get involved...
- Today is your birthday.
I couldn't let you be assaulted
on your own birthday.
Just consider it as your birthday gift.
What is this?
The only person who protects
me in case I get hurt...
is my mom.
Let's go home.
I'll give you a ride.
It's okay. I have dinner plans tonight.
With whom?
I'm not sure. Do I have to
report to you every time?
Actually, I'm having dinner
with the CEO of my agency.
He wants to have a talk.
I'll call you after dinner.
- Mr. Yeon.
- Yes?
Don't worry too much.
We can solve any misunderstandings
as we talk tonight.
Yes, Yun Seo. You're right.
You've been working hard lately,
and you even know how to console me.
You're all grown up now.
By the way, look at the time.
What's taking him so long?
He's here.
Wait. How could you...
It's been a while, Mr. Yeon.
And Ms. Oh.
Did I make you wait too long?
Let's see.
What did Ms. Oh use to like?
What do you think you're doing?
Get up, Yun Seo. Let's go.
Are you giving up...
on the drama like this?
Yes. We won't shoot this drama.
What are you doing? Let's go.
Ms. Oh seems to have a different opinion.
Sit down, Mr. Yeon.
I have something to say.
Yun Seo.
I thought I made it clear earlier.
That I don't want to see you ever again.
I also told you earlier.
You've gotten bolder...
since the last time I saw you.
Back then, I had a lot to lose...
but now, I have nothing left.
You have nothing to lose?
You even work at a law firm in order
to make your comeback in a drama.
You seem to be seriously
mistaken about something.
I don't have to shoot that drama.
Like you said,
I'm more than happy right now.
Don't get off.
- Go home safely.
- Okay. Good night.
What on earth is happening?
Then will her drama appearance
really be canceled?
But Yun Seo seems better than I expected.
I know, right?
Aren't we going?
Why are you resting your head too?
I'm sorry.
("Love Hurts")
The caller you have dialed is
not answering the phone...
I got home safely.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Is there something wrong?
(I got home safely. I'll see you tomorrow.)
Have a good night. I'll see you tomorrow.
Jung Ji Ho, the CEO of Giant Foods,
who got indicted for having gambled abroad,
got sentenced to two years in jail...
with a stay of execution for three years.
People are criticizing that the
punishment is way too weak.
However, the justice department
claimed that Mr. Jung...
admitted to all the charges...
and showed signs of deep regret.
Are you okay?
Of course not.
How about we go out for some soju?
Jung Ji Ho did more than
just gamble abroad.
He also embezzled more
than 20 million dollars.
The thought of having a jerk like
that back in society is just...
Do you think you'll be able to give up?
I have no other choice.
At least for now.
For now?
By the way, why do you look so down?
Can you tell me everything you
know about Lee Gang Joon?
Did he show up in front of Yun Seo?
He even made someone tail her.
What?
He secretly took photos of her,
and I have the memory card
from the camera as proof. But...
But?
But I don't think she wants
to cause a fuss about it yet.
Gosh, of course.
It took so long for the
huge scandal to die away.
I feel so frustrated...
because there's nothing I can do.
I'll try to look into him.
You're a hedgehog.
Why aren't you coming?
Oh, right.
You can go home first.
I need to go somewhere.
- Who is it?
- I'm a hedgehog.
What?
Do you like it?
I can't always be by your side.
I thought it could keep you company
when I'm not there.
Yes, I really like it.
But you don't look so happy.
Mr. Kwon.
I might not be able to
go to the law firm...
for a while.
I'll try to keep my promise and
work there for three months.
And I'll also do my best...
to complete all the work...
that I was given.
But...
I don't think I can go to work...
for the time being.
I can't seem to do it.
Is there something wrong?
Why all of a sudden?
I'm sorry.
I can't tell you anything right now.
Yun Seo won't be starring in the drama?
Gosh, why don't you just
broadcast it to everyone?
I'm sorry.
I was so shocked that I
talked without thinking.
It must feel so devastating.
What are we going to do?
Yes, I know.
Yun Seo...
The members of her fan site are
going to be so devastated.
They're waiting so desperately
for her to make a comeback...
through Lee Se Jin's drama.
And they're barely enduring the wait...
by making memes of her smiling and winking.
So imagine how devastated they'll
be once they hear this news.
Gosh, Joon Gyu.
Do you still create memes and
upload them on her fan site?
Why don't you just
broadcast it to everyone?
You're the only one that knows I'm
the founder of her fan site...
and that I'm also the
anonymous vice president.
You don't know how happy it
feels to support someone...
behind their back without them knowing.
Joon Gyu. Joon Gyu.
You really do have a way
of upsetting people.
That's not the problem right now.
What I'm trying to say is that
there are a lot of people...
waiting for Yun Seo to make a comeback.
I feel so sorry for Yun Seo.
I could see that she was
getting used to the work here.
But now, all her effort
would've been for nothing.
That's why I came to tell you that
Yun Seo won't be coming to work...
- starting from today.
- Okay.
But people will be really curious
because they don't know the story.
What should I tell them?
Just tell them that she's sick.
I'll try to think of how we
should deal with the rest.
- Did you eat garlic?
- Yes.
My gosh, no wonder.
What is that you need to tell us?
Is it a big announcement?
Well, not exactly. It's just a notice.
The thing is, Yun Seo is sick,
so she'll be taking a few days off.
My goodness, how bad is it?
For how long is she going to be absent?
I'm not sure.
We'll have to see.
Anyway, just keep that in mind.
And since Yun Seo won't be around,
Ms. Yang and the interns...
should help Jung Rok out...
- whenever you guys have time.
- Okay.
- Yes, sir.
Okay, let's get back to work.
Mr. Kwon, your client I told
you about yesterday is here.
I'm talking about the case
that Ms. Dan was in charge of...
but got declined because
she didn't seem fit for the job.
- The overseas gambling case.
- Right.
He's here right now,
so I'll send him to your office.
Okay.
First, you need to write
a letter of apology...
to hand in to the justice department.
You need to say that you
regret what you did...
and that you'll never gamble again.
You also need to receive
counseling from a psychiatrist...
and hand in the counseling records
or diagnosis for assessment.
Will that help me not
get sentenced to jail?
I can't be sure, but you have
no similar previous convictions.
So if you receive counseling and
prove that it's not habitual,
you can avoid going to prison.
This is only possible because
you only gambled a small amount.
I'm sure you heard the news.
If the amount were
millions like Jung Ji Ho,
you'd have to be in custody.
Jung Ji Ho?
His case is still a mystery to me.
What do you mean?
There's a rumor going around
our particular circle.
Jung Ji Ho...
isn't a gambler.
Sorry? What do you mean?
The NCT Hotel in Macao...
that Jung Ji Ho gambled at...
is where I'm a regular at.
Someone I know there...
works on the security team.
He says that he only saw Jung Ji Ho once...
on the day that he was
arrested for gambling.
It's odd because news reports say...
that he repeatedly came to gamble there.
It's like saying that someone drove...
while intoxicated...
when they didn't even
have a drop of alcohol.
Did you call?
Well, you see...
I'd like the bank account transactions...
of Attorney Choi Yoon Su.
Attorney Choi Yoon Su? Isn't he...
He's Jung Ji Ho's attorney,
and I have some questions.
But Mr. Kim...
I can't let this case slide like this.
I'll take full responsibility.
All right then.
Jung Rok?
Lee Gang Joon's got into a
lot of trouble abroad too.
Each time, he solved it with money though.
It's about Jung Ji Ho.
I'm not 100 percent sure,
but I hear that he
actually wasn't a gambler.
That's absurd.
It's certain that he gambled overseas.
He went in and out of Macao,
and photos put him at the casino.
Here. I have it on screen.
Who do you think you are?
- What is it?
- That man.
He was tailing Ms. Oh Jin Sim
per Lee Gang Joon's request.
Which overseas branch was
Lee Gang Joon placed at?
Macao.
Come to think of it,
these two have the same attorney.
Choi Yoon Su.
He argued for Lee Gang Joon on
his drug charge two years ago,
and now he's Jung Ji Ho's attorney.
I heard you were sick. How are you feeling?
(Ms. Yang Eun Ji)
Ms. Oh!
I thought you called in sick today.
I'm not here to work today.
Today, I'm here as a client.
Is Mr. Kwon inside?
Lee Gang Joon...
I'd like to press charges against him.
These are the photos and
threatening texts...
that he sent me.
I held onto them.
Will that be enough for evidence?
Of course.
This time,
make him pay for what he did.
Of course. I'll make sure of it.
Thank you for driving me home.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Actually,
I was so scared and terrified...
that I couldn't get
myself to think about it.
Trying to forget it and
pretending to be all right...
didn't make the pain go away.
That's why I'm mustering up the courage...
and putting my faith in you.
Of course. From now on, you can trust me.
You're home.
I missed you.
I love you, Yun Seo.
I know you still love me too.
You pretend to be angry
just to get my attention.
That's why you're pretending
to like that man.
You're trying to provoke me.
Don't come closer.
If you do,
I'll call the police.
The police?
I see you still have no idea
what I'm capable of.
Be honest with yourself now
and say that you love me.
Say that you need me
and that you'll never betray me!
Stay away from my girl.
♫ We went through so much ♫
♫ We fought so much ♫
♫ We made up so many times ♫
♫ Now we don't have to stay up
at night worrying anymore ♫
♫ Now have a peaceful, good night ♫
(Touch Your Heart)
I want you to be the leading lady
of my drama series.
Will she go back to acting?
She came to work here
because it's what she wants.
I'm sure she'll stay in this field.
The people at your law firm
will be shocked.
- Is she playing an attorney?
- Especially Kwon Jung Rok.
I need nothing else but to be by your side.
I'm like a rose, and you're a vase
that can embrace me.
What will I do with you?
There's no way they're dating.
- My gosh.
- You know something, don't you?
I probably don't.
I know it's a cliche,
Can you break up for Yun Seo's sake?
Are my feelings for Ms. Oh...
putting her in trouble?
♫ We went through so much ♫