I'm worried.
Just as much as you worry
about me and console me,
I wish...
to do so for you too.
Does that mean...
I've become a bit more...
special to you...
than before?
Yes.
Yes, this is Kwon Jung Rok.
Hello, Judge.
You don't need to send me
the sentencing report.
Okay.
Anyway, thank you for
working hard to help me...
win the difficult trial.
You should get some rest for tomorrow.
Wait.
"For tomorrow"?
Is tomorrow a special day or something?
Is he going to ask me out?
He probably would've asked me out
if he didn't get a call earlier.
My gosh!
Goodness me. He'll ask me out tomorrow.
(Episode 7)
- Good morning!
- Good morning.
- Hello.
Good morning!
Did something good happen to her?
I don't know.
Did he go somewhere?
What's with the flowers?
Are they from Mr. Kwon?
"The cold that didn't seem to
want to back off finally did,"
"and warm spring days are drawing near."
Gosh, can he be any more romantic?
"Although it's nothing grand,"
"the gift was chosen from the heart,"
"so I hope you willingly accept it."
What do you mean it's nothing grand?
It couldn't be more precious!
"The battle was tough,
but you never gave up."
"That's why she wasn't made a scapegoat."
A scapegoat?
"Thank you for taking Im Yun Hee's case."
"From President Lee Yeong Ok of
the Korean Women's Association."
Oh, you're here.
- These...
- The flowers?
The Korean Women's Association sent them.
I don't like flowers,
so I put them here for you to enjoy.
I see.
Mr. Yeon's calling everyone
to go over their cases.
All right.
Let's get ready and head out.
Before we begin the briefing,
let's give a round of applause to Mr. Kwon,
the hope...
and gem of our law firm,
for successfully winning
the Im Yun Hee Case.
That's enough, everyone. Thank you.
There's no reason to be embarrassed.
Although, that's what
makes you so charming.
Then let's get on with the briefing.
Our law firm is taking
on the Sangji-dong Case.
Since it's a big case,
Mr. Kwon will brief us
and we'll share ideas.
Sure.
Before I begin, let me show
you the defendant's photo.
What's going on?
Why is there a photo of Yun Seo,
the universe's goddess?
What crime did she commit?
Her crimes?
She committed theft by stealing my heart.
She committed assault by
blinding me with her beauty.
She even committed attempted murder
by making me break my heart...
if I don't see her even for a day.
I argue Jin Sim receives
life imprisonment...
and be with me for the rest of my life.
Jin Sim,
will you go out with me?
Take me. Put me in cuffs.
Take me right away!
Ms. Oh?
What are you doing?
What is this?
(Sangji-dong Parricide Case)
Him! He will...
be imprisoned for sure.
Mr. Kwon will do his best...
to make that happen.
Ms. Oh, you can be quite silly at times.
That's what makes her so charming.
Her looks are stunning,
but she has a whimsical side.
Thank you for thinking of me so nicely.
Anyway, he's a bad man.
Let me begin the briefing then.
Are you insane? What's wrong with you?
Get a grip on yourself.
You're an actress,
so wait for him elegantly.
Be hard-to-get.
It's already 6pm.
Gosh, is that a heart?
Is he sending it my way?
He's telling me how he feels
by small, trivial gestures.
Was he just wiping the glass?
I've been too busy to notice,
but the office is a mess.
I guess I should complain to the cleaners.
I'll do that, so don't worry about it.
Good night.
Wait.
Is that it?
Don't you have anything else to say?
- Sorry?
- Whatever.
It's nothing.
I'll head home first then.
I dolled myself up today for nothing.
You're doing it again.
You promised yourself that you'd wait.
Now, turn on the hard-to-get actress mode.
♫ One step at a time ♫
I'll nonchalantly wait for him.
♫ Too much for your mind  ♫
♫ I was only being kind ♫
♫ There's no need to analyze ♫
Nonchalantly.
(Secretary Oh Jin Sim)
- Jin Sim...
- I can't wait.
- Sorry?
- I can't wait any longer.
I won't play hard-to-get.
I'd rather just say
everything that's on my mind.
I've been going insane...
waiting for you to ask me out.
- What do you mean?
- Do you not want to?
Okay, fine.
I'll make the first move then.
My gosh. Now that I have to say it...
Hold on a second.
I like you, Mr. Kwon.
Do you remember what I told you?
I said I had...
something to tell you.
I couldn't say it now,
but I promised to tell you someday.
Do you remember that?
My gosh.
Anyway, that's...
I love you.
You see...
You have taken a spot...
in my heart.
I mean...
In my heart that is clean, clear, and pure,
you came and made a place for yourself.
That's what I mean.
That's why...
when you said last night...
that I've become a bit more special to you,
I felt so happy.
And I waited all day for
you to say something else.
But how could you humiliate me like that?
I'm Oh Yun Seo!
- Mr. Kwon, you're so mean!
- Jin Sim.
Jin Sim?
What are you doing?
What's the matter? Is something wrong?
Is the case you're working
on giving you trouble again?
Forget it.
What's the matter with him? Gosh.
I'll state the facts only,
so listen carefully.
A man started to develop
feelings for a woman.
So he told her,
"You've become a special person to me."
This is what he said.
The man thought that would be enough.
He thought they could take things slow,
since they liked each other.
But the woman had different thoughts.
She wanted him to make the next move,
but when he didn't,
she got extremely angry.
Is this really the man's fault?
Is this really about a case? Not you?
It's not about me!
- It's about my client.
- You've got to be kidding me.
Did you set up a dating
agency or something?
My goodness.
Forget it. It's no use asking you.
It's not the man's fault.
What you said isn't actually wrong.
- Right?
- Still,
I'd like to side with the woman.
Who on earth takes dating so
logically like you just said?
You normally get to know
each other as you date.
The man already made the first move.
He said something crucial,
by saying she was special.
But if he cuts her off suddenly,
who would like that?
You still don't understand?
Listen. Let's say you're at a trial.
"Your Honor, considering all
the circumstantial evidence,"
"the defendant did not behave
like that purposely, and..."
"his alibi on the day of the
incident has been confirmed."
"Therefore, I..."
How would you feel if the
trial ends like this?
- It feels uncomfortable.
- Right?
You said all the important words,
but there is no conclusion.
That's what you...
No, your client has done...
to that woman. Okay?
Jin Sim, I'm sorry.
I thought we were in the stage
of getting to know each other.
Jin Sim, I was inconsiderate.
Please forgive me, and be my...
Jin Sim, let's meet tomorrow and talk.
Yes, what is it this time?
Well, there's something you
should tell your client.
He should ask her out soon,
and prepare flowers,
or something small and shiny.
He should prepare anything that she likes.
- What?
- Going empty-handed...
when he asks her out...
is like going to a trial
without any evidence.
I know I've never met that client of yours,
but I'm just giving advice since
he seems really bad at dating.
- Good luck then.
- I'll make sure to tell him that.
What happened?
Did I fall asleep here?
(Jin Sim, let's meet tomorrow and talk.)
Meet and talk?
About what?
Did I make a mistake or something?
I've been going insane waiting
for you to ask me out.
In my heart that is
clean, clear, and pure...
I like you, Mr. Kwon.
I felt so happy.
Did you faint out of happiness?
Mr. Kwon, you're so mean!
What will he say to me?
"I really hate women like you."
"Let's never see each other again?"
Yun Seo, are you still sleeping?
Hey, you were awake.
Hyuk Joon, get me a white envelope.
A white envelope? Is it a
money gift for a wedding?
No. I won't put money in it.
- Then what?
- My letter of resignation.
- Letter of resignation?
- I won't go to work now.
No, I can't go now.
- Good morning.
Mr. Kwon, I'm glad to see you.
My cousin just called me.
He said Yun Seo can't
make it to work today.
- What?
- Why?
Is she sick?
I don't think so. I said...
I'd bring some flowers and
porridge and go see her,
and he said she's not sick,
but had a personal matter.
He tried to avoid talking about it.
I guess there's another reason.
Maybe she just wants to take a day off.
No way.
Yun Seo didn't seem like such
an irresponsible person.
That's strange, Ms. Yang.
You're finally taking Yun Seo's side.
I have to admit,
she did work very hard all this time.
She's right. At first,
I also had a bias against her
since she's a celebrity,
but during Yoon Ha's case last time...
and the recent Im Yun Hee Case,
she seems like a decent person.
She seems like a scarecrow
standing silently...
but sincerely in the
middle of a field in fall.
A scarecrow seems a bit strange.
Anyway, I wonder what's wrong.
Mr. Kwon, what's wrong with your face?
Did something happen
between you and Yun Seo?
- Nothing happened.
- I don't think so.
Your face is setting off all
these signals right now.
Was she stressed out because
you made her work so much?
Come on.
- It's nothing like that.
- No?
If it's not about work,
is it a relationship matter?
What if it turns out these two
were dating or something?
Come on, it's just a joke.
You're not even amused.
He's very talented, but horrible
when it comes to humor.
He's just the worst.
The caller you have dialed is
not answering the phone...
(Oh Jin Sim's Personal Information)
He should prepare flowers,
or something small and shiny.
He should prepare anything that she likes.
(Things Oh Jin Sim likes...)
(Things Oh Yun Seo likes)
(Oh Yun Seo's favorite rib eye)
Rib eye?
It's not even a holiday.
(Oh Yun Seo's ideal type of man)
It's time to have a sincere talk
at today's star's favorite bar.
Let me introduce today's
star of our talk show.
Don't be shocked.
She's Oh Yun Seo, the most beautiful
woman in the universe. Hello.
Hello, everyone.
(My goddess, your goddess,
the universe's goddess, Oh Yun Seo)
Once again, it's an honor to see you.
But I have to say,
this is quite unexpected.
I feel like you'd prefer to
eat at fancy restaurants.
But we're at a chicken feet restaurant.
I really like the chicken
feet they sell here.
It's near my house,
so I sometimes take it to go.
And they taste even better if you
eat them when you're feeling down.
- Chicken feet?
- Yun Seo, can you tell me...
your ideal type of man?
I have a feeling that you'll like...
competent guys who are really good-looking.
No, I don't care too much about looks.
I'd rather be with a guy...
who knows how to touch my heart.
For example, a guy who gives me
handwritten letters.
Handwritten letters?
It'd be nice if he asked me out
with a handwritten letter.
How am I supposed to...
Doesn't that sound so romantic?
Hello.
Gosh, she's driving me crazy.
Why won't she go to work?
What's her reason?
I'm not sure. She won't tell me why.
She won't come out from her room.
What should I do?
Writer Lee said she'll
give Yun Seo a chance...
only if she works at a law firm
for at least three months.
But it really doesn't seem
like Yun Seo will give in.
And it's not like we can
find another law firm...
that can keep a secret
as good as this place.
Don't worry. I'm here.
I'll do whatever I can to
make her go back to work.
I'm not sure if you'll be able to do that.
Hey, I'm Yeon Jun Seok.
I'm Yeon Jun Seok, the president
of Yeon Entertainment.
Have you seen anyone that's better
than me at handling Yun Seo?
No, sir.
Trust me.
- It's this way.
- Oh, really? Okay.
Yun Seo.
Yun Seo, Mr. Yeon's here.
I heard...
you said you want to stop
working at the law firm.
Yes. I'm not going to work there anymore.
No, I can't work there anymore.
Okay, good thinking.
You should quit.
- What?
- Mr. Yeon.
Why are you both so startled?
If she doesn't want to
work there, she shouldn't.
I get that she's doing this to be
able to act more realistically.
But she's my goddess, your goddess,
and the universe's goddess.
It obviously won't be easy
for someone like her...
to work at a law firm for three months.
To be honest, I never got
a good night's sleep...
after you started working there.
I was always worried about how
difficult it must be for you.
So you should stop working there.
Just quit.
Then she won't get to play the
attorney in Writer Lee's drama.
Is that so important?
She can play the role of a
jobless woman later on.
Once she quits the law firm...
and fails to make a comeback
with Writer Lee's drama,
she'll end up having to
rest at home for years.
Then I'm sure she'll be able
to play the role of a bored,
jobless woman better than anyone.
She'll seem bored all the time.
Don't you agree, Yun Seo?
- Mr. Yeon.
- Yes?
Do you suddenly want to go back to work?
No, not exactly. Right now,
I just want to kick you out.
I'm already really annoyed right now.
Why are you trying to threaten me?
Did you think I wouldn't catch that?
Yun Seo, you've become quick-witted
after all the socializing.
And I've become a really
angry person as well.
My gosh.
- Gosh.
- Yun Seo, where are you going?
I'm going out for some fresh air!
Wait for me. I'll give you a ride!
Hey, don't you know her?
She's too stubborn to listen.
Let's just see what happens.
Bring me some beer from the fridge.
My gosh!
A teddy bear.
She likes pink.
Pink.
Jin Sim, this letter is for you.
I, Kwon Jung Rok,
saw you for the very first time...
on February 6, 2019
at the secretary's office...
of Always Law Firm that's
located in Seocho-gu, Seoul.
As we interacted with each other
many times through work...
and ate about six meals together,
I realized that your feelings weren't fake.
I realized that they were actually sincere.
Therefore, I, Kwon Jung Rok,
request you, Oh Jin Sim,
to officially go out with me.
And I hope you give me your approval.
I might as well write a letter to a judge.
(Suspect of the Husband Murder
Case Gets Reversed in Court)
Prosecutor Yoo, let's go eat.
I'm not hungry.
Okay, then. We'll just go without you.
Okay.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thanks.
You're eating late.
Yes.
By the way, where's Prosecutor Yoo?
Is she having lunch outside?
No, she's in her office.
She doesn't have an appetite.
I think she's really stressed
because of Im Yun Hee Case.
She rarely eats these days.
Really?
(Chicken feet)
Let's cheer me up.
Welcome.
One serving of chicken feet to go, please.
Long time no see.
One serving of chicken feet to go.
- I want them spicy.
- Make them really spicy.
We have a regular customer.
Jin Sim?
No, I'm not Oh Jin Sim.
Wait...
Jin Sim.
- Jin Sim, let's talk.
- My gosh.
Jin Sim.
Gosh, why did you have to run after me?
Well...
Can we talk?
Why did you run away?
And why didn't you come to work today?
Because I was too embarrassed to face you.
You were embarrassed?
Of course, I was embarrassed.
I got drunk and asked you out.
I'm the one who did a lousy
job of asking you out.
Pardon?
I made you wait...
by expressing myself very ambiguously.
And that even ended up
making you feel embarrassed.
So I'm the one who did a
lousy job of asking you out.
Mr. Kwon.
So although it may be late,
I'd like to ask you out properly this time.
What's this?
I didn't know what you'd like,
so I searched the web a little.
And I saw a video clip of
an interview you did...
at your favorite chicken feet restaurant.
You like its chicken feet dish...
and want to be asked out
via a handwritten letter.
Then is this...
I didn't get you the chicken feet,
but please accept at least that.
Are you going to read it in front of me?
Yes, of course.
- The curiosity's killing me.
- But...
Then I'll wait for you in the car.
(Let's date.)
Yes, I'd love to!
Let's date!
♫ My one ♫
♫ The only one, one, one, you are ♫
♫ If this is love, love ♫
Thank you for accepting my proposal.
Thank you for finally telling me.
♫ What should I do? What if this is the love? ♫
You'll wear it out.
I'll read it until I do then.
Hold on a second.
I'll go and get changed.
We'll head to the office together.
- You should get some rest today.
- Why?
You have cases backed up due
to the Im Yun Hee Case.
You'll be up to your neck with work.
It'll be harder without me around.
You knew that, but you chose
not to come to work today?
I'm grateful, but you should rest
since you already have the day off.
I won't be at the office
anyway in the afternoon.
Why not?
I'm heading to the court,
the prosecutor's office,
and then to meet a client.
I'll be done at around 7pm.
- What do you say?
- Wait. What?
We should go on a date...
since it's our first day as a couple.
Why are you laughing?
Just.
You saying "date" and
"the first day as a couple"...
is just so pretty.
Then I'll pick you up at around 7pm.
All right.
See you later then.
The defendant turned out to be a victim.
We're being pressured to reveal
if there was any coercion.
What are you going to do?
She wasn't coerced.
How could you not investigate and
blindly believe her confession?
- I'm sorry.
- You're dismissed.
The case should've gone to Prosecutor Im.
I heard the news.
Your suspect became the victim.
That really was a twist.
- Please don't.
- Well,
you're just like that too.
You're a bundle of twists.
You were belittling your seniors,
so I thought you must have a great talent.
Instead, you're sloppy and ditsy.
Why did you only arrest
the innocent Ms. Im?
What do you mean she's innocent?
She may not have killed him herself,
but she either helped or at
least did nothing to stop it.
She actively covered up for Park Su Myeong.
You humiliated this office,
but you're still running your mouth.
I think it's best if I was
present during the questioning.
Yes, of course.
I'll schedule it with the
prosecutor and get back to you.
Sure.
Yeo Reum.
Hi.
Are you all right?
You seem pale.
How did you know that
Park Su Myeong was at the scene?
You caught on to it, but why didn't I?
I know you're not to blame,
so we'll talk some other time.
Yeo Reum!
(Hankuk Medical Center)
She has acute gastritis
brought on by stress,
and lethargy led to a fever.
She'll be fine once her temperature drops.
The case starts the day
after tomorrow, right?
Can I see the files?
When will we question the suspect again?
- That will be conducted tomorrow.
- I see.
The person you have reached is unavailable.
Please leave a message...
(Attorney Kwon Jung Rok)
Yes, Mr. Kwon. Are you here?
I'm sorry, but we'll have
to take a rain check.
Why?
Prosecutor Yoo fell ill,
so I brought her to the ER.
What happened?
She has gastritis and a fever.
I called another friend
to look after her today,
but I still have to meet with the client.
I'm afraid we won't be able to meet today.
I see. There's no other way, I guess.
All right.
Sure.
What happened?
You fainted after talking to Jung Rok.
Don't you remember?
What are you doing here though?
You finished your fluids,
and the doctor said you can leave.
- I asked what you were doing here.
- Is that really important?
I could ask you the same thing too.
You can't be this sensitive.
We'll keep having trials,
and some we'll lose.
You can't survive if you
let them get to you.
That's who I am though.
I hate it.
I hate that I crumbled after...
losing a trial.
Also, I hate that you're...
seeing me like this.
I hate it too.
I hate that this is how we are now.
Back then,
you used to be honest in front of me.
You'd laugh when you want...
and cry when you want.
I wonder if he's still busy.
How could he not call me even once?
He called. It's him.
Yes, Mr. Kwon.
Did I wake you up by any chance?
No.
Are you going home now?
Yes. My meeting with the client
took longer than I thought.
You must've already had dinner by now.
Do you want to go for some tea?
Tea?
It's okay.
You must've had a long day,
so you should go get some rest.
I'll see you tomorrow.
But Mr. Kwon...
Yes? What is it?
I don't want today to be
our first day as a couple.
- Sorry?
- Just listen to me.
Who lets their first day pass
by so meaninglessly like this?
So why don't we make...
tomorrow our first day as a couple?
All right.
Then tomorrow will be our first day.
I'm sorry I couldn't keep my promise today.
Don't worry about it.
Drive safely then. I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Okay. We've talked on the phone,
so that's enough for now.
Alright, let's start dating
properly from tomorrow.
Let's start dating.
What? You want me to go
to Mr. Choi's office?
Well...
Can you do me this favor
for just a couple of days?
The thing is, during this period
right after the holidays,
the divorce rate goes up rapidly.
Shall we call it a peak
season for divorces?
So Mr. Choi has dozens of
divorce cases waiting...
to be processed right now.
And Ms. Yang is really caught
up right now helping...
Ms. Dan with the
pharmaceutical company case.
But, the thing is...
if I'm not here, Mr. Kwon
will have a hard time alone.
You just wrapped up the Im Yun Hee Case.
Is there something you have
to take care of urgently?
No, I guess not, at the moment.
- I'll be fine.
- Thank you for understanding.
And since you're the ace here,
can't you manage well on your own?
If that's all, I'll get back to work.
Thank you.
I'll get going too.
Thank you for understanding, everyone.
I really have such considerate
employees around me.
Hey, Jun Seok.
Like you asked, I split up
Mr. Kwon and Yun Seo.
Thanks, Joon Gyu.
I'm afraid Yun Seo didn't want to...
go to work yesterday
because of that lawyer.
I heard from her manager, and those two...
had many issues all this time.
I heard Yun Seo said she'd crush
Kwon Jung Rok by all means.
Was it that bad?
Anyway, from now on, you should...
recycle... No, split them up.
Don't worry about it.
If it's for Yun Seo's happiness,
I'll make sure those two don't
even talk to each other.
Honey, it's me.
I was wondering if I could
drop by during lunch.
Oh, you're busy.
No, it's fine. Have a good day then.
Okay.
Ms. Dan.
Did you get a new boyfriend?
Yes, well...
I did get one, but...
But what? Why are you sighing?
- Well...
- Yes.
Forget it. Last time, you told me...
I had a chance with that
delivery guy, so I made a move...
and was rejected. Don't you remember?
I made up my mind then.
I will never receive dating
advice from you ever again.
I'm sorry about that time.
But there are more couples
that succeeded with my advice.
During "Sandabang", a couple
received counseling from me...
and expressed their feelings truthfully.
And they ended up getting married.
Married?
- They got married?
- Yes.
This is a secret, but my boyfriend is...
the owner of the cafe
that's across the street.
He's chic and handsome like americano,
but his voice is smooth like a latte,
and when he asked me out saying
he always had his eyes on me,
it was sweet like caramel macchiato.
That's so romantic.
So? Why are you sighing?
Well, the problem is...
I feel upset because it feels
like I'm the only one in love.
I want to put all things
aside to meet him...
and stay by his side all the time.
But I guess he doesn't feel the same.
Is that so?
We were supposed to go on
a date last night too.
But he suddenly said some
coffee beans arrived.
He said he had to roast them,
and canceled our date.
Just now, I told him I'd drop
by briefly during lunch,
but he said he's busy squeezing
oranges or something.
I can understand that he's busy,
but it seems like I'm always the
one nagging and wanting to meet.
It's so upsetting.
Me too.
- What?
I mean, if I was in your situation,
I'd feel really upset too.
Yun Seo, you...
are really good at sympathizing
since you're an actress and all.
I thought you were upset too
because you've started dating.
That's totally ridiculous.
Jin Sim, about yesterday's...
Yun Seo, thanks for
volunteering to help me out.
Since I have such high
win rates, my clients...
come to me like moths to a flame.
By the way, this is a table of my schedule.
You can call the clients and
tell them when they can visit.
Okay, I understand.
Hold on.
Ms. Hwang Yeon Du who's supposed
to come for counseling at 2pm.
It's not the Hwang Yeon Du
that I know, is she?
She probably is.
Wasn't she your rival once?
If you're talking about
the actress, it's her.
Oh, right. You working here
is confidential.
Then why don't you step
out briefly later on?
Yes, I guess I can do that.
But is she...
getting divorced?
Seeing that she's coming
to me for counseling,
I believe so.
Why? Why is she getting divorced?
Article 26 of the Attorneys-at-Law Act.
"The attorney shall not disclose
any confidential information..."
"relating to the
representation of a client."
This is quite upsetting.
I thought she was living
happily after getting married.
Were you close to her?
Close...
my foot.
She was like my arch enemy.
Oh Yun Seo.
What on earth? Why did you get so tall?
How high are your heels?
- 7cm.
- Stylist.
- Yes?
- Bring me 10cm heels.
No, bring me 20cm heels!
Okay.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Sir.
Use more reflectors for my scene.
2. No, 3 times more.
That's the kind of person she was.
She had to be better than me,
and she had to get treated well.
From the very beginning of her
career until she retired,
she really made things difficult for me.
I suddenly don't want
to defend her anymore.
Should I not take this case?
That's not right.
This is your work.
And you're a professional.
Then I'll just talk to her like a robot...
that has no feelings.
Are you here for counseling?
Things must be very difficult for you.
I'll even defend her in court...
like the AlphaGo that has no soul.
Watch carefully.
My client...
holds no responsibility...
for what happened.
My gosh, it's 1:30pm already.
- I might run into her.
- That can't happen.
You should go.
I'll call you once I'm done talking to her.
- Okay, please let me know.
- Sure.
I'm here to meet my attorney.
- Did you make a reservation?
- Of course.
What are you doing?
There's a fellow actress outside.
You know that no one's supposed
to find out that I work here.
Thank you.
Then I'll pull down the blinds.
You can stay in my office.
No, she has the eyes of a falcon.
It'd be better for me to just go outside.
Hello, my name is Hwang Yeon Du.
Hello, my name is Choi Yun Hyuk.
- Please take a seat.
- Okay.
I'm sure you already know me
since I used to be so famous.
My goodness.
My designer brand wallet is
full of cash and credit cards.
And I must've left it in the restroom.
- Please wait here for a minute.
- Sure.
Oh Yun Seo?
No, I'm not Oh Yun Seo.
I must've been mistaken. I'm sorry.
No problem.
My goodness, what are you doing?
See? It is you, Yun Seo.
How dare you lie to me?
But what are you doing here at a law firm?
I'm here as a client.
My goodness.
Do you have to go to court again?
My gosh.
It hasn't even been that long
since you last caused a ruckus...
by going to court.
You have such an unfortunate life.
Shouldn't you ask a shaman
to perform an exorcism?
Do you need some money?
What about you? What brings you here?
Aren't you here as a client as well?
Why would I come to a law firm as a client?
As you already know,
I'm being loved by my rich husband,
and I'm living a proud and happy life.
I'm just here...
to take a look at the building
because I might buy it.
I'm really interested in
buildings these days.
I'm sorry. I feel like
I'm boasting too much.
You won't be able to make
a comeback as an actress,
you're probably struggling financially,
and it even seems like you got
yourself involved in a lawsuit.
You've practically hit rock bottom.
I think I was a bit too harsh on you.
Yun Seo.
Go home safely.
Make sure the reporters
don't take photos of you.
Or do the reporters not
care about you anymore?
Yeon Du!
My gosh.
It's like she was born to harass me.
One time, I had a dress picked out
for an awards ceremony,
but she took it from me
and wore it herself.
And another time, she went to see
the director that cast me...
as the main character of his drama.
Then she told him that she
can do better than me...
and that she'll even get paid less than me.
So eventually, she ended up getting
the role of the main character.
My gosh.
That drama incident still makes angry.
Mr. Kwon, is it too late
to file a lawsuit on this?
Yes, it's too late.
What?
In order for it to be an obstruction
of business or an illegal act,
she had to spread false information
or make you get fired unfairly.
But what she did was merely
making a better offer...
by offering the director
to get paid less than you.
She wasn't being deceptive or unfair.
Gosh, you are very logical.
Pardon?
I was just complaining to my boyfriend.
But I actually thought I was getting
counseling from an attorney.
If you ever tell me that
someone was mean to you,
I feel like I'd take your side
regardless of who did what.
And I feel like I'd
really hate that person.
But you must not feel that way.
That's not it.
Also...
Never mind.
I'll be off now.
And I'm really sorry to say this,
but I don't want today to
be our first day either.
I'm sorry, but we'll have
to take a rain check.
There's no other way, I guess.
All right.
She did sound a little down that day.
You want me to go to Mr. Choi's office?
No, I guess not, at the moment.
I'll be fine.
And she did seem a little upset then.
But I only agreed to that for her sake...
because it'd be better for her
to experience various cases.
Does he even like me at all?
My gosh.
Mr. Kwon, what are you doing here?
Your cell phone was turned off.
Is it turned off?
Is that why you came?
- To tell me that?
- No.
- Let's go on a date.
- What?
A date?
What's going on all of a sudden?
I really didn't think we
should delay another day.
I don't want to put it off anymore.
Let's make today our first day.
That's what I'd like to do.
- Do you not feel the same way?
- No, I'd love to.
Let's go, then.
Where are we going?
I've never been to an observatory before.
How did you think of this place?
It was too late to go anywhere,
and we couldn't have our first date...
at a 24-hour pork backbone stew restaurant.
The location had to be
special but not crowded.
I weighed my options...
and came up with a place...
decent enough to go on a date on at night.
Do you like it?
I love it.
It's the best.
It must be easier to spot stars over there.
Let's go.
A shooting star!
Did you see it?
No, I didn't.
My gosh.
You should've been right behind me.
Why do you walk so slow?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Because I'm sorry.
What?
Jin Sim,
I'm sorry that I'm on the slow side.
This isn't anything to
apologize about though.
I thought about my actions,
and I was inattentive.
It took me a long time to ask you out...
and I canceled our first date.
I kept upsetting you in a lot of ways.
It's all because I'm awkward
at expressing my feelings.
I feel bad that my ineptness
is the cause of it.
I tend to be slow,
so I might not be able to match your pace.
However, I'll take steps towards you...
at my own pace though.
Slowly and but for a long time.
Actually, Mr. Kwon,
could I ask you something?
Do you like me?
Sorry?
It's nothing. Forget you heard anything.
I like you.
I like you, Jin Sim.
A lot.
♫ I'm looking at you for a while ♫
♫ Wondering if you feel the same way ♫
♫ Of course, I really don't know ♫
♫ It's still so hard ♫
♫ My heart has slow footsteps ♫
♫ So with all my strength,
I chased after you ♫
♫ Each step I take ♫
♫ You're right there
so why am I hesitating? ♫
♫ Oh love, love is, what is it, what is love? ♫
♫ Oh love ♫
(Touch Your Heart)
Ms. Oh will have men
vying for her attention,
so do better if you wish to keep her.
Let's get back to work.
Wait, are you...
- jealous?
- Of course not.
She used to be very popular.
Her commercials aired all the time.
She sure is a goddess.
I'll try being with Ms. Oh then.
I wonder what kind of men she'll date.
There's no way it's Mr. Kwon.
I want to be the one who makes you laugh.
Mr. Kwon, can we...
kiss?
Here?