I had a great time today.
I wanted to watch that movie with you,
so I'm glad that we got this chance.
I'm glad you think that way.
It was perfect.
It was the kind of goodbye
that I expected from you.
"Goodbye" seems a bit harsh, right?
It seems like we're parting,
but we only won't be seeing
each other at the law firm.
Although, that's quite sad too.
Ms. Oh Yun Seo.
Why are you suddenly
calling me by that name?
Thanks to you,
I was happy.
Why are you saying that?
Just like that movie,
you'll go back to your world,
and I'll go back to mine.
That's what I want.
♫ Your warmth still remains ♫
What are you saying, Mr. Kwon?
♫ At the tip of my left hand ♫
♫ It's wrapping around
the left side of my heart ♫
We...
♫ Just like then ♫
should break up.
♫ When I couldn't let go ♫
Why are you being like
this all of a sudden?
Did I do something wrong?
Is it because I lied to you?
Do you suddenly feel betrayed
now that you think about it?
Or did the paparazzi photo
make you feel uncomfortable?
Do you feel pressured because of
all the attention I'm getting?
Can you please say something?
Why do we need to break up?
Yes, you're right.
Because of all the reasons
you just mentioned,
I've come to a conclusion that we
shouldn't date each other anymore.
So...
I think it would be best that we break up.
Mr. Kwon.
Thank you...
for everything.
♫ Of your small hand
that touched my left hand ♫
♫ When we looked into each other's eyes ♫
♫ I can't forget that moment ♫
♫ Don't leave yet, don't let go ♫
♫ We can't let go yet ♫
♫ The beautiful you is smiling at me ♫
♫ I want to hold your hand and tell you ♫
♫ The feelings I wrote to you ♫
♫ Engraved deep in the left side of my heart ♫
♫ That hasn't reached you yet ♫
♫ Hold my hand ♫
(Episode 13)
Yun Seo.
Is she still sleeping?
Yun Seo, what's the matter?
Yun Seo, did you cry?
Hyuk Joon.
Yes, that's right. I'm right here,
so tell me what it is.
What's wrong?
Mr. Kwon broke up with me.
What?
He said that this is
where our story ends...
even when he admitted to liking me so much.
Even when he promised to
always be on my side.
How can someone change so drastically?
How can a relationship end with
just a few exchanges of words?
I've never experienced a breakup before,
so I don't know how to act or what to feel.
Yun Seo,
you have to clear out
your desk at the law firm,
but I'll do that for you.
Stay home and rest.
No, I'll go.
It doesn't seem like you're
in a shape to do so.
Still, I need to see Mr. Kwon.
Yun Seo.
Mr. Yeon, why are you sighing?
The law firm feels oddly dim today.
Do we have a burned-out bulb?
Mr. Yeon, I don't think that's what it is.
The six fluorescent lights we
have are shining brightly...
in their designated places.
Is that so? Why does it seem dim then?
Is it because of Ms. Oh?
That's right.
The luminous goddess is gone,
and darkness is back at the office.
You're right. It does feel
a bit empty around here.
Even we feel her absence,
so I can't imagine how it is for Mr. Kwon.
Ms. Oh helped him greatly as his secretary.
Her presence must be irreplaceable.
Just imagine...
a young lost deer that has nowhere to go.
That I'm not sure about.
Anyway, Ms. Yang,
aid him with whatever he needs.
Sure. I'll look out for him more.
Ms. Oh?
Ms. Oh!
What are you doing here?
I thought you weren't coming in anymore.
Well, I had to clear out my desk.
We could've just mailed
you your belongings.
You didn't have to come
down here personally.
Just...
She doesn't seem like
her bubbly self today.
Mr. Kwon.
I'll get going then.
I'm leaving.
Once I leave, there's no turning back.
Are you really not going to look at me?
You did a good job during your time here.
I hope that you do well
even after you leave.
♫ I locked the door ♫
♫ And stayed in bed all day ♫
♫ It'll get better if I sleep ♫
♫ I wish everything would just stop ♫
♫ Those words, "How are you?"  ♫
♫ They won't leave my head all day ♫
♫ In our photos ♫
♫ I'm just smiling, not knowing anything ♫
♫ Because of my damn pride ♫
♫ Only deep scars remain ♫
♫ Sorry, I don't know why ♫
♫ I only knew myself back then ♫
♫ In the photographs in my hands ♫
♫ You're just smiling ♫
♫ But you're never coming back ♫
♫ You're never coming back ♫
(Whenever and whatever!
Just tell me what you need.)
- Yes?
- If you don't have plans,
join me for drinks tonight.
Sure, I'd like that.
I've actually been craving some myself.
Jung Rok.
What are you two doing here together?
We agreed to give us another shot.
You have no idea how clingy she is.
I agreed to accept that devotion.
I gave in to her tenacity and persistence.
Stop joking in front of him.
Don't you know that he takes
everything seriously?
Actually, you're wrong about him on that.
He's not the stiff and
wooden person he used to be.
He's totally different now.
Dating someone has made him that way.
- Really?
- Yes.
If the old Jung Rok were
like this dried squid,
the Jung Rok that now dates...
is as soft and spongy like this egg roll.
What's with the long face though?
Don't you like my analogy?
I'm sure Ms. Oh would agree.
While we're at it,
let's ask her to join us.
He's right. You should ask her.
You had better brace yourself...
because you'll be shocked to see
how smitten he is with her.
Don't just sit there. Call her.
Hold on. Is this place a bit too shabby...
to call her?
Shall we go to a wine bar nearby?
Let's do that.
This place is too exposed and
she might feel uncomfortable.
- Right?
- Yes.
There's no need.
Why?
Are you worried we might tease her?
Look at him. This is
how much he cares for her.
We broke up.
What do you...
What? Why?
If I keep staying here,
I'll just make you guys uncomfortable.
Let's meet up again next time.
I'll get going then. Have fun.
Jung Rok.
Hey, how could you leave like that?
Let's go for a drink of soju.
- I sent Yeo Reum home.
- Why?
What are you talking about?
When you said that before,
I should've realized that
something was wrong.
Let's go. Come on.
- Ma'am, one more soju, please.
- Okay.
So...
You broke up with her for
the sake of her happiness?
Why did you if you're going
to be this depressed?
You should've stuck with her
until the end by all means.
I know well how much she
wanted to go back...
to that path again.
I didn't want to become a barrier
that blocked her in that path.
How could I do that?
There was nothing else I could
do besides letting her go.
Still...
Ms. Oh doesn't even know this fact.
She'll just remember you as a jerk
who suddenly changed. That's so...
So...
how did you endure it?
After you broke up with Yeo Reum.
How did you endure it?
However, regarding the damage caused
by infringement of copyright,
the software developed by
the plaintiff is being...
sold individually and independently.
Taking this into consideration,
the scope of compensation for damages...
must be limited to the infringement
committed by the defendant.
I was investigating the damages for
overseas real estate development,
and I found out the appraisal
and assessment methods between...
foreign investment countries
and Korea were different.
And as a result, the company
suffered a five-million-dollar loss.
♫ Your pillow that was always wet ♫
♫ Finally, it'll be dry ♫
♫ We went through so much ♫
He can be held legally
responsible for violation of...
the Protective Labor Legislation.
Please consider the fact that
the program developed by...
the defendant while he worked brought
huge profits to his company.
I hope the defendant receives the
maximum amount of leniency...
allowed by the law.
♫ Now we don't have to stay up
at night worrying anymore ♫
♫ Now have a peaceful, good night ♫
♫ We were so happy ♫
♫ We were crazy in love ♫
♫ Now we don't have to have
those late night, painful worries ♫
♫ Now really, good bye ♫
Let's drink to Mr. Kwon
who recorded number one in sales.
- Cheers.
Ma'am?
Mr. Kwon. You've been working like...
a madman these days. I love it.
It'd be nice if you answer me
when I talk to you.
But what's the big deal about...
recording number one in sales
to hold a team dinner?
What do you think it is?
It's what motivates our law
firm for a better tomorrow.
Mr. Choi. When will you become the
star of a team dinner like this?
You said you'd care more about our profits.
You said you'd give up
your sense of duty and justice.
But I just want to give you up.
My goodness! How could you say that?
That's too harsh!
You seem a bit too harsh right now.
Are you upset with me
over something lately?
Is that why you dress up like this
in order to protest against me?
You were terrifying
when you just did that gesture.
Please, Mr. Yeon.
She looks so pretty. Don't say that.
That's what I wanted to say.
You should mind yourself, sir.
And don't eat with food all over your lips.
Is that so?
Hearing something like that in front
of everyone is very embarrassing.
Wait a minute. What is this strange mood?
Ms. Dan and Mr. Choi took turns
just now covering for each other.
You can't fool my eyes.
Have you two...
formed an alliance?
You two recorded the lowest performance,
so you formed an alliance to
help each other out, right?
That's ridiculous, sir.
Still, they're better off this way.
Before, they used to bicker
like enemies, but now,
they're warm to each other
like cherry blossoms...
blooming in spring along the railroad.
Mr. Lee, you speak very poetically.
I don't think you know it. Am I right?
He might even become a poet.
That's a dream that I've
cherished for a long time.
Really? Then can you write a poem about me?
The subtitle can be
something like "charisma".
That sounds intense.
Don't you think? Cheers.
Cheers.
By the way, why aren't you smiling?
You keep scowling and ruining the mood.
It's okay if he doesn't
smile since he's competent.
You can stop smiling, as long
as you become more competent.
Mr. Kwon, let's have a drink.
With an expressionless face.
Your glass is empty.
Here you go. Let's say
cheers expressionlessly.
Eat up.
She's here!
(Oh Yun Seo Signing Event)
(Universe's Goddess, Oh Yun Seo)
(Writer, Lee Se Jin)
(Ju Ha, Oh Yun Seo)
("Love Hurts")
You dropped this.
Oh, my. Thank you.
I usually hate making mistakes.
I don't like people who
make mistakes either.
But you're the first one
who still looks cute.
I know I wrote this,
but this is embarrassing.
It's okay since you said it
to Yun Seo, right?
Ms. Oh did a script reading recently.
I guess she's doing well.
She looks pretty. Look.
Look at Ms. Oh. She's gorgeous as always.
She looks happier than
she did at our law firm.
Maybe it's because she's doing
something she really likes.
I really miss Ms. Oh.
Me too.
I grew quite attached to her,
and I think of her often.
It was fun to chat with her
in the office kitchen.
I miss her too.
Right? I'm not the only one
who misses her, am I?
Mr. Kwon, why aren't you saying anything?
Don't you miss Ms. Oh?
Can't you hear me?
Goodness. He's like a human
with no heart at all.
Hold on. I don't see Ms. Dan and Mr. Choi.
I think they both have
plans for lunch today.
Honey.
How do I look today?
You told me that you like
women who wear dresses,
so I bought this on the internet.
It's not too bad.
Honey.
Try this.
I'll dip it in this peanut butter
sauce that's just as sweet as you.
Here you go.
No, Ms. Dan. It's okay.
And I've been meaning to
tell you this for a while.
I know that we're dating
each other by contract,
but I personally think you're being...
a bit too forward.
And that wasn't part of our contract.
Okay, I understand.
Ms. Dan.
By any chance, did you forget
the contents of the contract?
Let me remind you one more time.
"Article 1. We will be dating
each other for 1 month."
We have five more days left.
I didn't forget.
"Article two. We are both
forbidden to date or flirt..."
"with a third party..."
"during the period of our contract."
Yes, of course. I'm not seeing
anyone else other than you.
"Article three. During the
period of the contract,"
"we must eat together at
least two times a week."
That's exactly why we're
eating together right now.
What exactly is the problem?
There are additional articles
that can break the contract.
"We shall not make any
kind of physical contact."
Does that mean our contract
is no longer valid...
because our hands touched while
trying to reach out for the sauce?
Well, it seemed like it was an accident,
so I'll just end it with a warning.
I hope you're more careful from now on.
Okay, I'll be really careful.
Just a second.
Yes, this is Choi Yun Hyuk.
Gosh, that was really close.
Our contract almost got canceled.
What a nightmare.
Left hand, you'd better be more careful.
This is a warning.
Does she like me that much?
Well, of course,
I can totally understand why.
But her feelings for me are a bit too much.
What should I do?
I get that she's nice and cute,
but my heart feels so numb.
My heart...
Jung Rok.
It seemed odd that you never
drove to work these days.
Have you always been taking the bus?
Yes, kind of.
Since we ran into each other,
should we go get some soju?
No, let's just go.
Wait for me.
Gosh, you must be so tired.
Goodness, are you that tired?
You must be exhausted.
Did you not get any sleep again last night?
I have no time to sleep.
I need to memorize so many lines.
I know, right? There are so
many legal terms in the script.
It seemed like it'll be really
hard to memorize the lines.
But having worked at the law
firm really helped out a lot.
I've heard of most of the terms.
It makes it easy for me to
memorize and understand my lines.
We're here.
Already? Gosh, what are you going to do?
I'm pretty sure the shoot
will finish at dawn again.
It's okay. Gosh, my back.
I should go outside and
stretch my body a little.
Hello.
I'm relieved that she quickly
managed to get better again.
(Supreme Court of Korea Information Center)
(Yun Seo Attends a Table-Read for
Her Comeback Drama, "Love Hurts")
I guess she's okay now.
Cheers.
By the way, what's in that big paper bag?
Oh, I got you some gifts.
These masks will protect you
from all the fine dust.
Are you sure you didn't
get them to protect me...
from all the other women?
Yes, you're right.
And these are...
some cosmetics that will make
your fine skin become even finer.
And these are vitamins that
will enhance your energy.
And these are...
Wait.
Ms. Dan, do you like me that much?
I mean, I'm very well aware...
of how extremely attractive I am.
But am I really worth all this?
Yes, you're worth it. You're so attractive.
The more I get to know you, I find
myself falling for you even more.
That's why it makes me feel sad.
I like you so much, but this happiness...
will only last for five more days.
Can you be honest with me?
How did you feel during the one month...
that we've dated each other?
Are you going to end it
with me cold turkey...
after five days?
You're a really good person.
You take such good care of me,
and you're also a little cute.
But how should I put this?
My heart feels numb when I'm with you.
What?
Are you okay? Why did you drink so much?
Why do you think?
I like you so much.
But once the contract's over,
we'll have to go back to being colleagues.
And that makes me feel miserable.
But I guess there's nothing we can do.
It's my fault for having failed
to make your heart flutter.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
I'm okay.
I'm relieved. I'm sorry about that.
What... What's with that face?
Did you just fall for him?
Yes, isn't he so attractive?
But you were just telling
me how much you like me...
and that you feel miserable.
You told me that your heart
feels numb when you're with me.
I tend to give up really quickly.
Hey, wait. My leg...
I think I hurt my leg a little.
So can you give me your number?
Or can you give me a ride?
Wait! Hey!
Gosh, my heart...
Why does my heart hurt?
I tend to give up really quickly.
Yes, Mom. A blind date?
I don't want to go on a blind date.
Yes, okay. Bye.
Mr. Lee, is your mother telling
you to go on a blind date?
Yes.
But I really don't have any
plans to go on a blind date.
I'm one of those people who think...
people who are meant to be are
strongly connected to each other.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Why does the defendant's proxy
keep asking to change the date?
Don't you think this is a bit out of line?
I'll reject their request for
wanting to change the date.
Then I'll submit a document
to the department of justice.
Where's Kwon Jung Rok?
- Ma'am...
- Where is he?
Please calm down first.
Where's Kwon Jung Rok?
Where is he?
There you are.
You remember my son, don't you?
You made my son a murderer in
court in just a blink of an eye.
Park Su Myeong.
Who murdered Kim Yeong Tae?
The person who stabbed him...
- The person who stabbed him...
- No, don't say a word!
The defendant will sit.
No, don't hit her. Don't hit her!
I came looking for you
because he doesn't deserve this.
- Ma'am, please calm down...
- Let go of me.
How can I calm down...
when this man made my son
look like a murderer?
My son...
isn't cruel enough...
to stab someone twice and kill him!
Ma'am, I understand how you feel,
but Mr. Kwon wasn't the one who
decided that he was guilty.
The case was ruled by a judge.
Tomorrow's the last hearing.
What is my son going to do?
What if he stays locked up forever?
I will never forgive you.
Never!
Ma'am.
Mr. Kwon, don't let it get to you.
That's just how mothers are.
When push comes to shove
and the child is cornered,
parents show a lapse in judgment...
and choose to believe their innocence.
Ms. Yang, don't you agree?
Yes, that sounds about right.
You know how my daughter was
accused of being a bully.
That case taught me something.
When a child is pushed into a corner,
no parent is able to think clearly.
The mind goes completely blank.
Mr. Park's mother just needed
someone to vent her frustration on.
The situation isn't ideal,
but hating and resenting you...
probably kept her sane all this time.
So please be understanding.
The prosecutor will recommend a sentence.
(Defendant)
The defendant Park Su Myeong...
adored Im Yun Hee, the victim's wife.
On the night of January 21, 2019,
in order to save Ms. Im who was
being assaulted by her husband,
the defendant picked up a knife.
If he only wished to protect Ms. Im though,
he could've called the
police or ran out with her.
He could've come up with another solution.
However, the defendant chose
the most drastic action.
He stabbed the victim
once in the abdomen...
and once in the chest...
and brutally murdered the victim.
Considering all circumstances,
it's hard to say...
that his actions were accidental
and that he only...
wished to protect Ms. Im
by means of self-defense.
Instead, it's most likely that
his violent side came through.
That is why I believe he must be...
isolated from the public for some time.
I recommend a sentence
of 20 years in prison.
Defense Attorney,
deliver your closing argument.
The defendant admits all of his actions...
and is in deep remorse.
I hope you put that into consideration.
Case number 2019G173.
The defendant Park Su Myeong
is on trial for murder.
I will now deliver his sentence.
We sentence the defendant
to 20 years in prison.
No! You're wrong!
My son didn't kill anyone!
My son isn't a monster!
- No!
- Don't hurt my mom.
- My boy... No!
- Not my mom!
- Get away from my mom.
- He's innocent!
Mom, take me with you. I want to go home.
Mom, I want to go home!
- Mom!
- My boy!
- He's innocent!
Mom, I want to go home!
My boy!
Get away from my mom!
Mr. Kwon.
Please help my son.
He didn't kill anyone.
I'm sorry about how I treated you before.
You didn't know the truth, right?
So please, help my boy.
I understand what you're going through.
However, your son...
confessed his crimes in court.
That's right. Then you
should've let him finish.
Why didn't you hear him out completely?
My son only stabbed the victim once.
Then the second stab...
might have come from the wife!
He may be a lot of things, but my son...
never lies.
I've been suspicious of
that Im Yun Hee woman.
It seemed like she adored my son...
so much that she was willing
to go to jail for him,
but she hasn't visited him even once.
She disappeared from the neighborhood!
(Statement)
(Cell phone number)
The number you have
called is not in service.
Please check the number and redial.
Yun Seo, you're always beautiful,
but you look exceptional today.
The makeup looks smooth too.
She's right. You look like a goddess.
I should take a photo later.
Why would you take a photo?
You're not here on a picnic, you know.
Also, don't bother her since she
has an emotional scene today.
We must help our actor
stay in her character.
Don't you agree?
Why? Do you have a problem?
We're ready for her.
- Sure thing.
- I'm ready too.
And action!
What is it?
Why are you having a hard time telling me?
- What is it?
- We...
should break up.
It's over.
We...
should break up.
Cut. Okay!
Yun Seo, that was great.
My gosh.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
I had no idea she could give deep emotions.
I know. She seems fully
absorbed in her character too.
Her acting has improved a lot.
She won't be called a
bad actor anymore now.
Bad actor? You won't have to
worry about that ever again.
- Director, please excuse me.
- Okay.
Yun Seo, are you okay?
Why are you crying?
Is it because you were reminded of him?
I tried to forget...
I tried so hard to forget about him.
But whenever I think about
Mr. Kwon from time to time,
I become unbearably sad.
I thought you were okay now.
How could I be okay? I liked him so much.
But there's nothing I can do.
I must think of my fans...
and everyone who is
waiting for my comeback.
And if I keep having a hard time like this,
Mr. Kwon won't like it either.
I'm sorry, Hyuk Joon.
I'll try my best...
to control my feelings.
Don't worry.
Okay. I'm sorry too.
You should get some rest, Yun Seo.
I wonder if he's doing well.
During Im Yun Hee's first hearing,
Park Su Myeong was pointed
out as the real culprit,
and she was released on bail.
After that, her whereabouts remain unknown.
I asked around the neighborhood,
but no one saw Im Yun Hee.
I also looked into something else.
There were a total of 11 insurances
signed under Kim Yeong Tae's name.
A part of the insurance
payouts went to Im Yun Hee.
Out of a total 4.49 million
dollars for his death benefit,
2.73 million was paid to her.
Was that insurance payout...
She withdrew all of it
in cash and disappeared.
She disappeared when the insurance
payout wasn't fully paid.
Something seems fishy, right?
First, let's go meet the employee
at the insurance company.
When did you first meet Ms. Im Yun Hee?
February 27.
She had to sign some papers
regarding the insurance payout,
so we met briefly.
We met at this cafe.
Do you remember anything
particular from your conversation?
For instance, did she say
where she was going...
or whom she was planning to meet?
No. There was nothing special
about our conversation.
But...
during our conversation,
she kept looking outside.
I wondered what it was
and looked outside...
A man was waiting for her?
After our meeting, I saw her
getting into his car clearly.
So I just thought he was
her friend or something.
This was such a controversial case,
and I was curious what
kind of person she was.
But when she came with a man,
so I thought it was strange.
Who do you think he is?
Do you think she had another lover?
I don't think she has any
other family members.
By the way, if Ms. Oh finds out about this,
she'll be so shocked.
Ms. Oh worked really hard on this case.
She went with you to Im Yun Hee's home too.
When you were attacked by
Park Su Myeong by a bat,
she was worried sick about you.
Ms. Oh, are you all right?
What about you? Are you hurt?
Oh, my gosh. It's still bleeding.
Oh, no...
Let's go now.
What? You'll represent
Park Su Myeong at his appeal?
You appointed him as a
witness during the trial,
and you're the one who pointed
him out as the real culprit.
But what do you mean,
there's another culprit?
You want to be Park Su Myeong's attorney?
What is this...
I don't know. I'll pretend I didn't
hear this, so you can leave.
- No, I'll just leave.
- Mr. Yeon.
How could you gamble over
something you're not certain of?
Mr. Kwon. Do you know this is
a violation of your work ethics?
Anyway, I cannot allow this.
I told you clearly not to do it.
That's final.
Goodness. Mr. Kwon is making me...
so anxious, and it's
practically killing me.
I might die out of anxiety.
What if he really...
insists on taking Park Su Myeong's case?
I doubt it.
This is so disturbing.
- I'm back.
- Hello.
Ms. Dan. How did your trial go?
Yes. Of course.
It seems like Ms. Oh is shooting
a drama in front of the court.
I saw a sign that read "Love Hurts"...
on a vehicle near there.
Yes, hello? This is Attorney Dan Moon Hee.
It'll be so fun if we all
visit her filming site.
Shall we go?
Hae Yeong, Mr. Yeon has a lot
on his mind right now...
and he's quite disturbed.
I don't think he's in the
mood to visit a filming site.
That's not appropriate.
Right. I got overexcited.
I was a bit out of line there.
Right. I'm not in a situation
to go there right now.
Of course not.
I thought we were going for lunch.
Why are we at court?
Why? I'm thinking of having lunch...
at the cafeteria that's
located inside this court.
The cafeteria at this place is
really famous for its food.
What? I've never heard anything like that.
I'm glad you heard it now.
The reason why I won all
those numerous trials...
is because of the delicious
food from the cafeteria here.
I received good energy
and became successful.
Mr. Yeon. Did you come here to
look at the drama shooting?
Yes... No.
Is that a yes or no?
Yes, no. No.
I mean, I didn't actually
come to see the filming site.
But since we're here, it's not
a bad idea to take a look around.
Don't take it the wrong way.
She used to be our staff,
and pretending not to know is rude.
And didn't you two say
you missed Ms. Oh last time?
You did, right?
To boost the energy of my employees,
I've decided to sacrifice myself...
and come take a stroll near here.
But where is Ms. Oh?
I'm sorry, but you can't come near.
- Okay.
- You might be caught on camera.
The camera? Wow, I know too.
But we're not just pedestrians passing by.
We are well acquainted with Ms. Oh Yun Seo.
I see.
Who here living in Korea
is not well acquainted...
with the famous Ms. Oh Yun Seo?
We'll begin shooting soon,
so we'd appreciate your cooperation.
Let's just go, Mr. Yeon.
- Ms. Yang.
- Yes, you can begin shooting.
Do I really have to mention
the fact that I am...
the CEO of the famous Always Law Firm?
He might not know who I am.
He must be so flustered.
No, I mean...
It's all right, stop mentioning it.
I didn't know, but you are
really bad at keeping secrets.
Why don't you just tell him that I
was also on national television...
for a debate show and
also numerous TV programs,
and that I'm a famous
attorney while you're at it?
Why don't you just
outright tell him that...
the law firm Oh Yun Seo used
to work at was our law firm?
Mr. Yeon.
Ms. Oh.
Ms. Oh is running towards me.
She's even calling my name.
Ms. Yang, Hae Yeong.
How did you come here?
I really missed you.
It's so nice to see you.
Me too.
What brings the three of you here?
I walk by the court like
this from time to time.
I never forget how I first felt
when I decided to become...
a judicial officer that
would fight for the weak.
Today seemed like that sort of day.
- Today was that sort of day?
- Yes, let's say it was.
Anyway, I'm glad.
My shoot has been delayed,
and I have some time.
You didn't have lunch yet, right?
Shall we have lunch together?
Why are you all looking at me
instead of eating your food?
This feels so cool.
It feels like I'm eating with
a celebrity all of a sudden.
I felt the same way when I saw
you at the film site earlier.
It made me realize that you're an actress.
I can't believe we used to
hang out and chat with each other.
Gosh, don't treat me like
I'm a different person.
It makes us feel so distant.
Do you even know how
much I missed you guys?
Really?
- You missed us?
- Yes.
I knew that I would've
left a hole in your heart.
But hearing you actually say that
is making me blush a little.
- You really haven't changed at all.
- No, I haven't.
Is everyone else doing well?
Mr. Choi and Ms. Dan...
are busy these days. I think
they both started dating someone.
And Mr. Lee is still very sensitive
and poetic as always.
Is Mr. Kwon also doing well?
No, not really.
I feel anxious because it feels like
he'll get himself in trouble soon.
I think he's going to
defend Park Su Myeong.
What? Park Su Myeong?
Mr. Kwon, are you doing well?
I'm texting because I suddenly
got reminded of you...
Do you remember me?
Yes, I remember you.
Your mother came to see me.
She asked me to help you.
So I'd appreciate it if you answer...
the questions I'm about to ask you.
Okay, I'll answer them.
I heard you stabbed
Im Yun Hee's husband just once.
Is that correct?
Yes, I stabbed him once.
He always beat her up.
So I got really angry and stabbed him.
Then Yun Hee told me to run away.
I did what she told me to do and ran away.
But where's my mom?
My mom's suffering.
I need to help her.
I need to help my mom.
I need to make deliveries.
I don't... I don't want
my mom to suffer anymore.
I really stabbed him just once. Only once.
I only stabbed him once. Just once.
Jung Rok, have you gone mad?
You're actually going to
defend Park Su Myeong?
Yes.
Okay, I'll be really generous
and try to assume...
that there could actually
be another culprit.
But if that's true,
people will criticize you...
for having made an innocent person guilty.
On the other hand, if Park Su Myeong
turns out to be the culprit,
you'll still get criticized...
for trying to defend him at this point...
when you've already accused him of murder.
They'll question why you're being
so wishy-washy about the case.
People will lose...
their trust for you as an attorney.
I've already decided to defend him.
I even filed a copy of the
POA at the courthouse.
What?
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
Why did you do it if you
were going to be sorry?
Why would you make such an
important decision on your own?
I knew you'd be against it until the end,
so I had no choice.
Do you think of me as a joke
because I always compliment you?
- Sir.
- "Sir"?
Do you even think of me as your boss?
Jung Rok.
People are going to start
badmouthing you from now on.
No one is going to be on your side.
You're the one who made him
get sentenced to jail.
And by doing this, you're admitting
that you made a mistake.
It's only right that I do that
because it was my mistake.
It may be too late,
- but I want to set things straight.
- Sure.
You think you're so noble, don't you?
But no one's going to acknowledge
your aspiration and goodwill.
You'll just get branded as an attorney...
who thinks of trials as a joke.
Like I already told you,
that's something I should deal with...
Then what about our firm?
What about the people who work here?
Do you not care that our reputation
might get ruined because of you?
If you have the least amount...
of affection and sense of
duty for this law firm,
you can't be doing this to me.
You really can't do this to me.
Hey, I heard you filed a POA
for the Park Su Myeong case.
What happened?
- It just happened.
- My gosh, seriously.
You'll have to put a lot at risk.
Is that really necessary?
To be honest, I'm scared.
I don't know what the truth is yet.
But my rash decision...
could've driven someone to
the point of no return.
And the fact that I could end up...
leaving a scar on someone that
they won't be able to forget...
for the rest of their lives...
really scares me.
But if I turn away from this...
and lose my chance to set things straight,
not only will I lose the right
to be anyone's attorney,
but I'll also lose my confidence
to defend anyone at all.
(Secretary Kim Hae Yeong)
Isn't it a nice photo?
You should visit the law firm
next time, Yun Seo.
(Okay.)
By the way, Mr. Kwon eventually decided...
to take the Park Su Myeong case.
Because of that, Mr. Kwon and
Mr. Yeon had a huge argument.
Things aren't so pretty
at the office right now.
Mr. Kwon will have to do
a lot of work by himself...
now that he no longer has a
secretary to help him out.
What? Kwon Jung Rok will be
defending Park Su Myeong?
Yes, that's what I heard.
My gosh.
He's the one who pointed
him out as the culprit.
And now, he wishes to defend him?
Is he joking right now?
Hello, sir. I'm Koo Sung Gil
from Daehan Daily.
I heard Park Su Myeong and his attorney...
are getting ready for an appeal.
Is that true?
I'm not sure.
But even if that happens,
I don't think anything will change.
I actually heard some interesting news.
- Mr. Kwon.
- He's here.
You claimed that Park Su Myeong was guilty.
Why are you suddenly
going back on your word?
That means someone innocent
is currently in jail.
Do you feel guilty about that?
Some say you violated the
Attorneys' Code of Ethics.
What's your opinion on that?
Is it true that you decided
to take the case for money?
A lawyer is now defending the suspect...
that confessed to the crime
of his former client.
He is claiming the suspect's innocence.
What are your thoughts on this case?
According to the Attorneys' Code of Ethics,
when a conflict of interest
arises between two clients,
one must only choose one.
Ethically, it's frowned upon.
It's not commonly practiced
in the legal field.
From what I think...
What is he going to do?
I know. He's being heavily criticized.
The Ethics Committee should
discuss this matter.
Let's stop watching it since
it'll only upset you.
When things were rough for me,
he gave me strength by my side.
Mr. Kwon.
Don't mind what the people say.
I believe that you'll win this case.
♫ I locked the door ♫
♫ And stayed in bed all day ♫
♫ It'll get better if I sleep ♫
(Say a wish.)
♫ I wish everything would just stop ♫
(Information on Park Su Myeong)
(Case study on punishment related
to overlooking a murder)
Mr. Kwon, how have you been?
I finally thought of a wish.
My wish is for you to
stay steady as a rock.
Just like you have been
so far, I believe that...
you'll serve justice.
♫ Because of my damn pride ♫
♫ Only deep scars remain ♫
♫ Sorry, I don't know why ♫
♫ I only knew myself back then ♫
♫ In the photographs in my hands ♫
♫ You're just smiling ♫
♫ But you're never coming back ♫
♫ You're never coming back ♫
♫ I can't fall asleep, oh no ♫
♫ I don't look forward to
a tomorrow without you ♫
♫ Like a lost child ♫
♫ Even if I cry, you won't ever hear it ♫
♫ Baby, now I talk to myself sometimes ♫
♫ As if you're next to me ♫
♫ It's the same today ♫
♫ Like a fool, I'm circling the same spot ♫
♫ It's hard to endure without tears ♫
♫ I don't wanna never give up on you ♫
♫ Because of my damn pride ♫
♫ Only deep scars remain ♫
♫ Sorry, I don't know why ♫
♫ I only knew myself back then ♫
(From Oh Jin Sim)
♫ You're just smiling ♫
♫ But you're never coming back ♫
♫ You're never coming back ♫
♫ I can't fall asleep, oh no ♫
♫ I don't look forward to
a tomorrow without you ♫
(Touch Your Heart)
I could've ruined someone's life.
I must set it straight.
- It's my letter of resignation.
- Do whatever you want!
I don't need someone
as irresponsible as you either.
Why are you arguing
like a bunch of school kids?
Are you heading to work?
I'll come to see you whenever I miss you.
Would you like to have dinner with me?
Why are you doing this?
Think of it as saving someone.
Who else? It's Mr. Kwon,
the nation's most-hated man.
My wish is for you
to stay steady as a rock.
I believe that you'll serve justice.