(Touch Your Heart)
I'm more scared about losing you than losing an opportunity...
in this industry because of a scandal.
So...
let's start over again.
Are you still not going to hold onto me?
If you let go now,
we'll never get to see each other again.
Ms. Oh Jin Sim.
I love you.
(Episode 15)
We're here already.
Why is my place so nearby?
I don't want to go home today.
I want to be with you.
To be honest, I feel the same way.
Can I go home after I see you fall asleep?
It takes quite a while for me to fall asleep.
That's better.
That means I'll get to see you for a long time.
My insomnia never really bothered me.
But after we broke up, my insomnia started...
giving me a hard time.
I had to stay up all night thinking about you.
When was the hardest for you?
Never mind. You were probably fine because you were so busy.
Who says I didn't have a hard time?
I had a hard time every night and every morning.
I had a hard time working and going to trials.
Every minute of the day was difficult for me.
Really?
Did you really have that much of a hard time?
Are you that happy to hear that I had a hard time?
Of course. That shows how much you really liked me.
Oddly enough, I feel very relieved now.
Let's never break up again.
Let's promise each other...
that we'll never let go of each other's hands.
Okay, I promise.
I won't ever let go.
And I'll protect you.
The reason I left you was...
because I didn't want to bother you...
since it was such an important time in your career.
And I still feel the same way.
So for the sake of protecting you,
we should do a better job in keeping our relationship a secret.
We should do a better job in keeping our relationship a secret?
Yes, we can't have anyone take photos of us like last time.
So we should refrain from meeting outside.
We should meet up in confined areas...
such as your place or mine from now on.
Confined areas?
Yes.
A secret and quiet place where there's no one else...
but the two of us.
Is it okay...
if I spend the night here?
I won't ever cross this line.
I promised you earlier that I'll protect you.
Oh, okay.
Thank you so much for protecting me.
- Good morning, Mr. Kwon. - Good morning.
It must've been uncomfortable for you to sleep in that.
It's okay.
What's your schedule for today?
I'm not that busy today.
My shoot starts at 1pm,
and it'll probably end at about 7pm.
Then we can have dinner together.
- I'll call as soon as I'm done. - Okay.
Who's here so early in the morning?
It's my manager. What are we going to do?
- Yun Seo. - He'll be suspicious of us...
if he sees us together at this hour.
- Let's pretend like we're not here. - Yun Seo.
No, we can't do that. He knows the passcode.
If I don't answer, he'll probably just come in.
- What should I do? - Why does he know your passcode?
I get that he's your manager, but he should...
- respect your privacy. - I'm going in.
What...
You should hide here for now.
What? Ms. Oh.
My gosh.
Hey, you're up.
I thought you were sleeping because you didn't open the door.
Oh, well...
I was using the blender.
That's why I didn't hear you ring the bell.
What brings you here so early in the morning?
Doesn't the shoot start at 1pm?
I got a call saying they changed the time.
Your shoot starts at 11am, so we need to get going.
I see. Okay.
I'll get ready really quickly and meet you downstairs.
You can wait for me in the car.
- I'll be right there. - Okay, don't take too long.
Okay.
Oh, I almost forgot. Yun Seo, let me use your bathroom.
Hyuk Joon!
- What? - I'm sorry.
Can you not go to the bathroom?
- Why not? - What?
- Well, the thing is... - Yun Seo.
I'm really sorry, but my bladder is about to burst.
- Please let me in. - No, wait.
- No, I really need to go. - Hyuk Joon!
I really need to go.
My gosh.
Yun Seo, how long are you going to stand there?
- Oh, right. I'm... I'm sorry. - Yes, you should be.
You should feel sorry for my bladder. Please leave.
- Go. - Okay.
Hurry.
Got you!
Mr. Kwon?
Yes, this is he. An investigation by the prosecution?
Gosh.
You see...
My gosh. It wasn't me!
Goodness...
My gosh,
Mr. Kwon.
It's all right. I was going to shower anyway.
(Singil 3-dong Morning Soccer Club)
Oh, dear.
I'm glad that he had something like this in his car.
I'll wash this and get it back to you.
So what's going on?
Why are you here this morning?
No way. Hold on.
Did you sleep here?
- No! - Yes.
No and yes. Yes and no!
That says it all. Mr. Kwon,
it's true that I approve of you two dating,
but this is completely inappropriate.
Hyuk Joon!
Mr. Kwon, you should get going.
You barely have time to go home and get changed.
Come on.
Mr. Kwon, I'm not finished, you know.
Does she not know how messed up this is?
Here.
- Bye. - I'll get going then.
Hyuk Joon, how could you say that to him...
when he got hosed down because of you?
Yun Seo.
He may have gotten hosed down, but I was struck by a lightning.
How can you bring him home when you've barely been dating?
What should I do then? Be with him on the streets...
and get photographed?
If you at least get photographed outside,
I can make up a cover story.
If he's photographed on his way out of here,
that's a done deal.
We're aware of that, so we take necessary precautions.
You approved our relationship, so just let us be.
Pretend you didn't see anything.
That's what I want to do,
but I'm worried that you'd get caught.
I approved, but my brain still doesn't allow it.
It's driving me insane too.
What are you looking at?
What's this? I was wondering where you were.
Were you out playing soccer?
Hold on. Singil 3-dong Morning Soccer Club?
Why go that far to play soccer?
They must be good.
Let me join you next time.
You'll never be able to join me there.
What? Why not?
Are they picky with the members they accept?
I'm quite good, you know.
Just know that it's not a place for you.
Seriously?
Just how good is he at soccer to shut me out?
Who knew that I'd end up doing this?
You finish around 7pm,
but I'm texting in advance because I miss you.
Are you done filming?
I think it'll be over soon. How about some dinner?
That'd be great.
Then I'll see you at my place.
Will I be hosed down again?
Of course not. I'm changing my lock combination...
as soon as I get home today.
Then I'll bring you sushi, your favorite.
Yes, I'm just about to...
I'm sorry, but I'll have to stay for some additional scenes.
I'm afraid I'll have to take a rain check.
I see. Well, it can't be helped.
Please don't tell me you already bought the sushi.
No, not yet.
Please don't worry about me and focus on your work.
Sure. I'll see you.
I'm home.
Wait. Why are you eating two portions alone?
One must be for me.
Not exactly.
Then who is it for?
I bought them both for me.
Boy, you're selfish.
You joined a good soccer club all by yourself...
and now you're eating two plates of the same sushi.
- You've changed. You know that? - That's not it.
Starting now,
I'll teach you the virtue of sharing.
Watch and learn. This is how a society works.
See?
Eat up then.
What do you mean you have something to say?
It's nothing big. The actors signed with my agency...
are getting more jobs overseas...
which means a variety of global contracts.
I was thinking about hiring a law firm...
as our legal adviser.
So you want our firm on retainer.
I'm not sure. I get what you're saying,
- but it might not be up to you. - What?
I'm sure you're aware of the hottest case in Korea.
It's the Im Yun Hee Case.
Who solved it?
Always Law Firm did.
If you're going to say something, at least say the truth.
It was Attorney Kwon's doing, not your firm's.
He may be a jerk, but he's talented.
Anyway,
because of it, my law firm has been in demand.
The same goes for me as well since I'm its owner and leader.
TV shows and magazines...
are all dying to get an interview with me.
I'm being contacted left and right.
Does that mean you won't take us on as a client?
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm just saying that we might not always be available.
That's too bad. Not available, you say?
If you take us on as a client, you'll enjoy a year-end party...
with the actors and artists.
Also, in the summer at Waikiki Beach,
we'll go camping and play beach volleyball.
Toss!
My ball!
You could enjoy it too, so I'm sad to hear that.
You should get going then.
Jun Seok, my little brother Jun Seok.
Don't you know a joke when you hear one?
Did you think I'd ignore my brother's request?
How do you get by in life being this naive?
Bring me the contract, and I'll sign it instantly.
My big brother!
Gosh.
Also, the team working on Yun Seo's TV series...
is looking for an advisory counsel.
An advisory counsel?
You know, an expert...
who advises the staff and writers on legal jargon.
They're looking for someone who Yun Seo knows well.
I can be that expert. There's me.
- You're an attorney too, right? - Of course I am.
It's too bad though.
You said you're not available.
Can you ask someone else to do it?
My cute little brother, just let me do it.
No, you make me nervous.
You'll probably annoy the actors on set...
and make animated photos.
Have someone else do it.
I doubt anyone would be willing to do it.
An advisory counsel?
Yes, I'm sure no one would like to do it.
It's exhausting, it's a hassle, and it'll waste your time.
I doubt anyone would want to do it.
No, I don't.
I have enough cases on my plate right now,
and I don't want entertainment agencies...
handing out there business cards trying to scout me.
I'll pass too.
Okay, then I'll take the job.
I bet you're delighted.
You'll see Ms. Oh often when you're on set.
Well, I guess that's highly possible.
I heard they need an advisory counsel starting today,
so I'll be the one to do it.
No.
I'll do it.
Am I hearing things right now?
Mr. Kwon, can you say that one more time?
I said, "I will do it." The advisory counsel.
Mr. Kwon, don't you hate those kinds of things?
Yes, well...
It sounds like a good idea to gain more experience.
Mr. Kwon, if someone does something that he usually never does, he dies.
So don't mind stuff like this as per usual,
and keep up the fight for justice.
No. I will be the advisory counsel.
What's your problem? You're so annoying.
Is it because of the interview from the Park Su Myeong Case...
a few days ago? Are you enjoying all the attention or what?
Why are you trying to show off?
I'm not showing off.
Why did you ask for volunteers in the first place then?
Forget it. Let's vote then.
Vote?
Yes. If he makes a mistake at the filming site,
he'll ruin the reputation of our law firm.
So let's vote on who will represent Always Law Firm.
Let's see who is more fit for this position.
Just like democratic citizens, let's decide by voting on it.
(Yeon Joon Gyu, 1 vote Kwon Jung Rok, 4 votes)
I'll get going then.
Ms. Oh Jin Sim. I have good news.
We have a chance to finally meet.
I will visit your filming site...
as an advisory counsel...
No, I'll surprise her.
(Filming Team)
Is it because I didn't see Mr. Kwon last night?
I have no energy, and no appetite either.
I see.
I see you've left two radishes because you have no appetite.
It's so squeaky clean people might think you licked everything off.
I said I don't have an appetite. I didn't say I don't like rice.
Yun Seo, I'm happy that you eat so well.
I'm very happy, but you have to watch your figure.
What if your face is all swollen up on TV?
By the way, you know you have a photo shoot next week, right?
Yes, I know. Don't worry. I have a conscience too, you know.
I heard this is helpful, so I'm drinking it constantly.
Good. Gosh, you look like you're shooting a commercial right now.
Drink some more.
- Mr. Gong, can we talk? - Sure.
I miss Mr. Kwon.
I never expected Mr. Kwon doing something like that.
Tell me about it.
It's unbelievable, like seeing a mirage in a desert.
Hey, you're all gathered here. Is it tea time?
Oh, boy. That looks tasty.
Oh, right. From now on, during our meetings,
I wish someone will take some meeting minutes.
The typing sound from the laptop is too loud,
so I think someone should handwrite some meeting minutes.
Okay. I'll do it.
Oh, Hae Yeong? Do you have good handwriting?
Yes.
But I think it should be someone who has some neat handwriting.
To find out, why don't we all write down some letters?
Write, "Minutes of Meeting" on this.
"Minutes of Meeting".
We should make sure, just in case.
(Minutes of Meeting)
I found it. It's this.
This letter looks the same.
Mr. Choi, Ms. Dan, Hae Yeong, and Ms. Yang.
I'm very disappointed in you. I never expected this.
I was always so nice to you, yet you betrayed me and chose Mr. Kwon?
What are you talking about?
I chose you.
You received one vote, right? That was me.
Liar.
Look at this.
I compared your handwritings when you wrote Kwon Jung Rok's name...
to the handwritings that you wrote just now.
This handwriting is the only one that I don't have.
This is the only one.
Ms. Yang, it seems like you thought a lot about this.
You said it was an anonymous vote. How could you do this?
I didn't say anything. I was simply curious.
Don't worry, I won't discriminate anyone over something like this.
But why is there so much dust suddenly in this place?
We should all gather this weekend...
and clean this place up thoroughly.
Except for you, Mr. Lee.
I'll give you a movie ticket, so go watch a movie.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
The advisory counsel for our drama has arrived.
Mr. Kwon, can you go over this script with me?
(Waiting Room, Oh Yun Seo)
Why on earth are you here?
How did you come?
You're the advisory counsel for our drama?
It wasn't easy to be elected as an advisory counsel.
- Elected? - Yes.
Mr. Yeon, who enjoys being exposed to the public, outright revealed...
his ambition that he wanted to be your advisory counsel.
However, out of my determination to see you,
and despite Mr. Yeon's persuasion and criticism,
we eventually decided to vote on it democratically.
And I won by an overwhelming score of 4 to 1. I have been...
proudly elected as the advisory counsel of your drama!
If I think about it now, it was a really thrilling and close fight.
It does indeed sound thrilling.
Yes. Once I came here and saw your face,
I realized it was a great choice to participate in the vote.
But do you feel uncomfortable or pressured...
- because of my sudden visit? - No way.
Do you know how happy I feel right now?
I missed you so much too.
Yun Seo, are you in here?
I'm sorry. No.
How have you been? No.
- Yun Seo. Oh Yun Seo! - What?
We're starting the shoot. You have to come out now.
Okay, I'm on my way.
- Mr. Kwon, you should come too. - Okay.
What's wrong?
Mr. Kwon, I understand how you feel,
but coming here as an advisory counsel seems a bit...
That's my free will.
Interfering with our relationship all the time like this...
is an invasion of one's freedom to pursue happiness...
and freedom of action, which is guaranteed by the constitution.
- Then... - Okay.
Yun Seo, don't go. Don't go with him. Wait for me.
Witness, you said you were at home at the day of the incident.
Is that correct?
Your Honor.
Wait, I have a question.
Mr. Kwon?
When I say, "Your Honor",
what is the proper hand gesture?
Oh, that.
Okay. Thanks.
Instead of pointing at the judge directly,
you should stand straight or gather your hands together.
This looks good.
Instead of this?
Using both hands is too weird.
You should stand straight...
Your Honor.
Mr. Kwon, have some coffee.
Thank you.
Excuse me, Mr. Kwon Jung Rok?
This part in the script is bothering me. Is this...
legally a correct expression?
(Kwon Jung Rok)
Yes. It's a very precise expression with no errors at all.
Yes.
Of course there aren't.
I can see this script has no errors at all.
So can we please move on to the next scene?
Come here. Follow me.
Ms. Dan.
Although our contract dating is over, we're still colleagues.
Why don't you ever talk to me and keep ignoring me?
Did I?
If I did, I'm sorry.
Wait.
Are things going well with the delivery guy you fell for...
- and chased after? - No.
I only did that out of habit because I was drunk.
But it was nothing sincere.
Anyway, I wasn't supposed to flirt with anyone else,
but I failed to stick to it until our contract ended...
and broke the contract by doing so.
I'm sorry about that.
You should be sorry.
I'm not quite sure about that.
It's not like you did everything right either.
You told me that your heart feels numb when you're with me.
There was no point in continuing our dating contract...
with someone who had no feelings for me.
I was practically making a fool out of myself.
Well, then. I'll be off now.
What was that? She used to look at me...
with hearts in her eyes.
But now, she's so cold toward me.
How can someone change so drastically?
Gosh, my heart. It hurts.
Was I too mean?
No, there's no point in apologizing to a guy...
who has no feelings for me.
Let's get over him.
For some reason,
it feels as if my heart is empty.
Why do I feel this way?
(Short-term Dating Contract)
Whatever the case, our contract has come to end.
So let's forget about her now.
Goodbye.
It's time to say goodbye...
to this chapter in my life...
that was full of clumsiness and innocence.
Gosh, that's hot! That's so hot!
Goodness, that's so hot!
[VIU Ver] tvN E15 'Touch Your Heart'
"Jung Rok Gets Jealous"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Do you need anything?
No, I'm just here for no reason.
Working as an advisory counsel must've worn you out...
seeing that you're starting the day with a cup of coffee.
I can imagine why. You're already in charge of so many cases.
But you're even working as an advisory counsel now.
So it's only natural that you're tired.
It seems like you really regret having taken the job.
Okay, I'll sacrifice myself on your behalf.
Although it may be bothersome and tiring,
I'll take your place and become Yun Seo's advisory counsel.
That's okay.
Really? I see.
I guess it's not that bad.
By the way,
how was the filming location? Did you have fun?
How does Yun Seo get along with the male lead?
I didn't get to see him yesterday. But why do you ask?
I got really curious yesterday, so I watched a few...
behind-the-scenes clips of the drama.
And I noticed that they have great chemistry together.
A few people even left comments...
saying it looks like they're dating each other.
- What? - You know I'm an expert at this.
I personally think...
there's something going on between the two.
I think the two might start dating because of this drama.
My gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- Aren't you going to leave? - This is really uncomfortable.
(Lastly, in the viewpoint of the market environment...)
(Moon Ji Hoo)
(Kiss master)
"Kiss master"?
Ms. Dan, here's your schedule for next week.
- Okay, I'll take a look. - Okay.
Ms. Dan, do you know how to play the ukulele?
I started playing it as a hobby.
Someone even taught me how to play it for a while.
I've always wanted to learn how to play it. If you don't mind,
can I take a closer look at it?
Sure, go ahead.
I learned the basic techniques by watching online videos.
Is this how you do it?
You need to use...
your second finger like this.
- Like this? - Your stance...
I'll show you.
You need to hold it like you're holding a baby.
Would you like to try playing the C chord?
- Is it this one? - You're good.
I gave that ukulele to her.
How could she use our ukulele that holds our precious memory...
to play harmony with another guy?
- I really don't understand... - I noticed...
- She's right there. - that there's a concert.
But I felt a little awkward to go there alone.
Why are they together?
It's nice that we're getting to go there together.
It's not a bad deal for me since I get to watch a concert.
Ms. Dan, we need to talk.
I have to go somewhere with Jong Hwa.
We agreed to go to a ukulele concert.
No, you can't go there.
I'm sorry, but can you go to that concert by yourself?
There's something very important I need to say...
to Ms. Dan right now.
What's the important thing that you need to tell me?
Ms. Dan.
I want you to return the ukulele I gave you.
What? Why...
Why are you taking back what you already gave me?
You're the one who took back what you gave me.
What do you mean?
You gave me your heart, but you took it away.
If you were going to be like this, why were you so nice to me?
On my birthday,
why did you get your hair pulled on my behalf?
Why did you debone the roasted mackerel for me?
And why did you get me vitamins?
Why did you do all that?
Why are you suddenly being like this?
You're the one who told me that your heart feels numb...
when you're with me.
Yes.
I thought it was going to stay that way.
But...
What's this?
It's beating so fast.
Foolishly enough,
my heart started beating after you left me.
And...
when I saw you smile with another man,
my heart even started hurting.
My heart...
had to feel all sorts of things because of you.
- So... - Yes?
Let's start dating each other.
I'm not talking about a contract. Let's become a real couple.
I'll give you three seconds to give me an answer.
Three.
Two.
One.
0.5.
0.25.
0.125.
Okay, let's date. I would love that.
- Those are the good times. - They must be dating.
Those are the good times.
Is she still filming?
- Mr. Kwon. - Ms. Oh Jin Sim!
What brings you here?
- Get in. - Sure.
You said you were on set.
Where's your manager?
Today's filming was canceled,
and I sent Hyuk Joon home.
I thought about calling ahead,
but I wanted to surprise you for once.
So surprise!
I'm glad you did.
It sure is nice to see you this way.
Right? Isn't it great?
I still don't know how we managed to stay apart.
Tell me about it.
I'm glad that today's filming was canceled.
You were probably exhausted.
It's all right. I'm hardly tired.
Still.
From what I experienced from being on set yesterday,
it takes a lot of stamina to be an actor.
So don't eat less to keep the weight off...
and stay healthy by eating what your body needs.
You should be the one watching out for your health.
You work the most out of all the attorneys at your firm.
You know what? Let's enjoy a healthy dessert then.
It's red ginseng.
Go ahead.
Sure.
You have something to use that energy on.
Sorry?
Can you help me with my lines?
- Your lines? - Yes.
It's easier when I have someone to practice the scene with.
I'd like to work on the scenes for tomorrow.
Will you help me?
Sure.
Who knew I'd be doing something like this?
Where's the script?
Here it is.
(The two reunite with a kiss outside the court.)
That's right.
There's a kiss scene in the fourth episode.
My gosh, Jung Do.
Shouldn't you be in Asrael?
I came so that I wouldn't regret.
I knew I'd regret it all my life if I just let you go.
It says here that Jung Do pulls Joo Ha in for a kiss.
We can just skip that part.
Why should we?
I agreed to help you practice, so I'll stay in character.
Oh, dear. My gosh.
Maybe we shouldn't do it.
No, I need to practice this.
It's just practice.
Mr. Kwon, here's the script.
This is fascinating.
So this is what a script looks like.
What on earth is this?
Sorry?
Mr. Kwon, here's the script.
This is fascinating.
So this is what a script looks like.
What on earth is this?
Sorry?
Look here.
"Your Honor, the defendant..."
"is in deep remorse regarding his actions."
And?
Isn't this supposed to be a criminal case?
"The accused" is for criminal cases...
while "the defendant" is for civil cases.
So the attorney should've referred to him as the accused.
I see, but I'm not the one who writes the script.
This is basic research for crime series.
Mr. Kwon, are you angry?
Well, I'll make sure to let...
the write know.
Right, please do so.
Let's try this scene then.
Which scene?
Scene number 27. The trial.
- The trial scene? - Yes.
Why not stand in the center and do it properly.
- What? You want me to stand? - Yes, go ahead.
- I'll see how you do. - Right.
The plaintiff hired Bujin Constructions...
and completed the demolition.
Ms. Oh Jin Sim.
The plaintiff normally sits...
on your left.
This way?
The plaintiff hired Bujin Constructions...
and completed the demolition.
However, you failed to supply the funds and...
"Therefore, you failed to make the payments."
Therefore, you failed to make the payments.
- Ms. Oh Jin Sim. - Yes?
I'm afraid that tone isn't appropriate.
In court, attorneys and prosecutors rarely raise their voices.
It's best to end your argument in a charismatic but refrained tone.
"The plaintiff hired Bujin Constructions..."
"and completed the demolition."
"However, you failed to supply the funds."
"Therefore, you failed to make the payments."
- Like that. - I get it.
- Let me try that again. - Sure.
The plaintiff hired "Mujin" Constructions...
Ms. Oh Jin Sim. It's Bujin, not Mujin.
Yes, of course. Mujin... No, Bujin Constructions.
Can I get a glass of water?
- Yes, of course. - Okay.
"The plaintiff hired Bujin Constructions..."
I thought it'd be romantic,
but he's working me harder than the staff on set.
I'm glad I can be of help to you this way.
Sure.
"Outside the court."
"After Joo Ha walks out, she's shocked at what she sees."
"Jung Do is there in his military uniform."
Okay, got it.
"Jung Do pulls Joo Ha in for..."
"a kiss?"
"The two reunite with a kiss outside the court."
(Kiss master)
A kiss master?
I have an announcement to make. I booked us a table...
at the nearby Korean beef restaurant for dinner.
That's a good choice.
The raw beef there is amazing.
The chef is known as the Beef Master.
As if.
There's no such thing as a kiss master.
Did I say that he kissed well?
It's nothing. May I be excused?
Aren't you finishing your meal?
I have business to attend in court.
A kiss master?
A ski master?
I'm sure he said, "kiss".
Maybe Mr. Kwon wants to find love.
I get it. Since it's spring,
he must be getting all sorts of feels.
Even he'd like some romance in his life too.
Come to think of it, we're all single.
Shouldn't someone in this group be in a relationship?
If you don't have time to find someone outside,
you should look for someone in here.
There are so many secret couples in other companies.
It's like our firm is the only place with nothing going on.
Don't CEOs usually dislike office romances?
Since it interferes with their work?
I'm not such an old-fashioned CEO.
Furthermore, if there is a couple...
within our law firm,
I will buy each of them a spring outfit they can wear on their date.
So, the moment you become a couple,
I hope you hold your hands up and report to me.
- What are you two doing? - You said to report to you.
Me and Ms. Dan are a couple.
Yes. We're a new couple that's been going out since yesterday.
Seriously. What do you think you're doing?
How desperate were you for some new clothes? Does that make sense?
My goodness. This is so silly.
Ms. Dan, Mr. Choi, are you two really a couple?
It feels like someone smacked me on the back of my head.
If that's the filming team, she must be somewhere over there.
Yun Seo,
how do you want to do this part?
If you have any suggestions, I'll follow it.
- Really? Okay. - Yes.
Mr. Kwon.
Hi.
What brings you here?
I had some business at court.
I heard you're shooting and came in case you need any help.
I'm so glad I'm shooting in front of the court.
We got to bump into each other like this.
- Yes. - Yun Seo, it's time to shoot.
What?
I have to go, Mr. Kwon.
Okay.
Jung Do.
How did you come here?
Shouldn't you be in Israel? Why are you here?
I came in order to leave no regrets.
In order not to regret letting you go for the rest of my life.
Cut. What was that?
Was that a car horn?
Make sure there aren't any unnecessary sounds.
All right, stand by. Let's try it again.
Hold on... Wait a minute.
May I say something as the advisory counsel?
Yes, of course.
I know it's a drama, but a man and woman kissing...
in front of the court like this seems so unrealistic.
On top of that, how could an attorney and a judicial officer...
kiss in front of a sacred court?
From my perspective, as a man who works in this industry,
I'm afraid this scene is a bit inappropriate.
This is a very conservative place.
Still, if there needs to be some sort of emotional exchange,
I believe a hug will be appropriate.
- A hug? - No, forget that.
Not even a hug.
A handshake.
A handshake sounds perfect.
Mr. Kwon, let's go get some coffee.
I don't want coffee.
No, you and I should get some coffee.
You told me not to interfere, mentioning something about...
one's right to pursue happiness.
What do you think you're doing right now?
I just did my job as an advisory counsel.
If you came as an advisory counsel, you should give advice.
Why are you being jealous?
- It's not jealousy. - It is jealousy.
Look at that. Mr. Kwon, look over there.
You said judicial officers are conservative or something.
But look at how they're holding hands. Conservative my foot.
Oh, well... That's ridiculous.
This industry is very conservative. There's no way...
Kim Se Won?
Jung Rok.
Jung Rok?
You even know them?
I don't.
Kim Se Won. Jung Rok.
I have my right to take the Fifth.
Goodness, you're just full of jealousy.
Can you hold hands like that in court in those robes?
Who cares? It's not like we're not working because we're dating.
I just got tired of dating secretly all the time.
I just decided to open about it without worrying about others.
Me too. I usually would never have imagined doing this,
but Se Won was right.
It was hard at first, but once I got used to it, it's nothing.
Jung Rok, what should I do?
I think I'm taking after Se Won.
Fine, whatever.
- Cheers to Always Law Firm! - Cheers!
So, how did you two start to get attracted to each other?
I know. You used to be enemies before.
I'm not saying this because he's my boyfriend.
But Mr. Choi was a man born to be loved.
He's handsome, competent, gentle, and on top of that,
he's a great son. He's really...
the best guy ever.
That goes for you too.
At times, you're cute, and at times, you're chic.
You're such an unpredictable woman.
I see. Although I don't...
agree with what you said, a promise is a promise.
You can each go buy some spring outfits.
Thank you, Mr. Yeon.
Why don't we buy a couple outfit?
Something that will look perfect for your cute style.
It's okay.
Let's get something that will...
look perfect on you, something luxurious and chic.
Let's eat.
Why do I have to use my own money and watch something like that?
Anyway, if there are any more hidden couples, tell me now.
We should all go get a group outfit while we're at it.
I'm already struggling with my loan. Another 7,000 dollars...
added to my 700,000 won't make a difference.
Hae Yeong, if it's okay with you,
would you like to go get a new spring dress with me...
I have many dresses.
Mr. Kwon.
Is something wrong?
I know.
Your face looks so grim today.
Is it because you had a crush on Ms. Dan...
and you feel heartbroken since she's going out with Mr. Choi?
Is that why you're drinking so much?
Is that true?
A crush is love too. I'll root for you.
- Goodness. - Oh, my.
Mr. Kwon, are you still at your company dinner?
I see.
I'm on my way home after today's shoot.
Call me after dinner then.
Okay.
Did he say anything in particular?
In particular? Like what?
Well, it's just...
It just seemed...
he was jealous because of your kiss scene.
I was just curious if he gave you a hard time about it.
What?
That's the fate of the boyfriend of a celebrity.
He has to pretend he's okay watching love scenes like that,
but he feels jealous inside.
He can't proudly tell anyone that he's dating you either.
And you can't even go to places where there are a lot of people.
Yun Seo.
That's why I'm so worried...
about the two of you dating.
You can't help but get exhausted...
when you're in a secret relationship.
Here you go, honey.
You too, honey.
You guys are bringing so much love to our firm.
I'm not sure about that. I'm starting to feel angry.
Those two are slowly helping me understand...
why CEOs don't want their employees to date each other.
I mean, why would the CEO...
want to pay people and see them dating at the same time?
I feel like I'll become furious if I stay here.
It seems like you're all done, so let's go now.
- Let's go. - But I don't want to go.
- Yun Seo! - Hello.
- Yun Seo. - Yun Seo.
What brings you here?
I heard you guys are having a team dinner here, so I dropped by.
I'm glad you're here. We were just getting started.
Come this way.
Sit here.
Jong Hwa, where's your seat?
- Over there, sir. - Oh, I see. Okay.
Yun Seo, we have big news.
Apparently, Ms. Dan and Mr. Choi are a couple now.
- Really? - Yes.
I was actually going to tell you tomorrow.
Congratulations.
Jung Rok, aren't you glad to see Yun Seo?
- Why aren't you saying anything? - Pardon?
Jung Rok, what's with you today? Why do you look so down?
Is it because it's spring?
It must be because you feel lonely.
- That must be it. - That's nonsense.
Don't lie to me.
You know what? We should set him up on a blind date.
That's not necessary.
Stop refusing the offer. You're obviously single right now.
You should do as I say and go on a blind date.
Ms. Kim, Ms. Dan, do you guys know anyone?
- Do you know any single women? - Anyone?
Wait.
Mr. Kwon actually has...
a girlfriend.
- What do you mean? - Are... Are you serious?
Mr. Kwon has a girlfriend?
Yes, well...
Well, it's...
It's me.
- You are so funny. - Come on.
- Seriously. - That was great acting.
She didn't even blink when she made that joke.
"It's me." Gosh, I don't think I can do it.
I'm serious.
I was quite hesitant to tell you at first.
But I really like and trust everyone here.
So I want to be honest with you.
Mr. Kwon and I...
are really dating.
I like Mr. Kwon...
very much.
Oh, I see.
Sir, isn't that hot?
Gosh, that's hot!
Water...
I'm crying because it's hot.
- Are you sure? - Yes, it's because it's hot.
Are you sure it's not because you're heartbroken?
No, it's because my hand's burning.
My hand is burning. That's why I'm crying. My gosh.
I sincerely congratulate you. My gosh, that was hot.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Gosh, I'm so happy.
Goodness, I need to go to the bathroom.
You guys should congratulate them. My goodness, seriously.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Yun Seo.
I never knew that so many people...
were dating in our firm.
I know, right?
I really didn't expect Mr. Kwon and Yun Seo to date each other.
They seem really different.
But at the same time, they look really good together.
I think they make a great couple.
My goodness, they're forsythia flowers.
You're right.
Forsythia flowers are my favorite.
By any chance, do you know the meaning of forsythia flowers?
No, what is it?
"My love is deeper than yours."
I see.
Hey, Ms. Yang.
If you don't mind, would you like to eat with me someday?
Sure, let's do that.
Why are we drinking all of a sudden?
Because I want to celebrate this day.
Today was the first time we ever told anyone...
about our relationship.
But are you really okay?
I'm worried that you're doing this for me.
Mr. Kwon, do you know...
what you say to me the most?
"Are you okay?"
"Are you really okay?"
You always ask me that.
But today, this is what suddenly came to my mind.
"He always asks me if I'm okay."
"But I wonder if he's okay."
"He's always so worried about me."
"And I'm worried he might not be taking care of himself."
If you're not okay, I'm not okay either.
Because how you feel...
directly affects how I feel.
And there's one more.
I had to meet you today because I wanted to tell you this.
What is it?
About that kissing scene earlier... We didn't actually kiss.
Okay, let's not talk about that anymore.
Don't try to avoid the subject and listen to me.
That was just acting.
We didn't actually kiss.
I'll show you. We held each other like this.
And then, we did this.
They shot us from an angle...
so that it would seem like we're really kissing.
Anyway, I just didn't want you to misunderstand.
Actors and actresses are good at doing stuff like that.
They know how to make fake stuff look real.
Then what if you really want to kiss someone?
Is this how you do it?
Is it okay...
if I cross the line today?
(Touch Your Heart)
- Ta-da. - Why did she choose Jung Rok...
instead of me?
You're so handsome.
You're so unnecessarily good-looking.
How could you be so sly?
You're seriously unbelievable.
I get that you fall in love very easily,
but how could you do that in front of your boyfriend?
You didn't forget about our dinner appointment tomorrow, right?
- Can I really go to your house? - Sure.
Your one-day secretary is waiting for you in your office.
Ms. Oh.
Your flight leaves tomorrow morning.
- What? - Now that you're dating an actress,
- you're starting to change. - Hello.
You're like a male lead in a romantic comedy.
I'll always be waiting for you here.
That's what I wanted to say.