[English subtitles are available]
[ACE TROOPS]
[Episode 31]
A team of number 5 defense line debugging contingent
which master station sent to Gui'er Ridge
was out of touch.
There were injuries during the rescue.
A soldier died due to stepping on a landmine,
and another one lost his leg from the explosion.
What?
Gui'er Ridge?
Yes.
Why exclude Gui'er Ridge?
It is the key experimental area of this place.
This is also my question.
Because it is a mine field,
it is dangerous to carry out.
Should we detour because it is dangerous?
If we carry out the experiment at Gui'er Ridge,
safety is not guaranteed.
[Gui'er Ridge]
[Tomographic map of Gui'er Ridge area]
How is the situation?
Debugging team has
lost touch
in the valley between Lidong and Xiangsi Village.
This area is one of the key mine field
during the Border War Era.
[Lidong Xiangsi Village]
The demining group from Military Command has
scanned this area.
But this area is complicated due to heavy rain
and loose soil here.
There are also many forgotten sunken mines.
The Military Command has requested the group army
to send the sappers to
assist the rescue to this area.
Anybody injured?
Yes.
Some people got hurt
during the rescue.
Nothing has come back from the
debugging team yet.
What about the basic situation of debugging team?
Captain Han Chunyu and
three others are first class.
They were out of touch ten hours ago.
Xia Lin.
Army commandor.
I suggest letting the sapper battalion of Division 234
go on the rescue mission.
[Tomographic map of Gui'er Ridge area]
Chief.
There are more than five hundred kilometers
from the sapper battalion to Gui'er Ridge, all are mountain roads.
It will be too late.
If someone gets injured,
we will lose the best timing for rescue.
I suggest
we move Special Force Team instead.
Their external training station
is only a hundred kilometers from Gui'er Ridge.
[Tomographic map of Gui'er Ridge area]
Connect to Special Force Team.
Gao Liang.
Chunyu is in the debugging contingent which is out of touch,
get her back
safely.
After that, you can do whatever you want to me.
Have you found anything?
Nothing, what about you?
Vice captain!
These belong to Han Chunyu and the team.
Gao!
Is it there?
It is them.
Scan the mines!
Yes!
Gao.
This is insane, this is insane.
Come with me!
Yes sir!
Don't move.
All of you, don't move.
There are many hen and egg mines and interlinked mines here.
If you ignite one on the river bank, there will be a chain after it.
Don't think of yourself as a member of special troops,
and a bullet can circle you around.
Stand still.
Chief.
Stop.
We have stepped on the land mine.
Chief, don't come here!
Sister Chunyu. Sister Chunyu.
Instructor hurt her leg,
and we did some simple management.
Gao Liang.
Sister Chunyu.
I am here, I am here, it's alright.
Where am I?
The Meng River.
Is it the river at Sanling Mountain?
I still remember
that I fell off your bike into the water.
Sister Chunyu.
Sister Chunyu, hang in there.
Gao Liang.
I am so cold.
Please help me set up the fire,
I want to get warm.
Instructor would not let us walk in the front.
We were blown out of consciousness
and lost our compasses.
We don't know the direction.
Raise your leg.
Cross the river, cross the river.
Come on, let's go!
Move.
I have stood for hours,
my legs are out of control.
Sister Chunyu.
I will carry you back.
Let's go home.
Sister Chunyu, wake up!
Sister Chunyu, don't sleep!
Let's go home!
Sister Chunyu,
wake up!
Hang in there, Sister Chunyu.
Gao Liang.
Ssiter Chunyu.
Take care of Jing.
Let her have
my cornea.
Don't talk nonsense.
Tell her
that I love her.
-Hang in there. -We are almost there!
Sister Chunyu, we will be right there!
Cold, it is so cold.
Almost there, we are almost there!
So cold.
Sister Chunyu.
At this moment,
I feel the spring rains
are warm.
Sister Chunyu.
Niu,
set up a fire.
Niu.
Sister Chunyu.
Sister Chunyu, the fire is here.
I will have the fire ready for you.
-Gao. -Let's go home.
Sister Chunyu has passed away.
Set up the fire.
Sister Chunyu. Sister.
Sister Chunyu, I will carry you home.
Let's go home, Sister Chunyu, let's go.
Let's go home.
Gao.
-Gao. -Let's go home.
Sister Chunyu has passed away.
She is gone.
Sister Chunyu is gone.
I am taking her home.
Pull the captain away.
Captain!
Don't pull me!
Captain, calm down.
Captain.
Niu.
Get away from me!
Gao,
listen to me.
Niu, that's Sister Chunyu.
I know, I know that is Sister Chunyu.
Carry her home with me.
Send her back with me.
Calm down.
She is gone.
Why don't you contact us.
The telephone that we used to look up the lines was bombed up.
The cable could not get connected.
How about the wireless?
This freaking talkback has no signal
behind the Xiangsi Village.
[Central Hospital of Military Command]
[Clinic]
Where is the emergency room?
Emergency room.
Gao Liang, where is Chunyu, where is Chunyu?
Speak up!
Where did you leave Chunyu?
Speak to me, Gao Liang.
We left her at the Gui'er Ridge.
We left her there together.
What did you say?
Say it again, what did you say?
Don't shout.
Don't shout, I am begging you.
Keep it down.
Let Sister Chunyu,
let her be in peace.
Alright?
Nanzheng,
these are the candies
that instructor Han wanted to give you.
She said you did not taste them
when you were drunk the other day.
She told me
she wished
to see you in your wedding dress soon.
I'm the chief designer of Mountain Net Number One.
Because its performance is not up to par,
it led to such a bad result.
I feel guilty about her.
I am willing to accept any punishment.
I was the vice captain of the joint test team
when Mountain Net Number one got tested.
At that time, our Special Forces Two
was responsible for working with them to verify.
I'm the one who didn't insist on covering Gui'er Ridge.
I am primarily responsible
for this.
You guys don't need
to fight over responsibility.
I have to stress
what Han Chunyu stepped on is not an ordinary mine.
They got blown up twice.
This is
a rare case.
The military has set up a task force
to investigate.
You want to take primary responsibility?
I should have taken it.
Xia Lin.
Tell you the truth.
In holding you accountable.
Chief's view is
to be as light as possible.
Which chief?
Commissar.
He said you're the martyr's family.
Thank you for his kindness.
But I've thought about it.
I'll never run away from this responsibility.
Xia Lin.
You've got to calm down.
Have you considered the consequences of this?
The order to appoint you
as Colonel of Regiment 720
has been officially approved by the Military Command.
If you take the main responsibility,
this matter will definitely get failed.
You may even have to
face the risk of changing careers.
Xia Lin.
I'm watching how you grow up.
I know how much you love this job.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have
overdue served in the army for so many years,
and shamelessly stayed
in the division reconnaissance,
until you
put on this uniform.
Otherwise,
you won't fall again and again,
and each time you have thrived on pressure,
and tried hard until today.
You are right.
I really love this job.
More than love
but obsession.
Before this accident,
I had never thought of doing any other job.
But because of my fault,
Han Chunyu,
my comrade in arms,
the one I loved the most is gone.
This is not just about my personal feelings.
If something goes wrong with the army,
someone has to take responsibility.
So,
this responsibility,
I can't escape,
I have to take.
In this way,
I will feel a little better.
Not just because of Chunyu,
but because of my love.
If I run away from it,
Chunyu would look down on me
if she found out.
Chief.
I have only one request now.
Please approve it.
Brother.
I failed to save her life,
I can't forgive myself.
Just as I can't forgive myself
for not having a chance
to ask for your forgiveness.
[Honor with the glorious team Shame with the decaying team]
She's like another you.
I admit
I am totally knocked down.
♫ When you leave ♫
♫ The sun is gone ♫
♫ The wind blew away ♫
♫ The heat in my heart ♫
♫ When you fall down♫
♫ The world is gone ♫
♫ The land scattered♫
♫ With my persistent ♫
♫ Thinking about the vows ♫
♫ And the legends you left me ♫
♫ And the immortal red fire in your eyes ♫
♫ Do you remember ♫
♫ Timidity falls like a meteor ♫
♫ Trembling like the lonely waves ♫
♫ I still remember ♫
♫ The river we helped each other cross ♫
It was because of me that Sister Chunyu died.
♫ I still remember ♫
Don't say that.
♫ The song I shouted with tears ♫
You did your best.
She died in your arms.
In the last moments of her life,
she was at peace.
She was smiling
when she died?
Right?
♫ When you leave ♫
♫ The sun is gone ♫
♫ The wind blew away ♫
♫ The heat in my heart ♫
The last thing Sergeant Han left to the world
♫ When you fall down♫
was a smile.
♫ The world is gone ♫
♫ The land scattered♫
♫ With my persistent ♫
♫ Thinking about the vows ♫
We are her comrades in arms.
For her,
♫ And the legends you left me ♫
we should live with a smile.
♫ And the immortal red fire in your eyes ♫
Nanzheng.
♫ Do you remember ♫
When Sister Chunyu died,
she asked me to tell you,
♫ Timidity falls like a meteor ♫
"I am honored
♫ Do you remember ♫
to be her sergeant."
♫ Trembling like the lonely waves ♫
She said it's nice for her
♫ I still remember ♫
to have a sister like you.
♫ The river we helped each other cross ♫
♫ I still remember ♫
♫ The song I shouted with tears ♫
♫ We have been together ♫
♫ And never been apart ♫
Jing.
What do you see?
I'm Uncle Gao Liang.
Jing.
I'm Aunt Jiang.
Can't you see?
Jing.
Don't you see?
I want to wait for mom.
I won't open my eyes
until mom comes.
So you see none of us are your mother,
right?
None of you three are my mother.
She can see.
Yes.
Where is mom? When is she back?
Why isn't she here now?
Jing.
Your mother
is a soldier.
And a soldier has to carry out her missions.
She's out on a mission.
She is brave.
Before she went,
she asked me to tell you,
she loved you so much.
The place she goes,
it's dark,
there's no light.
She said
you must open your eyes,
see the world,
and see the light.
What you see
is what she sees.
Do you get it?
Why is there no light where mom goes.
Jing.
Because your mother
left you the light.
Really?
What I see, Mom can see it too?
Yes.
Jing.
Open your eyes, okay?
That's how mom wiped my face.
Jing.
Good girl.
I'm Aunt Jiang.
Mom Han told me
before she left
to be your mom temporarily
before she is back.
Is that okay?
No. I only want Mom Han.
-Reporting for duty.-Come in.
I can tell you are not in a good mood.
Can you still execute your task?
Chief,
the Military Command has sent mine sweeping teams
to clear the mines in the Gui'er Ridge again.
I think I am more  familiar with the conditions there.
So I would like to apply
to sweep the mines in the front.
Aren't you attending the contest against the First Battalion of the Red?
You mentioned before that
practice is for fighting.
Mine fields
are the closest places
to battlefields in peaceful times.
I don't want innocent people
to die
in that mine field after many years.
As soldiers,
the trainings
and contests
are all for
the peaceful lives
of people.
I'm glad that you can think like that.
But I won't permit your application.
That's not what you should do.
Chief.
Soldiers present
for people's deeds.
How can it not be my duty?
Can I only be called a member of special troops
when I fly to the sky and go under the sea with the camouflage clothing?
If the soul
of me as a member of special troops is lost,
why should I still care the shell?
Fighting is the duty of soldiers.
Under any pressure,
they should be able to control their emotions,
analyze problems,
and give a precise attack.
I will give you 10 seconds to walk out of the emotion.
Yes, sir.
The battlefield will give you none.
Your turn.
Gao Liang. You have let me down.
As you are in this mood,
I cannot send you to the mine field
nor
assign you to
execute any dangerous tasks.
Reporting for duty.
Come in.
Emergency meeting of the War Room is ready.
Inform Gu Yiye of First Battalion of the Red of Regiment 700
to attend the meeting.
Yes, sir.
Director Wang,
what happened?
You just lost
the qualification to attend a fight.
Reporting for duty.
Come in.
How much do you know about terrorist organizations?
In March, 1991,
Flight 117 from Singapore was hijacked.
In May,
Gandhi, the former prime minister of India, was murdered.
In February, 1993,
US World Trade Center exploded.
In December, 1994,
an airliner of Air France was hijacked in Northern Africa.
In March, 1995,
the Sarin Poisonous Gas Incident in the subway of Tokyo.
In April, the explosion of Oklahoma in the US.
In June,
hostage-taking in Budennovsk, Russia.
In November,
Rabin, the prime minister of Israel, was murdered.
That's enough.
What about China?
Have a seat.
Don't think terrorist organizations are far away from us.
They not only act abroad
and in the border provinces of China.
It is very possible
that they have already
reached places under our nose.
Director Wang.
Introduce the condition.
Yes, sir.
This morning,
an encrypted emergency telegram was received.
A week ago,
two armed border-crossers
had an exchange of fire with border armed police.
The armed police failed to chase them.
Two of them died and three injured.
The other party had abundant experience in fighting in jungles
and was cunning and sophisticated.
It is confirmed that they crossed border with weapons.
What kind of weapons?
According to the description of the combatants there,
they were attacked by surprise
by two Scorpions.
And two Type 81 Assault rifles were taken by them.
Can they be drug dealers?
According to the analysis of the Department of Public Security,
they don't match the features of drug crime.
There is one more condition.
Yesterday afternoon at five,
the local police found some clues.
The suspects were located and monitored in a residence successfully.
37 armed police participated in the fight.
The capture was acted at four in the morning.
And it had a gunfight again.
What was the result?
Three joined the gunfight.
It ended at seven in the morning.
One was killed and the other two escaped.
As for the armed police,
five died and six injured.
And three innocent people were killed.
According to the analysis of the corpse
and the check of combatants,
none of the three in the gunfight
were the two escaped a week ago.
According to the preliminary judgement of the police,
they are relevant
multiple illegal armed border-crossers.
They are sophisticated in military skills
and have abundant experience in fighting.
And they are well armed.
It is suspected that it is highly relevant
to terrorism.
What is their goal?
That is the point.
We do not know
their goal yet.
The local police and armed forces
have asked Commander Yang of the Provincial Military Command for help.
Commander Yang sent a report to the Military Command,
which commanded the group army,
the Special Force Team,
the local police
and armed forces
work together to capture the nefarious
criminals.
The group army commanded that
the action
should be executed
by the Special Force Team and Regiment 700 together.
Yes, sir.
The contest between Special Forces Two and First Battalion of the Red
will be delayed.
Transfer capable personnels
and form a special force detachment.
Gu Yiye will be the commander of the detachment.
Yes, sir.
Reporting for duty.
I apply Gao Liang to be
the deputy commander of Special Forces Two.
Please approve.
Denied.
Considering his mood,
it is not appropriate for Gao Liang to join the fight.
Form two detachments
and take turns to be in position.
Before the local police
and armed forces sound the all-clear,
you should be in position and get ready all the time.
Yes, sir.
Why are you looking at me?
You are having a rest too?
Being kicked out.
You are a relative of a martyr.
My condition is similar to yours.
Gao Liang.
It was me that should be sorry for Chunyu.
In the past,
I was restless,
ambitious
and longed for being a leader.
I know you
do not like me
behaving like that.
Neither did Chunyu.
If this time
I still need to take advantage of
the sacrifice of Chunyu
to get promoted,
I will look down upon myself.
[Special forces, special spirits. Special forces, special humans. ]
But you cannot think like that.
Well.
Sister Chunyu definitely doesn't want to see you be like this.
Gao Liang.
I feel bad
for Chunyu.
And in the force,
I have done many wrong things.
Alright.
Don't repent in front of me here.
We can communicate more in the future.
Communicate more.
Then there definitely will be quarrels, right?
Alright.
I'm leaving.
What do you mean?
You really drive to see me?
You came for nothing?
There was something.
But seeing you like this.
You are already taking a rest.
Never mind.
I won't bother you.
It's ok. Say it quickly.
I am almost bored to death.
If I am okay,
I would be in the position of Gu Yiye
and have no time for you.
Hurry up and say it.
OK.
I would like to go to Xiangsi Village.
The second mine sweeping action has ended.
The superior departments have agreed.
Actually, I have started the investigation
and found something.
What did you find?
I have checked
the rainfall of the Gui'er Ridge
in recent months.
There were two times of heavy rain.
But in Lidong,
there was no mountain torrents.
That is to say.
If there are no other reasons,
the possibility of Sister Chunyu
stepping on rolling mines
is about zero.
There is one more possibility.
The mine sweeping group did not clear all the mines.
I thought so, too.
So several days ago,
I went to the Military Command
and asked the captain of the Mine Sweeping Team.
He denied it completely,
saying it was impossible to have any left,
especially in Lidong.
He took people to sweep the area by himself.
And he was unhappy with me
because he thought I slandered their team's honor.
Then, there is only one possibility.
Someone planted mines on purpose.
And
according to the description of the other two soldiers,
that mine
is not like the mines being left in previous wars.
The Mine Sweeping Team had never seen it before.
I
have found some similar types
from the equipment table of foreign forces.
I have also thought about it before.
But who would plant mines
in mine fields?
What's their purpose?
This is it.
Xia Lin,
have a look.
It was not blown up by bombs
but cut off by pliers.
It's obvious.
The guy failed at first and left the mark.
He must put forth his strengths at the second time and succeeded.
That't true.
It seems that the landmine
was laid by an expert.
And his purpose is obvious.
He wants to kill
the signalman who came to check the lines.
And this.
It is 9mm.
Was it left from the past?
Before liberation, this is
the most common type of bullet.
Yeah.
FN M1900, FN M1903, and FN M1910.
All pistols were loaded with this kind of bullet.
But this one is new.
It seems that it was produced in recent years.
Besides those old pistols,
there is another type of gun that is using these bullets.
Italian M9 handgun.
Sir,
do you remember me?
I have come here once.
Sir, don't be afraid.
We are from the People's Liberation Army.
I know that.
But you can't take away my guns.
Sir,
we...
Sir!
Why is he so afraid of us?
When I came here with Nanzheng
to rescue Jing, I had met him.
He has already told us.
He is afraid that you will take away his guns.
The Gun Control Regulations were established last year nationawide.
Here
is montane ghettoize
but is not qualified for hunting.
All guns should be handed over.
Let's walk further.
Hello.
Nanzheng.
Hou Jian.
Did you go to sleep?
No, I am sorting the projects.
The thing you asked me to do,
Jing's household register for enrollment,
needs a certificate from the original place of domicile.
From the original place of domicile?
How about Civil Affairs Bureau?
I tried.
That's not enough.
Got that.
Thank you, bye.
Mom! Mom!
Jing, what's wrong?
Come on.
What happened?
Did you have nightmares?
You are sweaty.
I dreamed about mom and dad.
I heard a boom.
And they all flew into the air.
Sweetheart. Nothing happened.
This is a dream. It's not real.
Auntie will be here with you.
Nothing will happen, ok?
Auntie, I wanna go home.
I miss mom.
Jing,
your mom
has gone to a faraway place.
She wrote us a letter, right?
Did you forget?
I wanna go back to Xiangsi Village.
My dog is waiting for me at home.
How about this?
Aunt Jiang will ask Uncle Gao
to bring your dog here.
But my dog doesn't know Uncle Gao.
He will be frightened.
Auntie, I wanna go home.
I miss mom.
Here, here.
From now on,
Aunt Jiang is also your mom,
ok?
Come on. Don't cry, sweetheart.
Who's there?
Sir!
Hello, sir.
You are non-natives, right?
We came here to collect medicines.
Collect medicines?
Do you
live in the village?
No.
Here is
the observation station.
There are landslides in every rainy season.
Others can't get in once the road is stuck.
I am responsible for
prediction and early warning.
If we want to get in the Xiangsi Village,
is this the only way?
There is another path. But
the path is heading beyond the borders.
When was the last landslide?
About three months ago.
But that was not severe.
They cleared the roads in a month.
You have asked me so many questions.
Are you aimed at taking away my guns?
[Lan Municipal Public Security Bureau]
Squad leader of the ninth squad!
Soldier from Division 234, Regiment 720,
the Third Battalion, the Ninth Company, the third platoon, the ninth squad,
Lin Beihai
is here ready for your order.
Beihai!
You
disappeared after retiring from the army.
You don't wanna see us, right?
You should know my character,
holding back bad news.
Your leg...
It was amputated. I got an artificial limb.
Although I took off my military uniform,
I keep thinking about the military camp
and you guys.
After leaving the army,
I had tried two different jobs.
But once they knew my condition,
they would refuse me.
But I am competent.
Finally,
the undersecretary of Division 234,
Li Guilin, who used to be a soldier,
picked me.
He employed me
and gave me this uniform.
Come on.
Don't worry.
There's no problem at all.
My child is 8 years old now.
Hongliu's mother
is being well taken care of.
Don't worry.
Three gangsters and prisoners
dived from here.
When the speedboat approached,
they were quickly picked up.
How many people were picked up?
Three.
One escaped.
We didn't find his body.
Maybe the body was carried away along the river.
This time, our police accidentally caught
an important figure of their gang.
However, because of the difficulties we had
when we checked his identity with foreign police,
we failed to lay emphasis on the case.
And that caused the armed hijacking.
Some time ago,
the two groups of people who stole into our territory
came for this important figure?
Yes. And they also hired professional mercenaries.
Can you investigate
the identity of this person?
We just got the report.
The Interpol offers a reward of a million US dollar.
His code name is "Earl".
By now,
criminal's escape route
is still unclear.
We still don't know where
he landed and turned to the land route.
We have got a speedboat.
Hang on to it.
The enemy has strong firepowers
and high-level tactics.
Don't worry.
We will do everything in our power to support you.
I also want to know that
if the Command has thought about
that the enemy didn't turn to the land route
but escaped by water
and left the country.
The fuel oil of the speedboat
is not enough for the trip.
Also,
downstream,
we had arranged checkpoints.
After all,
it is just a speed boat.
Its firepower and protective equipments
are limited.
It cannot break
the water police's line of defense.