- ( birds chirping )
- ( bugs chittering )
Boy: Mom!
Right here.
( pots rattling )
Any luck?
How do we tell if they're poison?
Uh, there's only
one sure way I know of.
Ask Shane when he gets back?
Yeah, you've got it.
Thank you.
Dale, I'm heading out.
Sweetheart, I want you to stay
where Dale can see you, okay?
Yes, Mom.
Dale: You too.
Don't wander too far.
Stay within shouting distance.
And if you see anything, holler.
I'll come running.
( softly )
Yes, Mom.
( bugs chittering )
( leaves rustle )
( bird wings flap )
- ( branch snaps )
- ( gasps )
( wings flap )
( branches snapping )
- ( gasps )
- ( panting )
Shh shh shh
shh shh shh shh.
- ( chuckles )
- You scared the hell out of me.
I bet. That's what you get
for keeping me waiting.
I was trying to be quiet.
- Where you been?
- Amy the mushroom queen--
I had to wait
for her to get back.
- How much time we have?
- Enough.
( moans )
( both moaning )
- Come here.
- Okay.
( both grunting )
( theme music playing )
( zombies growling, moaning )
- ( radio beeping, hissing )
- ( pounding )
Man on radio:
Hey, are you alive in there?
( thuds, grunts )
- Hello? Hello?
- ( man sighs ) There you are.
You had me wondering.
Where are you? Outside?
Can you see me right now?
Man:
Yeah, I can see you.
You're surrounded by walkers.
That's the bad news.
There's good news?
- Man: No.
- Listen, whoever you are,
I don't mind telling you
I'm a little concerned in here.
Man: Oh man.
You should see it from over here.
You'd be having a major freak-out.
Got any advice for me?
Man:
Yeah, I'd say make a run for it.
That's it? "Make a run for it"?
Man: My way's not
as dumb as it sounds.
You've got eyes
on the outside here.
There's one geek still up on the tank
but the others have climbed down
and joined the feeding frenzy
where the horse went down.
- With me so far?
- So far.
Okay, the street on the other side
of the tank is less crowded.
If you move now while they're
distracted, you stand a chance.
- You got ammo?
- In that duffel bag
I dropped out there,
and guns. Can I get to it?
Man: Forget the bag, okay?
It's not an option.
- What do you have on you?
- Hang on.
( gun clicks, clatters )
Yeah. Yeah.
I've got a Beretta with one clip,
- 15 rounds.
- Make 'em count.
Jump off the right side of the tank,
keep going in that direction.
There's an alley up the street,
maybe 50 yards.
Be there.
Hey, what's your name?
Have you been listening?
You're running out of time.
Right.
( breathing heavily )
( growling )
( groans )
- Ah!
- ( zombies moaning )
( gunshots )
Whoa! Not dead!
Come on! Come on!
Back here!
( gunshot )
What are you doing?! Come on!
( growling )
Come on, get up.
( both panting )
Nice moves there,
Clint Eastwood.
You the new sheriff come riding
in to clean up the town?
- It wasn't my intention.
- Yeah, whatever. Yeehaw.
You're still a dumbass.
Rick. Thanks.
Glenn. You're welcome.
Oh no.
( growling )
The bright side:
it'll be the fall that kills us.
I'm a glass-half-full kind of guy.
Rick: Are you the one
that barricaded the alley?
Somebody did--
I guess when the city got overrun.
Whoever did it was thinking
not many geeks would get through.
Back at the tank, why'd you stick
your neck out for me?
Call it foolish, naive hope
that if I'm ever
that far up Shit Creek,
somebody might
do the same for me.
Guess I'm an even bigger
dumbass than you.
I'm back. Got a guest
plus four geeks in the alley.
( zombies growling )
- Glenn: Let's go!
- ( men grunting )
Man:
Morales, let's go!
Woman: You son of a bitch.
We ought to kill you.
- Just chill out, Andrea. Back off.
- Come on, ease up.
Andrea: Ease up?
You're kidding me, right?
We're dead because
of this stupid asshole.
Andrea, I said
back the hell off.
Or pull the trigger.
We're dead-- all of us--
because of you.
I don't understand.
Look, we came into the city
to scavenge supplies.
You know what the key
to scavenging is? Surviving!
You know the key to surviving?
Sneaking in and out, tiptoeing.
Not shooting up the streets
like it's the O.K. Corral.
Every geek for miles around
heard you popping off rounds.
You just rang the dinner bell.
Morales:
Get the picture now?
( growling )
Andrea: Oh God.
What the hell were you
doing out there anyway?
Trying to flag the helicopter.
Man: Helicopter?
Man, that's crap.
- There ain't no damn helicopter.
- Woman: You were chasing
a hallucination,
imagining things. It happens.
I saw it.
Morales: Hey, T-Dog, try that CB.
Can you contact the others?
Others? The refugee center?
Yeah, the refugee center. They've got
biscuits waiting at the oven for us.
Got no signal.
Maybe the roof.
- ( gun firing )
- Oh no. Was that Dixon?
- Woman: What is that maniac doing?
- Morales: Come on, let's go.
( gun firing )
- Hey, Dixon, are you crazy?!
- ( Dixon laughing )
- ( gun fires )
- Andrea: Oh jeez.
Huh? Hey! You ought to be
more polite to a man with a gun!
Huh? Ah!
Only common sense.
( laughing )
Man, you wasting bullets
we ain't even got, man!
And you're bringing even more of them
down on our ass! Man, just chill.
Hey, bad enough I've got
this taco-bender on my ass all day.
Now I'm gonna
take orders from you?
I don't think so, bro.
That'll be the day.
"That'll be the day"?
You got something
- you want to tell me?
- Hey, T-Dog man, just leave it.
- No.
- All right? It ain't worth it.
Now, Merle, just relax, okay?
We've got enough trouble.
- Merle: You want to know the day?
- Yeah.
I'll tell you the day, Mr. "Yo."
It's the day I take orders
- from a nigger.
- Mother--
Morales:
Hey, come on, Merle. That's enough.
- Andrea: Okay, come on. Come on.
- ( all shouting )
Andrea: Dixon! Dixon!
Morales:
Whoa, cut it out, man!
Andrea: Stop it!
Dixon, come on! Get off him!
Dixon, you're gonna hurt him.
Morales:
Merle, cut it out!
( grunts )
No no no, please. Please.
( thunder rumbling )
( T-Dog grunting )
- ( yells )
- ( grunts )
Yeah! All right!
We're gonna have ourselves
a little powwow, huh?
Talk about who's in charge.
I vote me. Anybody else?
Huh? Democracy time, y'all.
Show of hands, huh?
All in favor? Huh?
Come on. Let's see 'em.
Andrea:
Oh, come on.
All in favor?
Yeah. That's good.
Yeah, that means
I'm the boss, right?
Yeah. Anybody else?
- Hmm? Anybody?
- Rick: Yeah.
( grunting )
- Who the hell are you, man?!
- Officer Friendly.
Look here, Merle.
Things are different now.
There are no niggers anymore.
No dumb-as-shit,
inbred white-trash fools either.
Only dark meat
and white meat.
There's us and the dead.
We survive this
by pulling together,
- not apart.
- Screw you, man.
I can see you make a habit
of missing the point.
Yeah? Well, screw you twice.
Ought to be polite
to a man with a gun.
Only common sense.
You wouldn't. You're a cop.
All I am anymore
is a man looking
for his wife and son.
Anybody gets in the way
of that is gonna lose.
I'll give you a moment
to think about that.
( pats )
Got some on your nose there.
What are you gonna do?
Arrest me?
( laughs )
Hey! Dude, what are you doing?
Man, that's my stuff!
Hey! ( grunts )
If I get loose,
you'd better pray--
yeah, you hear me, you pig?!
- You hear me?!
- Yeah, your voice carries.
Merle:
You hear me, you filthy pig?!
You're not Atlanta P.D.
- Where you from?
- Up the road a ways.
( chuckles ) Well, Officer Friendly
from up the road a ways,
- welcome to the big city.
- ( thunder rumbling )
( zombies moaning )
God, it's like
Times Square down there.
- Morales: How's that signal?
- T-Dog: Like Dixon's brain-- weak.
Morales:
Keep trying.
Andrea:
Why? There's nothing they can do.
Not a damn thing.
Got some people
outside the city is all.
There's no refugee center.
That's a pipe dream.
Rick: Then she's right.
We're on our own.
It's up to us to find a way out.
Merle:
Good luck with that.
These streets ain't safe in this part
of town from what I hear.
Ain't that right, sugar tits?
Hey, honeybunch,
what say you get me
out of these cuffs,
we go off somewhere
and bump some uglies?
- Gonna die anyway.
- I'd rather.
Rug muncher.
I figured as much.
"The streets ain't safe."
Now there's an understatement.
What about under the streets?
The sewers?
Morales: Oh man.
Hey, Glenn, check the alley.
You see any manhole covers?
- ( growling )
- ( thunder rumbling )
No, must be all out on the street
where the geeks are.
Maybe not. Old building like this
built in the '20s--
big structures often had
drainage tunnels into the sewers
in case of flooding
down in the subbasements.
- Glenn: How do you know that?
- It's my job-- was.
I worked in the city zoning office.
Morales:
This is it? Are you sure?
Glenn: I really scoped this place
out the other times I was here.
It's the only thing
in the building that goes down.
But I've never gone down it.
Who'd want to, right?
Oh. Great.
- We'll be right behind you.
- No, you won't. Not you.
Why not me? Think I can't?
I wasn't--
Speak your mind.
Look, until now
I always came here by myself--
in and out, grab a few things--
no problem.
The first time I bring a group--
everything goes to hell.
No offense.
If you want me to go down
this gnarly hole, fine--
but only if we do it my way.
It's tight down there. If I run into
something and have to get out quick,
I don't want you all jammed up
behind me getting me killed.
I'll take one person--
not you either.
You've got Merle's gun
and I've seen you shoot.
I'd feel better
if you were out in that store
watching those doors,
covering our ass.
You've got the only other gun,
so you should go with him.
You be my wingman.
Jacqui stays here.
Something happens,
yell down to us,
- get us back up here in a hurry.
- Okay.
Okay, everybody knows their jobs.
( water splashing )
( rats squeaking )
- ( rat squeals )
- Dah!
( zombies banging, growling )
Sorry for the gun in your face.
People do things
when they're afraid.
Not that it was entirely unjustified.
You did get us into this.
If I get us out,
would that make up for it?
No. But it'd be a start.
Next time though,
take the safety off.
It won't shoot otherwise.
- Oh.
- Is that your gun?
It was a gift. Why?
Little red dot means
it's ready to fire.
You may have occasion to use it.
Good to know.
- T-Dog: Anybody out there?
- ( thunder rumbling )
Hello? Anybody read?
I'm hoping to hear
somebody's voice,
'cause I'm getting sick
and tired of hearing mine.
Yeah, well, that makes two of us.
Why don't you knock
that crap off?
You're giving me
a headache, boy.
Why don't you pull
your head out of your ass?
Maybe your headache
will go away.
- ( Merle chuckles )
- Try some positivity for a change.
- Damn.
- I'll tell you what--
you get me out of these cuffs
and I'll be all "Sammy Sunshine"
positive for you.
Hey, see that hacksaw
over there in that toolbag?
Get it for me, hmm?
Make it worth your while.
What do you say, man?
Come on.
Get me out of these things.
So you can beat my ass again?
Or call me nigger some more?
Come on now. It wasn't personal.
It's just that your kind
and my kind ain't meant to mix.
That's all.
It don't mean we can't...
work together,
parley, as long as there's
some kind of mutual gain involved.
So... about that hacksaw--
I guess you want me to get
that rifle over there too
so you can shoot that cop
when he comes back up, huh?
- Huh.
- ( door clangs )
( rats squeaking )
Morales: Yeah, we've got
ourselves a sewer tunnel.
Jacqui was right.
Can we cut through it?
Morales: If we had
a blowtorch and half a day, sure.
Dale's hacksaw sure
as hell won't do it.
- ( rats squeaking )
- ( crunching )
( growling )
( zombies banging, growling )
Andrea: Mmm.
See something you like?
Not me, but I know
someone who would--
my sister.
She's still such a kid
in some ways.
Unicorns, dragons--
she's into all that stuff.
But mermaids-- they rule.
She loves mermaids.
Why not take it?
There's a cop staring at me.
( chuckles )
Would it be considered looting?
I don't think those rules
apply anymore. Do you?
( glass shatters )
- What did you find down there?
- Not a way out.
We need to find a way...
soon.
( thunder rumbling )
That construction site, those trucks--
they always keep keys on hand.
Morales: You'll never
make it past the walkers.
You got me out of that tank.
Yeah, but they were feeding.
They were distracted.
Rick:
Can we distract them again?
Merle: Right. Listen to him.
He's onto something.
A diversion,
like on "Hogan's Heroes."
- God. Give it a rest.
- They're drawn by sound, right?
Right, like dogs.
They hear a sound, they come.
- Rick: What else?
- Aside from they hear you?
They see you, smell you
and if they catch you, they eat you.
- They can tell us by smell?
- Glenn: Can't you?
They smell dead, we don't.
It's pretty distinct.
If bad ideas
were an Olympic event,
- this would take the gold.
- He's right.
Just stop, okay?
Take some time to think this through.
How much time? They already
got through one set of doors,
that glass won't hold forever.
( zombies growling )
( sighs )
Wayne Dunlap.
Georgia license.
Born in 1979.
He had $28 in his pocket
when he died...
and a picture of a pretty girl.
"With love, from Rachel."
He used to be like us--
worrying about bills
or the rent or the Super Bowl.
If I ever find my family,
I'm gonna tell them about Wayne.
Glenn:
One more thing--
he was an organ donor.
- ( grunts )
- Oh!
- Madre de Dios!
- ( chopping )
Glenn:
Oh! God...
damn it!
- Oh God.
- Andrea: Oh.
- ( all groan )
- Morales: Dios!
Oh God.
( all groaning )
( groans )
Keep chopping.
( Glenn groaning )
- I am so gonna hurl.
- Later.
Andrea: Oh!
Everybody got gloves?
Don't get any on your skin
or in your eyes.
( all groaning )
Glenn:
Oh God!
Oh jeez.
Oh, this is bad.
This is really bad.
Think about something else--
puppies and kittens.
Dead puppies and kittens.
( vomiting )
That is just evil.
What is wrong with you?
Next time let
the cracker beat his ass.
- T-Dog: I'm sorry, yo.
- Glenn: You suck!
- Do we smell like them?
- Oh yeah.
Glenn.
Just in case.
If we make it back, be ready.
What about Merle Dixon?
Rick:
Give me the axe.
- We nee-- we need more guts.
- Andrea: Oh God!
( door creaks )
( zombies moaning )
( growling )
( zombies groaning )
Merle:
Hey, what's happening, man?
Morales:
Hey, T-Dog, try that CB.
Merle: Hey, come on.
Talk to me, y'all.
Base camp, this is T-Dog.
Anybody hear me?
Can anybody out there hear me?
- There.
- ( thunder rumbling )
That asshole is out on the street
with the handcuff keys?
Boy, that hose isn't long
for this world, is it?
Man: No sir.
Dale: Where the hell are
we gonna find a replacement?
It's late. They should've
been back by now.
Worrying won't make it better.
- Shane: Attaboy.
- Carl: Yeah.
Shane:
And three, two, one-- pull it.
- Carl: Ah!
- ( both laugh )
Shane:
Start it over.
Make your "P" the other way--
around your finger.
- Oops.
- Good, just tie it around your finger.
Attaboy.
- ( radio squawking )
- T-Dog: Hello, base camp!
Can anybody out there hear me?
Base camp, this is T-Dog.
Anybody hear me?
Hello? Hello?
Reception's bad on this end.
- Repeat. Repeat.
- Shane, is that you?
Is that them?
- ( static )
- T-Dog: We're in some deep shit.
We're trapped in
the department store.
He say they're trapped?
T-Dog: There are geeks
all over the place. Hundreds of 'em.
We're surrounded.
T-Dog, repeat that last. Repeat.
( static )
- ( radio stops )
- He said the department store.
Dale:
I heard it too.
- Lori: Shane?
- No way.
We do not go after them.
We do not risk
the rest of the group.
- Y'all know that.
- So we're just gonna leave her there?
Look, Amy, I know that
this is not easy--
She volunteered to go
to help the rest of us.
I know, and she knew
the risks, right?
See, if she's trapped, she's gone.
So we just have to
deal with that.
There's nothing we can do.
She's my sister,
you son of a bitch.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- Lori: Amy...
Come on.
It's all right, buddy.
( moaning )
( whispers )
It's gonna work. I can't believe it.
Don't draw attention.
( growling )
( rain pattering )
Oh man.
( thunder crashes )
It's just a cloudburst.
We get 'em all the time.
It'll pass real quick.
( growling )
The smell's washing off. Isn't it?
- Is it washing off?
- No, it's not.
- Well, maybe.
- ( roars )
Oh shit! Run!
( zombies roaring )
Come on, come on, come on.
( gunshots )
Rick!
( engine starts )
Go go go go!
( tires screech )
They're leaving us.
- No. No no no no no.
- Dixon: What? What? What do you mean?
- Where they going? Where they going?
- No no, come back.
Oh God. Oh God.
They're all over that place!
You need to draw them away.
Those roll-up doors
at the front of the store--
that area?
--that's what I need cleared.
Raise your friends. Tell them
to get down there and be ready.
And I'm drawing the geeks away how?
I-- I missed that part.
Noise.
( car alarm blaring )
( engine revving )
( tires screech )
Those roll-up doors
at the front of the store
facing the street--
meet us there and be ready.
( alarm continues )
- Morales: Come on! Let's go, let's go!
- Hey, you can't leave me here!
I'm not fooling, man! Morales!
- Hey, man! Don't do this, Morales!
- Andrea: Come on!
Hey, that's my gun!
You guys just can't leave me!
- Don't leave me here, you guys!
- Morales, come on!
I'm coming!
We've gotta go!
Dixon: Morales!
You can't leave me like this, man!
Hey, T-Dog. No, man.
You can't leave me, man.
You can't leave me here--
not like this.
You can't, man. It's not human.
- Come on, don't do this.
- ( groans )
Come on, T. Come on!
Come on, yeah! Yeah!
Come on! Co-- that's it!
Yes! Come on, baby!
- Come on.
- ( key clinking )
( clanging )
( zombies banging )
Go.
Son of a bitch!
You did that on purpose!
- I didn't mean to!
- You lie! You did it on purpose!
- It was an accident!
- Don't leave me, man!
- Don't leave me! Don't leave me!
- ( cuffs rattling )
- I'm sorry. Man, I'm sorry.
- ( yells ) You liar!
- God damn it! Don't leave me!
- I'm sorry.
Don't do it, man!
Damn you all!
Don't leave me, man!
- Don't leave-- don't leave me!
- Ah!
Hey! What are you doing, man?
You're gonna rot in hell!
You're gonna
rot in hell!
- Come back, man!
- T-Dog: Wait a minute!
Here I come! Don't leave me!
Don't leave!
Okay. Okay.
I got it.
- ( car alarm blaring )
- Shh.
- What is that?
- ( car engine revving )
( tires screech )
Come on. Come on.
( zombies growling )
Get closer. Get closer.
Come on. Come on.
( tires screeching )
( glass shatters )
Hey, wait for me!
They're here! Let's go!
They're in here!
( bangs )
- T-Dog: Let's go!
- Andrea: Open the door!
- We've gotta go!
- Go!
( growling )
- I'm in!
- ( engine revving )
( tires screech )
( yells )
Damn it! Don't leave me!
You'll die!
Go to hell! Damn you!
( yells )
You'll rot in hell!
( yelling )
I dropped the damn key.
Where's Glenn?
( car alarm blaring )
- ( rock music playing )
- ♪ Now when I was a little boy ♪
♪ At the age of five ♪
♪ I had something in my pocket ♪
♪ Keeps a lot of folks alive... ♪
- Whoo-hoo-hoo! Yeah-hoo-hoo!
- ♪ Now I'm a man ♪
♪ Turnin' 21 ♪
♪ You know, baby ♪
♪ We can have a lot of fun ♪
♪ I'm a man ♪
- ♪ I spell M ♪
- ♪ M! ♪
- ♪ A ♪
- ♪ A! ♪
- ♪ N ♪
- ♪ N! ♪
- ♪ Whoa, I'm a man ♪
- ♪ Man! ♪