[English subtitles are available]
[Love Unexpected]
[Episode 19]
[2012]
I'll get going then.
Bye.
Let's go, Ruo Chen.
Let's grab a drink.
Let's go.
Your alcohol tolerance is a joke.
Don't look down on me.
I envy you.
You never get affected
by someone else's emotion.
I feel sick all the time these days.
Are you referring to Fan Fan?
You ask for it.
When you drink,
don't pull a long face.
If you ask me,
as long as you persist,
Fan Fan and you
can go through all the obstacles.
Drink up.
Women
are just like water.
You can neither grab them
nor sure of them.
But
I think Fan Fan is adorable.
Furthermore,
it's not hard to understand her.
Fan Fan is exceptionally cute.
She is really cute
but I can't figure her out.
Tell me.
What should I do?
You can't figure her out
because you have not tried hard enough.
Haven't I tried hard enough?
Liu Ruo Chen.
You should be grateful.
At least your crush likes you.
What about me?
I chose to not disturb her
and hide my feelings from her.
I have a crush too.
You are so lucky.
You have no idea how blessed you are.
Am I blessed?
I am living in pain.
I don't know what I should do.
Every day, in my heart,
I feel anxious.
What should I do?
Liu Ruo Chen.
Let me tell you.
Lu Fan Fan
stays away from you because of Gao Ru Wen.
She worries that Gao Ru Wen will harm you
if both of you get together.
Gao Ru Wen...
I'm not afraid of him,
not even a little bit.
No way.
Liu Ruo Chen.
I envy you.
I want to see Fan Fan.
I just want to see her for one time.
Just one time.
You are drunk.
How...
How can you see her?
I am going home.
Ruo Chen.
I will send you home.
Excuse me.
Bill.
Ruo Chen.
Where are you going?
I'll send you there.
Please send me home.
Sir,
let's go.
Are you doing this on purpose?
Are you really drunk?
This is Fan Fan's house.
This is not your house.
This is my house.
Fan Fan!
Stop slamming the door.
It's already late. We will be arrested
for causing nuisance.
Let me give Fan Fan a call.
Sit down.
Hello?
Hello,
Fan Fan.
Ruo Chen and I
are in front of your house.
[Please come out.]
Okay.
I'm coming right away.
What is going on?
Ruo Chen...
He is drunk.
He insisted to see you.
I'm at my wits' end.
That's why I called you.
Why did he drink so much?
Fan Fan.
Let's go inside. We'll talk later.
Slow down.
Fan Fan.
I told him to go home
but he insisted to come to your place.
He knew
that I won't let him in
if he is not drunk.
That's why he did this.
In that case,
I have accomplished the mission.
Take care of him.
Okay.
Take care.
Rest early.
Text me when you are home.
Okay.
I'll get going then.
Bye.
Liu Ruo Chen.
Stop pretending.
Are you drunk?
Fan Fan.
Don't chase me away.
Okay?
I'm not chasing you away.
Silly boy.
Rest well.
Good night.
Fan Fan.
It's burning.
Is he having a fever?
Come on.
Get up.
Take some medicine.
You may continue sleeping
after taking medicine.
Here.
Water.
I want water.
Okay, I will get some water for you.
Hold on.
Here is the water.
How did I end up in Fan Fan's house?
Fan Fan, don't go.
Fan Fan.
Don't chase me away.
Don't chase me away, okay?
Silly boy.
No one is chasing you away.
Rest well.
Good night.
Fan Fan.
What are you doing here?
Get some rest.
I'm fine now.
You are getting better.
I'm afraid you may
have no appetite due to fever.
That's why I cooked century egg porridge
with some side dishes.
After eating,
you may go back to sleep.
In the future,
don't you dare to drink so much.
When I had barbecue with Qing Yang,
I had a little beer.
A little?
Yet, you were terribly drunk.
God knows if you had barbecue
or just beers.
How do I get in here
if I didn't drink?
Fine.
Wait outside, the food is almost ready.
Yes, sir.
[I'm at your sister's place.
Everything goes well.]
[No wonder she takes a day off.]
[It turns out you are at her place.]
You are a teaching assistant.
You should take care of your appearance.
Your hair is as messy as a chicken coop.
I'm sick.
Why don't
you wash my hair?
Wash your hair?
Are you armless?
Go home and wash your hair.
I'm sick.
No one is taking care of me.
What if I pass out?
How about this?
Why don't
I bathe you as well?
If you are willing to do it,
I don't mind.
Dream on.
The shampoo smells so good.
I think it's clean.
I think
you can exert more strength.
Like this?
Move slightly to the right.
Move slightly more to the right.
Like this?
Yes.
Mr. Liu.
I think
you really enjoyed the service.
Well,
I shall continue.
What about this?
Okay.
Thank you for the service.
Let's rinse the hair.
What do you think?
Is my hairstyle okay?
It's acceptable.
You look like Pikachu.
You are comparing me to Pikachu.
You are incomparable to it.
That's better.
It is more adorable than you.
Am I not adorable?
All right.
Turn around.
Liu Ruo Chen.
When are you going home?
I still feel a little dizzy.
You are dizzy?
Are you still dizzy?
No, the dizziness is gone.
I will go home after lunch.
[I just want to spend more time with you.]
Happy weekend party!
You should have come empty handed.
Why did you bring food?
Why are you here?
I invited them.
It's been a while since we had gathering.
How is your mom doing?
She is getting better.
Furthermore,
ever since my dad went there,
her life is getting better.
My dad promised us,
when he is out of prison,
he will quit gambling.
We will live a good life together.
That's great.
If you face any difficulty, let us know.
Don't be shy.
Don't worry.
I can tell that
Mr. Liu really likes you.
Why did you break up with him?
Actually,
I did that for a reason.
After experiencing so much,
I'm really glad
that we have become friends.
Therefore,
I hope
you can live happily.
Same goes to you.
I hope
you can live happily too.
Lu Fan Fan's weekend party
also known as the first
dumpling cooking contest
will begin soon.
Are you two ready?
-Yes.
The winner
will get The Lu's 36-Style-Recipe.
The loser
will have to tell the opponent
"I admit defeat"
for three times.
Get ready.
Go!
Who would have thought
that they are
so skillful in cooking.
This...
This is...
That's so impressive.
Is that for real?
What do you usually do?
I have a wide variety of hobbies.
I vote for Qin Yang.
We unanimously decided
that the winner is
Qin Yang.
I admit defeat.
No matter what,
regardless the winner,
there are
so many dumplings,
we have to finish them.
Let's go.
Let's have dumplings.
[Stay tuned for the post-credits scene!]
♫ I never believed in ♫
[Wild]
[I can't change the reality]
♫ So-called obstacles ♫
[but I can't let]
♫ I only believed ♫
[the reality change me either.]
[On every new day,]
♫ That you loved me ♫
♫ It's you ♫
[I will try my best not to be a loser.]
♫ Who had shown me a sky full of love ♫
[Sweet dream]
♫ Every bit ♫
[will always come true.]
♫ Makes me happy ♫
♫ Because I have met you ♫
♫ From that day onwards ♫
♫ I will become careful ♫
♫ Not to wake you up in the morning ♫
♫ When you're still asleep ♫
[I hope Fan Fan lives happily forever,
from Qin Yang]
♫ In my heart ♫
[I hope my family
stays together forever, from Zhu]
♫ You're the stars
that are brighter than the sun ♫
♫ Bringing me unforgettable memories ♫
♫ You're the stars
that are gentler than the moon ♫
♫ Holding the secrets ♫
♫ Of my love ♫