[birds chirping]
[wind gushing]
[narrator] The past is a funny thing.
We like to hold onto it so tight.
But sometimes it's better to let go.
[train whistle blowing]
Sometimes we just gotta move on.
["Hello Miss Lonesome"
by Marlon Williams playing]
How are we gonna get tickets this time?
- We don't need 'em.
- What about my hat?
- Won't I need my hat?
- Just keep running!
[train whistle blowing]
- But won't people try to kill me?
- Gus!
♪ Oh, Miss Lonesome ♪
♪ I see you're back in town... ♪
[train whistle continues]
♪ It's funny how I lose mind
When you come around... ♪
- We're falling behind.
- I noticed!
We gotta go faster.
You go faster!
We gotta find a way in!
What about that?
[inhales sharply]
[vocalizes]
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[Bear panting]
[Gus] C'mon, Bear, hurry!
[train whistle blowing]
[panting]
Jepp! Come on!
[panting continues]
Jepp!
- He's not gonna make it.
- Yes, he is. He has to.
[vocalizes]
- [Gus] Come on, Big Man!
- Faster!
Come on, you can do it!
Come on.
[straining]
You can do it! Come on, Big Man!
Come on!
[dramatic music playing]
[players grunting]
[grunting continues]
Ya!
[breathing heavily]
[Gus] Come on, Big Man! You can do it!
[music halts]
No!
[triumphant music playing]
Big Man! You made it!
Didn't know you had it in ya!
Take your time.
Do people live here?
Not quite. These are crew quarters.
[Jepperd] We lucked out.
We hopped a hauler.
No passengers.
Except all the people
who work on the train.
One of them might come.
We should be able to hunker down
in one of the sleepers up ahead.
Should be easy to stay out of sight.
[Bear]
Hey, Gus, come on. Get down from there.
[Jepperd] Hey, Gus.
Guess what?
Next stop, Colorado.
[narrator] And sometimes, well,
sometimes the past won't let go of us.
[slam echoing]
[somber music playing]
[flames crackling]
[extinguisher gushing]
[Last Man 1] Go back to your house!
You're not supposed to be here.
Get inside!
[glass clinking]
[extinguisher gushing]
[indistinct yelling]
[Last Man 2] Burnt kitchen.
[extinguisher gushing]
[indistinct chatter]
- [Rani breathes heavily]
- [Dr. Singh strains]
Please, you have to help us.
[General Abbot] No, I'm good.
I got what I came for.
There's... There's a formula in there for
a treatment. It keeps the Sick at bay.
I know.
Uh... I can make it for you. I'm a doctor.
No. Just needed the book.
No, no, no, no, no!
If you let us die,
you'll never have the cure.
[ominous music playing]
[Rani breathing heavily]
[Dr. Singh] Hey.
She's not contagious.
Then why, pray tell,
is she the way she is?
Because you never sent us
the hybrid we asked for.
Jane Doe.
Yes, unfortunately,
we were running a little low on hybrids.
What is all this I hear about a cure?
Uh...
Uh, just... just...
Uh, just... just turn to the last page.
[panting] Go on.
[sighs]
Dr. Bell was mapping a hybrid genome
in an... in an effort to find the cure,
but she missed something.
There are tiny gaps in the base pairs,
missing chromosomes in the sequence.
Something that I call "Ghost DNA."
Go on.
[panting]
I've resequenced the genetic code
to locate those gaps.
And therein lies the cure.
[General Abbot] Let me guess.
None of this is in the book.
That's right.
So, if you want the cure,
you'll have to let both of us go.
[ominous music intensifies]
- Johnny!
- [yelps]
Yes, General.
Help our new friends pack.
Yes, sir.
We'll be moving you
to better accommodations,
where you'll have
everything you'll ever need.
You.
- [distant yelling]
- [slow footsteps]
You will not screw this up.
Sir.
[hopeful music playing]
[sniffs]
[Gus] Are we there yet?
What'd I say?
You said that when we cross
the big river, we'd be in Colorado.
And have you seen any river?
No.
- [Jepperd] So?
- So, we're not there yet.
So stop asking.
Hey, leave him alone.
Hey, Bear.
Can you tell me where GoGro is?
- I can't find it on my map.
- [Jepperd] Yeah, Bear.
Where is GoGro?
I'm not sure.
How are we supposed to find my mom
if we don't know where GoGro is?
Don't worry. We'll figure it out.
We've got plenty of time.
Gus, come here a second.
- Gus, keep away from the edge.
- It's okay. I'll keep an eye on him.
Wanna see something cool?
Look over there.
- [elephants trumpeting]
- [uplifting music playing]
Are those zebras?
Yeah.
I wish Pubba was here to see this.
Let's play a game.
You wanna play "I Spy"?
How do you play that?
Okay, it's easy.
You just look out and you pick something,
like one of the zebras,
then say, "I spy with my
little eye something that begins with Z."
Then I have to guess what you're thinking.
Make sense?
Uh...
I think so. Can I go first?
Mm-hmm.
I spy with my little eye
something that starts with the letter...
M.
The motorcycle?
No.
[Bear inhales]
The mountains?
I give up.
A monkey.
Where do you see a monkey?
I win.
This game is fun.
My parents used to play it with us
when we were little.
My sister was just a baby, but...
[chuckles]
...she'd point at things and giggle.
[melancholic music playing]
I didn't know you had a sister.
I bet you must miss them.
Your family.
Yeah.
I miss Pubba too.
What's your favorite memory of him?
It was on my birthday, when he got me Dog.
Yeah. It's when he got me Dog.
Is that your stuffed animal?
Then when I fell into the purple flowers,
Dog was there too.
And I followed him through the forest,
and he brought me to see Pubba.
And Pubba told me that I have to grow up
and trust what's in here.
Can I see him?
Dog, I mean?
- No. No, no, no, no, no.
- What's wrong?
[Gus] Dog's not in here.
He's lost. I can't find him.
- [Jepperd] What's going on?
- I lost Dog. He's not here.
[Bear] It's okay.
You must've dropped him here somewhere.
We'll check the other cars and find him.
[clattering]
[Bear] You heard that too, right?
[chains rattling]
[lock screeching]
Someone's coming.
Hide. Hide, now!
Come on. Hide.
[ominous music playing]
[tool clanking]
[mouthing] Stop.
[glass clinking]
[music swells]
[man] Who's there?
You're in trouble now.
This ain't no passenger train.
[bottle scraping]
[music builds]
Gotcha!
[Gus screaming]
[Gus] Let me go!
[Gus moans]
Wait a second!
[Jepperd] Leave him alone!
- [Jepperd grunts]
- [man] Ah!
[man grunts]
[man groans]
[man] Ah!
- [weapon clanging]
- [both grunting]
[boxes clattering]
[Bear] Holy shit.
- [Bear inhales]
- [both grunting]
[both grunting]
[man] Ah!
[both straining]
[grunting continues]
[boxes clattering]
- [man] Ah!
- Jimmy!
Jimmy Jacobs?
TJ?
[Jepperd laughs]
- Oh my God!
- Tommy Jepperd. It is you!
[Jepperd sighs]
It's good to see you, bubba!
Glad I recognized you when I did,
or I might've messed up your pretty face.
Ha! You wish!
What are you doing here?
You know, I thought I'd take a trip.
- [both chuckle]
- Man!
Great. Now there are two of you.
[chuckles] Bear, it's okay. I want to
introduce you to Jimmy "Fat Man" Jacobs.
[Jimmy] Fat Man.
- I forgot about that.
- Jimmy and I played ball together.
You're looking at the greatest defensive
end in the history of the Guardians!
[both] Ah-ooh!
[Jepperd laughs]
Only 'cause you took those hits for me.
Made me look good.
My head was harder,
but you took your fair share.
Ain't that the truth. I got this funny
sorta static in my head these days too.
Hard to focus sometimes.
I think those are called concussions.
Wait, so you must have
run across those other guys too, huh?
Troy? Rocco?
What about D-Train?
Oh, they're not around anymore, man.
[chuckles]
I wonder how those guys are doing.
We had some good times, didn't we?
[Jepperd exhales]
Yeah, well.
You're working on the train now, huh?
Oh, yeah. Been running charters and
hauling supplies to whoever hires us.
Company's got me on maintenance
and crap like that.
Ain't so bad,
but I sure do miss being on the field.
Don't you?
[inhales, exhales]
Where's Gus?
Hey, Gus.
- It's all right. You can come out.
- The one with the antlers?
Sweet Tooth.
Jepp.
- Hey, Gus. I'm not playing.
- Jepperd.
[ominous music playing]
Where is he?
I think he went looking for Dog.
[music builds to a climax]
[sinister music playing]
[Bobby warbles]
What is it?
What does it mean?
This area's been marked.
By the Last Men?
We need to go.
Right now.
Bobby, go check the tunnels.
But whatever you do, stay out of sight.
- Check.
- Okay?
Shouldn't we take the ribbons down?
That would keep the bad men away, right?
[bolt clicks]
They'd know we're here for sure if we did.
Maybe we should hide, then.
I can get the others and I can play
hide-and-seek, like you showed me.
If they already know we're here,
hiding won't do any good.
We wouldn't have time to run.
- [chains rattling]
- [lock clicks]
[Pigtail] Then what do we do?
Mom!
Hey. Everything's gonna be all right,
I promise.
But I wanna help.
Wendy, I promise.
Do you trust me?
- [sniffs]
- [ominous music playing]
Someone's outside.
[metal rattling]
The outer fence.
Who is he?
A Last Man.
[Pigtail] Why is he just standing there?
- He knows we're here, doesn't he?
- [shushing]
Let me think.
Move on, please, move on.
I thought we would have more time.
Are we safe?
[somber music playing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[glass clinking]
[Johnny] Oh, I can't remember
the last time I saw these.
Mind if I have one?
Rani, you shouldn't be exerting yourself.
Oh, hush, I'm all right.
[exhales]
It'd be easier to pack
if we knew where we were going.
Sorry.
Are we going east? That's where
your little Last Men clubhouse is, right?
Rani.
General Abbot says it's classified.
[distant chatter]
So that's Abbot, then.
[Dr. Singh] Rani.
I thought he'd be less beardy.
Rani, can you just stop, please?!
[exhales]
- Hey. What is it? What's going on?
- Hey.
- I can't find all the letters.
- Take a breath and relax.
[Dr. Singh] Don't tell me to relax!
We almost just burnt to death,
then Abbot showed up, then you...
[whispers] Okay.
[stammering] And now I can't...
I can't find the tiles,
and that means we can't play anymore.
- I know.
- And w-what we gonna do about Trixie?
They're never gonna let us bring her.
Who's Trixie?
That your kid?
Our horse.
She really helped us out a few times.
Hey.
Can you, uh...
Can you please just wait outside?
Hmm.
I can't.
Where exactly do you think we're gonna go?
Wait. Wait!
I know you're freaking out,
but just try to breathe. It'll be okay.
No, Rani, it's not going to be okay.
How on earth am I supposed
to find a cure for the Sick?
Everyone's been looking for one
for the last ten years.
I don't know, but what I do know is
we have more time together
than we did this morning.
[exhales]
[whispers] What do you think he's gonna do
when he finds out that we were bluffing?
[stammering]
If I didn't know the truth,
I would've believed you.
Your explanation was very convincing.
I'm gonna go pack my things.
Adi.
Adi, come on.
[ominous music playing]
[inhales sharply]
[melancholic music playing]
- [Dr. Singh exhales]
- [Rani sniffs]
I remember when the first patient came in.
Her name was Freya.
Oh, Adi.
It didn't seem like
anything to worry about at first,
just a strange case of the flu,
something that would pass, and then...
a week later she came back, and this time...
she was worse, much worse.
No matter what I did...
no matter how hard I tried to help her...
it didn't matter.
[scoffs]
Then she died.
[Rani sighs]
[Dr. Singh] I know.
I still see them, you know.
All of them. Their faces.
[ominous music playing]
We said we were gonna take care of them,
so they wouldn't be afraid, you know?
[sniffs]
[Dr. Singh]
But all the while, we knew they would die.
And that more would come
and take their place.
After a while, I stopped caring.
Well, I had to,
just to keep going with it.
It made me feel numb.
Hmm.
That's why I stopped being a doctor.
[inhales, exhales]
And after taking over
the clinic from Bell...
and what we did to Doug and Nancie...
that feeling's back, and for what?
To find a cure.
[chuckles]
You don't honestly believe...
I believe
in you, Adi.
[sniffs]
And so did Dr. Bell.
That's why she gave her journal to you.
You can finish what she started.
You're not alone in this.
We've made it this far together,
haven't we?
[chuckles]
Together.
Hmm?
[indistinct radio chatter]
[train whistle blowing]
Gus, you in here?
[Bear] Gus?
I used to sneak off
and I'd get my ass whooped.
He's a kid. He misses his toy.
[Jimmy] Don't worry, T. I know every nook
and cranny of this train. We'll find him.
You guys are hauling a lot of candy bars.
Yeah, part of the same transpo job.
Thought about snaggin'
a couple for myself.
Well, if he isn't in here,
I can't imagine where he is.
Gus?
Sweet Tooth, come on.
Stop playing games.
You'll never guess what they have on here.
A car full of Choc-O-Rockets!
Your boy's quite the troublemaker, huh?
Chip off the old block?
I think Louisa was still pregnant
the last time I saw you.
- Crazy you had one of them animal kids...
- Gus is not my kid.
We should spread out.
I'll check the next car.
- [door closes]
- Dumbass.
What happened, bubba?
To Louisa and the baby?
[somber music playing]
They're gone, Jimmy.
Just like D-Train and the others.
I'm sorry, T.
The Sick get 'em?
What's with the deer kid, then?
He's just a kid, um...
He's just a kid I'm trying to help.
Doesn't sound like the Jepp I remember.
It used to be all about you.
- Mm-hmm.
- [door opens]
Gus! Christ, kid.
Where the hell have you been?
Almost gave me a heart attack.
I can't find him, Jepp.
I... I still can't find Dog.
Hey. Buck up, kid.
There's no crying in the apocalypse.
I'll get you another Dog, I promise.
[Gus] You don't understand.
Pubba made Dog out of his own socks.
It even still smells like him.
[hopeful music playing]
Hey.
Hey. Remember I told you
about reaching Colorado?
When we cross the big river,
we'll be in Colorado.
Well...
Tell me what you see.
Does... Does that mean...
Yeah, Sweet Tooth.
We made it.
We're in Colorado.
[sighs]
We made it to Colorado.
All we have to figure out now
is where the hell GoGro is.
[Jimmy] GoGro?
Did you say GoGro?
Yeah, you know it?
Of course I know it.
Well, where the hell is it?
It...
It's actually...
It's, uh...
Focus, Jimmy.
No. I know I know it, it's...
I hear it all the time.
I'll check my cargo manifest. Yeah, yeah.
[Jimmy exhales]
- [Jepperd] G, as in GoGro.
- [Jimmy] GoGro.
[exhales, chuckles]
[giggles]
I remember.
It's short for Goss Grove,
but nobody calls it that,
everyone calls it GoGro.
It's a neighborhood outside of Essex City.
- [Jepperd] That's the next stop.
- Thanks, other Big Man!
[Jimmy] No worries, kid.
- What's wrong?
- Last Men. On the train.
What? What are Last Men
doing on this train?
It's their charter, T.
I thought I told you that.
You definitely did not
tell us that, Jimmy.
They're moving operations south,
including the Choc-O-Rockets.
General Abbot...
Not important.
- Where are they?
- In the next car, headed this way.
Shit.
Come on, let's take 'em. I'm done hiding.
No. We don't know
how many of them there are.
So what do we do?
[exhales] Um...
Follow me. Yeah.
[suspenseful music builds]
[Bear]
Uh, guys? There's nowhere else to go.
I'll talk to 'em,
you guys stay out of sight.
I'll tell them nobody's here,
they'll believe me.
Jimmy, no offense, but you've never
been able to sweet-talk anybody.
They're coming.
We jump. It's our only option.
[indistinct chatter]
You gotta be shittin' me.
[Gus] Jepp?
What are we gonna do?
We're gonna do something stupid.
Hold it.
[exhales]
What's up, fellas?
What are you doing here?
Uh, you didn't hear? They...
We got a leak out back in the galley.
It smells like gas.
The caboose is off limits
until we can sort it out.
Can't be too careful.
The stove is electric.
[inhales]
What?
The stove.
It's electric. Not gas.
[indistinct radio chatter]
Jepperd.
[music swells]
Oops.
- [Last Men clamoring]
- [clattering]
- [Last Man 1] Get him! Get him!
- [door slams]
What the hell did you do that for?
[Last Man 1] Open this door!
Dog!
[banging on door]
[Last Man 1] Bring the ax.
- Jepperd! You hear me?
- [Jepperd grunts]
Whatever you're gonna do, do it fast.
Jepperd, we gotta jump.
No. Uh, take Gus.
Jimmy and I will buy you some time.
- No, we all go together.
- [banging on door]
No, listen, Gus.
No, Jepp. Together.
[Last Man 1] Hey! I'm talking to you!
- [banging on door]
- Listen to them, Tommy.
I'mma buy you some time. I owe you
for taking all those hits for me.
No, Jimmy.
They'll kill you for helping us.
Let's face it, T.
You ain't the only one that's changed.
My mind's never gonna be the same.
But if I'm going out, I wanna be doing
the only thing I was ever good at.
Go.
- Be with your family.
- [Last Man 1] Jepperd!
[mouthing] Go.
[Last Man 1] Hey!
Shit. Come on.
[banging on door intensifies]
Are we really gonna jump?
Deep breath, Gus.
Ready? Three, two, one...
[Bear vocalizes]
[Gus screams]
[banging on door continues]
[music swells]
- [all grunting]
- [door clatters]
- [Last Man 1] Where is he?
- Where's who?
[Last Man 2] Check down there.
Hang on, hang on, hang on, hang on.
What?
So I can knock your lights out.
[Last Men grunting]
[train whistle blowing]
[audience cheering]
[announcer] Let's hear it
for Jimmy "Fat Man" Jacobs!
[music builds, fades]
[melancholic music]
[sighs]
[hybrids cooing]
- [Aimee] Do you remember the plan?
- [Pigtail] Yeah.
Follow the pipes. Hide in the church.
Protect the others.
Wait until you come for us.
- [Aimee] Good.
- Why aren't you coming now?
I have to stay behind,
in case the bad men come.
You shouldn't be alone.
[Aimee] Pigtail,
you need to look after the others.
Hmm?
What if I mess up?
[Aimee] You won't.
You remember when I said,
"No matter what happens, you'll be strong,
because you're Wendy.
Because you're my daughter."
Go on now, go. Go.
Promise you'll come for us?
Cross my heart.
[chuckles]
Bobby ready.
[Aimee] You have to get going.
Just go.
[narrator]
It's a difficult thing, letting go.
It's tough to say goodbye.
[Last Man 1] Hands, please.
[acoustic guitar music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[whispers] I just want to let you know,
I let your horse go.
She's free.
[Dr. Singh] Thank you.
[engine rumbling]
[banging on roof]
[narrator]
But the thing we don't always realize,
when we let go of something...
[Trixie neighing]
...it opens up a little space
to grow.
It shows us who we are...
[hybrids cooing]
...what we're capable of.
We find out what really matters,
and who we really were, all along.
[music intensifies]
- [Jepperd] Hey, don't go too far off.
- [Gus] I won't.
[Jepperd] Man.
Hey, that was pretty cool,
what you did back there.
Going back for Dog.
What, you didn't think I had it in me?
Hey, I know you're considering
going down south, but, uh...
you can stick with us if you want.
I'll think about it.
[positive music playing]
[Gus] Hey, you guys!
What is it?
I spy with my little eye
something that begins with the letter E!
- [Jepperd chuckles]
- [Gus] GoGro, here we come!
[triumphant music playing]