[radio interference]
[tense music playing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[narrator] You can't know Gus's story
without knowing Aimee's too.
The end of the world's got
a funny way of making connections.
Aimee never saw it coming,
because before the Great Crumble...
[man 1] It's like we never talk anymore.
[narrator]...she had a hard time
connecting to anything.
[woman 1] Whose decision was it
to have three kids?
You're not blaming our kids on me.
- [man 2] He never listens to me.
- That is completely unfair.
- All I do is listen to you.
- Then what did I just say?
[woman 2] He has a great job, but...
[narrator]
You see, Aimee lived inside a cage.
- [woman 2] He chews...
- The cage of a mundane life.
Disgusting.
[sniffs]
[sinister music playing]
[narrator]
And that cage was about to get smaller.
[alarm ringing]
[announcer]
This is the Emergency Broadcast System.
This is not a test.
[people clamoring]
[official on TV] It doesn't show mercy,
and it is here, and it is now.
And if you don't pray,
now might be a good time to start.
The H5G9 strain...
[announcer]
This is officially your final warning.
- This is a mandatory quarantine.
- [helicopter whirring]
Repeat, this is a mandatory quarantine.
- [gunshot]
- [gasps]
- [woman screaming]
- [Aimee panting]
[reporter] Officials are telling
everyone to stay indoors.
Lock your homes.
Do not come in contact
with anyone showing symptoms.
If you're healthy,
you need to quarantine in place.
[narrator] Hours became days.
Days became weeks.
Aimee became a prisoner.
[indistinct TV chatter]
[sinister music builds]
[gasps]
- [distant wailing]
- [suspenseful music playing]
[narrator] But just when she thought
the world had locked her away for good...
nature had another idea.
[distant wailing]
[animal trumpeting]
- [wind gushing]
- [birds squawking]
[elephants trumpeting]
[metal clanging]
- [trumpeting continues]
- [glass shattering]
[hopeful music playing]
[Aimee laughing]
[narrator]
And for the first time in Aimee's life...
she felt awake.
Just like that,
Aimee knew exactly where she needed to go.
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
- [bird squawking]
- [hopeful music continues]
[bird chirping]
Hi there.
Everybody left, huh?
[gate creaking]
Are you ready to be free?
Yeah?
Hm?
[narrator]
Some stories start at the beginning.
Well, go on, then.
[triumphant music playing]
[narrator] Aimee's story begins here.
[bird cawing]
And somewhere,
far, far out of the deep woods,
fate was bringing
all our stories together.
[Gus] Big Man!
Wait for me!
- [leaves rustling]
- [footsteps approaching]
How long are you gonna follow me?
Till we get there, I guess.
Get where?
Colorado. That's where she is.
Who?
- My mom.
- Aw...
I forgot to tell you.
Colorado blew up.
Yeah, it's...
Everything's gone.
Lasers, I think, and, um...
all the people there
are gone too. So sad.
Sorry you missed it.
Oh, well. Have a great life.
[light piano music playing]
That was a joke.
Your jokes aren't very funny, Big Man.
As funny as a little deer kid thinking
he could make it out here on his own.
- [sighs]
- I'm not alone, I got you.
- What'd I tell you?
- If I went and looked for her alone...
I said stay put,
as in don't leave,
as in stay your ass in the woods
and munch on shrubs
or whatever it is you do.
What are you doing?
My Pubba said
we gotta leave places like we found them,
hide our trash
so bad people don't find us.
Hm. [grunts]
[light piano music continues]
[Gus] Be right back.
[howling]
[velcro ripping]
[Big Man grunts]
[leaves rustling]
Let me guess.
You're nocturnal too.
[Gus] I'll be quiet, I promise.
Ain't gonna happen, little man.
You're creepy as hell back there.
Get out here where I can see you.
[sighs]
[Gus] Where do you live?
- [Big Man] Nowhere.
- Where's that?
- Anywhere I want.
- Do you have friends?
- Nope.
- How come?
- Dead.
- Do you know my mom?
- No.
- How come?
- Probably dead.
- How do you know?
- Most people are.
- How far's Colorado?
- A million miles.
- How long'll that take?
I don't know 'cause I'm not taking you.
How come?
'Cause I got things to do.
- Like what?
- Trust me, kid.
Guys like me
aren't good for kids like you.
Did you put out all the fires?
What fires?
Well, my Pubba said it was all bad people
and fires outside the fence,
but I haven't seen any other fires.
Finish your food.
Now what?
[exhales] I'm going to bed.
What should I do?
I don't give a shit,
as long as you're gone in the morning.
[Big Man grunts]
[contemplative music playing]
[Big Man] Dude. Dude.
Dude...
Oh, no. Not my food.
You little...
My map!
Uh...
Where are these?
I don't know.
I tried some, but they were gross.
They made me feel funny.
They're not candy.
Now, where are the rest of them?
Ah, damn!
[Gus] But I brought extra syrup!
Go home.
You can have my share too!
Come here.
I got no medicine,
I got no way out of here,
I got no water and I got no food.
I get angry when I don't have food.
Do you want to see what angry looks like?
I know where there's food.
[tense music playing]
Maybe we can go in together?
Get in there.
[mouthing] Go in!
[sighs]
Don't talk...
[ominous music playing]
...grab food, run back.
Don't talk, grab food...
[door opens, creaks]
Whoa!
[sniffing]
[items rattling]
[gasps]
- [ominous music building]
- [Gus panting]
- [trap rattling]
- [Gus screaming]
[Gus straining]
Uh...
Dad?
[Gus moaning, straining]
- Leave my head alone! You can't have it!
- [ominous music builds]
[glass shattering]
You get many visitors?
Never.
Then you can take off your masks.
I don't have the Sick.
If you've been isolated out here,
then you don't, either.
[woman] Is the virus still out there?
[Big Man] Comes and goes.
- [Gus crunching]
- What about...
[Big Man] Critters don't get sick
and they can't spread it, either.
I don't know why
people still believe that.
We don't get out much.
Rusty!
Not at the table.
Go on to your room.
Hold on.
All better.
Thank you.
Are you Rusty's mom?
- I never met a mom before.
- Don't get him started.
Who taught you to talk?
My Pubba did. He made me do school.
I figure the Sick got him.
- Do you know Birdie?
- Excuse me?
My mama. We're trying to find her.
I'm sorry. I'm afraid I don't know her.
She looks very nice, though.
I tried to tell him,
she ain't out there,
but he's stubborn as hell.
How do you guys know each other?
- We don't.
- He's taking me to Colorado.
How old are you, Gus?
I'm ten, I think.
Isn't that old for one of them?
How old's Rusty?
He's 11.
He's one of the last, uh...
One of the last
human babies before...
Before all kids were born
like you. [titters]
Can I go play with him?
I... I don't know.
Does he bite?
Do you bite?
- Go on, then, Sweet Tooth.
- [sucks fingers]
[whispering] Yeah, okay.
[tense music playing]
[thunder rumbling]
[gentle music playing]
Did you know
they used to send people to the moon?
My dad said they used to make people
go to outer space and stuff.
Have you ever been to the moon?
No. I went to a mall one time.
Do you poop pellets?
No.
Are your ears soft,
or are they gross like pig ears?
I forget I have them sometimes.
Except when they're itchy.
I had a golden retriever named Snickers,
and I used to scratch his ears,
and his leg would kick a lot.
Do you do that?
Um...
I don't know.
Can I try?
- [both giggling]
- [hopeful music playing]
[chuckles] Super cool.
- Do you know how to play trains?
- [Gus] Yeah. What's a train?
It's like a caterpillar, and it goes fast.
So how do I play it?
Put your hand on it,
and then you push it.
- [Gus gasps]
- [Rusty giggles]
It's so fun.
[beer can opening]
[ominous music playing]
Are you who I think you are?
I don't know, am I?
[chuckles] You know, the football guy.
You... you played for the... What was it...
The Gators?
- Guardians.
- Right.
- Timmy Jepperd.
- Tommy.
[man chuckles]
[thunder rumbling]
So, where were you when it all went...
[sighs]
Try not to think about it.
[man] Understandable.
Bev was at work.
[exhales] We both were, actually.
We barely saw each other
back then, really.
Guess in a lot of ways,
everything falling apart
actually brought us together as a family.
Yeah, you're lucky you made it.
That's 'cause no one knows we're here.
Hmm.
What do you want from us?
I wanna spend the night,
wait out the storm.
- I should talk to Bev first.
- I wasn't asking.
We don't want any trouble.
That makes two of us.
[sinister music playing]
[Last Man] Campfire.
Move out and look for him.
[thunder rumbling]
- [Gus] Marco.
- [Rusty] Polo.
- [bullet whooshing]
- [Rusty grunts]
[toy gun clicking]
[toy gun cocking]
Marco.
[whispers] Polo.
- [bullet whooshing]
- [grunts]
Not Fair! He hears everything, Mom!
He's not like you, honey. You have
to find a game you're both good at.
Why don't you show Gus your records?
- [record player clicking]
- [needle scratching]
["I Can't Get Next To You"
by The Temptations playing]
[music intensifies]
♪ I can turn the gray sky blue ♪
♪ I can make it rain... ♪
Have you heard music before, Gus?
♪ I can build a castle
from a single grain of sand ♪
♪ I can make a ship sail, on dry land ♪
♪ But my life is incomplete
And I'm so blue ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't get next to you ♪
- ♪ I can't get next to you, babe ♪
- ♪ Next to you ♪
- ♪ I can't get next to you ♪
- ♪ I just can't get next you ♪
♪ I can't get next to you ♪
♪ I can fly like a bird in the sky ♪
♪ Hey, and I can buy anything
That money can buy ♪
♪ Oh, I can turn a river
Into a raging fire ♪
♪ I can live forever if I so desired ♪
♪ Unimportant
Are all the things I can do ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't get next to you... ♪
[narrator] And as one storm was brewing...
- [kettle whistling]
- [sinister music playing]
...another was headed
far from Yellowstone,
and straight for Aditya Singh.
[spoon tapping]
[singing] Do, do, do, do.
[humming]
[Dr. Singh] Yes, thank you. Thank you.
- Really?
- Oh, come on, I have all the vowels again.
- I know you're cheating.
- Not sure I've met a sorer loser.
- Ha!
- What?
X-I is not a word!
It's a triple-word score,
14th letter of the Greek alphabet.
[groans]
I really miss having the Internet.
You miss the Internet
so you can double-check me on Scrabble?
Well, for that and other things,
but mostly...
that. Boom!
"Mosquito"... How long
have you been holding on to that one?
I will beat you. [chuckles]
[ominous music playing]
[sighs]
[somber music playing]
[Rani exhales sharply]
- I'm sorry, sweetheart.
- I hate it when you call me that.
[exhales]
Come on.
- [Dr. Singh sighs]
- [Rani sighs]
Right, we're running low.
I should head to Dr. Bell.
If this is your way
of getting out of our game...
[chuckles]
The last thing we need
is for the neighbors to see you like this.
Can you at least
bring me back some french fries?
And an apple pie?
- And a strawberry milkshake.
- Oh, gee.
[both laughing]
Hey.
I love you.
Ooh.
[grunts, exhales]
[sighs]
You ready for a ride, Trixie?
- Hey? [smooches]
- [Trixie nickering]
Come on.
[repetitive acoustic guitar music playing]
[whistling]
- Hey, Adi.
- [Dr. Singh] Hey, Bob.
[gate buzzes, creaks open]
- You two stay safe out there.
- Yeah, we will.
You're a good man, Bob.
[door alarm beeping]
[clears throat]
How are you?
Where's Kevin?
Oh, split a few days ago.
He heard they were starting
new safe zones on the east coast.
Didn't know there was
an east coast anymore. [snickers]
Between the two of us,
Kevin was getting suburban cabin fever,
so he'd use any excuse to get out of here.
Are you feeling okay?
Yeah, yeah, just a routine checkup.
You know,
it's easy to lose track of the days.
- Don't I know it. Wrist, please.
- Yeah, sorry.
[machine buzzing]
[beeping]
All good. Take a seat.
Thanks.
[distant coughing]
- [door opens]
- [door alarm beeping]
[door alarm beeping]
[radio interference]
[box clattering]
[ominous music building]
[receptionist]
Thank you. See you next week.
- [receptionist] Mr. Singh?
- Yes.
The doctor will see you now.
[Dr. Singh] Busy as usual tonight?
Refill?
Yeah. Thanks.
How long have the doses been lasting?
Um, about 28 days
she's in full remission, and then...
And then the Sick comes back?
Yeah.
Any symptoms with this new cocktail?
A small rash on her leg, slight nausea,
but, uh, her energy levels are up.
Must be inching closer to a cure.
It's funny, you've been saying
the same thing for the past ten years,
and I still can't tell if you're
talking to me as a relative of a patient
or as a colleague.
What's this?
All my records.
Detailed documentation
of every trial version I've used on Rani,
what has worked and what hasn't.
You want me to help keep track?
You know my medical days are over.
They don't have to be.
[ominous music playing]
I prefer it on the sidelines, you know,
less screaming and mass death.
- You know what I went through.
- What we all went through.
I wouldn't be asking you
if I had any other choice.
What aren't you saying, Gladys?
Before everything happened...
I used to preach to all my patients that
mammograms have saved countless women.
But since the virus hit,
cancer has been a secondary concern.
The thought of something inside you
and taking you down slowly
seems like a luxury.
How far along are you?
I'm pretty sure it's stage four now.
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
I don't know what to say.
Say you'll continue the work I started.
I wouldn't even know where to begin.
That is what the book is for.
Now, I've had to do
a lot of things that I'm not proud of.
But you, of all people, know that
this new world is all about survival,
no matter the cost.
[sighs]
Rani is alive today because of you,
and, um, we're both forever grateful...
You know, there was a time
when I was convinced my purpose
was to find the cure to the virus,
but now I know I was wrong.
It's yours.
How can you be so sure?
Because there's nothing that
you wouldn't do for your wife, Dr. Singh.
And that is exactly
what it's going to take.
[thunder rumbling]
[Dr. Singh exhales]
What's wrong?
Did she run out of medicine again?
No, she's... she's gone.
I don't understand.
She's left instructions.
It's up to me now to make your medicine.
[Rani exhales]
[ominous music playing]
You're acting like this is a bad thing.
I can't think of anything better than
my own husband keeping me healthy.
- My personal hero...
- No, you don't understand what she's been...
What she's been doing. It's...
[exhales]
[Rani] What is it, Adi?
It goes against
everything that we believe in.
I don't think I can do it.
- [music builds]
- [Rani inhales sharply]
[exhales sharply]
[sighs]
MRE tokens.
You can trade them in for military food.
I'm only taking what I need
to get back to the Market.
We don't want your money.
I'd offer you meds, but he lost all mine.
- What are you doing with him?
- Trying to get rid of him.
Easier said than done.
You're one of them,
aren't you?
I, uh...
saw your mark.
Not anymore.
How many people have you killed?
- Can we not do this?
- Did they all deserve it?
Did you come here for my family?
My son?
I came here for food.
Look, lady,
I did what I had to, to survive.
Just like everyone else.
We never stole.
Or kidnapped.
And we never killed anyone.
That's because people like you
had people like me to do it for you.
He believes you're gonna look after him.
He believes whatever the hell he wants.
If it were up to me...
there'd be no such thing as kids like him.
Then why did you save him?
Doesn't matter.
I got an idea.
[somber music playing]
Why don't you take him?
I saved him, you keep him.
He's better off here than out there.
What about his mom?
You're the closest thing
he'll ever have to a mom.
I have to... talk to George.
Good. Tell him you're out of beans.
[thunder rumbling]
Have you met kids like me before?
This one time,
we saw a bobcat girl in the woods,
but she didn't talk like you.
My dad scared her off.
Why?
He said 'cause it's animal kids' fault.
What is?
Making everyone get sick and die.
Hey, my Pubba wrote that.
[Rusty] Who?
My Pubba, he wrote lots of books.
That's not what
The Velveteen Rabbit looks like.
[chuckles] Who drew this?
His eyes are crazy.
He looks like he's got boogers.
[melancholic music playing]
Have you seen any fires?
What?
Outside,
there's supposed to be fires everywhere.
[Rusty] You're weird, Sweet Tooth.
Super weird.
[Bev] Boys, bed time.
What's it like having a mom?
It's cool, I guess.
It's like having a dad...
but better.
Hey, want a sweatshirt?
We got, like, 1,000 of them.
Thanks.
[George] Lights out, you two.
[Bev] You're stuck? [chuckles]
Here. He's all fixed.
Okay.
Good night, sweetheart.
[smooches]
Sweet dreams.
Did your mom live near Red Rocks?
Red what?
Looks like a place
George and I used to go to hear music,
back before you kids were born.
When we had a life. [chuckles]
We liked music
almost as much as you, apparently.
Red Rocks.
Good night, Gus.
It was nice to meet you.
We want to talk with you both
in the morning, okay?
Oh!
- I wasn't expecting that.
- Yeah, it's creepy.
- Good night, boys.
- Night, boys.
[melancholic music playing]
[thunder rumbling]
[door opens]
[Gus] Big Man.
I couldn't sleep, either.
Are we leaving?
[thunder rumbling]
Oh.
[ambient sound intensifies]
[footsteps approaching]
[sinister music builds]
[thunder rumbling]
[panting] There's more.
How many?
[panting, sniffing]
A lot. I can't smell in the rain.
[suspenseful music playing]
[gun clicking]
[gun cocking]
[Gus panting]
[Last Man 1] Can I have your attention?
- George.
- Oh, what was that?
[Last Man 1]
We are not here for you or your family.
But we have reason to believe
that you are harboring an animal child.
- Rusty.
- Now, that gives us the right to come in.
Rusty.
[Last Man 1] Under Abbot's code,
we have the right to search your home.
Or, you can surrender
the hybrid peacefully.
- And no one will get hurt.
- Gus, come here.
- You have to the count of three...
...to turn the child over.
One...
two...
Okay, then.
Three!
- [metal weapon clanging]
- [Last Man 2 grunting]
[metal weapon clanging]
- [metal weapon clanging]
- [Last Man 3 grunting]
- [Last Men grunting]
- [Jepperd grunting]
- [metal weapon clanging]
[Last Man 4 grunting]
[Jepperd grunting]
- [weapon whooshing]
- [Last Man 5 grunting]
[Jepperd grunting]
- [Last Man 6 grunting]
- [body clattering]
[Jepperd grunting]
[suspenseful music playing]
Come here, little freak.
You think you're safe out here?
Well, I got news for you.
We'll always find you.
[sinister music playing]
[thunder rumbling]
- [sling shot whooshing]
- [ammunition rattling]
Cute.
You like hanging around dead animals, boy?
How about I make you one?
[Gus] Ah!
- [Gus] Ah!
- [Last Man 1 yelping]
[breathing heavily]
[lightening cracking]
[sinister music builds]
- [Last Man 1 grunting]
- [body clattering]
- [weapon clanging]
- [panting]
Whoa!
Thank you.
[breathing heavily]
[exhales]
Couple more for the road?
Listen, don't take it the wrong way.
He seems like a good kid. Just...
We gotta protect the family.
You're doing what you have to, to survive.
Gotta admit, it was awesome
to see you still got it, though, man.
- I was like, "Holy..."
- George!
[George] Right. [titters]
Yeah.
["If I Could See The World"
by Patsy Cline playing]
♪ If I could see the world ♪
♪ Through the eyes of a child... ♪
Sorry I called you weird.
It's okay.
Sorry about all the dead people.
It's cool.
I hope you find your mom.
Me too.
♪ With a bluebird in every tree ♪
♪ I could see right, no wrong ♪
♪ I could see good, no bad ♪
♪ I could see all the good things ♪
♪ In life I've never had ♪
♪ If I could see the world ♪
♪ Through the eyes of a child ♪
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
♪ This would be ♪
♪ If I could see the world ♪
♪ Through the eyes of a child ♪
♪ Smiling faces would greet me
All the while ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh... ♪
You don't have to help me
look for her. I can do it on my own.
I'll tell you what.
I'll get you to the next town,
and then we're done.
Then we go to Red Rocks?
Don't push it.
[narrator] For the first time in his life,
Gus was on a real adventure.
- [cable car creaking]
- [birds squawking]
But with every new adventure...
comes new dangers.
[ominous music playing]
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
- ♪ This would be ♪
- ♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
[narrator] Aimee, on the other hand,
was through with the outside world.
What she didn't know
was the outside world
wasn't through with her.
[distant clattering]
[suspenseful music playing]
[gentle music playing]
[baby cooing]
[orchestral music playing]