[whirring]
[pensive music playing]
[sirens ringing]
[helicopter whirring]
[ambient sounds]
[narrator] The Great Crumble
happened slowly at first.
But the cracks had been forming
for some time.
[man 1] Uh...
You sure that's okay, man?
Why wouldn't it be?
Well, uh, I'm pretty sure it's exactly
what we're not supposed to do, right?
According to who?
- Everyone.
- We're outside.
We've just disinfected
for, like, the tenth time today.
We're safe, all right?
Don't freak out, man.
That's what they want you to do.
- That's what who wants us to do?
- The government.
The anti-government. Big Pharma. Whoever.
You know, this stuff is, like,
1,000 times more deadly than the virus.
Do you have any idea what's in this?
No.
Exactly.
[vehicle buzzing]
Do you have any idea what's in that?
Open your eyes, man.
Can you at least put your mask back on?
It's the protocol.
- [blows]
- Ah!
Hey!
- All right, give me that!
- No! Don't... Get... Hey!
[dramatic music playing]
[both grunting, straining]
[man 1] Get off!
You've changed, Greg.
- You're so angry.
- You've changed.
- [car engine roaring]
- [man 1 yelling]
Hey. Hey, sorry. Sorry, man. Are you okay?
Couldn't you see me? I'm so yellow!
Sorry, but we are full here.
You're gonna have to turn this around.
- If you're sick, you have to stay home.
- Nobody's sick, she's having a baby!
- [indistinct chatter]
- [vehicle buzzing]
- [Jepperd] Excuse me. Hey. Please.
- [Louisa] Excuse me.
Okay, breathe. Breathe.
We'll do it together.
Move!
[monitors beeping]
[Jepperd] Wait, wait, wait.
- [officer 1] Sir! We're at capacity.
- Please let us up to the maternity ward.
- [officer 2] Sorry, man, I can't do that.
- Come on, man.
[Louisa breathing heavily]
Eighth floor.
- [Louisa breathing heavily]
- [reader beeps]
Go to the second desk,
you'll get in quicker.
Thank you. Thank you.
[Louisa] Oh, my God.
[Jepperd] It's okay.
[breathing heavily]
[Jepperd] It's okay, baby.
We got this.
I know you don't have any beds left,
but we don't have anywhere else...
- Who let you in?
- I don't know how else to do this.
Sir, you shouldn't be here.
Please. We don't have
anywhere else to go.
[nurse inhales, exhales]
Okay. We can take her.
Okay.
But you gotta stay here.
Fathers aren't allowed upstairs.
No, no, no. I gotta be with her.
- Government rules, not mine.
- [Louisa] Tommy, it's good. Let me go.
- To hell with the rules.
- [breathing heavily]
Baby, this is the real world.
You can't fix everything
by knocking heads.
I thought that's why you married me.
[hopeful music playing]
I got this.
[melancholic music playing]
- What if it's...
- Shh. Don't be silly.
It's not gonna happen to us.
Are you sure, baby?
I need you to be strong for me right now.
- Can you do that for me?
- [breathing heavily]
Take a seat.
It's okay.
[Louisa sighs]
Okay, baby.
[Jepperd groans]
[indistinct TV announcement]
[reporter 1]
So many anti-hybrid protests in our area.
We go now live to one of those protests.
[reporter 2] Even as we see
the H5G9 numbers skyrocket,
the rising cases of hybrid children
have captured the country's attention.
[narrator] The thing that should have
brought us together
only pulled us further apart.
[suspenseful music playing]
We felt scared.
We felt... alone.
[Jepperd] Gus!
Gus, come on, man. Come back!
[Bear] He's not out front, either.
I've been through all the woods.
It's like a maze.
You get turned around real easy.
Imagine how he feels.
Everything you've been told
your whole life is one big lie.
I don't know, man. Maybe
we shouldn't have brought him here.
No, we did the right thing.
There's nothing worse than not knowing.
That never goes away.
[Bear] Did you have any idea?
No.
Didn't have "test-tube baby"
on my bingo card.
Did you see the dates on those photos?
Gus was born way before the others.
Yeah, I noticed.
- What if...
- Don't say it.
What if Gus was the first?
Yeah, but why do you think they did it?
Why did they make
a deer-kid baby, in a lab?
To see if they could.
Anyway, does it even change anything?
[birds chirping]
It does, doesn't it?
I've spent my entire life thinking
hybrids were a miracle of nature.
[scoffs]
I formed an army who believed it too.
[melancholic music playing]
At least you believed in something.
Stay here. See what else you can find.
I'll track down Gus.
Hell no. I'm coming with you.
Someone needs to wait here
in case he comes back.
Fine.
But be gentle with him,
or I'll kick your ass.
[pensive music playing]
- [birds squawking]
- [Gus panting]
Stupid book!
Stupid slingshot.
Stupid Dog.
Stupid bag.
[emotional music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[ambient sounds intensify]
[radio signal whooshing]
- [tense music playing]
- [radio signal whooshing]
[propellers screeching]
[radio signal whooshing]
[radio interference buzzing]
- [radio signal whooshing]
- [music swells]
- [footsteps splashing]
- [hybrids cooing]
Stop.
- [machinery whirring]
Don't make a sound.
[ominous music playing]
[footsteps marching]
[Bobby gasps] Uh-oh!
- [tanks whirring]
- [indistinct radio chatter]
- [tank whirring]
- [glass shattering]
[indistinct yelling]
[signal rattling]
[music intensifies]
[indistinct yelling]
[guns cocking]
[music builds]
[General Abbot on radio]
Testing. Testing. Hello and good evening.
[suspenseful music playing]
I am trying to reach
the lady of the house.
[radio buzzes]
[feedback echoing]
[Aimee on radio] Speaking.
[radio buzzes]
Aimee Eden.
Collector of mongrels.
I've been following your work here
for some time now.
Do you have any idea who I am?
[radio buzzes]
An asshole with a tank?
[clicks tongue]
I am the man who'll be giving you
your own little chapter
in the history books one day, Ms. Eden.
How that chapter ends,
that's entirely up to you.
Does the name "Laika"
mean anything to you?
She was a lucky dog,
a mutt from the streets of Moscow.
The Soviets launched Laika into
outer space in the name of science.
She never made it back.
Bummer.
But had it not been
for our sweet little Laika,
humans would never
have traveled to the stars.
You've collected quite a few Laikas
in your little zoo, haven't you?
I'm gonna stop you right there.
Whatever it is you're selling,
the answer's no.
[radio buzzes]
I probably didn't make myself clear.
My friends and I, we're not leaving.
And did I mention
I have brought a few friends?
There are only two goals
when it comes to these little freaks:
extermination and experimentation.
The problem is,
if you're really, really good
at the extermination part,
we find ourselves with
nowhere near the numbers we need
to experiment on these little rodents.
That's where you come in.
Allow me to be clear.
- [feedback echoing]
- [loudly] Go away.
What's your name, military guy?
[indistinct chatter]
Douglas Abbot,
but you can call me General.
You're a dinosaur, Abbot.
You're already extinct,
you just don't want to admit it.
Mankind's best days
are yet to come, I assure you.
- [radio beeping]
- No.
It's the children's turn now,
and it's our job to get out of their way.
[radio buzzes]
They're a mutation,
an invasive pest.
If not for some cruel trick of nature,
they do hold something
of a key to our survival.
That's why we're here.
[radio buzzes, beeps]
No.
They're better than us.
Better than you or me.
They're the good part of us.
Without the complications.
Nature doesn't want us back.
We never gave her a good reason
to keep us around in the first place.
["Für Elise" playing from jewelry box]
Do you miss fireworks, Abbot?
Who doesn't?
- ["Für Elise" continues]
- Disfruta, cabrón.
[fireworks crackling]
[dramatic music playing]
- Go!
Come on. Come on.
- [fireworks whooshing]
- [Last Man 1 shouts indistinctly]
[General Abbot grunts]
[hybrids vocalize]
- [fireworks banging]
- [Last Man 2 screaming]
[fireworks whooshing, banging]
[General Abbot breathing heavily]
[yells] Take her!
[glass shattering]
[door clattering]
[General Abbot] Hunt her down.
Make her regret that.
[Last Man] Yes, sir.
You two. Over here. Let's go.
[indistinct chatter]
[manhole cover scraping]
[breathing heavily]
[sniffing]
[Pigtail exhales]
[Bobby grunts]
[hybrids cooing]
Everybody, stay put till Mom comes.
Terrence, wait in the tunnel for Henry.
He's super slow.
Everybody stick together.
[sputtering] Scared.
Look, I'm scared too.
- [Bobby sniffs]
- The Preserve is our home.
But the important thing is, we're safe.
She's gonna be here any minute.
[hybrids cooing]
She promised she will come.
I believe in her.
[hybrids vocalizing]
Good.
Bobby?
Bobby...
Bobby? Bobby?
Bobby. Bob...
Bobby, no.
[ominous music playing]
- [Bobby breathes heavily]
- [guns cocking]
[sighs]
- [Last Man 1] What is that thing?
- [Last Man 2] It's one of them.
- [Last Man 3] Bag it.
- [Bobby gasps]
[Bobby straining]
- [Last Man 3] All right. Come on.
- [Bobby] No!
[Last Man 3] Easy. Here.
- Where do you want this thing?
- [Last Man 1] Bring it to the cages.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[music builds]
Nice try.
[Pigtail panting]
[Pigtail screaming]
- [Last Man grunting]
- [screaming continues]
[man on PA] We need all medics to medical.
I need all medics to medical.
[brakes screeching]
[Rani] Where are we?
Welcome to your new home.
Watch your step.
Let's go.
Let's get you down.
[indistinct chatter on PA]
Rani?
- [clattering]
- [indistinct radio chatter]
[vocalizes]
Rani?
Rani, I'm here.
[cries] Rani, I'm here. Rani!
[General Abbot] She can't hear you.
She can't see you, for that matter.
We sealed her in from us.
[ominous music playing]
But more importantly,
us from her.
I told you she wasn't contagious.
Yeah, I know.
But not everyone is
as aware of her unique condition.
[General Abbot groans]
Plus you and I both know
how rapidly this virus can adapt.
Right?
Welcome!
I want you to know that
you will have everything you want here.
Any half-breed you can imagine.
Anything you need, just snap your fingers
and we will find a way to get it to you.
I want my wife.
You don't have to motivate me,
you animal!
[Dr. Singh grunts, strains]
- [Dr. Singh yells, strains]
- [Last Men panting]
[Dr. Singh sobs]
[General Abbot] Are you done?
[Dr. Singh panting]
Cut the shit, Singh.
There's a new wave of the Sick coming.
Dr. Bell predicted it,
and my ears on the coast confirm as much.
It's just a matter of time. So...
I don't just want any cure.
I want the only cure.
And I want all of it.
[inhales, clears throat]
I... I never guaranteed I could,
um, I could make one.
I... I know.
You were bluffing to save yourselves. Duh.
Find me a cure with enough doses,
so I can decide who lives and who doesn't.
And then your little bird
can just fly out of her cage.
Do we have a deal?
[door clicks, creaks]
Wendy?
Wen...
[exhales] Wendy?
[screaming]
[Jepperd] Hey, Gus!
Aw, man. Come on, come back.
[birds chirping]
[nurse] Mr. Jepperd?
Mr. Jepperd?
Is it okay?
It's a boy.
[patient coughs]
Is... Is it human?
He and his mom are healthy and resting.
Congratulations.
Is it human?
[nurse] Would you like to see him?
They're just running
some last tests on your wife,
and then she can come and join you both.
Take your time.
[melancholic music playing]
[monitor beeping]
[baby cooing]
[cooing continues]
[Jepperd breathing heavily]
[music builds]
[doors clattering]
[inaudible screaming]
[inaudible crying]
- [Dr. Singh sighs]
- [Jepperd panting]
What kind is it?
Huh?
Your baby, what kind?
I don't know.
It was one of those things.
[inhales, exhales]
I don't know if I can do this.
Hey.
Hey!
You'll be surprised
what you're capable of
when it's for someone you love.
- [melancholic music playing]
- [stunted breathing]
[elevator door opens]
Good luck.
[heart beating]
[music builds to climax]
[flashlight whirring]
[somber music playing]
[sighs]
[flashlight whirring]
[Judy]
No sign of them, and it's been a while.
[sighs]
I'm gonna put out these porch lights.
What was really going on at Fort Smith?
That's another lifetime ago.
Why did they make Gus?
How did you do it?
[sighs]
Well, Gus was all Birdie.
But Fort Smith wasn't just about Gus.
I know.
It was about the virus too, wasn't it?
Why does it matter now?
What does the virus
have to do with kids like Gus?
[melancholic music playing]
[inhales] I once heard her say
they were two sides of the same coin.
But she wouldn't tell me
any more than that.
So why have you been
protecting her work for all these years?
[Judy] Because she was my best friend.
She was family to me.
Like a sister.
When she left me here...
Well, I had nowhere else to go.
[exhales] I mean, do you have
any idea what that's like?
Yes.
I know exactly what that's like.
[propeller screeching]
[Gus] I'm not coming back.
[emotional music playing]
[Jepperd sighs]
[Jepperd grunts]
Hey.
Stick together.
You lose that thing,
you'll regret it the rest of your life.
You broke all your gold men.
And look how I turned out.
I'd keep this stuff.
That's all you got of your dad.
What dad?
I don't have one.
I don't have anyone.
Just me.
I never should have crossed the fence.
I should have just stayed in the woods.
None of this would have ever happened.
None of what?
[Gus sighs]
Everything.
Everything's stupid.
Everyone wants to kill me.
Everyone lies.
Well, he did his best.
Then why couldn't he
just tell me the truth?
Being honest
is hard sometimes.
All that stuff back in the attic, at least
we know one thing he said was true.
You're a special kid.
I don't want to be special.
I want to be like everyone else.
I want to be with kids like me.
You said they were out there.
I'm gonna go to the Preserve.
Because I'm sick of being the weird one.
If there's anyone out there like me,
I wanna meet 'em.
I wanna see what they're like.
You know,
back when everything was falling apart...
I had a little baby.
A lot like you.
When I saw him,
I had no clue what to do with him.
I didn't even know what he was.
I mean, nobody knew
what to think in those days.
I mean, how could I be responsible
for a little, I mean...
So I wanted to run away too.
What happened?
Oh, I thought about it.
[inhales]
And I realized I was just scared.
I wasn't afraid of him.
I was afraid of me.
I think that fear was...
love that I didn't know what to do with.
But he needed me.
So I stopped running.
I turned around.
And I went back to get him.
Him and his mom.
[inhales] But they were already gone.
Someone had took 'em.
And I never saw them again.
[inhales]
I hurt a lot of people, Little Man.
Usually on purpose.
But sometimes I don't mean to hurt 'em.
Sometimes I just make bad decisions.
But you know what?
I think you're one of the good ones.
[inhales, exhales deeply]
Don't make me lose you too.
Come back with me.
And go where?
Anywhere we want.
What would we do?
Anything we want to do.
I could teach you stuff.
You can teach me...
What was that game called?
Pass the Ball?
That's the one.
We'll need a ball.
I think we can find one.
Maybe you can show me
how to make that syrup.
We need maple trees.
We'll find some.
Like, we need lots of them.
[Jepperd] We'll find a forest.
Maybe even live there.
Together?
Why do you think I'm here?
Can Bear come too?
I'll have to think about that one.
[both chuckle]
So, what should we say
to the Preserve when they get here?
What do you mean?
Don't get mad, but I kind of called them,
and they said that they were on their way.
Look, I fixed it.
[radio interference]
- [gunshot]
- [ambient sounds intensify]
Big Man! I heard a big boom!
[ominous music playing]
Big Man?
[screams] Big Man!
Big Man, wake up!
They're coming! They're here!
Big Man! Wake up! Big Man!
- [Gus whimpering]
- [music intensifies]
[Gus screams]
[Gus whimpering]
[Gus yelling]
[Abbot] He was one of us.
Traitor.
A disgrace to humanity.
[Gus whimpering]
[cage rattling]
- Come on, let's go!
- [emotional music playing]
[engine rumbling]
[man on PA] Incoming hybrid has arrived.
Prepare for receiving.
- [ominous music playing]
- [Gus panting]
[Last Man] Here's the info for this one.
[tools rattling]
- Hey, little bud.
- [Gus panting]
[Johnny] You okay in there?
Just a little longer, man.
- [General Abbot] Johnny!
- [Johnny] Yeah.
[Abbot] I thought I asked you
to clean the kennels.
[Johnny] Yes. Sorry, boss.
[blade shinking]
[music builds]
[Last Man] Start with this one.
Ready in five.
[whispering]
Don't let them know you can talk.
What I'm about to do
goes against everything that I believe in.
But I'm doing it for her.
[sniffs]
And we have very little time left.
- [Dr. Singh inhales]
- [distant yelling]
[whispering] My God.
[exhales]
They really are a wonder, these things.
Um...
It's, uh...
It's older than the others.
More human.
[exhales]
It's...
That?
[titters]
Thanks.
[shutter screeching, rattling]
Abbot's ready for you.
Got everything you put on your list.
It's all sharpened and laid out
just how you want it.
- Where did you find this one?
- [Johnny] Just arrived.
Someone called it in.
Are you...
Are you a superstitious man?
Trust me.
You don't want to keep him waiting.
When I graduated medical school,
Rani gave me a little statue
of the goddess of learning, as a gift.
[tense music playing]
Do you know what animal form
she once appeared as?
A deer?
A red deer.
Bring me another patient.
I want more time with this one.
- He's not gonna like that.
- Johnny!
[ominous music playing]
That's your name, right?
He won't know
because you're not going to tell him.
[kettle whistling]
- [Judy] Any sign of them?
- Not yet.
I should have gone with him.
He must be scared out there on his own.
You make a good team, you three.
Yeah, well, we did.
If I ever see them again.
What's your name, sweetie?
I told you.
It's Bear.
I know.
But no loving parent
names their child Bear.
[chuckles] So, what's your real name?
Look, I know we burst
into your life out of the blue,
but I'm not looking to make friends.
How old were you when it happened?
[tape ripping]
I was six.
I don't remember much, so...
And your family?
My foster parents were killed
in cold blood by Last Men.
[melancholic music playing]
I'm sorry.
You don't have to talk about it.
No, it's...
It's fine.
The truth is, no one killed them.
They just went like everyone else.
They got sick.
And they had a baby too.
My little sister.
She was a hybrid.
But people came to take her away,
and I was too little to stop them.
[inaudible screaming]
Where did you go?
I was alone.
For a long time.
I stayed away from humans.
And I tried to find my sister,
but I never could.
So I gave up.
I hated adults.
And then I met someone like me,
who'd been through what I went through.
I called her Tiger.
She called me Bear.
We made a family of kids like us.
Till she betrayed me.
And then I was alone again.
My name's Becky.
Rebecca Walker.
But my parents called me
their little Becky Bear.
[titters]
[Judy]
You can't give up on your sister, Becky.
If Gus can make it back here
after all these years,
you never know what you can find
if you look hard enough.
[phone beeping]
[Bear] Holy shit!
[propeller screeching]
[engine rumbling]
["Auld Lang Syne" playing]
♪ Should auld acquaintance be forgot... ♪
[narrator] The boy had forgotten
what it meant to be hidden
from the outside world.
[door slams]
But this fence was different.
This time, he wasn't truly alone.
♪ And days of auld lang syne? ♪
♪ We twa hae run about the braes ♪
♪ And pu'd the gowans fine ♪
♪ We've wandered many a weary foot... ♪
[Johnny] Ready, Dr. Singh?
Ready.
[tool whirring]
♪ From morning sun till dine... ♪
[fire crackling]
- [phone beeps]
- [interference buzzes]
♪ Since auld lang syne ♪
♪ And there's a hand my trusty friend! ♪
♪ And give us a hand o' thine! ♪
♪ We'll take
A right guid willie-waught... ♪
[narrator] Sometimes,
everything we thought we'd lost...
was right there all along.
When things fall apart,
we find out who we really are.
♪ We'll take a cup of kindness yet... ♪
[Aimee] Take it easy.
Who are you?
Get some sleep.
Heal up.
Tomorrow we get our kids back.
[radio buzzes]
[man on radio]
We got a full squad at the aviary, sir.
Got a suspicious cargo and another moving
forward to the perimeter fence down at...
[narrator] If we can see past the fear,
we find out what really matters.
And we learn that sometimes,
the things that set us apart...
can also bring us together.
[hybrids vocalizing]
♪ For auld lang syne, my dear ♪
♪ For auld lang syne ♪
♪ We'll take a cup of kindness yet ♪
[hopeful music playing]
Hi.
I'm Wendy.
Hi, I'm Gus.
[hybrid] Gus.
[hybrids cooing]
[exhales]
[narrator]
Because family is what we make it.
[hybrids vocalizing]
[narrator] Each one of us.
Together.
[music swells]
[phone ringing]
- [wind whistling]
- [phone continues ringing]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [door opens]
- [wind gushing]
[exhales]
[phone beeping]
- [phone line static buzzes]
- Hello?
Who are you?
[music builds to climax]
[dramatic music playing]