=City of Streamer=
=Episode 33=
To enjoy the high position
and great wealth of our family,
they must take the responsibility
it comes with,
either making great efforts
or contributing themselves.
Our family
doesn't support useless people.
What about Mrs. Bai
who married you before my mother?
She bore a son and a daughter for you.
Just because she got in your way
of marrying up,
you must have
killed her and her children?
What did Zhao Hua'an tell you?
There seem to be
a lot of things he didn't tell me.
Is he
still seeing Ma'am?
I don't know.
If you want to know,
I can call her in.
That awful woman!
I've had many women in my life.
Now I'm getting into such a plight.
Only your mother
was the nicest
and gentlest to me.
About Mrs. Bai,
it was complicated.
Zhao Hua'an and Huang Shujun
both have sinister motives
and harbor evil intentions.
Son.
You are my real
flesh and blood.
How can you turn against me
in cahoots with outsiders?
I'm not against you.
Father.
I'm saving you.
I'm correcting the past.
I'm making up for the past.
In the future, I don't want
another man like Meng Xu'an
to jump out at intervals
to wreak vengeance on us!
I want to smoke opium.
It's bad for your health.
I don't want to live long.
No!
If you let me smoke,
I'll tell you
about Mrs. Bai.
Tell me.
After I married Bai,
I came to Shanghai to do business
and seldom went home.
Hating to be neglected,
she had an affair
and had a son and a daughter
with a man.
I wouldn't acknowledge them,
so she took the children
and ran away with the man.
On their way…
On their way,
I don't know if they ran into bandits
or the man went back on his word.
Anyway,
they all got killed.
What about their children?
They all got killed.
Just leave if you finished asking.
Don't bother me again.
Father.
Were Mrs. Bai's children
really not yours?
No.
Whose children were they?
They were Rong Dingkun's.
Then who are you?
I'm Rong Dingkun
from Guojia Town.
I was born on March 4, 1884.
My pet name was Guangge.
My father was Rong Youde.
I got it. Stop!
Father.
You mentioned before
that Mrs. Bai's children
were your brother's.
Where is he now?
Vanished.
I did it myself...
You'll never find him again.
What did you say?
Father.
What did you do?
Who was the man exactly?
He.
He?
You'll never find He again.
He.
You knew I was desperate.
Why didn't you help me?
If you made allowances for me,
I wouldn't have done that.
You made me do it!
Father.
Who was He?
Father!
You made me do it…
Give us a minute.
Yang Xiucheng is back.
He found the clue about…
about your parentage.
Hello, Miss Feng.
Miss Feng.
Long time no see.
Hello, Mr. Yang.
So,
take your time.
I'll leave you alone.
I must apologize
to you and your family
for what happened in Wenchunli.
I didn't mean
to act as the paws of the tiger,
but still, I'm guilty.
I'm such a villain.
I deserve to be despised by you.
But from now on,
if there's anything I can help with,
just tell me.
I'll be at your service
without complaining.
Mr. Yang, playing your strong points
and helping Mr. Meng
to topple the Rong Family
are enough to atone for this sin.
As for your other sins,
I'm in no position to put in a word.
Have a seat.
Mr. Meng told me
that you found the clue
about my parentage.
Yes.
Rong Dingkun
is actually not a Rong.
He's a Qin.
What did you say?
Zhao Hua'an has been
following Rong Dingkun
since he started his business.
He knows all the secrets of him.
I bought off
one of his trusted followers.
The man told me something.
Zhao Hua'an's daughter
got married the year before last.
At her wedding,
he was so drunk
that he said a lot of crappy things.
One of those was
Rong Dingkun was supposed to be
Qin Shuigen.
How did he become Rong Dingkun?
Did he change his name midway?
He seemed to have assumed
the identity of Rong Dingkun
from the beginning.
He is probably not my biological father.
Were Zhao Hua'an's words credible?
It's said, "In wine there is truth."
I think they were credible.
All immediate family of Rong Dingkun,
his parents,
grandparents and siblings,
died of a plague.
But the local elders told me
that the Rong Family lived
outside the town,
sheltering at home.
They were fine all the time,
then Rong Dingkun
went home with the bodies
of his wife and children
who died of the plague,
bringing them with the disease.
That whole family
was infected with it and died.
Only Rong Dingkun,
who had taken western medicine,
was safe and sound.
You mean,
to disguise himself,
he killed the whole family?
That's my guess.
Over the past 20 years,
Rong Dingkun has never
been in touch with the rest relatives
of the Rong Family.
He'd rather put the children of
the Huang Family in important positions
than promote the people
of the Rong Family.
Isn't that strange?
You're right.
He has a guilty conscience
and dare not meet
with the people of the Rong Family.
Right.
If he was to hide
behind a false identity,
why was it Rong Dingkun?
Where is
the real Rong Dingkun?
I'll dig deep.
Mr. Yang,
thanks for your information.
I'm glad
it's helpful.
I want to correct my mistakes.
I hope Rong Dingkun
gets the punishment he deserves.
May I ask
what Mr. Meng will give you in return?
If I help him to absorb the Rong Family,
he'll give me their transportation line
to Taiwan.
That's a generous reward.
Miss Feng,
what's your plan next?
If the war is to be declared,
I'm afraid you and Jiashang...
We're done.
He seems
to mistake me for his sister.
But it's better this way.
Let him think like that.
Whatever the truth is,
we have no future.
So he got it.
Still talking?
You're back.
Come on. Let me carry it.
- You must be tired.
- Gotta go.
- OK. See you.
- See you.
See you.
(Red House Hospital)
Have you had lunch?
Yes.
Haven't you had yet?
Don't be too late, or there will be
no braised chicken legs.
Got it. I'm going now.
(Municipal Junior Primary School)
They're out.
- Here they are.
I'm here.
- Mom.
- I'm here.
- This way.
- Be careful.
- Mom.
- Come.
Mom.
Come on.
Let's go.
Come.
Shizhen,
don't wait.
Your brother probably
went home.
He wouldn't.
He promised me.
OK, then.
(Municipal Junior Primary School)
Shizhen.
Shixun.
Come on, let's go home.
Yeah.
Sorry, I'm late.
I hear
you apply to the hospital
for taking a family member abroad.
The news has spread among the nurses.
It's my sister.
I'm going to take her with me.
Your sister?
Isn't she teaching at Peking?
The scholarship
is generous enough
for the two of us
to live abroad.
I have
chosen a good college for her.
She is very intelligent.
I'm sure she'll get a master's degree.
I've never seen a brother
who loves his sister so much.
I'm afraid your future wife
wouldn't get along with your sister.
I have no plans to get married for now.
(Wenchunli)
Miss, do you want to buy a house?
The new houses
are built by the Rong Company.
They're all detached houses,
with four bedrooms,
two bathrooms
and the latest drainage.
Have all the old houses
been torn down?
Not yet.
There,
at the west corner,
there is an old house.
It isn't badly burned.
Somehow,
it hasn't been demolished.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Almost 60%
of the houses here have been sold.
Go along the street, you'll find
the river at the third turning.
When the port is completed…
Very good.
…private boats can...
And...
Jiashang,
what's wrong?
Nothing.
Sorry, where were we?
The port.
It will be a civilian port
with 80 to 100 berths.
The supporting shops
and hotel apartments
are all under construction.
Jiashang,
do you like sailing?
My uncle gave me a new yacht.
It was launched last month.
I'd have a cocktail party on it
with my schoolmates and friends.
Will you come?
Thanks for your kind invitation.
But,
I'm a little afraid of water.
I seldom go to the sea.
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
Hello?
Mr. Rong. Hello.
This is Peking Hotel.
About the hairy crabs
we've been keeping for you,
since Miss Feng never came again,
do you still want to keep them?
Keep them.
Yes.
Hello? Who's calling?
Hello.
May I talk to Miss Feng
on the third floor?
Miss Feng?
She isn't here.
Where is she?
I have no idea.
She left in a hurry
and didn't say goodbye to us.
When did she leave?
About two days ago.
She left early in the morning
with a suitcase.
OK, I see.
Thanks.
Secretary Chen.
Young master.
Trace the whereabouts
of Feng Shizhen right away.
Yes.
Young master,
is something wrong
with Miss Feng?
I suspect
that she has returned to Shanghai.
How could she be in Shanghai?
Isn't Miss Feng
teaching in Peking?
Send your men
to look for her all over Shanghai,
especially at Meng Xu'an's place.
Once you find her,
tell me immediately.
Yes.
What's wrong?
What happened out there?
You seem to be in a bad mood.
Is it because of your aunt?
I tell you what,
you can ask her at dinner.
Let's see what she'll say.
OK.
Be my guest.
Help yourself.
OK.
I just
had the kitchen cook several dishes.
I wonder if they're to your taste.
How would they not be?
Shanghai cuisines
are known to be delicate.
I'm lucky to enjoy them.
Here.
Thanks.
Aunt,
my father...
I know you want to know
what happened to your parents.
I've searched my memory.
I'll tell you everything I remember.
The Rong Family
was rich in their early years.
Later, the harvest
got worse year by year.
Actually, before you were born,
their life had already become hard.
Most of the farmhands were fired.
Your father was far-sighted.
He didn't want to rely on
the several acres of land.
He wanted to go out.
He took
about 50 silver dollars
and went to Shanghai
with some fellow-townsmen
to do business.
Why didn't my mother come with him?
She conceived you
soon after they were married.
So she stayed in Guojia Town.
What did my father do for a living
after he came to Shanghai?
He did...
I don't know it well.
He seemed to buy some
inferior imported goods on a dock
and go round the streets to sell them.
Later, he rented a shop
with one of his friends.
Their business was much better.
But it didn't last long.
His friend owed money,
so he pledged the shop
in order to pay debts for his friend.
Did my father
often help his friends?
He was very helpful.
He had many friends.
When he arrived in Shanghai,
he rented a house
with several friends at Shikumen.
One of his friends had a big family.
So he gave up the big sunlit room
to his friend.
He lived in the garret instead.
Because of that,
my sister often complained
that he was too honest
and he might get the worst of it.
Though your parents often lived
in two places,
they loved each other very much.
Fangzhen,
I hear
your father is now
the richest man in Shanghai.
Why don't you go to see him?
If he knew you were alive,
he would be so happy.
Yes.
Ms. Qian.
You said Rong Dingkun
made a lot of money
and became rich.
How did he make the money?
He hit the jackpot.
My sister wrote to me about it.
Did his friends at Shikumen
know about it?
I'm not sure about it.
But they lived in the same house.
Those who were
close with him must know.
Of all his friends,
did anyone look like him?
Yes,
there was one, actually.
When he arrived in Shanghai,
he saved a man
who was about to kill himself.
He paid the man's debt for him.
My sister blamed him
for spending money recklessly.
He said
the man looked very like him.
He thought they had a bond.
Later, they even
became sworn brothers.
Aunt,
do you remember that man's name?
Was it
Qin Shuigen?
Name?
I don't remember.
I think he was a bricklayer.
Because your parents
quarreled over him.
Your father said
the man got a job fixing roofs.
He would pay back the money.
My husband was fixing roofs, too.
So I remember it clearly.
He.
I...
Didn't I bury you?
Why do you come again?
Don't keep pestering me.
Go away.
Mr. Meng.
It occurs to me!
It occurs to me
when I heard the name He.
Calm down.
Take your time.
I once approached Rong Dingkun
after he smoked opium
in order to steal his seal.
He was clouded in mind
and mistook me for He.
He kept yelling at me,
begging me not to take revenge on him.
He almost had a meltdown.
Look at the evidence Mr. Yang found.
This is Rong Dingkun's
medical examinations.
(Medical Examinations of Rong Dingkun)
It records in detail
Rong Dingkun's condition.
His legs were never broken.
There are no signs of healing
of the bones.
(Medical Examinations of Rong Dingkun)
(The upper and lower limb bones
are intact without traces of healing.)
That's the truth.
Aunt said my father
was honest,
kind,
loyal to his friends,
and loved my mother very much.
But Rong Dingkun
is suspicious,
has lots of women,
and traffics arms and opium.
He is a devil.
That's enough to prove
they're two different men.
Though they were unrelated,
they looked so alike
that one could
take the place of the other
and win his relatives' trust.
He could intimate
the accent and behavior,
but
they were still two different men.
So all of the Rong Family
suddenly fell ill and died.
My mother died miserably.
People who were close
to the real Rong Dingkun
and could tell the true from the false
all died.
It's easy to explain.
You would think
the one who killed your mother
was your father.
I remember it was dark
in cold winter.
If a man who looked like my father
changed his appearance a bit with,
for example, a beard or a hat,
my mother was likely to mistake him.
If it were me,
I would kill your mother
before she knew.
An injured girl falling into a river
was the most hopeless.
And the little baby
was even easier to get rid of.
I began to remember things at that time.
He had to kill me.
But my brother
was just a baby.
He might...
He might be still alive.
Even though Rong Dingkun
is extremely violent and wicked,
he wouldn't have killed a baby.
Miss Feng, don't worry.
Tomorrow morning, I'll look into
if Rong Dingkun had given away a baby
or placed him with foster parents
around that time.
Mr. Yang,
I don't
quite agree with you.
Rong Dingkun…
Qin Shuigen.
Qin Shuigen didn't hesitate
to kill the entire Rong Family.
How would he care about a baby?
I'm going to see Qin Shuigen.
I'm going to ask him
where he hid my father's body.
Over the past 20 years,
my father has been accused
of killing his wife and children.
If he knew about it in heaven,
how painful would he feel?
(Medical Examinations of Rong Dingkun)
I must find him
and clear his name.
Though Qin Shuigen
is disabled now,
he isn't an ordinary person
after all.
If we confront him hastily,
we may be led by the nose.
We'll be thrown into passivity.
So,
the priority
is to find your father's body.
Then we'll make him confess.
It's like looking for a needle
in a haystack.
It's been over 20 years.
Who knows where he hid the body?
Anyway,
I'll ask my men to look into it.
Help!
Master,
what's up?
There...
There is a man.
Master,
they are just clothes
and the clothes stand.
No one is here.
Master.
This is...?
(Tian Qian runs 40%)
You think I have no idea
(or more of his business in Shanghai...)
about what the old guys in the company
have concealed from me?
People
are always insatiable.
Give them an inch,
and they'll reach out for a yard.
After some time,
we'll always catch them tripping.
Make good use of it.
Retake Rong Company's ownership
as soon as possible.
But...
Jiashang...
Ignore him.
He's a family traitor.
You and I made the Rong empire.
I won't watch him ruin it.
Hua'an.
Yes?
You're my most trusted man.
Don't betray me.
Dingkun,
I've been following you for years.
I've long regarded you
as my own elder brother.
Of all people,
I'm the least likely to betray you.
Good.
Young master.
Miss Feng
has left Peking
and returned to Shanghai.
Where is she now?
She's
at the Meng's Residence.
Mr. Meng.
Rong Jiashang came.
He asked to see Miss Feng.
Where's Miss Feng?
She's in the study with Mr. Yang.
Don't disturb her.
You can leave now.
Yes.
Where is Shizhen?
Why are you so sure she is here?
We both know it.
Stop playing games.
Since you know everything,
why don't you ask yourself
what right do you have to see her?
If you have the time,
you'd better go ask your father
what he had done.
What do you mean?
The photo…
Shizhen has seen it.
Meng Xu'an!
Get off him!
Don't get too worked up.
There are some things
that you just can't pretend
they've never happened.
Walk him out.
Meng Xu'an!
How is it going?
Mr. Meng,
we've overlooked
very important information.
When Qin Shuigen mistook me for He,
he said
he buried He with his own hands.
In that case,
my father's body must be somewhere.
But Shanghai is such a big city.
Your father's body
could be buried anywhere.
No.
The body was too important.
Qin Shuigen wouldn't
dispose of it carelessly.
He is very paranoid.
He killed my father
and took his identity.
Over the past 20 years,
he's been scared.
He's scared of my father.
He's scared of my father's ghost
coming back to demand his life.
Qin Shuigen did a lot of bad things.
He would make sure again and again
that his secret
couldn't be found out.
He probably buried the body
in a place
that under his own control,
nobody can find
and he can check on it
at any time.
Only in this way would he feel at ease.
The Rong Family
has many enemies in Shanghai.
Everyone wants to dig up their scandals.
Such a big secret
can never fall into the hands of others.
Therefore,
he must have buried your father's body
in his own territory.
20 years ago,
Qin Shuigen took
My father's lottery ticket.
At that time, he had no foundation
and no business
in Shanghai.
I remember, in his files,
the first properties he bought
were two warehouses.
(Wenchunli)
They should be near the water-gate.
Later, he married Mrs. Tang,
bought a house and a shop
and started a company.
Two years later,
he bought a piece of land,
on which he built
the Rong's Residence.
He shouldn't have buried the body
in his own residence.
Where would it be?
The warehouses are in use all the time.
It's inconvenient to hide a body there.
Guojia Town is too far away.
Besides, in a small town in the country,
any rustle of leaves in the wind
would attract attention.
What if we reason it reversely
and start with the clues
concerning my father?
Didn't my aunt say
when my father was in Shanghai,
he bought goods on a dock?
He should have lived nearby the dock.
I remember it.
Behind Wenchunli
was a small dock.
When I was a child,
I used to watch freighters
unloading there.
If
this friend my father mentioned
in his letter
who borrowed money from him
was Qin Shuigen,
they should have lived together.
So they must be near the dock.
There are many docks in Shanghai.
Why are you sure it's the dock
behind Wenchunli?
Because Qin Shuigen
set fire to that one.
It occurs to me
that the Rong Family
owns a property in Wenchunli.
They didn't buy it after the fire.
They've owned it since before.
Is it an old house
located near
a sweet-scented osmanthus tree
at a distance of 20 or 30 paces?
A house of an arched iron gate
with two stories
and iron fences
both upstairs and downstairs.
I only went there once after the fire.
I don't recall it clearly.
But it really is a two-story house.
The other houses around it
have all been torn down.
Qin Shuigen wouldn't
have this one demolished.
He only let the workers
repaint its wall.
He wouldn't let the workers in.
Yes.
I thought it was weird,
so I asked Zhao Hua'an.
He told me
it was the place where Rong Dingkun
lived before he made a fortune
in his early years.
He had emotional ties for it,
so he bought it
to mourn for the past.
He kept everything the same
in the house.
He also fitted a new big iron gate on.
Right.
It was the place.
They were together at that time.
They did business together.
They rented the house together.
Later on,
Qin Shuigen
killed my father
for a lottery ticket.
I suddenly remember a clue.
I thought it had nothing to do with it.
Now thinking about it, it's relevant.
The Zhang Family,
the real estate mogul in Shanghai,
once offered to buy Wenchunli.
But the negotiation had just begun
before Qin Shuigen stepped in.
He was afraid
people would know about the house,
so he rushed into absorbing Wenchunli
by setting fire to it.
But that's the only house
he dare not touch
because my father
is buried in there.
♪The aftertaste of love lingers♪
♪Hatred snaps roses in two♪
♪Tear-like drizzle seems fine♪
♪Where's the key to one's heart♪
♪Who knows what lies ahead♪
♪The moon isn't lonelier than us♪
♪Sitting alone to see
begonias in the breeze♪
♪I still remember our dance♪
♪I remember the way you looked at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away thick leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪I remember the way you smiled at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away innocent leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪And trust each other completely♪
♪However time flies♪
♪We're destined to love♪
♪And cherish each other♪