Dude
I have no idea what's going on between them
But
Pete won't come and check on him?
They used to love each other so much
What did you just say?
I said
You're just
An unloved child
Why didn’t you go to the party with mom?
Did she report that to her favorite son?
It’s you
You’re the son that she loves most
Don’t make me laugh
It’s because you’re not free today
That’s why she told me to come
You’re overthinking
How can she love a stepson like me
more than her real son?
If you want to keep acting
Do it somewhere else
I’m sick of it
You’re always like this
You should pay more attention to your family
Just do whatever you want
Someday
I will tear off your mask
That day won’t come
What did you just say?
I said
You are
An unloved child
He’s not disgusting…
But he called me an unloved child, didn’t he?
♪I used to tell you♪
♪That we could never be more than friends♪
♪We can only be friends♪
♪That's what we are♪
♪When I said that I don't love you, I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us to be just friends anymore♪
♪This time, you won't be sad♪
♪We will get through it together♪
♪From now on, let me take care of you♪
♪Tomorrow or whenever, our love will be everlasting♪
♪When I said that I don't love you, I actually don't know♪
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
♪Can I change it? I don't want us to be just friends anymore♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true and honest to you♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true and honest to you♪
Can
What’s wrong?
Can!
No! I didn’t kiss!
What’s wrong?
No
Nothing’s wrong
That’s right
I’m eating breakfast
Are you sure?
Sure
I’m just eating my breakfast
Sure?
Sure
Alright everyone
You guys probably understand about this
About today...
What I wrote on the board...
Please wake your friend up
If he’s going to sleep then don’t disturb other people
Can
Can!
No! I didn’t kiss!
It seems like you really miss your girlfriend
Why don’t you just drop the class and stay with her?
I…I don’t have any girlfriend
Also, I don’t want to drop the class
Let’s continue with the class
Are you serious?
Can was daydreaming and yelling in the class?
You’re amazing
I’m serious
He suddenly yelled in class
Even though he likes to yell and annoy others
But today he’s even worse
I think he’s crazy
I’m not
I just…
I didn’t sleep that much last night
What did you do then?
Bro
I have something to think about
Someone like you?
Apart from eating
And talking too much
I don't think you've used your brain much
So, what were you thinking about?
Maybe I can help you
That’s right
Tell us
Maybe we can help
Why would I tell you guys?
I won’t say a word!
Wait, Can!
Damn it
I still don’t know who he kissed and turned him into this
Exactly
Who would want to kiss someone like Can?
Come on
Look at Techno
Someone already has eye on him
Someone might like Can too
Even though he’s talkative
But…
You cannot even think about other good things about him
Wait, Bro. What were you saying again?
Who has eye on Techno?
Why would I tell you?
You again?
I still didn’t clear things up for what you did
Do you know that my life is such a mess now?
My sister scolded at me
Teacher also told me to drop the class
My friends were laughing at me
Also…
You kissed me
Where’s the guy named Ae?
You’re Ae’s friend?
No
Huh?
There's no reason for me to be friend with a guy from Thai program
Hey!
Are you here to mess with my friend?
If you’re here to mess with him, I’ll punch you in the face first
Whatever
You’re all pathetic
I don’t like it when other people insult my friend
You can call me stupid, annoying, dirty
Just do it
But you have no rights to insult my friend
What’s your problem?
Why are you so hostile towards everyone?
Who made you become like this?
Did the world hurt you so badly that’s why you become like this?
Maybe I’m like what you said
I said many things
Which one are you referring to?
An unloved child
Are you crazy?
Do you want to die?
Are you too stupid to know that you’re not supposed to cut off like that?
I’m sorry
What?
Please
I’m sorry
I know that I just knew you
I shouldn’t call you an unloved child
I’m sorry
Please
Forgive me
But you started it first
You’re foul-mouthed
But I didn’t mean to blame it on you
It’s my fault
Please don’t be mad at me
Or else I won't be able to sleep tonight. I will have a nightmare for sure
I don’t want to hurt other people’s feelings
Please
Let’s make peace
What did you do?
You’re not mad at me anymore, right?
♪I don't know what this feeling is♪
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
It’s useless to be mad at you
I’m off
♪When I said that we're just friends, I actually understand now♪
Can
♪Can I change it? I don't want us to be just friends anymore♪
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true and honest to you♪
He can remember my name
♪I promise I will love you forever♪
♪and you will be with me forever♪
♪I promise I will always be true and honest to you♪
Oh my Buddha!
You scared the shit out of me
You’re crazy!
Uncle Tin
Why did you just come back?
I waited for you for such a long time
I miss you
I miss you too
Are you here alone?
Yes
Dad is not here. He’s still at work
Mom went out to see grandmother
I’m so lonely. I’m home alone
Phupha
You’re here
Don’t rush out just like that
I’m already old
I cannot keep up with you
Then don’t follow me
I didn’t ask you to do that
What does she mean by rushing out?
When you abruptly ran out of the room like that
No one’s home?
No one comes back yet
Vadee said she will go to another house first
She left Phupha with me
Everyone left me alone again
Don’t say that, Phupha
Come with me
I don’t want to
I want to stay with uncle Tin
Okay
I will take care of him
Thank you so much
Let’s go and play over there
Uncle Tin, it wasn't fun at all to hang out with mom
I wanted to come back home
I missed dad
I missed you too, uncle Tin
It’s so cold there
Why?
You didn’t have any friends there?
No
I don’t want any friends
I just want dad to hang out with me
Do you feel lonely?
How about you?
Should I be lonely?
Of course
If I'm not here with you
You must think of me, okay?
My hair is messy now
Really?
When will dad come back home?
Why?
Because I miss him
You love him a lot, don’t you?
I love him so much
I love him this much
I love dad so much
I like my name too
Because Phupha means
The love that I have for someone
That love is strong and eternal
Dad!
I miss you so much
I miss you too
Thank you, Tin
For what?
Taking care of my love
Have you eaten yet?
Yes
Why did I suddenly think of him?
I know now who he’s like
He’s like a 5 years old kid
Hello
I have something for you to search for me
Ae!
Stop it
Are you going to keep drinking until you die?
I will drink until I die. Isn’t that great plan?
Pete won’t be happy to see you like this
He’s not here with me
He’s not here. Do you hear me?
I told you to stop
Leave me alone
Damn it
What should I do?
Mai
Right here
What’s up
Can you help me?
I can’t stop him
Hey!
What’s wrong with you, shorty?
I don’t know how long he’s been drinking like this
Normally he never drank
He always took care of his health
Look at him now
All you do is lecturing him
Do you think he will listen?
He’s drunk
What do you expect me to do?
What the hell are you doing, asshole?
Come with me, shorty
What are you doing?
Come with me
Let me go
Mai!
Come here
Get the ball for me, Pond
Just get it
Fine
Keep your eyes on him
Don’t fight with him
He's out of his mind now
I know
Look at my friend
He’s no better than a dog
Just leave me alone, asshole
I don’t want to bother you
If you’re not my friend
Give it to me
What are you going to do?
Wait
Mai, don’t
Mai!
You like to play football, don’t you?
Get up!
Why don’t you come back and play the sport that you love?
How long are you going to let yourself fall apart?
My friend, Ae, won't be weak like this
You’re not a loser before
Do you think your boyfriend will be happy to see you being pathetic like this?
Tell me
Answer me!
How long are you going to be like this?
My friend, Ae
He won’t be this vulnerable
♪I've been praying♪
Get up!
♪With a heart full of hope♪
Your boyfriend left you
♪With a heart full of dreams♪
Because he wanted to help you
You cannot hurt yourself like this
♪I will wait for a new day♪
Do you think he will be happy?
♪The day that I will finally meet you♪
I don’t know anything anymore
I don’t know what to do
♪Why am I still hoping when there is no hope?♪
I don’t fucking know
Damn you!
♪I still hope and wait for the lonely nights to pass♪
After you sober
I will kill you
♪I still hope and wait for the lonely nights to pass♪
♪In the pain and torment♪
That’s right
Please stop hurting yourself
♪It might take a lot of time that all the stars fall down from the sky♪
We can’t bear seeing you like this anymore
♪I still have hope even I know that it's hopeless♪
♪I've been hopelessly wishing for the impossible. I'm asking just for once♪
♪Just for once♪
Shit! What happened?
Shorty!
How dare you kick me off the bed?
Why not?
How come you’re sleeping on my bed?
Last night
You two wouldn’t stop hugging each other
That’s right
Last night, you hugged me
And something more
Shit! We’re doomed!
How come you’re here?
That dude
Your wife called me to come
He’s not my wife
Where’s your uniform?
Mai
I asked you to help him
Not to add insult to injury
If Pond didn’t threaten me that he will ask Dear to come instead
I won't come here at all
I didn’t ask for your help
Shorty
You should talk to me nicely
I told you already
I didn’t ask for help
You two, calm down
We’re friends
Ae
What did you tell us what friends are for?
You like to help other people, right?
Then why don’t you care about us?
We are very worried about you
Look at Pond
He’s so freaking worried about you
Have you thought about our friends?
We all know that you’re suffering
Do you think about them?
Do you know how they feel?
Huh?
We are very worried
Shorty
I’m not telling you to stop feeling sad
But please rely on us to help you
Understand?
Do you know what makes me angry the most?
You didn’t ask me to drink with you!
Damn it
What a waste
Damn it. You didn't even ask me to join you
How can you do that to me?
You’re always like this, asshole
You’re going to heal your heart
But you won't let me accompany you?
Damn you
I can’t believe it that you would kick the ball at Ae like that
Because he loves football so much
So, I need to use it to wake him up
Do you think…
he can think clearly now?
I don’t know
Damn you
I asked you for help
I don’t know
My job is to get him out of the bar
He’s wasting too much alcohol
He doesn’t know the pleasure of drinking
Obviously
Who would be such a drunker like you?
Normally it’s Ae who takes you out of the bar
So, you wanted to take a revenge on him, right?
Do you think I don’t know that?
Don't you know who I am?
I'm, Pond, Mr. know it all
You miss it. Come and get me
Come and get me if you dare
Can
What?
Don’t bother me now
I don’t want to lose
Can you come with me?
I don’t want to go. I’m lazy
I’m going shopping. Can you come with me to carry all the stuff?
I don’t want to. I won’t go
It’s my holiday
I’m too lazy
Are you coming or not?
No, I'm not
Fine
I will tell mom
Where you hide the porn magazine
On the bookshelf, second row
Inside your textbook
Mommy
Okay, my lovely sis
Calm down
Tell me where you want to go
I’ll take you there
Come on
Lemon
Do you know what you’re going to buy yet?
What’s the matter?
I cannot accept this
What are you talking about?
What can you not accept?
Pimple is right in front of your face. Can’t you see it yourself?
What are you doing?
Cover up your pimple so you will look more human-like
I don’t want to
I know that I’m stupid but at least I know that you shouldn’t apply makeup when you have pimple
You’re seriously stupid
This one can both reduce and cover pimples
Like this
Apply just a little bit
That’s it
It smoothly covers it
I told you
Well…
Can I have it?
I’ll take it as my reward for carrying stuff for you today
I’m off
It’s mine!
I have to use it to cover my pimple too!
Can!
I want this one
Let's go
Let's pay
Let’s go
Give me your hand
This one seems fun
This one too
This one!
Can I play?
Please
Can I play, please?
Give me the coin
This one looks fun
No! Let’s go
Get all the bags and let’s go
Quickly!
You are too slow
I want to go home now
I’m tired
I’m hungry
Lemon
Why did you buy so many things?
And you won’t carry anything by yourself
My arms and my back hurt
My arms hurt so much
Every time I see you
Why do you always look so weird?
How come you’re here?
Don’t you have any other question?
You suddenly show up
It’s not a coincidence, right?
It’s a coincidence
Tell me the truth
Are you here to take revenge because you’re mad at me since last time?
Hey!
Who tell you to sit down?
I want to
Fine
Just do whatever you want
What if it’s not a coincidence?
What the hell?
You just said it’s a coincidence
What if I tell you that…
I want to see you
What are you going to do?
What’s wrong with you?
I’m just joking
My heart is skipping a beat
I’m here to do an errand
What are you doing here?
It’s my business
Don’t stick your nose into my business
Who are you here with?
I told you
Don’t stick your nose into my business
Have you eaten yet?
Tin
I’m hungry
I told you not to bother me
That’s right
These are my girlfriend’s stuff
Girlfriend?
Why not?
Do you think someone like me don’t have a girlfriend?
You should go back where you came from
Can!
Where were you?
I called you but you didn’t pick up the phone
Opps
Hello
You are Can's friend?
I’m Lemon
I am Can’s sister
Sister?
Not girlfriend?
No!
Of course not!
Just sister
A guy like him cannot find any girlfriend
Give me that
Look up and look into my eyes
Look up!
You can cry only because of me
Do you understand?
♪I don't know♪
♪Until when my heart will remain in this loneliness♪
♪I want to be free from this feeling♪
♪I wish that I could meet the one that my heart is searching for♪
♪There's just me and loneliness♪
♪When will I get a chance to meet the one?♪
♪Give me just one minute♪
♪So I can meet that person who I've been waiting for♪
♪The one♪
♪I still have hope even I know that it's hopeless♪
♪I still hope and wait for the lonely nights to pass♪
♪In the pain and torment♪
♪It might take a lot of time that all the stars fall down from the sky♪
♪I still have hope even I know that it's hopeless♪
♪I've been hopelessly wishing for the impossible. I'm asking just for once♪
♪Just for once♪
♪Give me just a few seconds♪
♪So that I will no longer be lonely♪
♪I've been praying♪
♪With a heart full of hope♪
♪With a heart full of dreams♪
♪I will wait for a new day♪
♪The day that I will finally meet you♪
♪Why am I still hoping when there is no hope?♪
♪I still hope and wait for the lonely nights to pass♪
♪In the pain and torment♪
♪It might take a lot of time that all the stars fall down from the sky♪
♪I still have hope even I know that it's hopeless♪
♪I've been hopelessly wishing for the impossible. I'm asking just for once♪
♪Just for once♪
♪Give me just a few seconds♪
♪So that I...♪
♪Will no longer be lonely...♪