Chief,
I insist on repairing the road
even for being damned.
Chief,
I’m really scared.
At the end of last year,
the main force of Division 234
was stuck on the highway for 12 hours
during the Southern 83 Exercise.
I have never been afraid in all my years as a soldier.
I’m really scared this time.
I’m afraid that
when the country needs us in the field,
we won’t be able to make it.
The war will be lost before it has even begun.
The thought of this
makes me break out in a cold sweat.
If our Division 234 is not the main force,
there will be no problem in repairing the road a few years later.
Once the war comes,
there will be the main force in front of us.
But chief,
we are the main division.
We are the first motorized infantry division
in the entire military district.
Once the war breaks out,
who will stand in front of us?
Are you lecturing me?
Well, the porridge smells good.
It makes me hungry.
Let me have a taste first.
That’s not for you.
One, two, three, four.
The Ninth Company is back.
Hurry up, keep up.
Rest in place for a minute.
[Outstanding community-level officers and soldiers. Advanced community-level company.]
Stop.
All attention!
Stand at attention!
Dress right!
Eyes front!
Comrade deputy commander,
the Ninth Company has completed its training plan
and has returned to the camp.
Please give instructions.
Company Commander Qin Hanyong.
Stand at ease, please.
Yes, chief.
Stand at ease.
Qin Hanyong.
Yes.
Why did you come back now?
Chief,
two kilometers of highway roadbed
had been washed away
and vehicles could not pass through.
We could only get off the bus and walk for six hours,
climb over Banyueling
and return to the camp.
Chief,
we did not return to the camp
beyond the time stipulated
in the training plan.
Great.
Comrades,
I see something
in your eyes.
Something that
I once saw in the eyes of my comrades
on the Long March.
On the anti-Japanese front,
I saw it in the eyes of
the officers and soldiers of the Iron Hiker Regiment.
In the Korean battlefield,
I also saw it in the eyes of
the officers and men of
the Division 234 of the volunteer army.
That is the determination
to complete the task,
to overwhelm the enemy
and to seize the victory!
Comrades, you have worked hard!
Here are my orders.
Stand at attention.
Target Canteen
It’s dinner time.
Yes, Chief.
Er Ganzi.
After all these years with me,
can you see
why I care so much about
the food and shelter of my soldiers?
Chief,
When you were a soldier,
the troops were in poor condition and
logistics were not perfect at that time.
Our troops
have come from hard times.
In fact,
regardless of the era,
being a soldier is the most bitter.
For example,
I have sacrificed
many comrades
all the way from the Red Army period.
I can’t even remember
how many of my comrades
were killed by a bullet
with delicious food on their backs
or new shoes made by their mothers
or wives in their bags.
In the end,
when people died,
they left behind delicious food and clothes.
So,
[Learn from Comrade Lei Feng. Mao Zedong]
the last thing I can tolerate is
to keep the soldiers waiting.
However,
you’re right too.
A meal's late for six hours.
If there is a war,
some soldiers
may not get the meal.
I admit my mistake.
Chief, it’s my fault.
I pushed too hard.
I’ll
make a statement to you two.
The barracks
need to be renovated,
but your readiness road
needs to be repaired as well.
Thank you, Chief.
What?
Many thanks to Chief.
Well, I will immediately convey the good news
to all officers and soldiers in the division.
Thanks, Chief.
Political Commissar,
this trip to the headquarters of Deputy Commander Xiao
asked for the money
for road repairing for us.
The older, the wiser.
Have a seat, please.
Deputy Commander Xiao said that
this is due to
the report you wrote.
After reading the letter,
the head officer in charge of logistics
was in tears.
It’s your pen.
The credit must be
attributed to Deputy Commander Xiao.
However,
in order to balance with other units,
the funds allocated this time
are still 2-3 million
shorts of the actual cost.
So, what should we do?
There’s no choice.
We’ll repair the road ourselves,
tighten our belts
to repair this readiness road.
The construction section of the Regiment 720
is the most dangerous terrain in the whole section,
but they have an amazing construction speed.
Especially the Ninth Company, can complete the most difficult task.
Extremely combative.
More than half of the equipment and materials for road construction
are in their place.
You remind them to take precautions in advance
and reinforce the wall behind the warehouse
to prevent mountain torrents.
Hurry up.
In addition,
the No. 3 National Defense Readiness Depot
is in their neighborhood.
You send Chen Dashan to ask
what they need us to do.
These are all the country’s readiness materials.
They are treasures
and should be protected.
Yes, Commander.
Notify the Regiment 720
to withdraw from the construction site immediately
to ensure the safety of officers and soldiers.
All attention!
Stop
and move back.
We can’t stop.
If the flow of water is too strong, the warehouse may be washed away.
Director Zhao,
there’s nothing I can do. Our superiors told us to withdraw.
I have to follow orders.
I…
Qin Hanyong.
Division Commander.
How is it going?
The roadbed has been reinforced.
All the materials
have been rescued to the safe place.
Division commander,
Commander Qin is helping us to reinforce the flood wall,
but they are going to withdraw now.
They cannot withdraw.
If they withdraw,
the No. 3 Readiness Depot will be destroyed.
Qin Hanyong,
this is country’s readiness depot.
It’s like fighting a war.
Can you withdraw when a war is being fought?
Now I order you to
send your men up there right now
and secure the No. 3 Readiness Depot.
Yes, Commander.
Gao Liang, come on.
All of you
follow me.
Political Commissar,
how is it going?
The Division Commander is at the site of the Regiment 720,
leading them
to repair the flood wall of No. 3 Readiness Depot.
How about the other regiments?
Less than 10 minutes after
the Regiment 700 and Regiment 702 withdrew,
the construction site was flooded.
What?
Take care.
Chief,
go down, I’ll do it.
Don’t worry about me.
Hurry up.
Don’t mind me.
Hurry!
Go for it!
Don’t go.
Plug it up now!
Plug it up.
Chief, you go first.
Come on, do as I say.
Execute the command.
Come on.
Pull the Chief.
- Chief.
Chief.
Hold him.
Gao Liang.
[ICU]
Any of the chief’s family members here?
It’s me.
I am.
Doctor.
I’m the political commissar.
Let me know what’s going on.
Chief’s internal organs were severely impacted,
the old injury recurred,
and the rescue was not timely.
The director
has asked to be reported critically ill.
Chief,
don’t pull me.
Chief is critically ill, why are you pulling me?
It’s my fault for not catching chief.
Calm down, Gao Liang.
Gao Liang.
We have to find a way to get the division commander back.
I can drain my blood.
Go,
get Nanzheng here.
Hurry up!
How is he?
Still in the coma.
This way, this way.
Dad.
I’m Nanzheng.
Your daughter.
Dad, can you hear me?
Dad, you have to promise me that
you can’t just lie there and ignore me.
You can’t go away
for 18 years as before.
Dad, I’ll do as you say.
You can transfer me away.
Anywhere, dad.
I follow orders.
Dad.
Doctor Zhang,
the blood pressure is dropping,
down to below sixty.
- Families leave, please.
- Dad.
Families leave, please.
- Hurry up.
Dad.
Dad, you must hold on.
Adrenaline, 0.5 mg.
Intravenous injection.
Wake up, daddy.
Dad.
Dad, you have to hold on. I’m Nanzheng.
Wake up, daddy.
- Dad, don’t scare me.
- Electric shocks.
Dad.
Doctor Zhang, wait a minute.
- Seems to have regained vital signs.
- Dad.
Dad.
[Outpatient Building]
Nanzheng,
I’m telling you,
the mountain is so big that
you can’t see it clearly at night.
I can’t find him anywhere.
And then when I finally saw chief,
and I pulled him out.
I don’t know how long it took.
To me,
chief is usually a division commander,
sometimes he’s like my father.
He’s not only my father,
I think our division commander
is the father of all soldiers.
He is too tired every day.
Stay up all night reading books
and making battle plans.
Sometimes he was in a daze.
I brought him water to wash at night.
I saw him busy all the time,
and I didn’t disturb him.
In the end, I was so sleepy that
I sat at the door and fell asleep.
[Henry Norman Bethune]
When I woke up,
I saw chief,
all alone in the yard,
and the sight of his back
was poignant.
You know?
Now,
he writes letters every day.
He wrote a bunch of letters,
and your name
was on every letter.
And I’m telling you,
after chief was rescued,
he said one thing to me.
He asked me not to tell you,
for fear that you would be worried and upset.
Dad.
Dad, you’re awake.
Dad, how do you feel?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
Dad.
You’ve been in a coma for two days and two nights.
You know that?
Would you like me to call the nurse for you?
Gao Liang.
Chief.
Chief, you’re awake.
You scared the hell out of me, chief.
You have been in a coma for two days and two nights.
I’ve lost my mind.
How do you feel?
Is there any discomfort?
You finally woke up.
Should I call the nurse?
No.
Well,
let me wipe your face, dad.
What’s wrong, dad?
Are you uncomfortable?
I’ll call the nurse for you.
Gao Liang.
What’s up, Chief?
What’s up, dad?
What are you doing standing there?
Help me.
Yes, Chief.
Dad, do you want to take a leak?
Let me help you.
How can you help?
You can't help, and you don’t know how.
Okay, Chief, come on.
Go out.
Chief is nervous.
I’ll go out.
Okay, fine.
Close the door.
Okay, Chief.
One, two, three, four.
[Raise vigilance]
Political Commissar.
Well, that’s not cool.
Look at you.
How do you let me live
without a daughter?
I can’t help you.
We are blessed, anyway.
You are recovering well.
Look at your glowing face,
don’t even look like someone who just got out of the hospital.
You scared
the hell
out of us.
You recovered too suddenly.
It’s like a joke.
What do you mean?
Political Commissar.
Division Commander,
Political Commissar
is praising Jiang Nanzheng.
Don’t you realize it?
Political Commissar.
Division Commander.
Lunch break is almost over,
I have to go back.
Okay, fine.
I’m leaving, dad.
The transfer order of the political department of the military district has been approved,
and it is necessary to transfer Jiang Nanzheng
to the military district art troupe.
Colonel Ge said that
they had already inspected Jiang Nanzheng
and believed that her voice was good
and
her professional basis was solid.
The transfer order was sent half a month ago,
and now, since it’s a long way,
it came to us
today.
Colonel Ge has called more than once.
Political commissar,
they are transferring Nanzheng
to be an actress?
Yeah.
Division’s
art troupe wants her,
we
have to support it.
After all,
cultural and art work is also
an important part of military’s
ideological and political work.
Zheng, what do you think?
That’s right.
Well, I see you’ve recovered pretty well,
so,
in these two days,
you father and daughter can get together well.
After all the procedures are complete,
next week at most,
she’ll go there to check in.
Alright.
That’s it, I’ll go now.
See you, political commissar.
Alright, see you.
Gao Liang.
Here.
Go,
get some good liquor.
Make up for what I owed the political commissar last time.
[One Yuan]
But this is not enough.
Then borrow some from the political commissar.
From political commissar?
So stingy…
Colonel Ge,
This is Zheng Yuan.
Hello.
Last time your art troupe came to our troop
and performed that show, Fire,
it was very impressive.
It’s like we had
the political study for three months.
All the community-level soldiers like it very much.
Not worthy mentioning.
Learn from you!
Here’s the thing, Colonel Ge,
I have a soldier here,
and I looked into her files.
She has great quality,
sings well,
dances well,
and her family are all in music.
If you are interested,
you can look into her.
[Military Service]
Comrade Gao, what do you want?
Two bottles of liquor.
I need something with great quality.
Well, that’s tough,
quality liquor is hard to get now.
I’ll think about it.
The division commander’s business is my business.
Don’t worry.
No, no, no,
I didn’t say anything about the division commander,
you said it yourself.
You can’t make it special.
I won’t get it. I’m going.
Gao,
- Don’t go.
- No, no.
Listen to me, the division commander told me
that you can skip meals, or skip liquors,
but you can’t owe others. Owing someone is a big problem.
I really won’t get anything.
Gao.
Gao!
[Military Service]
Comrade Gao!
I’m really not buying. Really not.
Don’t go, I’ll get some for you.
Don’t be so distant.
You brother Gao Shan
was my comrade-in-arms.
You know my brother, huh?
You are?
I’m You Qianjin of administration and registration section.
Your brother and I
joined the army in the same year. We were in the same company.
We were good buddies.
[Military Service]
Were you and my brother buddies?
Comrade You…
Call me brother You.
Brother You.
Did you have a meal?
No? Let your brother take you for a meal.
Let’s go.
Let’s go and have some meal.
The meal is on me.
Let me show you this.
This
is a picture we took
in the photo gallery
before setting out.
Look at your brother.
He’s smiling so happily.
But now,
all that left on this picture
is me.
I really miss my brothers.
I really miss your brother.
These two bottles of liquor
are my gift to Gao Shan’s brother.
Army commander, division commander, colonel, driver, cook…
Give whoever you want!
These two bottles of liquor
are to my dearest Comrade Gao Shan.
♫ My friend, do you remember still ♫
Do you want to drink along?
Of course!
♫ With the same concerns ♫
Cheers!
♫ “Here” is our answer ♫
Gao Liang!
Bro!
You see I’m with four pockets now,
but
I’m actually still a volunteer soldier.
I just hope to become a cadre this year.
Now getting promotions for soldiers are becoming more and more difficult.
My age
is getting older and older too.
The last chance.
Your dear brother…
You are around the chief.
♫ Rain and wind are always missed with smile and tears ♫
If you can,
please help me.
♫ Let time be the milestone of friendship ♫
[It’s everybody’s duty to save water.]
Little Wangcheng,
do you think
Lei Feng had made any mistake?
You are not up to something bad,
and making an excuse for yourself, are you?
No, no!
I’m telling you Gao Liang.
You are different now.
You are division commander’s public servant.
All eyes in the division
are on you.
Remember,
don’t be hot blooded.
[Create a new situation in the revolution and modernization of the army]
One, two, three, four.
Let’s get to the next topic.
Let’s discuss the list of soldiers’ getting promotion
from the cadre section.
Let’s see if you have any things to say.
The lists have already given to you.
Why isn’t Zhang Fei from Regiment 720 on the list?
Qin Hanyong told me
Zhang Fei
was the first on the list of promoted soldiers,
why isn’t he on this list?
Here’s the thing,
this time,
the places for soldiers’ promotion
are really few.
Zhangfei,
in Regiment 720,
is very outstanding.
But
among the whole division,
especially his
meritorious, awards,
and education background, age,
these solid conditions
compared to other soldiers in competition
are really at disadvantage.
Is that really the case?
Division commander,
we’ve investigated it,
that is the real situation.
Hello,
I’m the Deputy Section Chief Wu Jianwen of the cadre section.
The division commander is not here, huh?
He was inspecting the troops.
Chief Wu,
has the list of promoted soldiers
been out yet?
Soldiers’ promotion is always strictly controlled.
A battle company
has to wait for years to get one place,
and it’s basically for volunteer soldiers
and long served cadres.
Did you want to know…
You don’t have to explain it to me.
I just want to know
whether You Qianjin from the division’s administration and registration section is
on the list.
You Qianjin…
Does he know the division commander?
Or,
does the division commander know him?
The division commander doesn’t know him.
I do.
I mean,
just,
if you can help,
please help him.
After the investigation above,
it is proved
that during the process of soldiers’ promotion,
there really exists
serious disciplinary problems.
I took him here for you.
You take care.
Wang Tianming!
Don’t always do my job.
If I used the toilet, would you flush it for me too?
You dumby!
Ungrateful.
Stand straight!
I’m telling you!
That You Qianjin took full responsibility.
He said
this has nothing to do with you.
Chief,
he’s actually
kind of buddy great-hearted.
Great-hearted?
I didn’t see that.
He’s a recidivist.
He used to be the cook.
He was getting all comfortable
in the guest house doing nothing.
It’s him
that took your old sergeant’s
promotion place.
Do you know?
Chief,
actually,
I actually helped him
because he told me that
he’s one of the comrades of Gao Shan.
He just met Gao Shan once
together with over a thousand other comrades in the regiment.
How would you know that they knew each other?
They did.
He was on good terms with my brother.
He even showed me their picture.
I’ve investigated on it.
He’s Guan Zili,
who has transferred to civilian work,
instead of You Qianjin.
He fooled me!
Did you lie to Wu Jianwen as well?
I did not lie to him. I just...
told him to
give a hand when possible.
He thought that he was so clever.
Your attitude is on behalf of mine.
What have you done?
Is that your so-called wisdom?
Chief,
I understand now.
I’ll not be fooled again.
You’ll never be fooled
as long as
you stick to principles
and behave yourself,
understand?
Yes sir.
Did you bring your notebook?
Confiscated when I was grounded.
Then keep it in mind.
Yes.
I’ve looked into it.
The two bottles of wine you drank
were plonk, but filled
into the bottles of nice wine.
You pay him back
the two bottles of plonk,
and then the whole thing is over.
Yes sir.
I pay for
these two bottles of wine,
as a lesson learned.
My expectation for you
is having a bright future.
This lesson is learned
in fairly reasonable price.
Chief.
Smell it.
Can you smell it?
What a nice-smelling lesson.
Chief,
I have a question.
Don’t know whether I should ask.
If that’s about the wine,
then go ahead.
Chief,
how come this smell
is the same as the plonk?
Nonsense!
How stupid do you think I am?
Jiang Nanzheng is coming for lunch tomorrow.
Do we need more wine?
Yes sir.
What did I say?
You meant soup only. No more wine.
Get out!
Yes sir.
[Raise vigilance, defend the motherland]
Go!
Jiang Nanzheng.
After failing in the maneuver,
I’ve locked
my heart away,
and did nothing
but training.
Just as what I said to my father,
I forge myself
for my dreams.
Other than that,
[Carry every red flag.]
nothing else matters.
Jiang Nanzheng,
wish you all the best.
Chief.
Jiang Nanzheng
has always loved singing and dancing since her childhood.
Being recruited into the art troupe
is a dream come true.
Congratulations!
Thanks!
How do you know my childhood hobbies?
I’m just guessing.
Didn’t they give you assessments?
Yeah, they did.
Actually,
I was extremely nervous
facing a row of supervisors.
They asked me to perform
two songs and one dance.
I think that
I did okay.
It seems that the examination of art troupe
is much more difficult than college entrance examination, chief.
That depends on
whose daughter she is.
Come on.
Have some more.
Eat more meat.
Thanks, chief.
Thanks, dad.
Go ahead and eat.
That’s okay. Thanks.
Gao Liang,
you risked your life to save mine.
With the soup, on behalf of wine,
I thanked you for saving my life.
Here.
Chief!
Sit down.
[Carry every red flag.]
Sergeant.
Come on. Stop it.
Let me do it for you.
I’ll wash it myself.
You can wash mine
upon recovery.
Sergeant,
something’s wrong.
What?
What’s wrong?
Anything wrong?
Yiye,
are we bros?
As my bro,
you have to do me a favor.
What favor?
I got promoted.
Sergeant!
That’s great!
How about that?
I’ll call up the guys and get together for a drink.
Yes.
That’s for sure.
But the major problem now
is that I am badly in need of
a dress.
A dress?
A red dress.
A stylish dress.
You’ll buy me one.
What?
See, I got promoted.
And I promised Xiu
to marry her
after being a platoon leader.
No, sergeant.
No, platoon leader.
Now,
let me get this straight.
You need a red dress.
Yes.
And you need it for Xiu in your wedding.
That’s right.
And I’ll buy this dress for you, right?
Right.
You...
How should I put it?
Just that...
You...
You are highly educated,
what’s the word?
Aesthetic.
You have the aesthetic judgement.
You are literate, well-educated
and will definitely buy a nicer dress than I do.
No, platoon leader.
This may not be appropriate.
Let alone the fact that I’m a soldier and you’re a platoon leader,
you should never assign me this kind of task
even if I were the university professor.
Xiu is your wife.
You’re her husband.
You can buy her anything
as her husband.
But what about me?
That’s inappropriate.
What’s wrong with it?
I want to give her the best.
And the dress you choose will be the best.
It doesn’t matter
who buys it,
right?
Platoon leader,
you are all Xiu wants,
instead of something nice.
Understand?
No.
I thought that, simple as it is,
you would say yes without hesitation.
What a fuss
you made!
No wonder Gao Liang said that
he would marry you
if he were a girl.
You think too much.
Platoon leader,
girls do not expect you
to give her anything nice.
You need to look out for her,
be there for her.
Then...
What happened between you and Jiang?
Platoon leader,
don’t bring that up again.
I won’t.
Here’s what I am thinking.
I think that Xiu...
She...
She doesn’t expect for anything nice.
Whatever from me is fine.
It means that she loves me.
As for me,
I want to give her everything nice.
Whoever buys it is fine.
What does it mean?
It means I love her, right?
Platoon leader.
Alright, how about this?
I’ll help you.
You may rest assured.
I’ll not let you down.
Chief.
Comrade Jiang Nanzheng.
Now that chief is here,
I would like to take this opportunity,
and say something.
Comrade Jiang Nanzheng,
you’re the best comrade,
female comrade,
I have ever had
since I joined the army.
Here’s to you.
Gao Liang.
You’ve been so good to me
from Zhuangmu to division headquarter.
You’re not only my comrade,
but also my best friend.
You will always be my comrade
after I go to the art troupe.
And you will be my best friend for a lifetime.
Come on.
Here’s to you.
Okay.
Comrade Jiang Nanzheng.
Yes sir.
All of us here
want to
listen to a song
from the comrade from art troupe.
Yeah.
That’s right.
♫ Your shadow, your voice ♫
♫ will always be ♫
♫ in my heart. ♫
♫ Yesterday has gone by. ♫
♫ Reunion is hard to meet after parting. ♫
♫ How can I forget ♫
♫ your deep love? ♫
♫ Yesterday has gone by. ♫
♫ Reunion is hard to meet after parting. ♫
♫ How can I forget ♫
♫ your deep love? ♫
Chief,
I have something in my eyes.
I’m going out.
Zheng.
Go check it out.
What’s matter?
Are you crying?
No.
Who’s crying?
I’m just
happy for you.
Aren’t you crying?
This is happy tears.
Is this happy?
Come on, take a look.
No.
Just take a look.
Look at you.
No.
What?
You don’t want me to go to the art troupe, do you?
I can’t finish my words just now
with division commander there.
You’ve always been my best comrade
from Zhangmu
to division headquarter.
We were climbing walls,
hiding from provost together
to avoid being overseed.
But from now on,
I can only see you
in the performance as an audience.