[English subtitles are available]
[Cohabitation Agreement]
[Jang Ki-yong, Lee Hye-ri]
[Kang Han-na, Kim Do-wan]
[Bae In-hyuk, Park Gyeong-hye]
[My Roommate is a Gumiho]
[I'll also show you]
[what could become her future.]
[It all began because of my selfishness,
so I tried to bear through this.]
[My life was made up
of nothing but patience,]
[so I thought
it would be a piece of cake.]
[Why did I]
[delude myself into thinking
I could bear through?]
Dam.
Wake up.
Stop
looking at that.
Sir.
I had a dream and...
Forget it. That man...
He was just here.
Are you okay, Miss Dam?
I'm all right now, sir.
Anyway, about that man.
I think I ran into him
at the bookstore too.
Who is he?
A being who put me here today,
People usually call him
the mountain spirit.
He's a spirit?
So that's how he could
tie that red thread on me
and made me have that dream...
Did you see my dream too?
I didn't see anything.
It was nothing.
There was Seon-woo involved,
but it's not a big deal.
He said something about my fate,
but I won't let fate do this to me.
The more I think about it,
the angrier I get.
Who does he think he is
to tie that on me and give me that dream?
Why does he do this to us?
Because it's right for a human
to be with another human.
We can decide what's right for us.
Sir, don't worry about it.
That dream and that thread?
Those mean nothing to us.
I won't let it happen.
[What? He gave her a dream?]
Why did he show her something
that isn't true by using her dream?
How much did you see?
Were they hugging each other?
Or did they kiss?
Their ordinary day looked nice.
They were like a young couple
as they should be,
enjoying their time in peace
without any worries.
That's something I can't give her.
Whatever. Why do you care
about some dumb dream?
Right?
Why does it bother me so much?
I might have been envious
of living such an ordinary life.
How much time
do you have left
until your 1,000 years are over?
I'm not sure.
It'll be over soon, I guess.
[Then]
[I'll disappear without a trace.]
[Episode 12]
-Are you busy tomorrow?
-No, why?
Come early. I'm making kimchi.
You can't mix the seasoning,
but you have good taste.
I do have good taste,
but you're busy training now.
Let's just buy it this time.
I just ordered a few heads.
I'll send some to Mom,
and since you love to eat new kimchi
with bossam, I want to show my gratitude.
Show your gratitude? What?
I made you get a part-time job.
You should be busy partying.
Hey, win a gold medal,
then pay me back with 50 percent interest.
You're a loan shark.
So how's your job? Isn't it too tough?
Well, it's all right.
-It's okay.
-Really?
[You're off today, aren't you?]
[Gye Seon-woo]
[I'll organize the inventory,
so you don't have to mind it.]
I don't want to mind it, but I do.
Good morning, Dam.
Hey, don't hug me from the back.
I hate this.
Why? Do you have a bad memory
of your man hugging you from the back?
It would've been better if it was him.
-My gosh, girl.
-That's Professor Shin.
Is something bothering him?
He doesn't look so energetic.
He doesn't.
He usually looks handsome and smart,
but today,
he makes me want to protect him.
He looks as if he stayed up all night
because he was sad.
You know, heartrending.
-Soo-kyung, let me ask you a question.
-Okay.
Let's say you have a boyfriend.
And your boyfriend...
You can tell me. What about him?
He's not human.
What? He's such a jerk
that you can't even call him human?
No, that's not what I meant.
He literally isn't human.
He's a sort of non-human.
For example, a vampire or a gumiho.
Okay, a gumiho.
And?
Then this mountain spirit showed up
and tied you up with a human man
with a red string of fate in front of him.
And there's a mountain spirit now?
-And?
-And
what now?
If you want to tell him
that's not what's important,
what can you do to get that point across?
Well, first off,
I'd stop reading webtoons.
I thought this was about your boyfriend.
You're reading a fantasy webtoon
after binging on historical dramas?
And you got a part-time job too.
You're one busy girl.
Hey, yes.
Let's say this is a plot of a webtoon.
So what would you do?
No idea. My future would be
way more important than my boyfriend.
Right? That's how it is, right?
But this is really odd.
When you like someone,
you're more worried about him than...
Soo-kyung, wait up!
What are you doing?
What are you writing down?
I'm planning my date.
Lunch, dinner, dessert, then a walk.
Everything is perfect.
Yes, you're a perfect pushover.
Has the story of this pushover begun?
It's not that. Hye-sun comforted me
when I was sad last time.
So one day, when she feels down,
I want to comfort her
by going on a fun date.
-Can a fun date be comforting?
-Yes.
-Jae-jin, let me ask you a question.
-Okay.
You said
you're dating Hye-sun
because of your grade, right?
But since when have you been
so concerned about your grades?
She's right.
What?
And if you're only dating her
because of your grade,
why are you putting in so much effort?
She's right.
Well...
Hey, be honest.
The one you spent...
that time with.
It's Hye-sun, isn't it?
Well...
[What do I do? If I say yes,
it'll make Hye-sun look weird.]
[But if I say no, I'll be this jerk]
[who had a random one-night-stand.]
That girl I spent the night with
isn't Hye-sun.
-What?
-You. You jerk.
What's with you?
How are you this open-minded?
You deserve a beating.
[That was a good choice, Jae-jin.]
[My reputation has gone down the drain,]
[but I saved Hye-sun's reputation.]
My gosh.
I'm taking this.
All of a sudden? Why?
-You can't have it.
-Give it back.
[Professor of History, Shin Woo-yeo]
Sir, are you busy?
Even if I was, I won't be. You're here.
Then let's go out.
Ta-da.
I stole Jae-jin's notebook of date ideas.
[Date Plan, Movies, Dinner,
Night views, Drinks]
Let's do everything here
to change things up.
Change things up?
We've gone through so much
with energy, red thread, and whatnot.
You can call it a day and focus on us.
[Professor of History, Shin Woo-yeo]
One second.
Hey, Dan.
What? The cabbage is coming today?
I thought it was tomorrow.
No idea. There must've been
a misunderstanding in the order.
What should we do?
They left it in front of our house.
It can't be out there for long.
Okay, I'll carry those back inside.
Well, carrying those in
wouldn't be the end of it.
What? Are you telling me
to make kimchi alone?
I'm sorry. I have an important tournament,
[and I'll be really late
after I finish analyzing the game.]
You can't let salted cabbage be
for too long.
Hang up for now.
Sir, I'm sorry.
We'll have to reschedule our date.
I'm even feeling cold
now that I'm a human.
I used to go around fine
in the middle of winter
wearing my flimsy hanbok.
That's why he can never date.
Have you all heard
about Hye-sun and Jae-jin's relationship?
Yes, we've heard.
The boys in our department were shocked,
then they got wasted.
You talk as if you didn't.
You were the worst case.
-I thought you lost your country.
-Hey.
But doesn't this seem odd?
-What?
-What is?
I mean, it's all too sudden.
And they went public
on the day our grades came out.
Do you think they're pretending to date
because of their grades?
Just to get A pluses?
Exactly.
No way.
Grades are very important these days,
and they wouldn't mess with it.
Exactly. If that's the case,
we should tell the professor
and end their lives.
Then I'll upload it online.
-It'll be a huge scandal.
-They'll have to quit school.
-No way.
-Oh no.
I might end up getting embarrassed
in front of kids who are
700 years younger than me.
-What should I do?
-Hye-sun.
-Are you done with your class?
-What?
I prepared lots of things for you,
but everything got stolen.
Babe, aren't you cold?
"Babe"?
Yes, babe.
Hold this in your hand
and stay warm in your class.
Even if you get tired,
think of me and stay strong. Okay?
Babe, you're so...
I'll do my best.
[Salted Cabbage, Salted Radish]
It'll take me forever to move these.
This is so much work.
[Salted Cabbage]
Sir.
I thought you could use help.
My gosh.
Thanks for using your power, sir.
Can you make kimchi with magic?
I'm not sure.
Making food requires
a delicate touch of hand,
so there's a limit.
So I wanted to help out myself.
You want to make kimchi?
Of course.
I believe that making kimchi is
a family event,
which means you need many people.
You can't do it alone, can you?
But it'll be tough
when you actually do it.
I want to do this together.
Something ordinary in your everyday life.
I want to do that with you.
Sure, you can do that.
Gosh, you have the looks
to make everything you want come true.
What should we begin with?
First off, you should
get dressed properly.
Is there a certain outfit?
How should I be dressed to look proper
in this traditional human event
of making kimchi?
Do you have something
in a different color?
Something less flashy, but more classy.
But sir, are you sure you can do this?
Miss Dam, have you heard of an expression,
"a man of uncommon acquirements"?
Of course, someone who's smart
and talented in many ways.
That's who I am.
I've lived for a long time, so I have
much knowledge of traditional dishes,
and I'm also amazingly talented,
so don't worry.
[Salted Cabbage]
[Pear]
It's now the final step.
Do it over.
What? Why?
You need to get the seasoning
all the way in.
It's completely white inside.
Are you making white kimchi?
Kimchi must be
very significant for humans.
You've been doing this strenuous work
every single year.
When there's no reward.
Of course, there's a reward.
There's always a special
and amazing reward
after you make kimchi.
What exactly is this reward?
Ta-da. We have some suyuk here.
Freshly made kimchi
with freshly boiled suyuk.
Isn't it the best reward or what?
I'm not sure.
It'll be different once you have a bite.
Open up.
So?
It's good.
Come on. That's not the response
of someone who thinks this is good.
I'll walk in one more time, so do it over.
Ta-da. Sir, we have some suyuk here.
It looks so good.
Open up.
So?
-It's really good, Miss Dam.
-See?
I didn't learn to use magic to do this.
Right, this is when we need our friend.
Our friend?
Sir, I got some makgeolli.
Suyuk's friend, makgeolli.
Oh wait, you get easily drunk.
Sorry?
When we went to that cart bar,
we ordered two bottles of soju,
and you had only one glass.
And your faced turned red after that.
I think you were the one
who got drunk that night.
You wouldn't let me drink back then,
so I was weak for that period.
I'm a hard drinker.
I was famous for winning
a beer-drinking contest.
Miss Dam.
I was also famous for my alcohol intake
in the Joseon era.
Once I began to drink,
they had to use up rice
to satisfy my need for alcohol,
so people went starving that year.
That's an exaggeration.
I'll prove that
it wasn't just an exaggeration.
-Who's this?
-My mom.
It's ancient history.
I haven't looked at this for long.
I look really ugly
when I was a baby, right?
You were cute.
-This one?
-Yes.
This is Dan.
This is me.
Right.
So this is how you grew up.
What were you like as a kid?
I never had a childhood.
I've always looked like this.
Pick out a photo. I'll give you one.
Then give me five.
What? Five?
This one. This, and this.
This one and this. I like them all.
What should I do, then?
Should I give you the entire album?
Dam!
-What are you doing?
-Well, I...
We only made kimchi, I mean it.
Just kimchi.
I had to do it alone, right?
But he offered to help
since it's tough to do it alone.
Then we got a little drunk
on makgeolli, so...
Say hi. This is my boyfriend.
Is Admiral Yi Sun-sin your boyfriend?
What?
[If I seek to live, I shall die.
But if I seek to die, I shall live!]
I must have had one too many drinks.
I must've dreamed of my boyfriend
after I fell asleep drunk.
You had 12 empty bottles
of makgeolli out there.
Clean those up.
Never mind, I'll clean up. Get some rest.
Oh, thanks.
Do you actually have a boyfriend?
[Sir, what happened?]
[Miss Dam]
[I didn't want to trouble you,
so I got out.]
[Oh, you should've met my brother
before you left.]
[Miss Dam]
[You'll have to lie
if you want to tell him about me.]
Then sir, you'll look like this for life.
You know,
I don't care that he said
a human should only be with another human.
I really don't care
if you aren't human.
But
I'll keep changing
as I grow older.
So I do get a little worried
about how you'll be left alone.
But I do hope
we could be together for a long time.
I'd love to do that too.
[At first,]
[I wanted you to go back
to your ordinary life.]
[That's why]
[I let you go with much pain.]
[But now,]
[I want to be your ordinary future.]
[One day, there will come a moment]
[when you can't stand
that you're actually a fox.]
Professor Shin.
Are you going to class?
Yes.
Do you want to grab a cup of coffee
after your lecture?
[Sir, are you feeling all right?]
[It must've been tough
to keep up with me.]
[Let's relieve our hangovers together.]
Hey, I know how you feel, but...
How I feel about what?
Oh, right.
That you adore me
as a cute and nice junior.
What? I never had such a scary thought.
Oh, right. I heard you got
Mr. Han Seok-won to do an interview.
How did you get him to do it?
I sent him about 100 emails.
I'm going for the interview next week.
That's amazing.
But I'm sorry.
There's no one to come with you.
Exactly.
Ever since Da Young and everyone left,
no one else will join us.
Right, should we ask Professor Shin
to help us get the word out?
Professor Shin?
I have an announcement
before we begin the lecture.
[History 101]
We need more members
in the history club I oversee.
Me! I'll do it.
I'm busy studying for my classes
and for my teacher certification,
But I wish to add
my little effort for your sake, sir.
[History 101]
I'm in too.
Anyone else?
Me too.
All right, then.
Then it's Choi Soo-kyung, Jung Seok,
and Gye Seon-woo.
On top of that, Yang Hye-sun too.
Let's get started.
Why do I have to join it?
I already told them you applied before.
So why did you make up that lie?
Stop pulling a prank.
It's not a prank.
I'm asking you for a favor.
Please keep an eye on her.
If you're that worried, go there yourself.
Aren't you the advisor?
It'll make her feel overwhelmed.
If you don't want to do it alone,
you can bring him too.
What?
What now?
We're only dating because of our grades.
I didn't say anything.
You did. You said it in your head.
What do you want?
[Professor Shin Woo-yeo]
It feels worse when he says nothing.
But still, it looks like
he has been keeping his calm.
Hye-sun.
I heard you joined Dam's club.
I'll join you.
-You too?
-Yes, of course.
Did you hear about the interview tomorrow?
What?
Tomorrow? Right away?
Yes, the historian I'm about to interview
has to travel abroad soon.
If we don't do it tomorrow,
we'll have to wait a month.
So I'll be away for two days, one night.
Two days, one night.
Do you have to stay the night?
Yes, that's the only way
we could work things out.
I'm thirsty.
To be honest, I don't want you to go.
Just hang out with me.
[He's so cute.]
Promise to text me often.
Come on. It's not like
a month-long backpacking trip.
Don't drink too much.
I can't promise that.
And don't stay too close to him.
What you're worrying about
will never happen.
Do you trust me?
I do.
Have fun.
But don't have too much fun.
Okay.
Hye-sun, we must be
the first to arrive here.
I guess you're right.
[Floor 3, Tracks]
Right.
I didn't need any supplements before,
but now I'm a human,
I need them to get myself going.
Now you're a human?
My Korean is still bad. It's probably
because I've been abroad for so long.
Two each. Try it.
It's my present for you. It's good
for health, so take it regularly.
Thank you. This is my first time getting
something like this from my girlfriend.
All I have gotten were sudden goodbyes.
Thank you.
If you like it so much,
make it your profile photo
so other guys don't suspect us.
Suspect?
Haven't I told you?
Our fellow students suspect
that we might not be a real couple.
You mean, they think we are a fake couple?
That's not what I meant.
They think we are just pretending
to be a couple just for show.
That's what I meant by, a fake couple.
Is that so?
So that's why you've been nice to me.
You want to show them that we're not fake.
Yes. So tell your friends
to keep their mouth shut too.
-Okay.
-Jae-jin.
Hey.
The other guys are
at the ticket office now.
Let's hurry.
Thank you for your time, sir.
Thank you.
We will take a look at the museum too.
Good. Goodbye then.
Thank you.
What a charismatic man he is!
Every single thing he said was
a pearl of wisdom. You heard it, right?
Of course, I did.
"I think getting
our cultural assets back is"
"getting our ancestors' spirit back."
It touched my heart. You should
definitely mention this in the magazine.
Of course. Excuse me for a second.
Yes!
Yes! It's finished now.
It went well.
[How are you doing, Sir?]
[I'm doing all right.
So you don't need to worry.]
Be careful!
-Are you okay?
-Thanks, Seon-woo.
I feel like she's avoiding me even more.
Thank you for coming today.
I appreciate your participation.
Your participation should be
appreciated the most.
You just started seeing your boyfriend,
and you had to give up a weekend date.
What are you talking about?
By the way, Seon-woo,
I had no idea you'd come.
You've never participated
in things like this before.
Well...
I thought today might be
the last chance for me.
How about we play a game? Truth or dare?
-We're not playing that.
-Come on. What else do we do?
Let me fill up the glass.
All right. Three, two, one.
Soo-kyung.
Oh, well.
I guess I have to disclose
the veiled secrets of mine now.
Ask me anything,
please.
-Come on.
-What?
Ask me.
Have you ever had a crush
on one of us here?
-Come on. That's ridiculous...
-Yes.
I have.
You're not
about to start a long story, are you?
I'm not interested. Let's move on.
Next.
There you go. Dam.
All right. Dam.
Where did you first meet your boyfriend?
Where could you have possibly met him
to drink it right away?
I don't know. Let's move on.
-It's Dam again.
-What do you like about your boyfriend?
I just like him.
I like him so much
that nothing can sway me.
I think I should go grill a squid.
I'll go get some fruits too.
-Soo-kyung.
-Yes?
You said you had a crush on one of us.
Is that true?
The game is over now,
you Seogwa's thief.
Seogwa's thief?
Why is Jae-jin a thief?
Soy sauce marinated crab is a rice thief
because it makes us crave rice.
Rain is a thief
because he married Kim Tae Hee.
And he's a thief too
because he's going out with you.
You're too good for him.
I'm not sure about that.
I think he's too good for me.
Come on. You can be honest with me.
There's nobody here.
You don't have to pretend to like him.
I mean it. I haven't seen
such a nice and ingenuous man
in a long time.
I meant it
when I said he's too good for me.
Are you sure?
Can you put your hand on the chest
and swear?
Do I really have to put
my hand on the chest?
You can't, can you?
Why? Is it because it will make you
feel guilty?
I should get going.
Why did you want me to put my hand
on your chest?
Because there seems to be
nothing to brag about.
Hey!
I didn't mean my chest.
And what do you mean by,
there's nothing to brag about?
Mine is just fine!
It's snowing.
It's pretty.
Is he drunk?
It's none of my business. I should go.
Seon-woo, you should get inside
and go to bed.
I warned you.
I like you.
I know you have a boyfriend
and I know I should stop.
But still...
What should I do to make you look at me?
Is it too late?
Or have I never had a chance at all?
[I should stop. I might make a mistake.]
Seon-woo, you're drunk.
You should get inside
before you make any mistake.
It's not a mistake.
[Why does my heart suddenly...]
[Sir]
[If I answer this call now
and he happens to hear his voice...]
[Sir]
Seon-woo, I told you.
I really like my boyfriend.
I don't want to give you false hope.
What must I say to turn you down for good?
Where did she go?
Woo-yeo told me to keep an eye on her.
Hye-sun.
What are you doing in the snow?
Jae-jin, have you seen Dam?
No.
Why? Do you need to talk to her?
Well, kind of.
I'll go find her,
so stay inside. It's cold.
Come on. We don't need to look so sweet.
There's no one looking anyway...
There is someone looking.
What? Someone looking?
Seok is behind us.
Pretend we're a sweet couple.
Let's go. Smile and walk naturally.
I shouldn't have asked you to date me.
I thought it was a good idea
to get good grades,
but now I'm a bit worried it might get
more complicated than I thought.
Hye-sun.
I'm not seeing you for good grades.
What?
About what happened to us that night
after the festival after-party,
I thought about it a lot,
and I don't think it was just a mistake.
I think you're cute and really cool.
Thinking about you makes me happy.
So don't mind about what others say.
I'm seeing you because I like you.
Is Seok still there?
No, he's still there.
I need to find Dam.
She'll find her way back on her own.
It's snowing a lot, isn't it?
[Should I go?]
[No.]
[If I suddenly show up,
it will look weird.]
I felt that way
because of the red thread?
[Dam, you're arriving
at two tomorrow, right?]
[Sir]
[I'll pick you up.]
I promised I wouldn't do anything
that might worry him.
He will probably worry more
if he finds out that I can see it too.
Dam, where have you been?
I've been looking for you.
Why did you look for me?
I couldn't find both you and Seon-woo.
Nothing happened, right?
What?
I heard that you two are tied
with the red thread.
I see. Nothing happened.
That's good.
It's cold. Let's get inside.
Hey, Hye-sun.
Do you think only the person
who you're tied with the red thread
is considered destiny?
Yes and no.
Do you know
why all animals want to be humans?
Only humans can decide their own destiny.
[Third Floor, Platforms]
Good work, guys.
I'll get going now.
Bye.
Let's go.
It was fun.
-Hye-sun, let me help.
-It's okay. It's heavy.
That's why I'm offering help.
Thanks.
Cool.
Should I drive? I'm sure you're tired.
That would be great.
-Bye.
-Can I...
He said Exit Eight.
Are you okay?
You were still around here.
I'm taking a cab here.
How are you going home?
-By car.
-Whose car?
-Well...
-Dam.
Dam is riding my car. Is there an issue?
Hello, Professor.
I'm Gye Seon-woo, and I take your class.
How do you
know Dam?
Is there a reason
why you want to know that, Mr. Gye?
Pardon?
Yes, there is.
Wait.
He's my boyfriend.
What?
I didn't tell anyone
because I didn't want any rumors,
but we met even before
he came to our school.
I'm not taking his classes now,
so there won't be any problem.
What are you talking about?
That's not the problem.
-Then...
-Dam.
I wanted to apologize
for what happened yesterday.
I was going to apologize,
stay away from you
and stop talking to you
if you said so. No, actually,
I thought you wouldn't let me.
But this is not right.
I get that I might not be the one.
But if I'm not,
it at least can't be him either.
What do you mean?
I'm not saying this because of rumors.
I saw it myself.
I don't understand what you're
talking about. What rumors?
The thing is...
[They say Professor Shin
and Professor Seo are going out.]
[Dae-hoon]
[The entire school knows it.]
[Moo-geun]
You should leave.
Whatever I did or didn't,
it's a matter between me and Miss Dam.
Now tell me
what the rumor is.
You know Professor Seo Young-ju.
Yes, she teaches Ancient History.
I had a cup of coffee with her
because of work,
and apparently that made false rumors
that we date.
Gosh, I got scared for nothing.
So it's not a big deal, right?
Of course. It's not.
By the way,
did something happen yesterday?
What?
He said he wanted to apologize
for what happened yesterday.
Oh, that.
If you don't want to talk about it,
you don't have to.
He said he liked me.
I kept getting involved with him
because of the red thread.
I tried to be careful
because I didn't want to worry you,
but one thing led to another,
and it happened.
I don't know
how honest I should be with you,
but I thought I should tell you this.
Thank you for being honest with me.
[Why is he holding it like that?]
[He must have been worried.]
[Look what I have done
to the person I care for.]
[Only humans can decide
their own destiny.]
[Okay.]
[I will make the decision.]
I'd like a chicken sandwich
with extra avocados.
For the sauce, please drizzle the one
you think would go well with it.
Okay.
What a shame. You were of great help.
I'm sorry I'm quitting
on such short notice.
It's okay.
You must have your own situation.
I hope to see you again one day.
I hope so too. Thank you for everything.
Thank you.
Hi, Uncle.
Hey, Dam is quitting.
It's because of you, right?
You made her feel uncomfortable.
Well, it's...
Did you think I wouldn't know
you had a crush on her?
You always waited for her to come
and did all the work for her.
Since when you've been
such a devoted type?
Seon-woo.
Being too nice to women
only pushes them away.
If you want to keep her, let her free.
If you want a passionate love,
be cold to her.
If I had given you
this wonderful tip earlier, you...
-I would have become an old single man.
-That's right. An old single...
Anyway, I think it's for the best.
You guys made me feel awkward.
She probably has someone better than you.
If he was actually a good person,
I would have given up.
Sir, I decided to quit the job.
The work was harder than I thought.
Let me know if you need any help.
Good luck with the class.
I'll talk to you later.
Professor Shin.
Hey.
Why the long face?
Well...
I probably shouldn't have joined the club.
Why? You were the first one
to raise your hand
and say things like, "I'd like to provide
help to Professor Shin."
It turned out he didn't need my help.
Apparently, Professor Seo
and Professor Shin are going out.
I'm sure Professor Seo provides him
a lot of help,
which is love.
I heard it's not true.
I heard they just had a cup of coffee
because of work.
Hey, who talks about work
holding other's hand so tightly?
You don't know anything.
Dam, aren't you just
envious of Professor Seo?
I wonder what it feels like
to date a man like Professor Shin.
I'm sure you feel on top of the world.
[It can't be true.
He said it was nothing.]
Hey, it looks like the rumors were right.
I just saw Professor Seo on my way here.
And she was walking
into Professor Shin's office.
They must be really going out.
Hey, we all know it.
We all do.
-I need to go somewhere.
-What?
Where? The class is starting soon.
What's going on with her?
[Professor's Office]
Thanks for the coffee.
Are you free this evening?
There's a fine dining restaurant I like,
and the chef is...
Professor Shin?
Is this what you meant
when you said you had a way?
Wait. I can explain.
How will you explain that?
Miss Dam.
You were trying to hurt others
instead of me.
Wait up.
-Hurry.
-Where are you going?
[Professor's Office]
I can explain.
Let me ask you one thing.
And I really wish your answer is no.
Miss Dam.
You urgently needed some energy
because of me,
and you put someone in danger
instead of putting me in danger.
Am I right?
Because of me?
Did you do what you did to me?
There was no other way.
You could have told me
there was no way then.
You should have been honest with me.
I know I'm horrible,
but could you just...
Could you just bear with it?
I was willing to bear with it.
Even if I always had to be scared to death
just to hold your hand,
I was willing to bear it.
I wanted this relationship
despite of everything.
Though you were not a human,
you lied to me and you used me,
I liked you.
So many things scared and worried me,
but all I cared about is
if I would hurt you.
And how could you do this to me?
Miss Dam.
Let's...
stop this.
[We appreciate Shim Hyoung-tak,
Go Kyung-pyo, and Son Sung-yoon]
[for the guest appearances.]
[My Roommate is a Gumiho]
[I was fully convinced
that he was a good person.]
[Professor Shin Woo-yeo]
[The Marble has changed.
So I had a vain dream.]
[She's a human. Of course,
she doesn't understand this situation.]
[I'm sorry]
[I like you.]
The Marble started to turn blue.
[If someone can help him,]
[that would be me.]
[You might be the only one
who can make him humane.]