♪Confessing to the moon
in the rustling wind back then♪
♪Like a boat being swallowed up
among the cities♪
♪Scared to hear the flowers falling
with so many worries to consider♪
♪Am I going to where I want♪
♪Staying or leaving depends on you♪
♪Nations are different♪
♪No desires in the world,
refusing to be vivid♪
♪Looking at the sky side by side♪
♪The years are passing by♪
♪One look can empty Chang'an♪
♪Among the ridiculous people
and things is me♪
=Dream of Chang'An=
=Episode 7=
Since Zheng Wu appeared,
I've become suspicious.
Who helped her get into the Palace?
Who forced her to attempt
an assassination on Qiu Ziliang?
And who arranged the assassin
to attempt an assassination
on Your Majesty at the Wine Shop?
You're saying
that Qiu Yanzhi did all of that?
Yes.
Qiu Ziliang is suspicious of
Violet Bureau,
so he arranged for Zheng Wu
to come here.
Who knew that the real training
occurred in Yuzhen Hall?
There was nothing suspicious
with Violet Bureau itself.
That was why
she forced Zheng Wu to perform
the assassination,
and use this opportunity
to openly investigate the Violet Bureau.
Right.
But they didn't find any proof,
so they decided
to arrange
a Wine Shop assassination.
For the Wine Shop's murder incident,
Mrs. Cai should have
investigated Zheng Wu.
But because of my protection,
I commanded the Commissioner
of the Capital
to keep the matter low-key,
so they think
that Cai's Wine Shop is mine.
They arrested Madam Cai
and tortured her.
I had no choice but to send
a warrior of sacrifice
to kill her.
Yet I fell into their trap
and led them in finding Yuzhen Hall.
In my accounting records,
a big sum of money
went into Cai's Wine Shop.
I
also went there to investigate.
And I ended up following your niece
to Yuzhen Hall as well.
Madam Cheng.
If I didn't
find out myself,
how long are you planning to hide this?
You're incredible.
You're just a fifth-rank official,
and you used my money
to support 300 warriors of sacrifice.
What exactly are you planning to do?
I committed a crime.
I'm willing to accept punishment.
After Yu'er recovers,
let her take over Yuzhen Hall.
I...
But Your Majesty,
hasn't Yu'er already been fired?
Starting today,
Cheng Ruoyu is reinstated
to her position.
And she will manage both
the Violet Bureau and Yuzhen Hall
and become a real Sword Bearer.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
I...
Can you let me check Yu'er's pulse?
My medical skills are crude.
I'm afraid I can't do anything.
But I have an idea.
I don't know if I should tell you.
Go ahead.
His Highness Prince Guang
has great medical skills.
I wonder if I can
bring Yu'er to him to get treated.
Sure.
I'll bring her there myself.
Madam Cheng.
Starting today,
stay in the Violet Bureau
and focus on recovering.
You may go now.
Yes.
Rosa rubus.
That's the herb's name.
It looks very ordinary,
yet it has such a unique name.
They say that there was a tribulation
in heaven back then.
Lightning struck,
and everything was eliminated.
Only this herb remained.
Buddha smiled
when he saw it.
It's so tenacious.
It's quite similar
to that person inside.
Yu'er needs to rest to recover
from her injury.
Let her return to the Palace
only after she recovers.
As for Qi Rong,
I already asked someone
to send him
to a relative in Huainan.
In the next few days,
don't act by yourself
as much as possible.
Thank you, Uncle.
I won't drink anymore.
You're suspecting Prince Guang?
I gave it some thought.
If the Violet Bureau
fights with the Chess of Generals Camp,
and Qi Yan fights with Father,
the one who will benefit the most
is Prince Guang.
But even if His Majesty is killed,
he won't be the emperor.
There are still a bunch
of young royal princes
who are easier to control.
What if
he has the posthumous edict?
If Prince Guang has the late emperor's
posthumous edict,
then if Qi Yan
and Father bring destruction
upon each other,
he can legitimately ascend
to the throne then.
But the problem
is that he couldn't have gotten
the posthumous edict.
Why not?
If he couldn't get it,
he'd think that Father
has it.
But Eunuch Qiu doesn't.
We know that,
but others don't.
Guards.
Chess Overseer.
What have Prince Guang been doing
in the past few days?
Chess Overseer.
Aside from tending to plants,
he never left the cottage.
He only has one servant
named Yuan Du,
who goes down the mountain
to buy necessities sometimes.
Yes.
Since Prince Guang is suspicious,
let's go and sound him out.
When I insisted on living in seclusion
in the mountains back then,
the late emperor asked me why.
I told him
that it was to distance myself
from strife.
Back then, the late emperor
may have been under house arrest,
but his life wasn't in danger.
But Your Majesty is different.
Since you ascended to the throne,
you were in danger numerous times.
Do you know why?
Why?
Two reasons.
First.
You have martial arts skills.
Second.
You like using martial arts.
If the late emperor found out
about what happened to Qi Rong,
he'd surely send people
to check the Chess of Generals Camp.
Yet Your Majesty
went there yourself.
And for the Yuzhen Hall,
Your Majesty shouldn't
have personally gone there.
Around me...
You still have me.
I'll go back.
Uncle.
Are you serious?
But Your Majesty,
you can't act with undue haste
regarding this matter.
You must find the right opportunity.
Uncle.
My heart is like my blood,
forever loyal to Xing.
My blood is like my heart,
it swears to kill traitors.
Thank you, Uncle.
Come in.
Since you're here,
have some tea.
Are you skilled in martial arts?
No.
Then how did you know that I'm here?
Every being has a soul.
Every plant and tree has life.
Every plant, tree,
and beings here
has senses.
It's poisonous.
Which poison is it?
It's deadly.
(Chess of Generals Camp
You Ma)
You Ma.
Why are you here?
I'm monitoring things.
Out in the open?
I've learned from you.
Actually,
I just came to see
if you're doing well lately,
Prince Guang.
Thank you for your concern.
Please report to Chess Overseer
that I'm doing well.
I'm not up to no good.
It's not up to you to say
whether you're up to no good or not.
It's up to us to determine that.
He's not up to no good.
You Ma.
The late emperor said
that if the new emperor
has high aspirations,
I can assist him.
My heart is like my blood,
forever loyal to Xing.
My blood is like my heart,
it swears to kill traitors.
Do you believe
what they said?
(If I can't even find)
(who the enemy is)
(and why they're here,)
(how can I use my sword)
(to protect the emperor?)
(Protecting the emperor's safety)
(and preventing you from encountering
another assassination attempt)
is what a Sword Bearer
should do.
I don't believe
what they said.
But you're different.
Maybe
you're really my Sword Bearer.
Guards.
Your Majesty.
Find someone to repair this sword.
It must be exactly the same as before.
Yes.
His Majesty has arrived!
Greetings, Grandmother.
Come.
Have a seat.
I heard that Your Majesty is finally
attending the imperial court meeting.
Yes.
Before that,
there's something
I want to discuss with you.
How strange.
If you need anything,
shouldn't you discuss it with Duke Chu
instead of me?
I can only consult you with this matter.
Your birthday
is next month.
I
would like to let Prince Guang come back
to make arrangements for this.
I don't like Qi Chen.
I know.
I can't believe
that you're letting someone I dislike
arrange my birthday banquet.
Grandmother.
I also know
that Prince Guang's birth mother
betrayed you back then
and had Prince Guang.
That's why
you've never liked him.
Do you like him?
All these years,
the rumors outside
are very spectacular.
They say that he should be the emperor.
They say
that Emperors Muzong and Wenzong
both wanted to pass the throne to him.
They say that you usurped his empire.
Grandmother.
That is why
we should let him return all the more,
so that the whole nation can see
who exactly
acts like an emperor more.
Grandmother.
I need someone to assist me.
It's more like you're bringing a fox
into your house.
At least this wolf
is part of the family.
With regards to how those rumors
leaked out,
I think you know that
more clearly than me.
That's right.
I asked people to spread it.
Why?
Because I don't like him.
I wanted your father to kill him.
How can the son of a maid
who washes feet
deserve such favor?
Father didn't kill him.
My brother didn't kill him either.
I
won't kill him as well.
I know
that you don't like him.
Qiu Ziliang also knows
That is why
he'll surely agree for him
to return to the capital.
Please
help me.
Your Majesty can make the decision
on your own.
You don't need to discuss with me.
Thank you, Grandmother.
Madam Xiu.
Grand Empress Dowager.
He's the fifth emperor
in my lifetime.
He's also the one
I can't read the most.
I heard that His Majesty and Duke Chu
are not in good terms now.
Back then,
when he acknowledged Duke Chu
as his godfather,
I knew
that this day would come.
Did you see his eyes clearly?
They're an eagle's eyes.
Duke Chu is proud to be
an eagle taming expert.
But this eagle
will blind him in the end.
- Long live Your Majesty!
Rise.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
Next month is
Grand Empress Dowager's 70th birthday.
Officials.
Any ideas on how we'll make
the arrangements?
(Shencai Army Commander Yuan Xing)
Grand Empress Dowager
told me this morning
that it doesn't have
to be a big celebration.
But she wants to benefit the citizens.
I gave it some thought.
What if we give out clothes and food
and celebrate together
with the citizens?
But who will handle
this matter?
Duke Chu.
Any suitable candidates?
How would I dare to comment
about Grand Empress Dowager's birthday?
Your Majesty should make the decision.
I thought about it.
What if
we ask Prince Guang to do it?
What do you think, Duke Chu?
All right.
Let's do that.
Officials, anything else
you want to report?
GrandFather.
Why is Qi Yan
summoning Prince Guang back?
Prince Guang
and Grand Empress Dowager Guo
have never gotten along.
Why would His Majesty let Prince Guang
make arrangements
for the birthday banquet?
Right.
(Shencai Army Commander Jiang Ding)
Do you know about this?
Summon You Ma.
Come.
When did Qi Yan
speak with Prince Guang?
Yesterday
at 1pm.
You were there?
Yes.
It's really just
for Grand Empress Dowager's birthday,
and nothing else?
Yes.
All right.
I got it.
You may go.
Father.
I heard that Prince Guang's birth mother
was Grand Empress Dowager's maid.
She seduced the emperor
when Grand Empress Dowager was pregnant.
This matter
has always been like a bone
in the throat for her.
That's interesting.
How can His Majesty let Prince Guang
handle this matter,
and why did Prince Guang agree?
What do you think?
I think there's only one possibility.
They want to work together
*They want to work together
against you.
I've asked You Ma
to monitor Prince Guang
for eight years.
He always said that he behaves properly.
The imperial court even sends
new provincial military commissioners
every four years.
Because if someone
is with another person for too long,
he doesn't only develop feelings,
he understands him.
You mean
Prince Guang bought off You Ma?
I don't dare to speculate about that.
Is there a problem?
I came to say goodbye.
They're suspecting you?
It's fine.
We can't blame them
for being suspicious.
You've been monitoring me
for many years,
yet you couldn't report anything
about me.
I have a clear conscience.
Yes.
You have a clear conscience.
Me too.
This is for you.
Thank you
for letting me live in peace
for so many years.
No.
Take it.
You've been staring at it
for so many years.
I know that you like it.
Grand Councilor of the Left.
(Slow and stead wins the race)
(Chess of Generals Camp
Grand Councilor of the Left)
Grand Councilor of the Left.
This lady is so pitiful.
Her husband bullies her,
and she has bad parent-in-laws.
Liu Yi.
You must save her from disaster.
What a shame.
I originally wanted
to give Grand Councilor of the Left
the new "Legend of Liu Yi".
Since he's not here,
I can only give it to someone else.
Wait.
It turns out that you're here.
Let me see.
(Legend of Liu Yi)
Tell me.
What do you want?
Rosa rubus.
Rosa rubus?
Its stem is poisonous.
You'll have hallucinations
if you smell it.
You'll slowly die with a smile
if you eat it.
It causes hallucinations?
Does the person poisoned with it knows?
Do you know about Zhuangzi's dream?
Zhuangzi isn't sure if he dreamed
of becoming a butterfly,
or if the butterfly dreamed
of becoming him.
Is there a way to know
if someone is poisoned
with rosa rubus?
Of course.
It's the same with addiction to pills.
The person needs to continue taking it.
Once he stops,
he'd feel unbearably hot.
The consequences are unimaginable
if it's not handled well.
Thank you, Grand Councilor of the Left.
(Slow and stead wins the race)
(Chess of Generals Camp)
That's not right.
What's not right?
Everything.
Even if rosa rubus is rare,
I only found out that it's poisonous
after asking Grand Councilor of the Left.
But there must be others
who know about this.
If Prince Guang is controlling
You Ma this way,
then Prince Guang should have
destroyed it immediately
after he left.
Why did he openly give him one?
(Chess of Generals Camp)
Didn't he tell you that herb is fishy?
If you don't smell it,
it feels unbearable.
But there are many reasons
for feeling unbearable.
Who would suspect an herb?
Could it be
that there's nothing wrong
with that herb,
and You Ma is not being
controlled either?
There must be something fishy
with that herb.
I'm sure You Ma is being controlled
by it too.
However,
he openly sent such a big loophole
in front of me.
Does he have other intentions?
Other intentions?
He's sounding me out.
Rosa rubus.
He wants to see me.
Why are you up?
Savior.
Does it still hurt?
Not anymore.
However,
before fainting,
His Majesty was reprimanding Aunt.
I can't accept it
when I think about that.
Don't worry.
Madam Cheng will be fine.
His Majesty won't give her a hard time.
Drink your medicine.
Thank you, Savior.
Drink it slower.
Savior.
When will my injury
be fully healed?
You're in good health.
Your injury isn't a big deal.
But we must treat
your headaches.
Cheng Ruoyu.
Who are you?
Was it really just a dream?
Savior.
How did I get here?
I brought you here.
- Your Majesty.
Cheng Ruoyu.
It turns out that you and Uncle
have known each other for a long time.
I once fell into the hands
of human traffickers.
Fortunately, he saved me.
That was how I was able to find Aunt.
Everything in this world
is a result of karma and destiny.
I saved Yu'er.
Yu'er saved you.
It's all karma.
Go on chatting.
I have to go out for a while.
It's yours.
Mine?
Open it.
Wasn't the sword broken?
It was remade.
I told you that I'll give you one
as compensation.
You said you'll give me 100 of them.
Is that so?
Then return this to me.
There's no need.
I'm not greedy.
I just need one.
One is fine.
Since you got the Qingguang Sword,
let's go.
Where are we going?
Have you forgotten?
I told you.
You'll take over the Violet Bureau
and Yuzhen Hall from now on.
So
you can return to the Palace
with me now.
What's the matter?
You don't want to go back?
Your Majesty.
Don't you
trust Aunt anymore?
What do you think?
Then why do you trust
her niece,
me?
You're different from your aunt.
I gave up on Cheng Xi,
yet I kept Huaizhi.
It's also because
Huaizhi is different from Cheng Xi.
Even if you're relatives,
I'll consider you two separately.
However,
I'm not confident.
I entered the palace
to become a maid in Violet Bureau
not because I like it,
but because Aunt is there.
I practiced the sword
to become the Sword Bearer
not because I like it too,
but because Aunt wanted me to do it.
I'm by your side
because Aunt
told me to protect you.
Everything I did
was for Aunt.
If Aunt told me to go against you,
I...
So
you'll turn your sword towards me?
I don't know.
Maybe I will,
maybe I won't.
That's why
I'm not confident.
Your Majesty should ask
someone else to do it.
Why are you choosing me?
Why is it me?
Why me?
What is an emperor?
An emperor
is someone who doesn't have a choice.
I don't have a choice.
And my fifth brother,
you don't have a choice either.
I'm very happy
that you spoke honestly.
It's very rare for me to hear
honest words anymore.
No one tells me the truth.
In that case,
keep this sword well.
Your Majesty.
Stop acting on your own anymore.
What happened this time
surely has something to do with Wu.
You must continue investigating.
I don't need to.
But can you really bear
the repeated assassination attempts?
You won't be safe each time.
Mind your manners.
Your Majesty.
If you agree
for me to continue investigating
Wu's case,
I'll return to the palace with you.
Only you
can clear Wu's reputation.
And only you
can give Aunt
an opportunity to make up
for her mistake.
Also,
even if I don't deserve to be
the Sword Bearer,
Qiu Yanzhi
doesn't deserve to be
the Chess Overseer all the more.
The Violet Bureau is my home.
I can't let it fall
into Qiu Yanzhi's hands.
Aside from me,
no one can help you
deal with Qiu Yanzhi now.
You're quite confident
about yourself.
In saying that,
that means he agrees?
Your Majesty.
If you agree,
can you tell me
the truth?
What do you want to know?
Did you really release Wu?
Yes.
Does she know then?
She doesn't.
In front of everyone,
I shot an arrow towards her.
Not long after she fainted,
I wore a mask,
treated her, and sent her outside
of Heng'an.
Why did you spare her?
You want to know the truth?
I was testing the arrow.
What?
I want to know
if I intentionally deviated a shot
using a specially-made arrowhead,
causing one to suffocate and appear dead,
can she be saved?
Why?
Because if that trick works,
it will be very useful.
Then why
did you allow Wu to die?
Your Majesty
is afraid that when they check
Wu's wound,
they'll find out that you spared her?
Yes.
I spared her life,
yet she had a death wish.
What's the use of keeping her alive?
Cheng Ruoyu, listen carefully.
You can investigate the case,
but you must take good care of yourself.
And you can't disregard your life.
Why do you keep staring at me?
Fireflies?
Fireflies.
Your Majesty, look.
There are so many of them.
Your Majesty.
Look.
(I can only tell you half
of the truth now,)
(and keep the other half.)
(Someday,)
(I hope that you can really make me
tell you everything.)
- Greetings, Sword Bearer.
This is the detailed list
of Yuzhen Hall's 300 members.
They're in Mount Qi?
Yes.
After things have quieted down,
find a way
to get them back to the capital.
How would I let them obey me then?
The Qingguang Sword is the token.
Whoever has that sword
is their master.
That's why
I already planned
to let you manage all of these
since before.
Aunt.
There's one thing I want
to confirm with you.
What is it?
Did you
really send someone to kill Mrs. Cai?
Yes.
Why are you...
Why am I so heartless?
Open these musical scores.
(Song of Sword)
In order to escape the notice of others,
Yuzhen Hall's actions
were all written in code.
Assist means slow.
Hay means quick.
Omit means stop.
Like this one,
three assists, two hays, five omits.
It means three people going slowly,
two people going quickly,
five people stopping.
What about this?
Death.
The Yuzhen Hall isn't the Violet Bureau.
The people there
have all received the harshest training.
They're ready to die for their mission
at any time.
In the same way,
you must also have that realization.
What does the Sword Bearer use
to protect the emperor?
Her sword?
No.
Her life.
You're his second life.
♪Life is a dream,
how long do happy times last♪
♪In the windy rain,
where will my heart settle?♪
♪The sword can't break this karma♪
♪Look how blurry
and lonely the world is♪
♪Fate can't do anything
about the bleak bonds of this world♪
♪Still can't let go of this life
as time goes by♪
♪Even the iron and golden dagger-axe
cannot extinguish the fire in my heart♪
♪Remembering the past
and letting time while away♪
♪The past is in front of you♪
♪Forgetting while piecing it together♪
♪Like when I sincerely
put my hands together♪
♪I only wish that you can be saved♪
♪The past is in front of you♪
♪Forgetting while piecing it together♪
♪Like when I sincerely
put my hands together♪
♪I only wish that you can be saved♪