[English subtitles are available]
[Ji Sung]
[Kim Min-jung]
[Jinyoung]
[Park Gyu-young]
[Moon Yu-seok]
[Choi Jung-gyu]
[The Devil Judge]
[We would like to announce that
the cathedral fire scene from Episode 4]
[was not meant to portray
a certain character as an evil person.]
[We would like to apologize
to all firefighters and viewers]
[whom we may have disturbed.]
[This drama was set
in the dystopian future of Korea.]
[All characters, organizations,
places, and events are fictional.]
Did you have a bad dream?
You don't look well.
Are you okay?
Don't touch me.
What's wrong?
What are you two doing?
What do you want?
Oh. Am I being the third wheel?
What are you doing here?
I had something to say to you,
but I suppose I should wait.
You don't look very well.
What was that earlier?
What do you mean?
I mean, when you woke up.
Why were you so surprised?
It's not like you.
You seemed really flustered.
What are you trying to say?
You looked like you saw
the face of someone you killed.
I don't care
about those who are already killed.
That is, if they were killed by me.
[Episode 5]
Mr. Kang.
I'm sorry for what happened yesterday.
Even if you kick me out,
I'll have nothing to say.
Kick you out?
After everything you have been through,
you had to hear
that you killed your brother.
I'm really sorry.
[Ethology]
Right.
That wasn't the kind of thing
I wanted to hear from this face.
I understand
you don't want to see my face.
I'll leave the department.
You don't need to apologize
for a coincidence.
The two of you look alike,
and that's just a coincidence.
There's more.
There's more?
You know I have been
suspecting and spying on you.
I wonder how much you found out.
You've been preparing
for this hunt for a long time.
What do you mean?
I read all your past court records.
And I found that you used to
judge like a robot,
following the practice.
Hunters must hide their smells completely.
Until the right time comes.
I have no idea why I did that.
I got my son in my old age,
and he's more precious
than anything to me.
[Judge]
It's because of the darn alcohol.
I was raising my hand before I knew it.
After beating the boy into a pulp,
that's your excuse?
Your Honor, please kill me!
After getting fired,
I was pushed from pillar to post.
[Judge]
The darn money made my life miserable.
I must have lost my mind.
This is not your first time.
The defendant has been assaulting
his wife and son for several years.
He must be punished severely.
I'm sorry, Your Honor.
Please forgive me this once!
I deserve to die.
[I will never hit my wife again!]
[Please forgive me this once!]
[I promise I'll be good.]
[Please forgive me just this once.
Please.]
[I was bad.]
[If you forgive me just this once,
I will never even touch them!]
Please...
[Judge]
[Court]
The victim's family has filed a petition
to be lenient with the defendant.
[Court]
[Judge]
And the defendant was intoxicated
when he committed the crime.
Given these factors, I will
suspend the punishment for the defendant.
Your Honor!
[9A3 2364]
[Court]
-I don't understand this.
-What is this?
How could he do that?
But there's just one thing.
I can't figure out your motive.
I just can't understand you.
You probably can't.
But when it has to do with your rage,
I can understand that.
You can understand that?
The whole world might not understand you,
but I will understand
how you must have felt.
However, what's wrong is still wrong.
Using the court as your weapon is a crime.
How ridiculous.
I've never asked you to understand me.
I don't need you to understand me.
I just need you to decide.
Will you get in my way?
Or will you stand with me?
For your information, I do not hesitate
when I have to get rid of people
who get in my way.
I'm well aware of that.
You may leave.
I won't kick you out.
Come back to work.
Having you around is fun.
I expected this...
Then, why the long face?
I'm not sure.
Having someone sympathize with me
is quite flustering.
I rarely had to deal
with something like this.
Anyway,
any movements from Cha Kyung-hee?
Ma'am.
This isn't a place
where you can casually walk in and out.
Please leave.
Please leave now. Don't just stand there.
Minister Cha.
Well, your son's punishment, flogging,
hasn't been fully executed yet.
You cannot see him yet.
Grade Nine, Guard Park Young-jin.
[Park Young-jin]
Yes, ma'am.
Have you seen the organization chart
of Korea Correctional Service?
Pardon?
The warden is in charge of this facility.
And above the warden, there's a chief
of regional corrections services
who oversees
detention centers and prisons.
And above the chief,
there's the commissioner who supervises
the chiefs from all over Korea.
Yes. I'm aware of that.
And I supervise the commissioner.
I'm not some inmate's family.
I am here as the Minister who's
in charge of Korea Correctional Service.
Out of my way.
Yes, ma'am.
Keep a close eye on him
until his sentence is fully carried out.
Yes, ma'am.
You're cooking today. That's new.
Well, we are having a guest after all.
A guest?
I'm no guest.
Although he's an unwelcome guest.
I see.
Do you like Korean food, by the way?
That's the only cuisine I can cook.
I love Korean food.
What are you doing here?
My apologies, Young Master.
Since there's a guest,
we should at least--
I told you to leave before the sun sets.
I'm sorry.
Ma'am.
You were just trying to be nice to me.
Why is he so mean?
I guess he's suspicious
that I might add poison to his food.
He must be feeling guilty
because of what he's done.
Do you honestly believe it was his doing?
The boy whom you raised yourself?
Be honest.
You don't want to believe that, right?
I'm sorry,
but please throw out the ingredients.
Or they will attract bugs.
Gosh. Come on.
Must you do this at the Blue House?
[President]
Hey, you don't know anything.
Because of Kang Yo-han,
no one is paying attention to us.
We have to do something.
Hey, this is working. I haven't used this
for ages, but it works.
Hey, go outside.
Hello.
["Heo Joong-se Hits the Spot"]
[A total change to Korea!]
[-It's the President.
-A total change to Korea!]
[-Have you all been well?
-I've been waiting!]
[This is "Heo Joong-se..."]
"Hits the Spot!"
[Guess where I am.
You know where I am, right?]
[-It's been so long.
-What's today's show about?]
[-This is huge.
-Our President is the best!]
[It's my residence.]
This is the first and exclusive tour
of the Blue House for you!
[An exclusive live stream
for the tour of the Blue House.]
[-This one will be legendary.
-The Blue House?]
We're going to start right now!
[Come with me.]
[-This will be so fun.
-I can't believe this.]
All right.
Here's what I think.
I'm no more than a mere servant
of our dear people.
That's what my role is for you.
[-Let's go. We can just stay with him.
-A servant?]
[You know, I make a great servant.]
[-I'll support you forever.
-Let's give it up for him!]
[Ma'am!]
[-I love you and respect you.
-You're the best President.]
[It's been a while, everyone.
You've all been well, right?]
[-He's calling his wife.
-No way!]
[-What?
-This is crazy.]
[-I'm so jealous of him.
-She's so beautiful.]
[Thank you.]
["How is she that pretty?"
"She's still as classy as ever."]
[-Can you hold a fan meet-up?
-She should always be on the show!]
[It's all thanks to your support.]
You will be joining us...
[for the tour of the Blue House.]
[-No way. Let's go.
-She's the prettiest lady in Korea.]
[-I love this show.
-We love you, Mr. President!]
[-We'll begin now.
-Go, go.]
What do you think? Now that
you're getting a glimpse of our life here,
[Isn't it interesting?]
[-I'm so curious.
-Go, go!]
[Yes, it was very interesting for me too.]
[-The Blue House is so intriguing.
-This is crazy.]
[I found it very interesting
at first too.]
[-But it's not that different.]
-Right.
Right. A while ago,
someone tried to renovate our residence.
So I scolded the secretary
who suggested the idea.
[It would all come
from our taxpayers' money.]
[-He's so considerate.
-Gosh, he's amazing.]
[-I respect you.
-I'll work out to be his security detail.]
[It's from our taxpayers. Right?]
Since we're on the subject,
we should move to a smaller residence.
We could expand more welfare centers--
[-Come on, guys. Let's make a donation.
-Make a donation before you speak.]
[You have such amazing ideas.]
[Hurry Cane Cane donated 50,000 won.]
Well, as for this matter,
I've been thinking a lot about it.
I haven't stopped thinking about it.
-Right.
-A lot of people are in need.
This is my favorite room.
[-Thank you, Mr. President.
-He's the best President.]
[I've been doing woodcraft
for a long time.]
[-She's amazing.
-Really? No way.]
[She's an artist.]
[-She's the real patriot.
-She's got a heart of gold too.]
[A while ago, a curator offered
to put my work on display]
[-They are the best couple.
-Can you read our messages?]
[-Gosh. So impressive.
-She's unbelievably amazing.]
[at an art gallery.]
I really hate to cut this short.
But the Cabinet meeting is about to start.
So this will be all for today.
Let's shout our slogan.
[A total change to Korea.]
[-Can you do this more often?
-Can you show it to us more?]
[-Good luck!
-I support you!]
["Heo Joong-se Hits the Spot."
-"Hits the Spot."]
[-"Heo Joong-se Hits the Spot."
-"Heo Joong-se Hits the Spot."]
[-You're the best!
-Bye, everyone!]
[Bye, everyone!]
[Blue House]
Hey.
Why are you bringing up
your exhibition now?
I'm the First Lady of this country.
Holding my own exhibit
won't be any problem.
Hey.
[Even so, you must be so heartbroken.]
[You are still a mother.]
[Talk with Minister Cha Kyung-hee]
[No.]
[Before I was a mother,]
[Talk with Minister Cha Kyung-hee]
[I have the duty to uphold justice.]
[I cannot make any exceptions.]
I am just trying
to fulfill my obligations.
Can there be
another civil servant like her?
Let's give Minister Cha Kyung-hee
another warm round of applause.
["TV Morning Together"]
Thank you.
We love you!
We'll be back
after a short commercial break.
You did so well. You should take a break.
Thank you.
-I'll take a quick break.
-Sure.
You truly impress me.
You turned a crisis into an opportunity.
It seems like the foundation
wants to just sit back and watch.
I must try to survive my own way.
From what I know,
you usually opt for offense
rather than defense.
You look like you prepared something.
I knew it.
You should go back inside.
The show's not over yet.
[Main Conference Room]
[I'm saying this cautiously.]
Regarding the recent flogging,
many people are voicing concern.
Here's a photo we obtained.
["TV Morning Together"]
-My gosh.
-What is that?
[Photo]
"Isn't this too harsh?"
"Isn't it too barbaric
for the 21st century?"
Many are saying that.
No, it's a punishment
he rightfully deserves.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
Also, even though it was a trial,
there were some inhumane scenes.
[As this ruling was joined
by the public's ruling,]
["Live Court Show"]
[it is fair that flogging
must be executed publicly,]
[so everyone will be able to watch it.]
[The executioner of the punishment,
the Ministry of Justice,]
[be aware of this.]
That is what Judge Kang Yo-han said
during the trial.
["Live Court Show"]
This caused a lot of controversies.
What do you all think of this?
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
["TV Morning Together"]
[Can you continue?]
[-Yes, I'm really sorry.
-My gosh.]
[It's all right.]
The public is fickle.
Not bad, I must say.
I must find out
who's behind Cha Kyung-hee.
Kim Ga-on!
My gosh, welcome back!
It still hurts.
Really? I'm sorry.
-Hey, do you know how worried I was?
-Thank you.
Not just me though. Look at that!
What is all this?
Just accept it. You're a celebrity now.
[Beautiful Kim Ga-on]
[Associate Judge Kim Ga-on]
I am grateful, but why...
[Ga-on]
Oh, please.
Too much humility is arrogance.
Attention magnets like us
must live with a sense of responsibility.
That's right.
The sense of responsibility as a star.
Oh, hello.
Congratulations.
He gives off so much glow
just by standing there.
But he bravely threw himself
to save a co-worker before a blast.
He nearly died,
but has miraculously returned to court.
About the special episode
celebrating his survival.
It was so touching.
"Survival"? I wasn't that badly injured.
Come on. Don't be fixated
on such minor details.
The hero's crisis looks better
when it's more serious.
Ms. Oh sure understands storytelling.
It's your natural-born talent.
Maestro.
Diva.
Will I ever get another opportunity
to direct something like this?
I'll put my life on the line
to shoot this episode.
Judges, good luck!
We got this!
-Take care of yourself.
-I will. Thank you.
See you.
-Wait, Director.
-Yes?
You know, that thing... Will it be okay?
What?
Oh, the morning talk show?
Gosh, the minister just had to cry.
[Associate Judge Kim Ga-on]
But don't worry too much.
For a show to be successful,
having issues at the beginning
can be helpful.
It's called noise marketing.
What are you talking about?
Oh, nothing important.
You're still recovering,
so you should take it easy.
[Handsome Kim Ga-on]
I didn't know flogging could leave
such serious marks.
Who knows?
The Ministry of Justice
carries out the execution.
[Idol Judge Kim Ga-on]
[Poverty is guilt,
and money buys you innocence.]
[Unfair rulings]
[Quality Improvement]
Hey, Ga-on.
[Hey, Soo-hyun.]
Are you free this evening?
[Yes, of course.]
I'm free for once.
I'll pick out the menu.
[Okay.]
[Temperature Controlled,
Keep the Door Closed]
Darn it, who...
We're from
the Regional Investigation Unit.
[Sungdo Express Delivery]
You little...
Kang Yo-han has just left work.
I used our connections
in the Prosecutors' Office
but wasn't able to find out
who's behind Cha Kyung-hee.
Really?
Could she have done it on her own?
She manipulated the photo
with the flogging marks
and showed it on a TV show?
She's not into such showmanship.
She'd never do anything
that might leave a trace.
I'll keep digging.
Let's hit the body first.
The foundation's Home of Dreams project.
Did you find out who's organizing it?
Yes, I've made contact with one person.
This Saturday at 4 p.m.
The same place as last time.
Got it. I'll set up the meeting.
[Master Ga-on left a message for you.]
A message?
[You just need to heat up
the rice and the soup.]
[Eat it all up.]
[That way, you can sleep well.]
[If you keep skipping meals,]
[you'll get more wrinkles.]
[You're not young anymore.]
I don't have any wrinkles--
[Wrinkles. Caused by the aging of skin,]
[they appear folded
as the skin loses elasticity.]
"Master Ga-on"?
Since when did you have another owner?
Are you deciding who owns you now?
The manual didn't mention
a function like that.
You're pretending to be asleep again.
Don't pretend to be asleep.
It's good.
Detective Park,
we still have something to talk about.
Where's your big severance pay from?
Get lost. I have nothing to tell you.
I've checked everything.
From your debt for gambling
to opening this business,
it cost you over a billion won.
Since when was the severance pay
for police officers so generous?
Let me guess.
In exchange for covering up the case,
Kang Yo-han--
No, let me guess.
How much did you receive
from the foundation?
It was the foundation?
[Real Estate Consulting]
Kim Ga-on,
what on earth have you found out?
What a story.
But how can we believe it?
That's just Kang Yo-han's claim.
That's right.
Which is why I was here to check.
There's something that bothers me too.
What is it?
How all the people present on the site
and everything else was hidden.
That's not something Kang Yo-han
could've done alone ten years ago.
He would've had to stop
the prosecution and the press.
-Right.
-But even then,
what about canceling
the donation agreement?
Wasn't that to take his brother's money?
That could be the case,
but if what Kang Yo-han said is true,
I would've done the same
after finding out how trashy they are.
Whatever it may be, what's sure is
that Kang Yo-han is doing something
very risky right now.
I'll take care of this case.
You just keep your distance from him.
-You haven't changed a bit.
-What?
[Ga-on, I told you]
[that they're dangerous kids.]
Come here.
Come on.
You're a mess right now.
Ga-on, stop scarring your face.
You're going to be in some real trouble
if you keep this up.
You need to think about your parents
looking out for you from the above.
They must be so heartbroken
to see you like this.
Soo-hyun.
[I'll be careful. Don't you worry.]
And don't you misunderstand.
Misunderstand?
Whether Kang Yo-han has a story or not,
it doesn't change anything.
There's no person without a story.
But that doesn't make
everyone go around breaking the law.
You're right.
You're a great policewoman, indeed.
What are you talking about?
[Report Card]
Your grades are up again.
[Ranking: 6th out of all 446 students]
Soo-hyun, you're amazing.
It seems like you'll make it
to the police college.
Do you really think so?
Of course.
But Soo-hyun, do you have to go there?
You could go to any other great college
with these grades.
I have to go there.
Why? To become the chief?
No.
Then what?
There's someone I want to help out.
Help out?
There's someone
who keeps getting in trouble,
and I want to make sure
he doesn't stay in jail.
I'm not that great of a policewoman
that you think I am.
You're an awful one, then.
-Soo-hyun,
-Yes?
can you be a real awful policewoman
just this time?
Things have gotten out of my hands.
From the press to Minister of Justice
and President.
You saw that detective earlier, right?
I'm scared
that something might happen to you.
Can we be lame and fearful?
It's too late for that.
I'd like to go forward with this case
for the next live trial...
No, let's do another case.
Another case?
The Prosecution is insisting
on one particular case.
Is that right?
It's not always best
for one judge to take all the spotlight.
Let's give them a chance.
Since we said we'd negotiate
on all the future cases
for the live trial,
let's do so.
We're just starting. Shouldn't we focus
on making it succeed?
Calming the public down is our priority.
If you find it so difficult to comply,
[Supreme Court]
there are many other excellent judges
available in the country,
though they may not be
as great as you are.
Is that right?
Don't forget who holds the key, Mr. Kang.
I'll keep that in mind.
You indeed haven't forgotten
who holds your key.
Mr. Kang!
Viewers,
please welcome the judges
who will run the trial today!
[You will be the judge.]
Today, after overcoming death,
we have
Judge Kim Ga-on back with us!
We love you, Kim Ga-on!
[The star of judges, Kim Ga-on]
[Beautiful Kim Ga-on]
["Live Court Show"]
[I'm suing Judge Kim
for stealing my heart!]
Kim Ga-on!
Don't be surprised by today's defendant.
He's a big-shot, Korea's actor,
Nam Seok-hoon.
[Defendant]
[A celebrity instead of someone in power.]
We, the prosecutors, will put an end
["Sexual Harassments Needs
Tougher Punishments."]
to all the sexual harassment
in the movie and showbiz industries.
In the name of Korea's people,
the Prosecution demands
[Defendant]
for Nam Seok-hoon be arraigned
for constant sexual harassment.
A cameo, a stylist, and a colleague.
That's 3 cases of rape
and 2 cases of sexual harassment.
Defendant?
Do you admit your charges?
[Court]
I do.
[I can't admit it.]
I may have made a few drunken mistakes,
but sexual assault?
"Mistake"?
[Yes, Seok-hoon.]
Listen to your senior and just come.
We should practice acting together.
But it's a bit too late now.
[Can we do it tomorrow?]
What are you talking about?
Tomorrow is the shoot!
I'm sorry.
I'll be right there.
What do I do?
You call that a mistake, Mr. Nam?
Well, she flirted with me first.
There are so many girls
who would like to be in my favor.
I'm a father of a daughter myself.
Me? Rapist?
That's just ridiculous.
And honestly,
there's no evidence, is there?
Can you prove it?
We live in a high-tech world these days.
-What?
-That thing you hammered and threw away.
This hard disk.
Even this can be restored these days.
I understand everyone has
secret porn videos.
But you seem to have
a very unique taste in pornography.
-I...
-You're a paid-up member of the VIP room.
I heard the membership fee was
pretty expensive.
That's...
Your family will be a bit surprised
to find out about your hobby.
Especially your daughter.
Don't you think?
The defendant has been
habitually committing sexual assaults
using his power
in the entertainment industry.
Thus, the prosecution suggests
20 years of imprisonment
along with treatments
for compulsive sexual behavior
to prevent additional crimes.
What?
It can't be...
Treatments for compulsive sexual behavior,
you mean by chemical castration?
[Chemical Castration]
The chemical method is costly,
and can't be the ultimate solution.
Interesting.
-Are you then suggesting--
-Yes.
The prosecution suggests
[Defendant]
physical castration of the defendant.
What? You didn't say this.
Just wait.
-Your Honor, this is nonsense...
-Animals...
don't have human rights.
This is what most of our people want.
Isn't that right, Your Honor?
Yes, it is!
[Defendant]
Cut it off!
Mr. Kang...
[You want me to take a gamble?]
I wouldn't call it a gamble.
It's an assignment for Kang Yo-han.
What if he actually
makes a judgment like that?
You saw people's reactions
when your son's photo was on air.
Watching something happening in reality,
is not necessarily as satisfying
as imagining it.
It's gross just to imagine it.
Mr. Kang must know it too.
He's a smart man.
If he opposes it...
People will be disappointed,
[thinking Judge Kang Yo-han was
not different after all.]
The more they expect,
the more likely they will be disappointed.
Your Honor.
It is a hard assignment indeed.
Your Honor!
I would like to hear
the defendant's opinion in the next trial.
[Defendant's Counsel, Defendant]
This court is adjourned.
[Prosecution]
["Neutering, Pet Owners' Biggest Concern.
Why Is It Recommended?"]
Mr. Kang.
What's that?
These?
They're really sharp.
They were made
by a 100-year-old German company.
The artisans carefully--
Not that.
What's the article you're reading?
["Neutering Keeps Your Dogs Healthy"]
These articles?
You're not...
I'm not sure what you mean.
I have always been interested in animals.
And humans are animals too?
Don't say you're imagining
something against human dignity.
That's mean.
I'm used to people treat me
like a monster,
but seeing your face
looking at me like that
breaks my heart.
That's not what I meant.
[Talking like this, I can sway him.]
I was just...
Actually, people might be right.
Some humans are born monsters.
-Sir.
-And some of them just enjoy hunting,
using revenge as an excuse.
Instincts are powerful.
Stop acting cool.
You'd rather be a monster than a victim?
You call yourself a monster
when you don't have the guts
to face your wound?
Talking like this, I can sway you.
Come on down.
Don't.
Don't hit him, please.
This house gives me nothing but pain.
-Come here.
-Hey, don't bother my cat.
-I didn't do anything. The cat came to me.
Didn't you, Ggomi?
Did you name my cat already?
Ggomi? No way.
[What? I think Ggomi likes the name.]
[See? Ggomi isn't moving.]
[Ggomi. Ggomi, come here.]
[-Look.
-Ggomi won't go to you.]
[Don't laugh.]
[I didn't laugh.]
[Do you have evidence that I laughed?]
[I'll kill you.]
[Another death threat?]
Come here.
[What?]
Ggomi is biting it.
Nice. You're strong.
Let's see which one of us she'll pick.
Come here.
Come here. Right here.
She won't go to you.
[All right. Go to Elijah now.]
[-Here.
-Gosh.]
[I told you.
I'm really popular among stray cats.]
[Seriously.]
You like me more, right?
[Answer me right now.]
[Yes?]
I haven't heard from you for a while.
Especially
after you moved into Kang's house.
Is that so?
Well, I wasn't feeling well, you know.
Okay.
Let's go eat.
Goodness.
The weather is great today.
Right?
[Speedy Courier Services]
[The suspension, engine, and frame.]
[That setup is too much for a courier.]
[Speedy Courier Services]
Want to go for a ride?
No.
Don't lie. I know you want to.
[Fair Police with Kind People]
Get in.
I can just drive this.
[Seobu Police Station]
No. Not that...
If you get into trouble again
because of the motorcycle,
that will be the day when you and I die
in front of your parents' graves.
Come on. Get in.
Will you walk?
Close the trunk.
Gosh. Is he a thug or what?
If I get one,
I'll let you ride in the back.
What did you say?
We're at the Supreme Court building.
Lower your voice.
-You...
-Hello.
Hey.
You still haven't learned your lesson.
-You could be an actor.
-What?
Gosh.
No. The leg...
-Hey!
-That's mine! Stop!
-That's mine!
Goodness.
-I'm sorry.
-It's all right.
-It's mine!
-Hey.
-Hey!
-This is the place.
-It's mine.
[Spicy Pork Restaurant]
-Give me back.
-No.
-Give it.
-It doesn't look good.
I don't know what happened at his house.
But you cannot be neutral.
You are already part of his department.
You will have to choose.
You can either become his accomplice
or the whistleblower.
[I just need you to decide.]
Will you get in my way?
Or will you stand with me?
It was you who pushed me
into his department.
Trying to control my heart
is already hard as it is.
Why must I burden myself
with the world's trouble?
Goodness. That's so gruesome.
[The controversy regarding flogging
has begun to gain more attention.]
[And this time,
there's the topic of physical castration.]
That's all they talk about on TV.
That's so gruesome.
[Spicy Pork Restaurant]
Five!
See? You shouldn't have taken it.
Six!
Hey. Don't take our things from now on.
Seven.
This is my favorite doll.
Eight.
Doesn't it hurt?
I'll hit you harder!
[Harder!]
[Good job!]
Keep hitting him!
Eight.
What?
We were just playing.
Give it back.
Give it back, please.
[Spicy Pork Restaurant]
Can you not hear me?
Sir.
["Bamboo Spear TV"]
A total change to Korea!
I'm holding this episode
to show my support to cut off
Nam Seok-hoon's manhood.
[Is everyone here? Are you all here?]
[Chief Judge Kang Yo-han]
[Okay. Did you get the scissors ready?]
[-Are you watching this, Your Honor?
-This is the real law!]
[There you go.]
[-What a great world we live in.
-Let's do this for real.]
[I hope our judge, Yo-han,
is watching this.]
[Are you watching this?]
[Can you see how much
the people of our country want this?]
[To be honest, this trial is a done deal.]
Why? Because
I know what's going to happen.
[-Bye, Seok-hoon.
-He's humiliating all the men.]
[I know Yo-han is going to cut it off.]
[Nam Seok-hoon, you are a piece of trash,
disgracing all the men in Korea.]
["Bamboo Spear TV"]
[Tomorrow...]
[Our judge, Kang Yo-han, will completely]
[cut it off.]
[Good job.]
[Beautiful Kim Ga-on]
[-When you're hurt, I'm hurt too.
-Me too.]
[Ga-on, marry me.]
[-No, he'll marry me.
-He's mine.]
[-Marry me!
-Please marry me!]
[-No! Marry me!
-Pick me!]
["Bamboo Spear TV"]
[-We will be the judge.
-And he's handsome too.]
[We are Kang Yo-han.]
[-We believe in you.
-Let's cut it!]
[Kang Yo-han!]
Gosh. Why am I only getting weirdos?
I've already contacted the Mayor
and got his permission.
Before we decide to send
our inmates to Texas,
I need to get some extra information
regarding the circumstances
and the system of Texas State Prison.
So if you let me know the direct number
of the correctional officer
in your state prison, it'll be great.
Ma'am.
Hello, Young Master.
Please don't call me that.
Sorry. But it will be too much for me
to call you otherwise
when you look like that.
Fine.
By the way, what is Elijah doing now?
She's a college student.
She must be in a lecture.
She was talking to some foreigner.
Of course,
she goes to Stanford University.
Wait, isn't she too young to...
Impatience runs in the family.
It's not a place you can go
just because you're impatient.
Can she keep up with the classes?
She won
the computer engineering scholarship.
She gets excellent grades.
They are all geniuses.
But still, can she get her degree
from home
without actually going to school?
Why don't you ask Young Master Yo-han
or check the school website?
"Elijah Hall"?
When it comes to Elijah,
Young Master Yo-han tends to go all out.
Indeed.
-By the way,
-Yes.
just cut it off.
Cut what off?
Must you ask?
Just cut off that prick's junk.
Nam Seok-hoon.
I want to cut it off myself.
That scumbag.
[9A6 7804]
What are we going to do now?
I know it's Kang Yo-han,
but he won't go that far.
Darn it. I only admitted to the charges
because the prosecutor coerced me.
How did the prosecutor coerce you?
Should I expose him?
No, don't.
[9A6 7804]
What do you think
the prosecutor is thinking?
Obviously,
he just wants to be in the limelight.
[Associate Judge Oh Jin-joo]
If he brings it up,
people will applaud him.
Even so, we can't...
Of course not.
As a judge, I do not think
it's the right ruling.
But as a citizen...
To be honest, I'm not sure.
I mean, why not? He's a total scumbag.
[Associate Judge Oh Jin-joo]
[Associate Judge Kim Ga-on]
I feel the same way,
but do you really think it's okay?
What do you mean?
Can the law allow someone's body part
to be severed?
Do you think it's okay to let it happen?
To be honest,
I'm as scared of what this country can do
in the name of law
as I am of criminals.
A jail sentence will be sufficient enough
to punish him for what he did.
[Defendant]
He'll try to get out early
by becoming a model prisoner.
And when he gets out, he'll do it again.
-So you'll castrate a man?
-No!
That's a negative connotation.
This is an effective treatment.
He says that he cannot control his urges,
so we will treat him!
Your Honor, this is simply barbaric.
Even criminals have rights.
[Against]
[Castration, For]
Your Honor.
[Court]
Your...
Your Honor?
[Hourly Graph]
Korea has a low crime rate.
[Castration, Against, For]
Instead of reforming criminals,
severely punishing them as a deterrent--
Where do you live?
Pardon?
I live in an apartment.
You live in a building
with tight security, right?
No one can enter unless you let them in.
You must also have many security guards.
Right, but...
You see, I'm not so smart.
So I had to study for a long time
to become a judge.
-What do you mean?
-And I didn't have a lot of money,
so I lived in a tiny studio.
Anyone could just walk in to the building,
all the way to my door.
I bet you've never received a notice
informing you
that felons had moved
to your neighborhood.
Not everyone can live in the area
where you currently live.
I used to receive those letters every day.
And once, there was a homicide
in the neighboring district.
I'm aware
that you're a human rights activist,
and I've always admired you for that.
But you know...
[You think this country
has a low crime rate?]
We may live in the same country,
but it's different for everyone.
What the poor working class is faced with
is very different
from what you see every day.
Please think about their rights as well.
I urge you.
[Defendant]
[Voter Turnout Across the Country]
-Yes!
-It's so true.
[Defendant]
Such inhumane punishment
will tarnish our national reputation.
The defendant
is an influential actor
in Korea and overseas.
Our country is already struggling
as you know.
-Why make things worse--
-I understand.
-Pardon?
-I think we've heard enough from you.
Your Honor.
We'll take a short recess
and deliver our verdict.
[Against, For]
[Charges]
Let's take a quick break.
Yes, sir.
Physical castration of the defendant.
Just cut it off.
We will now announce our decision.
Mr. Nam Seok-hoon.
[Defendant]
-Yes, Your Honor.
-You are sentenced
to 20 years in prison.
Okay.
[20 years in prison]
And...
[There's more?]
[20 years in prison]
That is all.
[Prosecution]
Your Honor!
-Only 20 years?
-Seriously?
-My gosh.
-I can't believe this.
-This is crazy.
-Unbelievable.
This is ridiculous.
Well done.
[Defendant's Counsel]
I totally dodged a bullet with this one.
All right!
I'll use some money
and be on parole or something.
[9A5 8247]
Oh, my.
Goodness.
Oh, no.
Help!
My goodness.
Help me!
Help!
It's acute appendicitis. Don't worry.
It'll be a simple procedure.
My goodness.
Doctor!
I'm awake.
Are you?
It's almost over. Don't worry.
Yes, sir.
But where are the nurses?
Why are you alone?
I told you to not worry.
Hey!
Where are you operating on right now?
You sure are talkative.
Why are you so noisy?
Do you not know where I'm operating on?
You do.
You!
Don't worry. I'll get it done nicely.
A German master craftsman made this.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
I'll make it look great too.
Very nice!
What is it? Did you have a dream?
You're still not feeling great, are you?
[Associate Judge Kim Ga-on]
It's time. Let's go.
[Defendant]
[9A6 7804]
It took a lot of thinking
to come to the best suitable verdict.
Defendant,
[Defendant Nam Seok-hoon]
[9A6 7804]
Yes, Judge.
The Live Court Department had
divided opinions,
so you are
only subjected to time in jail.
Your Honor!
However,
you'll be serving your time in a jail
that knows the best
about sexual harassment.
What do you mean by that?
[Defendant]
Let's watch.
This is a jail for sex offenders
located in Texas, US.
The judicial departments
of the two countries signed an MOU
and agreed on assisting each other
in punishing sex offenders.
I hope you'll work hard to fix yourself
over a very long period of time
with inmates just like you,
for 20 years.
[Good!]
[We're waiting for you!]
[Defendant]
[Come here, honey.]
[Hey, I can speak Korean.]
[I've been waiting for you.]
What is this?
[I'm so excited to see you!]
[Final verdict: 20 years in jail]
No!
[Prosecution]
We knew we could count on you!
This is how you're doing your assignment?
[Final Verdict]
Student Kang Yo-han,
you even know
how to surprise your teacher.
["Live Court Show"]
You must be happy.
It's nice to be kind sometimes.
Kind?
I heard that you had a weird dream
during the break.
-Yes.
-Who do you think I am?
How could I possibly do that?
Sure. You're right.
Elijah seems to be asleep all day.
Let her sleep. It's Saturday.
She was probably deprived of sleep
for a while.
Why is that?
Who do you think was the one
that looked through all US prisons
and changed her voice to negotiate
with the State Justice Department?
What?
Young Master.
You received this.
[From Social Responsibility Foundation
To Judge Kang Yo-han]
[Invitation for Judge Kang Yo-han]
[285 S 7511]
You're still pretty.
Don't say you...
Hi, Young Master.
[The Devil Judge]
[We appreciate Actor Ju Seok-tae
for his guest appearance.]
[Threatening is meaningless.]
[We got a tip-off]
[that Judge Kang Yo-han has provided
a lot of money and valuables to them.]
[What a pity.]
Public sentiment can be hasty and cruel.
[Once suspicion sprouts,]
it grows fast.
Soo-hyun, it's dangerous.
[You were the shiniest one.]
It was blinding.
[Whoever messes with him,]
I'll make them pay for it.
How could you do that to Soo-hyun?
How could you?
[You have nothing to protect?]
Everyone has something to protect.