♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
♪Moonlight flows in the night♪
♪Between poems and songs♪
♪It's my obsession♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
=My Queen=
=Episode 4=
Jin Hua, wait a second.
How about having a drink
to heat up the atmosphere
on our wedding night?
Sure.
It's up to you.
(Double Happiness)
Hubby,
come on.
Come to the bedroom.
(Yin Hua)
Come here, hubby.
Come to the bedroom.
I will make up the bed.
Drink more.
Have some more.
Don't stop.
All the women in Bai Hua Village
are orphans
who have no parents
or anyone to rely on.
Since we were young,
they liked to bully us.
We rob people
not only to survive,
but also
to get back
our pride.
Sure.
We will make everyone afraid of us.
So, they will never look down on us.
Look down...
Oh, no...
Look up to us.
Come on, let's drink.
Cheers.
I will fill it up for you.
Nowadays,
people around this area
all get scared when
they hear my name.
But I don't feel as happy as I thought.
Rather than having people afraid of me,
I hope that they love me.
Can you understand?
Yes, I can.
Come on, cheers.
Cheers.
After this toast,
I'll love you even more.
OK.
Cheers.
I will fill it up for you.
Love is sharing.
It's like this bottle of wine.
You won't enjoy it if
drink only by yourself.
But if we share it,
it will be tastier.
Right?
Sharing?
Yes, sharing.
I'd love to share with you.
I'd love to share all my
good things with you,
including myself.
All with you.
You don't have to share yourself.
But
I heard that
you had got some good stuff recently.
Good stuff?
Yes.
Right.
I have tons of good stuff
that I like to share with you.
Good stuff.
Really?
Over there. Over there.
Is this the blood night-blooming cereus?
It doesn't look like it.
I think this trip is all for nothing.
No.
It's not.
Happy wedding.
Are you trying to scare me to death?
Where is Yin Hua?
Passed out.
Good job.
You, too.
No,
we have to leave now.
It will be too late if they wake up.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
(Double Happiness)
(Feng Yi Palace)
Mengmeng has been missing
for the whole day.
And the 5th prince has been missing
for 2 days.
Why is there no news about them at all?
Xiao Ai, A Liang.
Did Mengmeng mention
where she was going?
I don't know.
Is there any clue about
where the 5th prince went?
8th brother, Song Che.
Any clue?
I found this
from a pawnshop.
This is...
It's a gift I gave to Mengmeng.
Ah right.
I remember that when Her Highness left,
she was dressed like
a cook.
She was holding knifes
and spatula in her hands.
Right.
We found the guy
who traded in the jade bracelet,
and he said that
Mengmeng used this jade bracelet to
trade all their cooking
equipment and clothes.
This information also matches
what Xiao Ai and A Liang said.
Recently, many cooks have gone missing.
Based on the investigation,
they are caught up
and sent to Bai Hua Village.
Bai Hua Village!
Quickly, this way.
Stop there.
I'm so exhausted.
Don't run.
How did they catch up so quickly?
Stop there.
Hurry, run.
How come there're so many people?
What should we do?
What else can we do?
Let's fight.
You have me here.
It will be ok.
Stay behind me.
Stop it.
Let me do it.
Can you handle it?
Why are you pulling my clothes?
You told me to stay behind you.
I told you to stay behind me
so you can watch my back.
I can't watch my back by myself.
Be careful.
Don't move.
Kneel down.
Stay still.
Song Che.
You are finally here.
I thought you’d never come.
I thought I would die.
Mengmeng.
Don't be scared.
I'm here to rescue you.
Let's go.
Hurry.
But why are you here?
It's all arranged by Her Majesty.
Sister queen?
Sister queen.
Did you get hurt?
It's fine.
Just a little scratch.
But,
sister queen,
what's going on?
The bandits in Ruo Shui Kingdom
are always my big concern.
It has not been resolved for years.
This time, you and the emperor's
son-in-law went missing.
Your brother and Song Che found out
it has something to do
with Bai Hua Village.
We are here to take
all of them down once.
But this time,
you and the emperor's son-in-law
have made huge contribution.
We?
A piece of cake.
Because I know
our Mengmeng is very kind.
As soon as you knew cooks got kidnapped,
you would come to enemy's lair
to rescue them.
Right?
(What's going on?)
(Isn't this what Murong Chen made up?)
Sister queen, actually…
(Whatever.)
(The blood night-blooming cereus
is still missing anyway.)
(No need to spill out the truth.)
Sorry, sister queen.
I made you worried.
You bandits
have been doing all kinds of evil
for years.
Robbing and kidnapping.
Now you even dare to
kidnap my 9th princess.
9th princess?
If I don't bring you to justice,
Ruo Shui Kingdom will never be safe.
Guards.
Sister queen,
please let them go.
After all,
they're forced to do this
just for living.
And as bandits,
they only robbed people
without actually harming anyone.
This time, they kidnapped cooks
just for cooking.
I also feel they are guilty,
but they don't deserve to die.
How about this?
I have an idea.
Do you wanna hear it?
Speak out.
I think that,
rather than killing them,
why don't we guide them
to do good things?
I think that
we can order them to hand over
the spoils,
and we can use them to help the people.
In this way,
they can also have a second chance
to change and start over.
Sister queen, please.
OK.
You must check carefully
against the list.
Don't miss anything.
It's not right.
Some are missing.
What's missing?
Go and search around corners carefully,
and see if there's anything left.
There's no need.
Right, this is it!
This is the bracelet.
The white pearl necklace
is still missing.
Keep searching.
Right, right. It's that white one.
The colorful bead necklace
is also missing.
Still missing...
Missing...
The last one.
Now everything's here.
Found it!
You don't need to check it.
It's also fake.
This is much more complicated
than we imagined.
But there's one thing we can be sure of.
It was a right decision to
come to Ruo Shui Kingdom.
But Your Highness, you are now
the emperor's son-in-law.
If we continue to dig into it,
I'm afraid that it won't be easy.
But if we somehow break off
the engagement,
we don't have excuse to stay here.
I have an idea.
What is it?
She also wants to get the
blood night-blooming cereus, right?
You mean the 9th princess?
(It shouldn't be like this.)
(Why did I feel nothing
when I hugged him?)
Brother.
Coming.
Mengmeng.
What happened?
Hug me.
My sister,
although we've been close to each other
and used to hug, kiss and hold high,
you are a big girl now.
And it's a little...
Mengmeng,
did anyone bully you?
Tell me,
and I'll teach him a lesson.
Can you teach
the game designer a lesson?
Game design...
Designer?
Who is that?
Wait, Mengmeng.
Mengmeng?
Where does that designer live?
Energetic.
Powerful.
Loyal.
Enterprising?
Except for being a little
straightforward,
what went wrong?
Your Highness,
is there anything I can do for you?
Xiao Ai,
tell me,
Song Che and I,
do we match each other?
General Song has
powerful family background,
and he has achieved a lot at his age.
He's handsome and brave,
and he's grown up together with you.
Of course, you two match each other.
That's right.
That's what I thought.
When he came to save me
the other day at Bai Hua Village,
I ran into his arms.
It should be the kind of climax
of a love story.
Love story?
But I didn't feel anything.
What is a
love story?
My point is...
Well... this...
Well...
I was supposed to feel nervous
and excited
with fast heartbeat.
But I didn't.
That's why I even tested
it out with the 8th brother.
I found that
I felt the same when
I hugged them.
Is the so-called destiny
determined by storyline
and character setting,
or by my real feelings?
No, no.
Even Song Che is not the right man.
How come that guy is. Impossible!
What's impossible?
Speaking of the devil.
Wow.
What is this?
What?
Oh...
Well.
What are you doing here?
Are you here to make fun of me?
That's misunderstanding.
You got hurt because of me after all.
Of course, I should
come to visit you.
This is
the special medicine
from our Cang Yun Kingdom.
It's particularly effective.
You can think of it as a gift in payment
for what you have done for me.
I saved your life.
You think this can suffice?
If you don't want it,
forget about it.
I do.
Speaking of which,
did you actually go to Bai Hua Village
to rescue those cooks?
What about you?
Since we don't trust each other,
let's talk frankly.
I went there
to look for something.
Stealing something!
Can those outfits
you ancient people wear
actually hold that many stuff?
Wow.
Is this the blood night-blooming cereus?
Yes.
Neither did I find it in
Jin Hua's room yesterday,
nor at the site where
we were counting the spoils.
This
was found in Yin Hua's room.
Yin Hua robbed this
behind Jin Hua's back.
That explains it.
Are you giving it to me?
Of course.
Take it.
This is the blood night-blooming cereus?
Why does it look so familiar?
Look.
It is fake.
The one at the lantern festival
and the one at Bai Hua Village this time
are both fake.
So, I come here today
to collaborate with you.
You want to collaborate with me?
Since we have the same objective,
rather than making things
difficult for each other,
it's better to cooperate.
When we find
the real blood night-blooming cereus,
we can each get half of it.
What do you think?
Deal.
You and me, we can work together.
Then from now on,
we are partners.
Okay, come on.
Give me five.
Are you praising my good looking?
(Jing Yue Sect)
(Qing He)
(Yu Qingzhu,)
(Cold-blood Godmother)
(founder and master)
(of Jing Yue Sect,)
(planned to use the blood
night-blooming cereus)
(to master blood moon superb skill,)
(so that she can rule
the martial arts circles)
(and become more powerful than
the Empire.)
Master,
so far there have been
two fake blood night-blooming cereuses.
Do we need to take action?
(Zhe Xiang,
top disciple of Jing Yue Sect.)
(Aloof and domineering lady)
(Beautiful, cold yet powerful.)
(She's got full marks in attacking.)
(She believes in fighting over arguing.)
No hurry.
These years I've spread out
many rumors around,
just to wait for this to start.
Finally, someone comes into our trap,
and it's still not the time for us
to tighten the ring of encirclement.
Yes.
Let's leave these small potatoes
struggling in the trap for a while.
This is what I asked Xiao Ai
to buy on the market.
These three jade boxes are different in
materials,
crafts
and prices.
But their patterns and
looks are almost the same.
These are the hot sales on the market.
What are hot sales?
Hot sales are the products
that sell well.
It seems like this counterfeiter
is very cautious.
So, I'm afraid that
the clue of jade box is useless now.
Ah right.
The guy who gave us the clue.
Zhao Qian?
We got nothing from him?
Zhao Qian is only a speculator.
He didn't even know
the blood night-blooming cereus
he had was fake.
And this fake one had been sold
many times already.
We won't get anything from him.
It sounds like
the fake flower was mass produced.
Mass produced?
You mean
there are many fake flowers
like that on the market?
Think about it.
Zhao Qian just lost a fake one,
and he bought another one right away.
This is the best evidence
that proves my point.
It's surprising to see that
you look bewildered most of the time,
but you have a clear mind when
it comes to something serious.
You bet.
So, are you admiring my wisdom?
Put it on for me.
Why?
Someone's here.
Well, my dear Mengmeng,
you have such pretty hands.
Come on,
put on the expensive bracelet
I bought for you.
Such a beautiful jade
on such a pretty girl.
It's amazing.
Nice taste.
So pretty!
The color looks good, too.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I want to buy you even more things.
Well.
What I did was nothing
but saving your life.
This is too much.
I don't deserve them.
Let's go.
I didn't expect that
you prepared all these.
I have to buy some other stuff
as a cover.
That makes sense.
What?
Reimbursement.
You need to pay for these stuff.
The amount doesn't seem right.
How come it's only this little?
It's too little for you?
We made a deal.
Each of us gets half of the blood
night-blooming cereus.
Of course, we will also
share the expenditure.
You...
Unbelievable.
You said that this flower
was mass produced?
Right.
I bought all these from the
flower shop on Jin Xiu Street.
It seems like this counterfeiter has
invested a lot for it.
It's an investment.
You need a high cost for a high return.
As long as there could be
a dozen of stupid
people like you who pay a lot
for fake flowers,
he can earn it back.
What did you just say?
Did you say I'm stupid?
You dare to say it again?
What?
Someone's here.
Thank you, Murong Chen,
for giving me such a pretty flower.
Of course.
Beautiful flower should belong
to beautiful girls like you.
Here, I will put it on you.
Well.
It's so embarrassing.
Why did you hit me?
You pricked too hard.
Did I?
So beautiful!
Mengmeng,
you are so adorable.
Have they gone?
They've gone for a while.
It's not the jade box
or the dry flower.
So, the only thing left is…
- The paint.
(The book)
Jiang Mengmeng,
you are so smart.
You found it so quickly.
I'm the princess of Ruo Shui Kingdom.
How would a book trouble me?
I've read it before
bringing it to you.
The mineral
that Qian Xiu Workshop bought
over the past half year is
half of the whole amount.
I know what you want to say.
I will go to sister queen right now,
and ask for a leave.
Ah right,
I need to return this.
Your Highness,
why didn't you tell the 9th princess
from the very beginning
that she should track the paint?
Jiang Mengmeng thinks that she's smart.
Of course, I should use some
help from the engagement.
So, it would be easier to make moves.
Also, I need her to feel that
she‘s the one who leads everything.
Although she's made some detour,
she is not too stupid
and finally will come
back on the right track.
What's going on?
Didn't she go to see Song Che
quite often those days?
How did she suddenly get so
close to Murong Chen?
It was like that before.
But ever since she came
back from Bai Hua Village,
I often see them
chatting and laughing together.
The 5th prince also bought
the 9th princess
many gifts to make her happy.
Today the 9th princess also
went to Liu Guang Palace
to find the 5th prince.
Is it because they were kidnapped
together at Bai Hua Village,
and Jiang Mengmeng
blocked the knife for him?
So, they started have feelings
for each other?
So far it seems reasonable.
Jiang Mengmeng is so freakish.
No way.
I can't let them continue like this.
Song Che,
I thought you'd never come.
I thought I would die.
Young general.
Young...
Who closed the gate?
Young general,
this is the wrong way.
It should be this way.
It's my pleasure
to see you, My Highness.
You like my sister,
right?
Then do you know that she's
already with Murong Chen?
Mengmeng and the 5th prince?
It is impossible.
Mengmeng told me that their
engagement was an accident.
There's nothing real between them.
They became
so close lately.
Everyone at He Palace has seen it.
You are the only one
who still has no idea.
Self-deceiving.
I trust Mengmeng.
She'll never lie to me.
Besides,
even if they seem close now,
Mengmeng will have her own hardship.
A man and a woman.
A fiance and a fiancee.
They spend every day together.
What else can it be?
You are so ignorant.
Why are you so worried
about it?
I...
No matter what you decide to do,
you don't have to worry about
Mengmeng and me.
I still have work to do.
Excuse me.
Stupid.
I heard from Hai Qian that
you have stayed low
in the palace these days.
How's your hand?
Sister queen,
it has recovered.
The saying that you and the 5th prince
are getting close to each other
seems real.
(How come there are gossip
spreaders everywhere?)
(These nosy people.)
Hai Qian was right about it.
After the engagement,
you were well-behaved.
Sister queen,
I want to ask for a little favor.
Say it.
I will permit anything.
I want to...
I want to go out of the palace.
Sister queen.
I just said you had been good,
and now you want to go out again.
No.
It's all because it's too depressing
to stay in the palace
for such a long time.
Also, the 5th prince
must be even more bored than me.
Think about it.
He travelled to our kingdom
by himself from thousands of miles away.
He hasn't even had time
to travel around
and see how nice and beautiful
the Ruo Shui Kingdom is
before he was locked within the palace.
Poor guy.
How bored he must be.
Right?
It's not completely unreasonable.
Ever since men get married,
they are like the canary in the birdcage
without freedom.
However,
since you are already
so considerate of him,
he might become
haughty and willful
after you are married.
Sister queen.
Make a finger heart.
What?
You are saying that sister
queen permitted them to go out?
Yes.
Another chance for them to get closer.
Exactly, Your Highness.
How about we go to
talk with Song Che again?
It's useless.
He's as stupid as a piece of wood.
Then you mean...
Since she wants to go out,
I will keep her out forever.
♪With the singing of girls,
I passed the South♪
♪The scenery has come into my painting♪
♪Who would understand
my unrestrained affection♪
♪But as time goes by♪
♪I know she is my only one♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪