[English subtitles are available]
[ACE TROOPS]
[Episode 39]
Director Xia. He's turned off the intercom.
Number One. Red Side has news to report.
[Blue Side Director, Chief Director, Red Side Director]
They've got ready. Ten minutes later,
they'll start to attack.
Gao Liang.
What are you up to?
According to the rules of the drill,
you will get knocked out,
your hands and feet will get tied,
and your mouth will be sealed.
Your bodies
will be equipped with trigger bombs.
And this whole place
will be blown up.
No one will know where you get buried,
and no one
will find your bodies.
Stop screwing around.
Is that how I taught you?
Don't move.
[Political official]
While you've already suffered a lot,
so I won't follow the standards of the drill,
but it's regarded as the execution.
Gao Liang. Are you insane?
Gao Liang. You've gone too far.
Don't move.
Gao.
The Red Side's troops on the island
suddenly stop their attack
and begin to retreat orderly.
Their landing crafts
begin to move forward.
It seems that they are ready
to attack.
The big one is coming.
Get ready to fight.
Jiang Nanzheng is here.
The Red Side sent her to the island.
She is a civilian
with 50 boxes of boxed lunches.
Why did you help him?
I didn't.
But you still came here.
I am a civilian.
I'm just here to bring you boxed lunches.
To give us the poisoned boxed lunch, right?
I've promised.
I won't tell you a thing.
You don't need to tell me anything.
I know better than anyone.
We stayed on this island for five days.
And we only brought two days' food.
The last time they drank water
was when it rained two days ago.
My soldiers have reached
their final limit.
Now, you
bring these boxed lunches here.
What do you want to do?
Gu Yiye
tries to crush my men
with these boxed lunches.
Why did you bring them up here?
You shouldn't
even be here.
I just wanted to see you.
Sorry.
Don't bother.
You know you're a key member of Mountain Net Number Two.
You know better than anyone
this is not
a matched battle.
It's a slaughter.
We're Special Forces.
We'll fight until the last moment.
We'll fight to the death,
shedding the last drop of blood.
This is the fate of Special Forces.
We don't need anyone
to walk into the graves of Special Forces.
Number One.
We've spotted a group of enemy bombers.
Dudes.
We are now in the final moment.
We have no reinforcements,
no heavy weapons,
no ammunition.
All we have is 49 of us.
We can't fight trench warfare.
Thank you, dudes.
You didn't touch these boxed lunches
in front of outsiders.
These boxed lunches
are indeed tempting.
I know
many of you
are starving to death.
Before departure,
each of you carries a rice ball
and puts it on you.
If you can't hold on,
eat it.
Yes, sir.
Keep in mind.
After eating the rice ball,
you only have ten minutes.
In ten minutes,
according to the rules,
you will automatically withdraw from the battle.
Chen Nianqing.
Here.
The flag stands us, and we mustn't lose it.
It won't be allowed
to fall into the enemy's hands.
Yes, sir.
Enter the underground fortifications
and rescue the hostages.
Destroy all enemies in the fortifications.
Go.
Team One.
Withdraw to the bunker.
The rest of you,
hang in there.
Comrades.
I want you to show
the skills of Special Forces
and disappear
from this 2.6 square mile
Qiaotou Island.
You each fight on your own.
Everyone
is a fighting unit.
From now on,
you have no comrades,
no reinforcements,
no victory.
You need to pick up all
weapons you can attack,
even if they're stones, fists,
or teeth,
to destroy every
enemy appears in front of you.
I want you
to stay
for a long time.
You have to conserve your strength.
You have to show up
every 12 hours.
Keep this island under fire
as long as possible,
with continuing fighting.
Keep this island out of enemy hands.
You
are the ghosts on this island.
You are the nightmare
that the enemy can never get rid of.
What we are guarding
is not the island,
but
the sovereignty and territory of China,
and the dignity of China's military.
I want our flag
to be planted at the highest of the island.
The fighting spirit
never fails!
[Life and Death Together Company]
Gao Liang.
I still have supplies.
You gave them to me.
here are snipers on the main peak.
Request for fire.
Are you okay?
I'm running out of bullets.
I will draw them out,
and you go straight to the cliff.
It's a poisonous rice ball,
just enough for you to hold on for ten minutes.
And
the flag must be with us.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Number One.
The fire spots on the island have all been cleared.
The troop has occupied the bunker,
seized 421 hammocks,
a batch of toiletries,
a small amount of edible wild plants,
and lots of personal items.
Inform the troop
to search for the remnants of the Blue Army.
If you meet a rival on your way
without firepower,
no shooting is allowed.
Catch him alive.
Come on.
Here.
My reaction point is here.
Shoot me with your gun.
I'll be out if you do that. Come on.
Why are you doing that?
[Sword of the South]
General died in a battle,
soldier returned in ten years.
Do you know what Special Troops are?
Which means even if I die in the battle,
I can't be taken down by you today.
Do you get it?
So you think I dare not kill you,
right?
Yes, that's what I thought.
Reaction point is here.
Shoot it.
Come on. Here. Shoot.
Okay, I'll do that.
Come on.
He's Number Two.
He got information.
The Blue Side has abandoned the underground fortifications,
and they are scattered around the island,
making a last stand
in fighting units.
Don't shoot. Catch them alive.
In the current situation,
they can't organize
any more attacks with well form.
[Integrated coordination, Blue Side Director, Chief Director]
How many men are left in Blue Army?
Three days ago,
the Blue Army command post had refused to report.
Their reason was
they had lost all contact
with the outside world,
and can only fought on their own.
While,
I'm guessing there are
less than 30 of them,
and they're out of ammunition.
They can pack up
and come back.
Command Wang.
I just don't like what Army B is doing.
The numbers in every drill report
are pretty good,
but they just lack vigor.
I love to see the DF-2 rocket
whizzing and flying into the sky.
[Integrated coordination]
BeiDou System issues instructions.
But I prefer to watch how men will fight.
If they can't go on any longer,
what should they do?
Sergeant, your leg is broken.
Does that scare you?
That's... That's how tough I am.
Xiaopao!
Number one. Come on and check it out.
Platoon leader. He's heading for the sea.
[Integrated coordination, Blue Side Director, Chief Director]
Chief Director
He is moving towards the sea.
Tell the observer to hurry up and stop him.
Yes sir.
Watch out. Xiaopao.
Wait for me. I'll come up to fix your leg.
Both you parties.
I'm the drill observer.
Now, I order you
to cease pursuing.
The Red Side soldiers withdraw from the battlefield.
The Blue Side soldiers are regarded as laying down arms.
Again.
Tell them.
There's freaking judge on the plane.
Be careful.
Tell our chief.
We do not lose the flag.
[Life and Death Together Company]
Xiaopao.
[Integrated coordination, Blue Side Director, Chief Director]
Tell the observer to save him.
Who is this freaking observer?
Crap. Kick his ass.
What a good soldier.
Stop holding me.
Go to help Minister Liu.
His blood pressure is high
and has reached 180.
Come. Liu.
Here. Take a break.
Take a break first.
Easy.
Have a rest.
Is the island cleaned up?
The ending fighting is still going on.
But it will be soon.
Then leave us alone.
We'll be onboard the landing craft later.
Get us some water.
We need to be hydrating.
You guys keep going on.
Yes sir.
Protect the chief.
Red Army soldiers, come with me.
Chief.
It seems two figures
are going to show up.
This should be fun.
[Bayi]
You, such a group of idiot soldiers,
I have blown up your command post.
Watch out for 40 RPG behind you.
[Bayi]
Gao.
I didn't expect there are only a few of you,
and you even take so much effort
to get it done.
Just because there are only a few of us,
I have
only last trick.
Attack the key spot first.
[Bayi]
Gao.
Let me tell you.
My command post is not here,
but where you once fought.
It's in the central bunker
of the underground fortifications.
[Bayi]
You got Niu.
You can use that trick.
But I can't let you take advantage of it.
Tell me the truth.
See if I took down
your real command post.
You're silly.
You should ask your men.
You thought
you got the bunker.
I know you're good at familiarizing the environment.
You've been on the island for almost
a hundred hours.
With that time,
you can do whatever you want
inside the underground fortifications.
I like your compliment.
This brat,
Gao Liang.
In return,
I'll give you a message.
Come on.
Tell him.
I got a good beating
from him.
But he didn't take advantage of me, either.
Just get to the point.
Colonel!
After the drill,
I'll apply for a transfer to Special Force Team.
I have to beat him back.
You should wait until I leave to talk about it.
Now you tell him,
he will get mad,
and maybe he'll get fainted
in a moment.
Let's go.
Check it out.
Come on.
Minister Liu.
Chief.
There.
Gao Liang.
Gu Yiye.
Qin Hanyong. Li Shaobing.
Now go and stop your two men.
No.
Keep them going on.
The drill is not over yet.
They are enemies.
Gao Liang.
Stand up.
Let go of him.
You are comrades.
You should live and die together.
Let's get married.
I want to marry you.
The wind is strong,
so I can't hear that.
You asshole.
Gao Liang.
Good.
Chief.
Enjoy that?
[Integrated coordination, Blue Side Director, Chief Director]
好Great.
[Be alert and protect our country]
Secretary Wang,
do you find Wei Xiaopao?
I'm waiting for news.
It's been two hours.
Aren't you tired of standing?
Relax.
Chief.
I don't know when he will be back.
It's okay.
Go ahead.
Leave us alone.
Admit defeat this time, right?
Excuse me?
You'd better count how many teeth you have left.
I should kick all your teeth, right?
I mean,
you have got her.
Well.
Actually,
she got me.
I have to admit that.
Don't you congratulate me?
Forget it.
I'll bless her.
I bless you both.
Zheng.
Calm down.
How can I?
Look.
It's fine to punish me.
There's no need for punishing them two,
Gu Yiye and Gao Liang.
Wang, why did they do that?
Why?
Zheng.
The superiors are in a higher power than us.
You saw that, too.
The chief of headquarters
especially praised Special Force Team and Regiment 700
at the meeting.
They thought the drill
showed up
the brave spirit of the Special Troops.
They are indeed
the first Special Forces of
Sword of the South.
They also saw
the main force of
our Military Command's
fighting attitude.
Generally,
they affirmed our competence.
Afraid of getting hurt,
nd does that get men real skills?
I'm in charge of the drill.
The members of the observation group
were on the scene.
I saw
that kind of state
when they're in real fighting.
That is real fighting power,
real fighting spirit.
It makes me, a veteran,
so excited.
I'm educated.
With such troops
and soldiers,
shall we still need to worry about winning?
But now,
each of them gets a punishment.
How can they lead their soldiers in the future?
Whether to tell them,
while training in the future,
you don't need to make efforts
on the actual fighting.
If there is an accident,
you will get punishment.
Tell them this?
Why?
Man.
I understand.
The army
has always been
subordinate to its superiors.
We got such a result.
Do not mention you,
I also need a while to take it.
But one missing,
and five seriously injured,
which is unprecedented in the history
of drills in our Military Command.
And,
the missing soldier has not been found yet.
Aren't we working hard to find him?
But then again,
as long as there are drills
and training,
there will be accidents.
That's the price we have to pay.
Of course,
the fewer accidents the better.
However, we should not be less strict
for fear of accidents
and then loosen training.
In that case,
we will pay a huge sacrifice
in the future war.
I remember
six months ago.
On the first two days of the Iraq war,
you spent every day
in the training room
on a drip.
On March 20th.
During those days,
we all gathered
in the preparation room
and studied the war.
While the results
were not beyond your judgment.
Don't mention
the 2,000 precision missiles for the air attack.
On April 8th,
the US-UK coalition forces
began the ground war.
The Iraqi army
got badly beaten.
It's because the strength was too different.
That's just one of the reasons.
I am not talking about the defeated side,
I'll say the victor.
At the end of the war,
The US
officially declared
in this war,
262 Americans
have been killed.
The war between the two countries
ended up
at the cost of 262 men.
Do you know
how many Americans
actually died
in this war?
Didn't you just say that?
262.
It's 139,
and another
123 men
died in the accidents.
Wang,
when it comes to politics,
I can't compete with you.
But in my understanding,
the highest politics of the military
is that
when the state gives the order,
the military can keep pace.
The first battle
must be won.
What shall we take to fight now?
How can we win?
Accidents always happen
in war and training,
and there are casualties.
We only have to turn the training
into the actual fighting,
so that
when the war starts,
we don't panic,
get messy
and feel horrible.
That's what Gao Liang and Gu Yiye did.
At the last step,
they were still fighting together,
never giving up,
and showing courage,
will,
and determination.
Such an army
is invincible.
I've got to go out.
Zheng.
Where are you going?
I'm going to Army A
to check the missing soldier.
None of my soldiers
can be lost.
Well.
What are you two doing here,
not at the hospital?
Zheng.
I got an idea.
I'll go
to the commander and political commissar
to make a report,
suggest
making a report to the superiors.
Let them off punishment.
Ask them to go back to the hospital.
Alright.
I'll immediately report to chief.
Chief.
Chief,
Army A reports
they've found the missing soldier of the Special Force Team.
Where did they find him?
How is he going on?
Thirteenth District Sea Area.
He was rescued by a fishing boat.
And the detail of his injuries is unknown.
But he is conscious.
He's on his way to the military hospital.
Tell Dean Chen
to try his best to save him.
If there is any problem,
report it directly to me.
Yes sir.
Since the wounded have been found,
you don't have to go.
Have them go back to the hospital.
No.
I have to go and see the soldier.
I have to ask him
what he thought when he disappeared.
I'll get him next time.
Chief.
[Secretary]
Captain Qin, they've
been waiting in the meeting room
all morning.
Tell them to get back to me,
and after 70 minutes,
I'll listen to their report.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, chief.
[Loyalty to the party, love the people, serve the country]
[Military District General Hospital]
[One month later]
You know, you got removed this time.
It's probably a good thing.
Actually,
you can take advantage of this recovery period
to get everything done.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah.
Okay.
I got to go.
Xia.
I heard
you've been tracking Prince?
You know,
for six years,
there has been no whereabouts.
Listen to my advice.
You are not young.
You should hurry up
and sort out your personal issues.
You are disabled now,
but you still care about others' business.
You should take care of yourself.
It's been six years.
If you keep tracking down Prince,
it will get in the way of you doing something else,
You should move forward.
Think about it.
Cut the crap.
I'll leave.
Just go.
Hello, Uncle Xia.
Gu Xiaofei.
Boy.
I heard
you got admitted to Tsinghua University
majoring in computer science and technology.
You're amazing.
How about
joining the army after graduation?
Joining the army?
Maybe talk about it later.
You little brat.
Alright.
Enjoy your chat.
You may leave.
Goodbye, Uncle Xia.
Bye.
Bro Xia.
I told Gu,
I won't be a soldier.
Sit down.
Why are you standing there?
You're rude.
You come to the hospital
and don't ask me how well I'm getting.
You guys are really hurt?
I thought Gu pretended to be injured
to get my Mom's love.
Of course, we got injured.
If we hadn't been injured,
we wouldn't have been in hospital for so long.
You're right.
Come.
Come on.
What do you intend to do?
Let me see if you get well.
Try harder.
Come on.
Harder!
You're messing around here.
Okay. That's enough.
I don't feel like you're hurt.
I'll tell you one last thing.
Keep it between us.
Go ahead.
I
applied for Tsinghua's National Defense Student.
So what?
Regret it?
Nonsense.
It's not afraid of Gu.
A few years ago,
there was the Confederate Embassy bombing
and the South China Sea collision.
These two times I cried,
but that's enough.
I don't want anything else to happen.
So I determined
to join the army in my own way,
to make a contribution to my country
and people.
Good.
Perfect.
Well done.
Don't tell anyone else.
Don't worry.
I heard both of you have been removed.
It's really exciting.
This is more exciting than my application to Tsinghua University.
Stop nonsense.
Little brat.
You know nothing.
Let me tell you.
This is called
cultivating future talents for our army.
Do you get it?
Well. Cultivating...
Cultivating talents.
Stop showing off.
Let me tell you.
Your dad and I
are going to school in Beijing, too.
That place is not far from Tsinghua University.
That's where all the generals are trained.
Do you know?
Really?
Let's go.
Get out of the hospital.
Come on. Let me help you.
Stop.
Go and get
the stuff inside the cupboard
and put it on the bed.
What's that?
Is it this one?
Put it on the bed.
Stop looking at it.
[To Jiang Nanzheng only]
Nanzheng.
I knew
you would come to get me out of the hospital today.
And then,
as you wish,
we can get married.
But I want to tell you,
I already have someone I love.
It makes me suffer.
I don't know how to tell you.
I think we need to
have a talk.
I'll wait for you in the barrack of the Ninth Company in Sanling Mountain.
You can choose not to come,
[Ward]
but I will keep waiting.
[Never shed tears even for bloody sweat. Never be left behind even being peeled of the meat.]
[Learn from Comrade Lei Feng. Mao Zedong]
[Iron discipline, iron company, iron style, iron quality]
[Strengthen ideals and beliefs]
Nanzheng.
Yiye.
How come you are here?
Nanzheng.
After hearing what I say,
you must hold on.
Gao Liang, he
doesn't know how to face you,
so he asked me to tell you.
But I...
I don't know how to tell you, either.
Where is he?