[English subtitles are available]
[Nothing But You]
[Episode 11]
I never thought
there would come a day
where I could take you
on a stroll like this.
Cut the rambling.
You are so ruthless.
In the past we could only meet once a month.
I don't care,
I am going to make up for all the time
we lost in the past.
Our type of relation does not
require us to meet up often.
We can turn it into
one that can meet up often.
That's not necessary.
Finished your water?
I'll buy you another bottle.
Hey handsome,
want to keep in touch?
My girlfriend is right over there,
no need.
Does that mean if she is not here,
you would do it?
Hey, don't
cling to me like that.
Let go!
Honey!
That stinking rascal,
he bullied me!
Don't worry babe,
I'll handle this.
Who the hell are you?
Why did you harass my wife?
Who are you?
With which eye did you see me
harassing her?
She was the one who clung to me.
He did it!
Her? Please.
I have standards.
What, you mean to tell me
my wife is cheating on me?
I have no objections if
you want to put it that way.
-No. -Listen here you-
Babe! Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
Are you alright?
What is your problem?
Excuse me,
I mistook you for a rubbish bin.
You bitch.
You think I don't dare to hit you?
Sure,
give it your best shot.
I-
I'll hit-
My eyes!
Darling, darling!
Are you alright, darling?
Stay right there!
Hey! Don't run off!
That muscular guy
was truly all brawn
and no brain.
If grass grows on his head every time
his wife cheats on him,
I bet it would become a grassland soon.
Horses could be galloping on that land
and he still wouldn't have a clue.
But a lady like you
shouldn't confront people like them head-on,
especially when you're still injured.
You're too disadvantaged.
[Lemeng Pictures]
Nianxue!
Not a step closer!
Please, I can explain.
Nianxue.
I don't want to hear it!
You have been lying to me all this time,
haven't you?
I can't forgive you anymore.
Alright, cut!
-Thank you director. -Thank you.
Thank you.
Good job,
take a break.
Thank you
Meijia.
Xiaoran,
Mr. Lai.
I think her acting is fine,
but her image doesn't really fit the role.
She is more suited to be a...
Female General.
Right?
A tough woman
or a general, something like that.
She does lack the feel
of a stone-cold beauty.
I will put her on the tentative list.
Next.
Next, please.
Ye Shu'er.
Okay,
I will note that down.
Nianxue!
Not a step closer!
I can explain!
Don't come closer!
Please, let me explain.
No! I don't want to hear it!
Director,
why don't I want to hear it?
When a couple is dealing with conflict,
shouldn't they communicate and talk it out
instead of being unreasonable like this?
[Lemeng Pictures]
What is she doing?
I have no idea.
It is fine
to portray a woman in love
in a slightly more emotional manner.
No, no.
I think Su Nianxue and I are alike.
We are both the intelligent
and rational kind of woman.
So I think this scene
should not be acted in this way.
Stop, stop.
That's enough for today.
We'll inform you when the result is out.
Alright.
Okay.
Her understanding of the character
is a little lacking.
This way please.
Hey!
Seriously?
Did she even read the script?
She made no sense!
What a weird person.
Ye Shu'er's understanding of the character
is a bit wrong.
Should we settle for Meijia after all?
No.
Xiaoran.
Please wait a moment,
my apprentice will be here soon.
Your apprentice is here to audition too?
Mm.
She is a good actress.
Mr. Lai knows her too.
Since she is your apprentice,
I am sure her acting is up to standard.
Excuse me,
sorry for the wait.
Hello, master.
[Lemeng Pictures]
Hello, Mr. Lai.
Alright.
Now then, I shall begin.
Wait.
This character of ours,
Su Nianxue,
is a stone-cold beauty,
with a pure, other-worldly vibe.
Your
makeup is too heavy for that.
Will this do?
Please continue.
A moment, please.
Alright.
Action.
Nianxue.
Please.
Please, I can explain.
Not a step closer!
Please hear me out!
No, no!
I don't want to hear it!
You have been lying to me all this time.
I cannot forgive you.
The love and affection between us.
My everything-
Hold on!
There is no 'love and affection' in your lines.
Please don't play it by ear.
My bad, Xiaoran.
I forgot.
-Can I try again? -It's fine, don't worry.
Go on.
You have been lying to me all this time.
I cannot-
Wait!
Xiaoran,
Is there anything else I need to adjust?
You.
You're too thin.
According to the script,
-Su Nianxue is a skilled martial artist. -Xiaoran.
So she should have a fitter form.
Your image
makes it hard for me to relate you to the character.
Xiaoran.
Now you are just deliberately finding faults.
Liu Yue is good enough.
Her acting is good,
and she can make bold performances.
Such a good actress!
Besides, isn't it good
to be thinner?
Being thinner will look good on camera.
Mr. Lai.
What do you think?
I think it's pretty good.
Besides, she is Director Wang's direct apprentice.
After she joins the crew,
she will adjust and fit in in no time.
Thank you.
Then, let me ask her one last question.
Go ahead.
Erm...
There is a supporting female character in the show
who is keen to separate Su Nianxue
from the male lead Ming Jue.
If you are Su Nianxue,
what would you do?
If a relationship
can be intervened by a third party,
then this relationship is not good in the first place.
No loss ending it.
But I believe,
Ming Jue would never
do the wrong things to Su Nianxue.
Splendid!
You have firmly grasped the feelings
and relations between characters.
You are like Su Nianxue in person.
My choice
is her.
Not bad.
Thank you for your approval, Mr. Lai.
See you later.
Alright.
I will take my leave first.
Okay.
Mr. Lai.
Thanks for your handkerchief.
Thank you
for giving me this opportunity.
No need to thank me,
you earned this opportunity
with your own hard work.
Why is your handkerchief
with her?
Xiaoran,
don't be mistaken.
Mr. Lai lent it to me
to wipe a stain off my shirt
when we ate together.
I still have a event tomorrow,
I won't bother you two any longer.
Mr. Lai.
Hey, you're here.
Having lunch?
Yes we are.
Mr. Lai, where is your food?
My food is
not here yet.
Then we will dig in first.
Yes, let's start eating.
What are you guys eating?
Homemade meals, the usual.
You're just eating vegetables?
There is meat too.
Still not here yet?
Oh you're finally here!
I almost starved to death.
Mr. Lai, you're so lucky.
You get to eat Ding Dong's cooking everyday.
Well, you see.
She insisted on cooking for me.
I couldn't stop her even if I try.
Guess what I saw.
Mr. Lai and Xiaoran quarreled with each other.
Don't be such a gossiper.
Exactly.
You know what they say,
a couple's quarrel never lasts.
they'll make up in a day or two.
Your future is bleak
if you spend all day thinking about love.
You know why Lai Zhengyi is still
just a CEO after all this time?
Why is that?
It's because he's busy dating.
If he had focused solely on his career,
he would have done much better by now.
Don't believe me?
Don't be so absolute about it.
You will fall in love sooner or later too.
Impossible.
Women will only affect
the speed at which I draw my sword.
Love will forever
be a stumbling block
on my path to victory.
I will never date or fall in love.
Never.
Have some food first.
I'm not hungry.
Ouch!
Lili.
The stick gave me a splinter.
You can pluck it out yourself.
Such a trivial matter.
Also,
I am formally informing you
that I am moving out.
I'm leaving.
From now on,
don't contact me anymore.
Lili.
Please don't go.
If you go,
how will I live?
Lai Zhengyi.
We
are over.
Lili.
I love you.
I love you with all my might.
Do I really have no chance anymore?
Lili.
Will you please love me one more time?
Well, if you put it that way,
I shall...
Lili?
Lili!
Yes?
Do you need a ride?
No need.
Qin Yanfei is fetching me.
Alright.
"Alright?"
Just like that?
Not even an attempt to keep me?
I'm leaving.
I'm home!
That was fast.
Aren't you always rushing me for it?
I was so busy moving,
I didn't even eat.
There's food.
Hold it right there.
You came back out of the blue
so I didn't prepare your portion.
How could you!
Forsaking friendship for your relationship.
Are you trying to starve me to death?
Who wants to starve you?
What now!
Here.
Just wait here for a while.
How could your dear brother-in-law
ever bear to starve you to death?
One moment,
I'll make you a feast right now.
Be patient, alright?
A feast.
Come, come.
Your favorite seafood feast has been served!
Enjoy.
Tell me if you need seconds.
Babe!
Are you even human?
You call this a feast?
Have a prawn.
Eat the prawn,
don't bother about her.
I'll peel it for you.
Isn't your table empty
with just the two of you?
That reminds me.
How is the heroine selection
for  going?
Don't talk about it.
Just mentioning it makes me angry.
Meijia and Ye Shu'er
may not be the best.
But with some guidance,
they could do a good job too.
-I just don't get why Lai Zhengyi -Here.
had to choose Liu Yue.
Among the three of them,
Liu Yue is the best choice.
'The best' my ass!
What you don't know is,
Liu Yue privately invited
Lai Zhengyi for a meal together.
That is directly infringing an unspoken rule.
I think it's not the role of Su Nianxue she's after,
it's Lai Zhengyi himself.
Jiang Lili.
Do you like Lai Zhengyi?
Huh?
Yes, I like him.
So what?
The two of you are not from the same world.
What a familiar line.
Are you going to
put out 5 million dollars next
and ask me to leave him?
I am being serious,
it's not a joke.
Lai Zhengyi is a shrewd person,
you can't fool him around.
Who is fooling around?
I'm very serious about it too.
You are serious,
but what about him?
He.
He should be.
There is no such thing as
'should be' in this world.
You know, Jiangjiang.
That angelic Mr. Lai of yours
have you in a tight grip.
Why don't I make you a cup of tea?
Don't call him that again!
What's wrong with you!
I'm going back to my table.
I'm not bothering with her anymore.
Let's resume our seafood feast.
Here, have some fish.
Mm, tasty.
Open up.
Yes?
[Meeting Room One]
's heroine
is now confirmed to be Liu Yue.
She has joined the crew.
Tomorrow, we will
officially begin filming.
Liu Yue is not very popular or well-known,
but her acting is top notch.
Of course.
[Liu Yue]
Someone with Mr. Lai's approval
can't possibly be bad.
Looks like Liu Yue
will become popular with this drama.
[Lemeng Pictures]
Finish the minutes for the meeting
and send it to me tomorrow.
Mm.
Must it be by tomorrow?
Yes.
Let go.
I am not Liu Yue,
keep your hands to yourself.
Then, let's have dinner tonight.
I'm not free.
I'm very busy.
Lover's quarrel?
Come closer.
She's jealous.
Oh.
What do you think?
Isn't it cute?
I think you might have
misunderstood the meaning of 'cute'
by a little bit.
Mm.
What do you know.
[Lemeng Pictures]
[Lift Lobby]
Mr. Lai.
Off work.
[Reserved Parking]
The battery is flat?
Jenifer.
You disappoint me.
I need to queue to get a cab?
There are already 215 people in queue?
[Longyi North Road Yongning Intersection]
Never thought that someone like me
would experience riding a bus in this lifetime.
[Jiangbin Bus Group]
What?
Hey!
What's up with this guy?
Yeah.
You can scan to pay instead.
Is he boarding or not?
He's so slow.
Open your payment app
and scan the QR code.
Hurry up.
Dude, can you hurry up?
We're all waiting to get home.
One moment, one moment.
Young people can't even take the bus nowadays.
I got this instead, what do I do?
Excuse me.
You can pay with my card.
Alright, hurry and board the bus.
[Jiangbin Bus Group]
If not for my supercar
running out of power,
I-
I would have never chosen
to take the bus.
So, it's perfectly normal that I don't know
how to pay for the bus for the first time,
right?
It is also perfectly normal that
I couldn't find the QR code, right?
You don't have to explain anything,
I am not interested.
How dare a small assistant like you
talk to me, the CEO, like that.
So sorry.
[Jiangbin Bus Group]
My dear husband,
do you know?
Today is our 30th
wedding anniversary.
Here.
May our years ahead be as joyful as today,
and may there be plenty of years to come.
Cheers.
Zhengling?
Why are you home?
You little brat,
suddenly back without a word of greeting.
Where are your manners?
That's right,
you should have told us earlier.
I will tell the housekeeper
to prepare some nice dishes for you.
I'm not eating.
Zhengling,
what's wrong?
You can talk to me, your mother.
[Jiangbin Bus Group]
Right, greetings.
Hello,
hello.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Don't bother with him.
This child
never ceases to make me worry.
Sighs.
Who would have ever thought?
[Sometimes it is difficult to stop the rolling stone]
I avoided that gold digger
who threw herself at me.
[But no matter where it is rolling]
I also avoided that
old rich woman thirsting for me.
And yet, I fell
for the unexpected trap that is Ding Dong.
My twenty over years of innocence, tarnished...
I blame the driver.
Yes!
I blame it all on the driver.
Good morning everyone.
Morning.
[Lemeng Pictures]
Mr. Lai.
you must have scored
some good ones last night.
What are you talking about?
I thought you went to a bar last night.
Not at all.
There was only one evil bus.
Morning, everyone.
Ding Dong, good morning.
Morning, Ding Dong.
Erm...
Hi.
I...
Xia Shan.
Help me organize this,
and summarize this news article.
Alright.
No problem.
Good morning!
Hello.
From now onward,
this is my seat.
We're switching seats.
But to change seats,
we need to report it to the administrative department.
Damn this company,
so full of rules.
I- I.
What's going on?
I have no clue.
He's avoiding someone.
Who?
It's not you anyway.
To think there's someone in this world
Mr. Lai would hide from.
Ding Dong.
Just a kid throwing a tantrum,
don't mind him.
Throwing a tantrum?
[Lemeng Pictures]
What are you doing!
What?
Why are you in my seat?
you gave me a scare.
Others hide when they want to be lazy,
but you don't bother hiding at all.
I have always been an upright person,
none of that sneaking and hiding for me.
Of all the seats out there,
you have to choose mine?
Don't you have your own desk?
I don't want to sit there.
I am the future successor
of Lemeng!
I will sit where I want to sit.
You will sit where you want to sit?
That's right.
You can go to the toilet,
or the security office.
So why must it be my seat?
The toilet stinks,
the security office is too hot,
but your place
has decent lighting and everything.
I can tolerate it.
My place is pretty good.
Watch my mouth shape.
Scram!
Yes?
What does that mean?
Scram!
[My beloved baby Li]
Let's have lunch together.
[My beloved baby Li Let's have lunch together]
No way.
I quit eating lunch.
She is still angry.
[Lemeng Pictures]
Done with work?
Mm.
I'll drive you home.
No need.
It's on the way, anyway.
Let me send you home.
You live in the east,
I live in the west.
How is that on the way?
Is everything north of earth on the way?
Hello? Sister.
It is 5 minutes past dismissal time.
Have you boarded a car?
Not yet.
Are you currently with
Lai Zhengyi?
No, no.
It's not him.
I'm on my way home now.
Even a rabbit is hard to
appease when it's agitated.
[Mr. Lai]
Hello?
What now?
Hello, Lili.
I don't know why,
but there is a sudden blackout in my hou-
Yes?
[Lili]
Hello?
What was that sound?
The phone you are calling is powered off.
Did something bad happen?
Mr. Lai.
Mr. Lai!
What happened to you?
Are you ok?
Are you hurt?
Lili.
It's alright now.
I am here.
I am right here.
I checked it out.
It's nothing serious,
a circuit breaker just tripped.
Your call just now ended abruptly,
and there was no answer when I called back.
It gave me such a fright.
It was pitch black in the house
so I tripped and fell.
My phone ran out of power too.
I'm so sorry for making you
come here in the middle of the night.
As long as you're okay, it's fine.
Lili.
Did I do anything to make you angry?
What?
No such thing.
I'm very happy.
Then why have you been ignoring me?
I'm not ignoring you.
Didn't I come to save you?
Is it because of Liu Yue?
Do you suspect my relation with her?
I was eating with Director Wang that day.
He was the one who invited Liu Yue.
I couldn't refuse it.
Director Wang said she was his direct apprentice.
Her capability was so exceptional,
even Bi Xiaoran approved of it.
That is why I agreed to let her star in
.
There was absolutely
no personal feelings involved.
Why did you lend her your handkerchief
if no personal feeling was involved?
Even I never got to use your handkerchief.
That was Xiao He's handkerchief,
not mine.
Xiao- Xiao He's?
I don't even use a handkerchief,
don't you know?
You have lived with me for so long
and you didn't know?
In the end,
you still don't believe me.
I.
I didn't know that was Xiao He's handkerchief.
I am to blame.
I was being petty.
I'm at fault, I'm at fault.
I believe you, really.
I'm sorry.
Really?
Mm.
Then,
can you stay here for the night?
Huh?
I'm scared.
I can't.
My sister is going through menopause lately.
She keeps a very close eye on me.
If I don't go home tonight,
she will be charging in here
with her 50 meter long broadsword.
My life is on the line here,
I really should go.
Take care of yourself, okay?
Sleep soon.
Sorry
for making you travel all this way.
You can go home,
I'll be fine alone.
Then I will be on my way.
Mm.
Let me know when you get home.
Be safe.
I'll be fine on my own.
How about
I stay here
for the night?