since you left
Father has always been thinking about
After all, they are biological parents
Is it
free at kisskh.me
Can you really not let go?
before mother died
He told me personally
If I am not selected
Mr. Mu doesn't have to die
Mothers don't have to die with hatred
he said everything
all because of me
I want to see my mother one last time
he took me
escorted to Pengcheng House
Imprisoned for half a year
Only the sound of wind and rain in the cold night
ever heard
A voice of care from a loved one
at that time
where is the father
brother
where are you
empress empress t-shirt
That's why I entered the palace to see you
such a grace
how rare
sister
You can blame us
hate us
you can't just watch
The whole Sun family is suffering
my brother
I beg you
you go now
i don't want to see you again
even if all of us
I can't help you
What about the mother who died?
She has cared for you since childhood
Have you fulfilled her last wish?
you have not
If she is alive
And keep your eyes open
looking at her husband
and my own son died because of you
you can handle her
You are not afraid of the Queen's intimidation
is worried
your own glory
rest assured
If you want to kill
just kill me
won't implicate you
dignified boy
Ziping
want a future sister
earn it yourself
This
Ziping
sister
pinning on crony
Ziping
Don't fight, you greedy rat.
sister
get out of here
roll
Zijin
Meng Shang food
Originally you hand-picked
Participate in the Shangyuan Banquet
This time her hand was severely damaged
I'm afraid it's hard to heal for a while
whether
Master of Food
free at kisskh.me
aren't you still sick
Master of Food
Please allow me to participate in the Shangyuan Banquet
as a cook
Both carving and spooning
your hand hurts badly
In case because of the test
aggravated the injury
can you
Meng Shangshi chose me as his deputy
If I just cherish my hands
How to be worthy
The kindness of adults
I have made up my mind
Please allow the food
Okay
I promise you
Hu Shangshi
everyone laughs
Hu Shangshi is beyond his own power
blatantly provocative
I guess
over the years
Hu Shangshi has been hiding his strength
Until the big day
in front of people
this is a
Hu Shang suffers
Ten years of waiting
Prepare to spend half a lifetime of forbearance
To fight for the most desired glory
But this time
God will be on my side
just you
probably never again
Can't lift the knife's hand?
Yes
Just me
May drop disabled right hand
I want to see you lose
Lose the most desired power
Desperate to leave the Forbidden City
As expected of the person I trained
Okay
I'd like to see
How do you fulfill this oath
You are so annoying, so annoying, so annoying
stop following me
Your Highness just had a nightmare
Reminds me of a lot of old times
There are many that I don't remember
say anything
Don't hesitate
Your Highness
Shangyuan Festival
Aoshan Long Live Lantern Festival
in preparation
At that time, His Majesty will invite the concubines and ministers
Tongguan Aoshan
Must send more staff
Strict inspection
Yes
adult
everything is ready
If it hurts like this, just give up
Meng Shang food
Why insist on participating in the test
I can choose another deputy
Master of Food
I asked the Seasonal Medicine
If I rest in peace
When will it be restored
she says
It's all up to God
just in case
then this is me
Last chance of life
injured hand
Even the most basic skills have been forgotten
mashed chicken
The knife should not be too heavy
Otherwise the tendon will break in it
Again
Yes
Since this is your request
I will make strict demands on you
no matter your hand
Will it really be ruined?
must persevere
Yes
Okay
another one
beautiful fireworks
Okay
His Majesty
another one
good one more
well
come again, come again
another one
go
wonderful
it looks so good
The lights are going on
Why hasn't His Royal Highness arrived yet?
well
Okay
Ziping
What did you bring me here for?
really too late
one more hour
coming to dinner
What are you panicking about?
Today's Shangyuan Festival
Aoshan Lantern must see
look
Okay
You look good
So beautiful
wonderful
it looks so good
so beautiful
Ziping
look at you
you
Where is Zijin going?
sons and ministers see father and queen mother
Brother you are awesome
your majesty
Prince is all for you
just finished the show
just smile
superfluous
prince of a kingdom
reckless
what kind of system
Erchen just wanted to
happy after coaxing mother
mother
Just now you have seen it
I saw it all
can you have this kindness
The mother is so happy
Hu Shangshi
It's up to you to decide
Eight Chinese Cuisines
But in general terms
More than 10 million delicacies from all over the world
we are fighting
No limit to cuisine
How about a complete fight?
How to call a fight
As usual
Good cuisine to be praised by His Majesty
feast for the ministers
You and I show our talents
compare final
Delicious dishes on the list of official banquets
Who is the best chef in the world
Not at a glance
as you say
Later if you can't stand it
I'm going to make a substitution
Don't worry, Lord Shangshi
millet
I come
free at kisskh.me
What is Yao Dianshan doing?
serve
Chicken skin is soft
meat is tender
unusual taste
back to the emperor
This Salted Chicken
wrapped in gauze paper
dried chicken
Salt
That's kind of fun.
His Majesty
This exquisite peony
Not only beautiful
taste better
There is also a unique smoky flavor
Lord said yes
slaves specially
Raw smoked fish with tea
There is a slight fragrance in the smoke
Then take this
Didn't you say you want to offer nine cold dishes?
Why is a savings box sent away?
Is this giving up?
People are worth knowing
so good
His Majesty
slaves dare
Please, Your Majesty, reveal it in person
you
don't scare her
I really want to see
in this box
What a treasure
This is
Nine-color storage box
This box looks so fancy
Available with the usual box
It's just one more cold dish
I see
Haven't worked hard yet
Back to the words of His Royal Highness
The so-called nine-color storage box
is
garlic white meat
Gold robe white ball
Chili Ma Chicken Slices
Crispy crucian carp
Sauce Crispy Peach Kernel
Red Oil Rabbit
beef with tangerine peel
Ginger Cowpea
Sweet and Sour Snow Rolls
Nine kinds of ingredients, nine kinds of knife skills
Nine different cooking techniques
The beauty is not in the dish itself
but according to different seasons
Dishes can be adjusted at any time
The combination of meat and vegetables is different
The little box is all-encompassing.
Just follow this nine-color storage box
Instructed Guanglu Temple to give a banquet to the ministers
Yes
what is the queen laughing at
His Majesty
How interesting do you see this drama
which drama
Pain relief with acupuncture
Can only seal the pain for a while
If you can't stand it
must not be forced
Yao Zijin
so sharp
It's rare to see
how
your hands
Can you support it?
until you lose to me
it will be clear
Duck breast not yet coloured
Plus the fire
Yes
Meng Shang food
Unurgent
Hidden set
give me this
It turned out to be slow roasting
i want to try
Silent
Why eat today
so solemnly
Your Majesty congratulates the Shangyuan Festival
The Food Bureau carefully prepares meals
slaves dare
Your Majesty please taste
His Majesty
This is the Shang Food Bureau in front of the royal family
How about a test of cooking skills?
It's more fun than watching a hundred dramas
That's true
Your Majesty please wait
roast duck
This duck meat is tender and delicious
Crispy and crispy skin
And this thin layer
oil on skin
Duck is too oily
Less oil is not fragrant
Good thing this is just right
fragrant
It's indescribably fragrant
Do not
The Roasted Duck at Guanglu Temple is Old and Oily
Can't compare to this
His Majesty
Jinling Roasted Duck Raw Material
wild duck
It is now carefully selected
stuffed white duck
food is only one
The cooking skills are the most important
heat difference
a thousand miles
dipped in duck's paw
The unique aroma of ham
There is also a light floral fragrance
is honey
Slaves use the sweetness of honey
Neutralized savory ham
To highlight the umami of the main ingredient duck feet
This roast duck
It's about technique
And this ladder duck
The test is ingenuity
Can't decide this game.
so
It's a draw
Chicken is crispy
It's also unique
Your Highness, what's wrong with this dish?
fresh and smooth
mellow taste
looks like bean curd
But how can there be bean curd
so delicious
It seems
The two Shang Shi are again
It's a tie
This winter squash chicken
It is combined with winter melon cup
The practice of chicken with watermelon
very fresh
only
This watermelon can be greasy and fresh
can for chicken soup
bring a sweet
But this winter melon is thick
No matter how beautifully carved
can only be reduced to a container
What's up with this chicken soup?
His Highness said
each ingredient
It should be put to good use, right?
His Highness said
Everything is the negligence of slaves
what is this doing
What is this thing going up?
I don't know
Hidden set
Hu Shangshi
Are you rubbing yellow mud on the winter bamboo shoots?
You come
Okay
concentrate
don't make a fuss
Your Majesty's forgiveness
His Majesty
Once the fish and shrimp are dehydrated
Shipped into the palace chilled
often lose its taste
The best chef in the world
Can't make up for this regret
So is winter bamboo shoots
Winter bamboo shoots dug in the forest
Baked in place with puree
It is the most beautiful in the world
This bamboo shoot is off the ground
less than half an hour
The slaves are wrapped in yellow mud
simmer
to retain its natural fragrance
Please taste your majesty
This
This mountain family cleans up
The recorded forest fresh
should be eaten on the spot
Leave the soil for a long time and then smear with yellow mud
What's the use
Your Highness, you will know
fresh which
delicious
Please see the king
it's salt
This lotus root has a special taste
I can't even taste it
free at kisskh.me
food inside
Taiping Shenghui Fangnei
recorded a
Qi and Zhong
Medicinal diet for invigorating the lungs
It is this Taiping assorted lotus root
But lily yam
Asparagus and Poria cocos
Speaking of
nothing unusual
That medicinal meal
Is it for His Majesty?
Pity
Your Majesty must be
The delicacies of the mountains and the sea have been used for a long time
Stomach tired
will feel
This Qingquan is more fresh with winter bamboo shoots
yes princess
princess
should be fine
I do not know
Hu Shangshi, they are gone
check
Hu Shangshi
Are you ready?
ready
Kuai
careful
fine
strangeness
time is up
Why haven't you seen Hu Shangshi for so long?
goose meat rotten
The soup is fragrant
Your Majesty likes to eat goose
The way of roasting goose collected from the folk
no less than a thousand
to be praised by His Majesty
It's not easy
Eat two goose
I'm afraid I won't be able to taste it
Come
Even better than Yunlin Goose
The taste is three-pointed
There are also snow vegetables hidden in the belly of the goose
Aifei
queen
together
This goose is ivory
tender bone fragrance
end of product
blood in the bone
The taste is extremely mellow
It's unforgettable
right
Hu Shangshi
How this goose meal is cooked
back to your majesty
His Majesty
This dish presented by Hu Shangshi
It is the legendary fire goose
mother concubine
What is flaming goose
His Royal Highness King Wei
That's the goose
imprisoned in iron cage
charcoal grill
Goose drinking pepper paste when heated
goose feathers fall off
goose still alive
pepper paste penetration
goose meat tender
cook goose this way
The goose meat is extremely tender
bold
too cruel
Your Majesty's forgiveness
Hu Shangshi
Cook a dish from nature
how can you cook
Such cruel food
where are you coming from?
His Majesty
Your Majesty is gracious and merciful
Bans come before
How dare the slaves dare to disobey
only
How to make this goose meal
It is carefully developed by slaves
I hope your majesty
Please see the king
what is this
Your Majesty This is Coarse Shell Ash
This goose meal is made with coarse shell ash
Made in place of an open flame
No Fire Roasted Goose
Slaves are stupid and ignorant
Misunderstood Hu Shangshi
Please forgive me
Jealousy can slander and slander
No matter how high the cooking skills are
But there is nothing in my heart
How to be in charge of a game
Your Majesty, today is Shangyuan Festival
Not because of these little things
ruined the festive mood
The two Shang Shi must feel that
Today's banquet is boring
So specially
make everyone happy
alright alright you go down
Let's prepare meals
Yes
His Majesty
Is Yao Dianshan's hand alright?
Yes
It seems to be seriously injured.
You said she was hurt like this
Still sticking to the meal
I can't do it anyway
I can't do it for me
Yes
do not know either
Will it affect the future?
I think it hurts like this
never rest
It will definitely fall down in the future
I'll do the rest
you're sweating
you go do something else
Ziping
Do you know this seasoning recipe?
How many times have I peeked
learned early
you go
do something else
If I'm so badly injured
I can't even hold a knife
fine
be careful
Zijin
free at kisskh.me
This is my secret
Works wonders for musculoskeletal pain
At least relieve the pain for a while