Our Secret
EP08
I see now.
My daughter's grown up.
You think you can make a choice by yourself, right?
I can't control you anymore, right?
But I can still control you! Am I right?
I don't care!
No matter what method you use,
you have to change her to the liberal arts class!
If you can't, let me tell you,
from tomorrow,
wash your clothes yourself!
Cook by yourself!
I won't care about you anymore!
You…
Xianxian
Your teacher paid a home visit today.
He gave us this.
That's what your mother's angry for.
Xianxian
Do you know why your mother's so angry?
She thinks you've grown up.
and don't need her anymore.
She doesn't know how to express it,
so she behaves like that.
You should understand her.
I should also criticize you.
Why did you keep it as a secret
to hand in the application form?
Dad. It's my bad.
I should have told you.
Please help me beg mom
not to change me to the liberal arts class, okay?
I feel really happy at my present class.
And I don't want to be separated from my friends.
Alright. As for your mom,
I can help you.
But,
I am not that capable.
I can only give you one month.
For next monthly test,
try to get a good grade.
If you can do it,
there will be a way out of this.
Alight?
So students to the liberal arts and natural science classes
are temporarily settled.
It's not finalized, of course.
If some of you still want to study liberal arts
after studying for a while in this class,
tell me as soon as possible
to change it.
As for the placement test questions,
I won't teach them.
Later I'll hand out answers to you.
Analyze your errors after class,
and hand in the analysis before this Friday.
Alright. Let's continue.
I can only give you one month.
For the next monthly test,
try to get a good grade.
If you can do it,
there will be a way out of this.
Alright?
What's on your mind?
I was thinking…
I don't see great changes
of this class placement.
Because students who choose liberal arts
are few in reality.
No changes?
My dream girl, Yang Chunzi, left.
Now that you miss her so much,
just go with her.
It's too late.
Do you know anything else also late?
What?
The game disc I lent to you before.
I won't lend it now.
No, no, no.
Please! Lend me for a while!
Ask Yang Chunzi if she has it or not.
Borrow it from her.
I won't give you.
Song Ziqi! Kong Shadi!
Stand up!
It's all your fault.
Stand back!
Let's take out Mathematics Compulsory III.
Turn to Page 23.
Let's continue our class.
Let's learn Euclidean algorithm.
Euclidean algorithm is a kind of algorithm
recorded by Euclid in the "Elements".
Assume two integers are unequal.
Divide the larger one by the smaller one.
If the remainder
is still a non-zero number,
continue to divide until the remainder is zero.
Dad
Xianxian
Why do you come to this floor?
Didn't you say you would give me one month?
I come here to print a material.
The printer upstairs breaks down. Don't worry.
Did you chat with my mom?
Is she still angry?
Still a little bit.
She has another requirement for you.
Get at least 270 points in natural science.
That's killing me.
Just give my life to her!
My silly girl! Your life was originally given by your mom.
Well, I am not that capable.
That's all I can help you.
Fighting!
Thanks, Dad.
How can I get 270 points?
Studying while preparing for the competition
is such a burden for normal people.
Poor thing!
You are awake.
Did you stay up late to study?
Aren't you too tired in this way?
Can you get enough sleep?
It doesn't matter.
I've just made up for it.
What happened to you?
May I ask you:
Is there a way
to raise my grade to 270 points
of natural science in one month?
By dreaming.
Right now,
don't think too much.
Do more exam papers.
At your current level, you cannot even get 250 points,
let alone 270 points.
You're the 250 ("250" means "stupid" in Chinese)!
At least, I should work hard from now on.
Fighting!
Come on, Congcong.
Eat more meat.
Your body are growing. Eat more.
Mom
Why did you make so many delicious dishes today?
I wouldn't do it if you were not students.
Come on. Dishes will be cold soon.
Delicious!
Mom. Thanks for your hard work.
Eat more.
I've been cooking for over a decade.
Not until now have I heard a good word.
Come on, Congcong.
Eat more.
What a big dinner this evening!
Where's mine?
Well, I, I'm not that hungry.
Help yourselves, help yourselves.
I'll go reading for a while.
Tomorrow is weekend.
I'll take you to fill a prescription for your lenses.
Thanks, Mom.
Don't slack off in your study.
Two hundred and seventy points. We've made a deal.
One point less is not allowed.
Two hundred and seventy.
Be quiet.
The last weekly physics test papers
have been handed out.
Mr. Yang asks every student
to bring the error analysis
to him in his office in one week.
Don't forget it.
What's going on?
I'm helpless!
Let me see.
You got the formula wrong for this question.
You should've got this score.
And this one.
You didn't understand this question well.
The mass of the ping-pong ball is a misleading proposition.
You should've also got this score.
And this one.
It's even more unreasonable.
Every procedure is right
except for the result, which is so easy to get.
What were you thinking at that time?
If I could do everything right,
I would be the one to get 90 points.
No excuse for doing it wrongly.
This one…
Xianxian
Su
Why are you here?
Don't you need to take classes back in your university?
The new term hasn't begun yet.
So I want to come here to see you.
Are you free now?
Your mom is so demanding of you,
because she believes you are able to do it.
Don't be discouraged.
Because I also believe
you can do it.
I also thought I could,
but no comparison, no harm.
If there's anything you don't understand, you can ask me.
Didn't you learn liberal arts?
You look down upon me, don't you?
It's a piece of cake for me to teach you.
Maybe I think
I'm not that confident.
Thanks anyway, Su.
Oh, right.
I have another thing to say.
On the day of the graduation ceremony,
I wanted to take a photo with you.
But I didn't get a chance.
You should make it up to me today.
No problem.
Come here.
How time flies!
You're a college student now.
Does it mean we won't see each other for a long time?
What are you afraid of?
I'll come back during vacation.
I should go back for the class.
Our class supervisor will come there soon.
Xianxian
This is for you.
I hope you
can smile like that forever.
Definitely.
Go back for your class.
Xianxian, it just occurred to me…
Who took this photo for you?
Su took it for me just now.
Let me see. Let me see.
Look at the smile while looking back.
Su really knows how to take photos!
Look, look, look.
I've written down reasons why you made mistakes.
Look at them carefully this evening.
And there are two papers.
Finish them and give me tomorrow.
Two papers for one evening?
If you find them hard, don't do them.
If you get 200 points, you can still go to a college.
I didn't mean it.
Zhou Siyue
Why are you so cruel to our Xianxian?
Am I cruel to her?
College entrance examination is much crueler than me.
I'm helping her.
How about that?
Pay attention to the National Mathematics Olympiad first.
Fine. I won't care about you anymore.
Xianxian
Why haven't you been to the school?
Good morning. I'm waiting for Zhou Siyue.
Did he go downstairs?
Didn't he tell you?
He went to the training camp with other team members
of the Olympiad by bus this early morning.
I see.
I'll go to school now, Madam.
Be careful.
Good-bye, Madam.
Good-bye.
With huge waves are gone all those. Gallant heroes of bygone years.
(A Song Poem by Su Shi)
West of the ancient fortress appears.
At Red Cliff General Zhou won fame during the Three Kingdom.
Rocks tower in the air and waves teat on the shore.
Rolling up a thousand heaps of snow.
Zhou Siyue is off for the National Olympiad.
Not until now do I notice
that it's so hard to get used to the days
without a deskmate.
It seems as if he went to
a battlefield alone.
It may just be my illusion.
After all,
he should be very familiar with
this kind of competition life.
Who would pluck them?
(A Song Poem by Li Qingzhao)
Leaning on the window, how can I pass the time till night alone?
The drizzle falls on the buttonwood trees.
Rain-drops drip down at dusk.
As a time like this, what immense sorrow I must bear!
I always feel that he will go to a bigger
and broader world.
By his light,
I've also glimpsed what the broad world looks like.
I come to realize
that I also want to go there.
I don't want to be left behind.
I've heard that there's no
recruitment plan for the Shot Put Team.
Fine, fine, fine.
What are you doing here?
What? You frightened me!
Are you tailing after someone?
No, I'm not.
How stubborn you are!
Song Ziqi
I understand he didn't wait for me after class.
How dare he walk with another girl!
Piss me off!
Are you jealous?
I'm not.
I'll go home.
Well,
do you have any good idea?
I haven't come up with one,
but I'm a little bit hungry.
I see.
I'll treat you. Let's go!
Xianxian
Shadi, Keke.
Why do you study so hard recently?
Monthly test is coming.
I should be fully prepared.
When did you two hang out together?
Hello. May I help you?
Two lemonades.
Okay.
I thought you didn't care about Song Ziqi.
If the dog you raised from childhood ran with someone else,
wouldn't you feel anxious?
If I'm angry,
Song Ziqi also cannot live cozily!
I have an idea.
You can also find someone else to hang out.
Make him jealous.
You can organize a party.
Invite all classmates in front of him
except for him.
Let's see what his reaction is.
Good idea!
My birthday happens to be coming.
I'll organize a birthday party this weekend.
You must come there at that time!
When did you two
become such good friends?
You friends are also my friends.
Are you coming or not?
Of course. I'm sure I'll go there.
Here are your drinks.
-Thank you.  –Thank you.
You're welcome.
Why are you here?
Why didn't you say hello to me?
Let me sip yours. I'm dying of thirst!
Buy it by yourself!
I'll drink…
Song Ziqi
What's wrong by drinking yours?
How stingy you are!
Thank you.
Come on. Let's go home.
Go back yourself.
I'll go with Keke today.
Alright.
I'll go alone. Bye-bye.
Do you think
it's an indirect kiss?
Okay. I see.
Wait for me in the billiard room.
We should stop here. I'll hang up now.
Hello, Siyue!
Aren't you in the training camp?
Yes.
Do me a favor.
Take care of the little monster.
Guys! I'll hold a birthday party this weekend.
Come together!
Okay. Who will be there?
Just me, Ding Xian,
and a girl in Class Ten.
Only three of us.
Come over there. All of you!
Okay!
Good. They two will just play for these days.
Will you come or not?
Kong Shadi, what do you do in your birthday party?
In my birthday party?
We just sing, have dinner,
and play billiard.
Whatever you want to do.
You have fun, and my father pays the bill!
-Is it great?  -Really?
Don't cheat us!
For what?
I can prove it.
The party last year was even bigger than this year's.
To be honest, it was really interesting.
Count me in.
Count you in.
Who else?
Remember to come to me after class!
Come to me! Come to me!
Come to me after class! Did you hear me?
Your Highness
Are you going to celebrate your great birthday?
What a big scale!
Don't you know there will be a monthly test
after the National Day holiday?
Can you all get full marks
or achieve something like that?
Can you?
No.
Then cancel it!
Do your homework!
You two are awake?
I'm coming!
Xianxian
Shadi, Keke.
Come in.
No need to change your shoes.
I was just mopping the floor.
Come in.
Have a seat.
Are you alone at home?
My mom went out with my little brother.
My father went back to Keshan.
Why did you come here?
To invite you to my birthday party!
After being criticized by Auntie,
didn't you say you wouldn't organize it?
Forget it.
Song Ziqi, the bastard,
has no reaction at all!
But it doesn't hinder us three
to hang out together!
But
I still have so much homework to do.
Are you nuts?
Today's my birthday, Ding Xian.
Yes. How about that?
Take your homework with us.
Okay.
So, let's go!
Ding Xian. Are you going to wear these
to celebrate birthday with us?
What's wrong with these clothes?
I knew it.
Thankfully, I prepared this.
Here you are. Wear it.
What's this?
You celebrate your birthday.
Why should I wear it?
If I wear it, nobody's going to notice.
Try it on.
Hang on.
What's the matter again?
What's wrong with your jarhead?
Don't mention it!
Of course it's her who is to blame!
Alright. Let me handle it for you.
Let's go!
How will you fix it?
I'll help you to trim your jarhead.
Will it become…
If you keep doing it, I'll go back!
It's the most boring birthday
I've ever celebrated!
How miserable I am!
Well… How about shopping?
Boring.
How about the amusement park?
Then what on earth do you want?
I want a buzz.
I want a party.
I want him to hang out with me!
I know you are all here.
Aren't you celebrating your birthday?
Where are others?
The birthday party has been canceled.
Didn't you say you wouldn't come?
Why didn't I come?
I went to each of your birthday party!
This is your present.
Don't ask me for more this year.
What's the matter? Your Highness?
She just wants a buzz,
a party,
and others to hang out with her.
It's not a big deal.
Come on. Let's go to karaoke together.
I'll contact my classmates for you.
Ask more to come here.
Really?
Okay.
Xianxian, let's go together.
You go and have fun.
I should finish doing the paper first.
Today's my birthday!
I want you to be with me!
I'm not really good at singing, actually.
I'm afraid I'll spoil your spirits.
After the monthly test,
I guarantee that I'll make it up to you.
I swear.
Just let her go home.
Or her parents will be worried.
Alright.
Be careful when you go back home.
We'll go now.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Zhou Siyue
The monthly test is coming.
If I can't get good grades this time,
my parents will transfer me to a liberal arts class.
I feel so nervous!
Give me two.
Okay.
Here you are. Hold them.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Excuse me. I need a bottle of water.
Okay.
Here's your change.
Hold it.
Okay. Thank you.
Hello. May I help you?
A bottle of water, please.
Okay.
Your phone's here!
You! Thief! Stop!
Hello. What's the matter?
Siyue
Ding Xian is being followed by someone.
Where is she?
I'll go there first.
Stop!
Go to find her.
Thief! Give me my phone!
What if I don't give it to you?
Bro, you're here.
It's you.
Stop!
Come back!
Come down right now!
Don't run!
Come back!
Stop!
Song Ziqi. Come back now.
Something's wrong.
Open the door! Open the door!
Get out!
Open the door! Get out!
Open the door! Hurry up!
Open the door!
Open the door! Get out right now!
Get out right now!
Do you think you're safe in there?
Open the door!
Hurry up! Get out!
Open the door! Open it!
Open the door!
What are you doing here?
Are you the one we met last time?
Let me tell you.
It has nothing to do with you.
Leave us alone!
What if I don't leave?
What are you doing?
Want a fight?
Fuck you!
Fight with us?
Bastard!
Look how weak you are!
You piece of shit!
Siyue
Are you okay?
Come on!
Siyue
What's going on?
Who are you?
If you don't want to die, piss off!
Go.
Go. Hurry up!
Ding Xian
Xianxian
Are you okay?
I feel so worried!
I'll accompany her home now.
Let's leave here right away.
Or they'll ask more to come here.
Let's go.
Go, go, go!
Well, I haven't celebrated my birthday.
Let's go to celebrate your birthday.
Let's sing! Go, go, go!
Alright.
Go upstairs now.
Are you hurt?
No.
How come?
Don't worry.
From now on,
they dare not make trouble on you anymore.
How did you find me?
Jiang Chen
stumbled upon someone following you.
So he called me.
Did you see the message I texted to you?
Yes, I saw it.
You
just relax.
Don't give too much pressure on yourself.
I got a good grade of mathematics last week.
So I think I'll reach my goal in the monthly test.
It seems that you can still
get good grades without me around.
Of course.
No.
If you're around,
I can do better.
Alright.
Go upstairs.
Okay.
Zhou Siyue. You are sure to get good results.
And I will also stay in the natural science class.
Fighting!
I'm leaving.
Mom! You scared me!
Oh, you know you should come back.
I…
Whose clothes are you wearing?
A classmate of mine.
Today's her birthday.
So we hung out together.
Good for you.
Your monthly test is coming.
If you don't get good grades…
I see!
Mom. I will study hard.
Hello.
Did you come back?
I'm in my dormitory.
When you came back, were you criticized?
How come?
Teachers didn't notice it.
That's great.
I felt at ease when
I heard your voice.
Didn't you say you would study hard?
If you leave the camp without permission,
you will be disqualified!
Do you know it or not?
Where did you go?
Are you going to tell me or not?
If you aren't,
run ten laps around the playground right now!
Reflect on what you've done!