(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(This drama is set in an imaginary dystopian Korea,)
(and all people, organizations, and incidents are fictitious.)
Why did the police arrest Yo Han?
What on earth is going on?
Why aren't you saying anything? What is it?
Did Yo Han really do it? The church fire.
Did he really kill my mom and dad?
No, Elijah. That's not true.
It's all my fault.
I was stupid enough to be fooled by them.
I told the police that Yo Han killed Soo Hyun.
What?
I'll fix it no matter what.
I'll bring Yo Han back by all means.
I'll even risk my life.
Why... Why did you do that?
Why? Tell me.
I'm sorry, Elijah.
Why did you do that? Why?
Ms. Ji.
Please stay with Elijah at all times.
What about you?
Why did you want to see me in the middle of the night?
So are you saying...
Judge Kang has nothing to do with Lieutenant Yoon's death,
and it's all Ms. Jung's doing,
the Board Chairman of Social Responsibility Foundation?
That's right.
All right. I see.
That's an interesting claim,
but as you probably know,
we can't take action unless we have enough evidence.
Wait a second.
I accused Kang Yo Han of something he didn't do.
Is that right?
Are you saying you made a false accusation?
Yes.
I falsely accused him with malicious intent.
He got away with tampering with the trial by using public opinion.
I wanted to make sure he gets punished.
That's why I tampered with evidence...
and falsely accused him.
Arrest me.
Sir, please don't get so worked up.
Go home, have a good night's sleep,
and give it some thought.
The case is already closed. There's no point in doing this.
I guess you already received an order from the higher-ups.
I might have to report you for dereliction of duty.
I'll talk to the press as well.
Go ahead.
Oh, let me remind you of something.
A state of national emergency has been declared.
Under the emergency law, the press can't report anything...
without the government's permission.
But go ahead and try.
Who knows you'll find a company crazy enough to report it?
Kang Yo Han!
Kang Yo Han is here!
Welcome, punk. I missed you.
You're never going to leave this place.
Why? Because I'll kill you!
I'll kill you with my own hands, okay?
This place will be your grave!
We have shocking news.
Judge Kang of the live court show was arrested last night...
for aiding and abetting a murder...
and is being held in custody at Jungbu Detention Center.
The investigation revealed that the victim is...
Lieutenant Yoon Soo Hyun from RIU.
I can't believe this.
Judge Kang Yo Han was arrested without a warrant.
Judge Kang has been loved by the people...
running the live court show.
But now that Judge Kang is accused of murder by proxy,
it seems he'll face a public outcry.
You're the one who put Kang Yo Han...
in charge of the live court show, sir.
He fabricated the trials.
And he's arrested for solicitation to commit murder.
My goodness, Chief Justice Min.
How would I have known that?
And it wasn't me who wanted to put him in charge.
Are you saying it's not your responsibility?
Chief Justice Min.
Don't insult the judiciary anymore.
Now make a decision.
You're here.
Didn't you say you'll resign?
I'm here because someone has to clean up the mess.
I don't avoid taking responsibility.
How shameless you have become.
What about Soo Hyun?
Did you really let Soo Hyun die?
Just to put Kang Yo Han in danger?
How could you possibly do that?
I didn't know Soo Hyun would die.
I didn't think Board Chairman Jung Sun Ah would go that far.
One, two, three.
(Professor Min Jung Ho)
You want me to be the chief justice?
I know well enough that you don't care about the position.
But this generation needs someone like you.
Someone like Heo Joong Se is in politics...
and someone like Kang Yo Han conducts trials.
They're all the same.
Crooks who incite the masses.
The live court show they're planning run.
It seems very dangerous.
They're turning trials into cheap street shows.
I'm only assisting Mr. Seo Jeong Hak.
But I sincerely believe we should stop this no matter what.
I will try it at the foundation and you at the Supreme Court.
Maybe we could do something about this quietly.
You're a brave woman.
Well, someone has to do it.
When you become the chief justice, there's something you need to do.
You should put someone near him to keep an eye on him.
Keep an eye on him?
Professor Min.
My goodness.
I'm sorry. It's Chief Justice Min now.
You want me to be Judas?
Someone has to be there.
Someone who can keep his eyes wide open in this crazy wind.
Please.
There's no easy way...
to make justice in this world.
I hated Kang Yo Han for ruining the world.
So I just wanted to stop him.
Kang Yo Han's supporters are attacking me...
and revealing my family's personal affairs.
I can't let them do this.
I'll drag Kang Yo Han down...
from his position at all costs.
(Board Chairman Jung Sun Ah)
Did you kill Soo Hyun?
You didn't say something like that will happen!
Soo Hyun was like a daughter to me.
So? Are you saying you want to quit now?
Didn't you say you want to stop Kang Yo Han...
"at all costs"?
There's no going back now.
We're almost there.
The great chief justice of the supreme court...
who ended the time of chaos.
Don't you want to be remembered like that in history?
What do you think?
Chief Justice.
Someone has to become a monster to stop Kang Yo Han.
You can blame me all you want.
But history will judge me.
You dirty hypocrite.
Call security.
How could you do it?
How could you let Soo Hyun die?
How could you?
Tell me, Min Jung Ho! Tell me!
- Tell me. - Sir!
Tell me!
Let go. Let go!
Min Jung Ho, tell me!
Tell me! How could you do it?
Min Jung Ho!
Judge Kim, I just watched the news. What's going on?
It's not true, is it? Chief Kang didn't do it, right?
It's not true. The foundation set this up.
I knew it.
What can I do to help?
We should get the chief out of this.
Oh my. Look who's here.
(Chief Warden Nam Shi Woo)
They say you'll run into your enemy at the worst place and time.
Do you know what I've been through because of you?
What about the testimony from the prison warden? Did it go well?
Yes. He's very scared. He'll do as we say.
Did the Minister of Justice order you to do this?
("Minister Cha ordered me to switch out Doh Young Choon.")
Yes. Minister Cha Kyung Hee ordered me to do it.
Were you bribed or blackmailed?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't endure the threats from Minister Cha.
I was demoted and ended up here because of you.
You're assigned for the victims of major cases.
Isn't that a good thing for you?
How dare you!
Hey. Do you still think you're a judge?
You're now a rat under my control. Do you get that?
Got that?
Gosh.
Board Chairman Jung, you're amazing.
When did you turn Min Jung Ho over to our side?
You're the best! The best!
The best!
Gosh.
My goodness.
Here, Board Chairman Jung...
Sit.
Board Chairman Jung, you're a brilliant storyteller.
You know Jesus loved Judas the most among his disciples.
But Judas stabs him in the back...
and betrays him.
I bet Kang Yo Han is out of his mind in jail by now.
He ordered someone to murder a police officer.
He's completely out of the game now.
Kang Yo Han...
don't have to be put on a trial, right?
What do you mean?
Now that he's out of the game anyway.
So if he just disappears quietly,
won't everyone be happy?
That's what I think.
Our president thinks too much.
If you have too many trivial thoughts,
that means it's time for you to step down.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sure you won't need my help. My apologies.
Well, if you'll excuse me. I need to go to the toilet.
Stop right there!
She can do a perfect job on her own.
What's wrong with you?
Of course, she can.
Board Chairman Jung is not an ordinary woman.
How dare you!
Heo Joong Se got used to it pretty quickly.
His position changed,
then the man has completely changed too.
Right.
But...
he changed too quickly.
What?
Plus, the conniving old men who only care about money...
are suddenly playing up to Heo Joong Se, who's useless now.
I might have underestimated Heo Joong Se.
Look into it. I'm sure there's something there.
Heo Joong Se...
kept obsessing over forcing more residents out.
Check the Dream Home Village accommodations.
See if there any places with missing people...
or if they have been moving the residents to some other place.
Thank you for supporting my husband's plans.
The weekend farm?
Yes.
You guys did a great job convincing your husbands.
It was close.
No need to thank us.
To be honest, we support things that make us money.
Since we're on the topic, do you want to visit the weekend farm?
Sounds good.
I'm curious to see if our crops are growing well.
Okay. I'll set it up.
Even if you fell for a trap,
how could you frame Judge Kang for murder?
I know it's shameless,
but can you help me out this one time?
I need to save Chief Kang,
but I can't do anything without your help.
I'm not sure.
I don't know if we can continue trusting in you, Judge Kim.
We don't have time.
Do you think they would leave Chief Kang alone...
until before his trial?
You don't know what they would do.
The only thing we can do is...
disclose something huge to tie up their hands and feet.
If the attention of the nation falls on them,
they'll back off to save themselves.
Hold on.
By something big, do you mean...
Yes, the inside of Dream Home Village.
It's an internment camp, so I'm sure it'll be dismal.
We need to expose that.
That's impossible.
There are soldiers standing guard.
I'll go alone.
Which facility is the most strictly guarded?
That place...
will have something they want to hide.
Then it's the Dream Home Medical Center.
Even if you manage to get inside,
there's no way you can manage to get out.
Will you still do it?
Yes.
Just get me in.
Okay. Let's say you get lucky, and you find something.
We have no means of revealing it.
The media is busy walking on eggshells around the administration.
Video platforms and social media have all been blocked.
This country...
is no longer a free nation.
There's...
something that I've come up with for that.
What did you come up with?
Just get me one thing.
Elijah.
There's something I wanted to tell you.
I met someone who worked at that cathedral recently.
That fire...
happened because a switchboard caught on fire...
due to some old wiring.
It wasn't anyone's fault. It was just an accident.
But Yo Han purposely tried to get you to suspect him.
You said, if you can walk again, you'll kill me first.
Don't get ahead of yourself. One at a time, okay?
He purposely filled out the application form...
to cancel the deed of covenant for you to see,
and he kept saying things to irritate you.
I don't care about someone I've already killed.
If I'm the one who really killed that someone.
It's because...
you had a really hard time after you lost your parents.
You didn't eat or sleep,
and you got thinner every day.
That's why Yo Han wanted you to continue living...
even if it was based on your hatred towards him.
But Elijah. Even if you were mistaken about Yo Han,
- You have to come soon. - that isn't your fault.
Yo Han did it because he wanted to.
You didn't do anything wrong, Elijah.
You just need to treat him well when you see him again.
Yo Han will come back to you soon.
It won't take long. I promise.
So eat something.
When Yo Han gets back,
how would he feel if you were sick?
- What are you doing? - Hey!
Hey, step back!
You've already been charged with the death penalty.
You can be executed at any time if that's what you want.
Don't kill me.
Is that as loud as you can be?
Don't kill me!
Go!
Hey!
- Hey! - Break it up!
Move it! Move out of the way!
Hey! Break it up!
- What are you doing? - Get out of here!
(Dream Home Foods)
(Handle with Care)
Hello.
(Shelter)
Over here.
Okay.
Let's go.
(Handle with Care)
(Dream Home Medical Center)
(Restricted Area)
You're almost done.
There you go.
I feel like my head is splitting!
Let go of me!
Ms. Han. What happened?
It's me, Kim Ga On.
Judge Kim. What are you doing here?
You can relax now.
The president is coming.
The president is here.
Excuse me. I'll be right back.
Hello.
Our selected medical staff.
You're doing a really good job.
As requested by EU, we're clinically testing the new vaccine.
Out of the 3,620 subjects,
the number of people who have died from side effects so far...
is 182.
Only 182? That's not bad.
Share the results with the client.
And let me know if any countries are behind in their payments.
One more thing.
Including Russia and Japan, we've received requests...
from a few more countries.
I think we should expand our farm quickly.
Many countries are competing to develop vaccines first.
Clinical trials are in extremely high demand right now.
My goodness. If Seoul citizens are not enough,
we'll need Busan, Daegu, and Gwangju citizens as well.
Nice. Our country doesn't produce a single drop of oil,
but we're fine as long as we have human resources.
As I always say, human lives come first.
You know I say that all the time, right?
Take a look around.
Do you know how much money each person is worth...
in clinical trials?
It's beyond your imagination.
And when they die, we remove all the functioning organs.
It doesn't end there. From hair to blood,
we collect and export all the by-products as well.
Absolutely nothing goes to waste.
Mr. President, you're a genius businessman.
Why have you been hiding it from us?
Were you going to hog all the profits for yourself?
I was waiting for the right moment to share it with you.
By the way, do we have to let Jung Sun Ah in?
I'm not saying we should leave her out though.
Without her, there's more for us, I guess.
She's not that useful anymore anyway.
She's just like Cha Kyung Hee. I hate aggressive women.
She's too smart for her own good.
She's just a lowly maid, after all.
Right? This is our chance to cut her off.
Also, send a man to the prison...
and take care of Kang Yo Han before he gets up to anything.
Yes, Mr. President!
Why are you doing this?
Do you like it?
Wait for me.
- Let's go. - Yes, let's go.
So Yoon, let's get out of here.
What are you doing?
I've been ordered to check her vitals.
I see.
Let's go.
Hold on a second.
What is it?
Relax, Judge Kim.
I've been waiting for someone to come and help.
And I'm not the only one.
We're all locked up here with our phones have been taken away.
There are sane people in here too.
This doesn't make any sense.
How could a nation do this to its people?
The person is dead.
The organs have been removed. We're taking her to the incinerator.
We'll help you.
We'll help you two escape. Please tell the world...
what's happening in here.
Yes, I will.
Are you okay?
(Village Home Medical Center)
Hello, Judge Kim. Are you okay?
Yes. I saved Ms. Han too.
I was lucky.
Did you get what I asked for?
Are you sure it's the only way?
Why don't you look for a brave reporter...
That's a long shot. We don't have time for that.
I understand.
(Phase-3 Clinical Trial In Progress)
You're so pretty. How old are you?
I'm 18 years old.
What have I done?
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
(Associate Judge Oh Jin Joo)
Ga On, have you come up with any idea?
Have you?
I need to ask you for a favor.
Just say it. I'll do anything.
Chief Justice Min Jung Ho will be inaugurated tomorrow.
(Chief Warden Nam Shi Woo)
Darn you.
That's really all I have to do?
Yes. Do just that for me.
Okay, but...
what will you do at his inauguration?
(Judge Jung: Bad news. Turn on the TV.)
This just in.
Kang Yo Han who was arrested for instigating murder is dead.
He was taken to Jungbu Detention Center...
where it seems he was stabbed by an assailant.
Judge Kang was the first judge in Korea to...
(Kang Yo Han killed in prison)
Sun Ah.
It's okay.
I'm okay.
I took him down myself.
It worked out.
It's really over now.
"The End" appears on screen...
and the ending credits go up.
Then, at long last, the lights come on.
And people clap and leave.
I guess Kang Yo Han had grown on me.
I think I'll miss him a bit.
Should we host his memorial every year?
Stick a candle and an incense stick in a cake...
and lay out meat pancakes and jabchae...
Do you have a serious problem? A concern?
Pardon?
As if I would.
I was just...
thinking about the dreadful things he put us through.
Wasn't it just sickening?
It was dreadfully sickening.
We should let him go now.
Which is why I think...
we should host something meaningful.
Like what?
Something to commemorate Kang Yo Han and congratulate us.
Chief Justice Min Jung Ho will be inaugurated tomorrow.
And?
Now it will forever be your reign.
Celebrate with the core members of the foundation.
In the hall where Kang Yo Han held court...
and dared to challenge you.
What's the occasion, Chairman Min?
Is it your time to die? Why act out of character?
No, it's not a bad idea.
Oh, call Jung Sun Ah and make sure she's there.
Even in the middle of the night,
I jump up.
I get why you two did what you did, but her...
How dare someone like her...
In the hall where her lover held court,
we'll end her too.
(Board Chairman Jung Sun Ah)
Now that it's all over, we should make a toast.
Your era has come.
We need a female president!
Okay. See you in the Supreme Court.
Sure.
(Board Chairman Jung Sun Ah)
Jae Hee.
Yes?
Get me a pistol.
A cute one that'll fit in my purse.
What for?
I think...
I'll become president.
Now I must protect myself.
You've done a good job until now.
The time of madness is over.
Now,
it's time to rebuild justice.
I will be a chief justice...
who builds up the once fallen judiciary...
with new foundations.
Thank you.
Sir. May I ask why you held a press conference...
instead of a formal inauguration ceremony?
We're in a state of emergency.
This is not a time to put my personal honor at the forefront.
I hope you will all understand. Thank you.
May I ask what your future plans are?
(Chief Justice Min Jung Ho's Inaugural Press Conference)
Sir.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Judge Oh.
While you were talking to the press...
Chairman Jung Sun Ah asked me to tell you...
she wants to see you in private.
- Did she? - She said...
she'd wait in your old office...
because it's still empty.
Okay.
Ga On, I gave him the message.
Thank you.
Now please leave the building.
What? Leave the building? Why?
I'll explain later.
Do as I say for now.
Okay.
Wow, the interior here is actually quite nice.
Up here, wow, what a great view.
You all look like minions.
So this is why Kang Yo Han...
was so haughty and arrogant.
Chairman Jung, you look amazing up there.
It's as if there's a light shining from behind you.
That's right.
Can we host future important foundation events here now?
Upper-class ladies definitely have...
a better sense of theatrics.
- Yes, we're experts. - You don't know anything.
Honey.
- Oh, my gosh. - You can't climb up?
Help me.
Ga On. What are you doing?
[VIU Ver] tvN E16 'The Devil Judge'
"To Save Yo Han"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Come with me, Professor.
Ga On.
There's no media outlet with the conscience to report the truth.
But things might change if the news is tantalizing and money-making.
How about...
the new chief justice who died with his pupil...
on his first day in office?
No!
Once the bomb goes off,
the major media companies will get an email in my name.
Exposing the truth of the Dream Home project.
This time, they won't be able to ignore it.
Ga On, please...
Consider this...
your atonement for what happened to Soo Hyun.
If you have any conscience left.
Ga On, no.
Was I a bit late?
I had to dig myself out.
Chief.
Darn you.
You're alive.
I'm so relieved.
What happened?
You're now a rat under my control. Do you get that?
But, sir.
How was the weather in the Bahamas?
What are you talking about?
The 12 million dollars you amassed...
doing all sorts of corruption and crimes for 30 years.
You put it all in a secret account in the Bahamas.
During your vacation last summer.
How do you know that?
Sit down.
I told you to sit down.
Do you think it's a coincidence you're here and not jobless?
You were my insurance policy.
In case things went wrong.
You'd better check.
The money is not there anymore.
(Chief Warden Nam Shi Woo)
Judge. Please help me.
That money means my life.
What do you want?
What can I do for you?
Your specialty.
- Pardon? - Swapping prisoners.
You're so well-known, there's no way we won't get caught.
Did I say we must get away with it forever?
For just 24 hours.
Keep the secret for just 24 hours.
Then I'll give you back your money.
Will you really do that?
You did something terribly bad.
No. It wasn't me.
The Blue House, someone from the Blue House...
It wasn't part of my plan, but it'll work.
We have a body to swap out for mine, don't we?
Yes.
You had a plan?
To get out on your own?
As if.
- Sorry, Judge Kim. - Lawyer Ko.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
I wasn't sure I could trust you 100 percent.
You got out with the help of the guy who swapped Doh Young Choon?
Then did you really return his money?
I did.
In the form of love, not cash.
(Chief Warden's Office)
(Thank you for your donation.)
(Care Home, Orphanage, Welfare Center)
Kang Yo Han, you punk.
What now?
He must pay for what he did.
A life for a life.
Will you let me...
take care of him personally?
Let's go.
A toast! Cheers!
- Cheers! - Cheers!
- Why raise it so high? - Right?
He's so funny.
What's this?
What's going on?
Is there a special event?
Who set this up?
It's chilling.
It's not me.
(Live Court Show)
How are you?
To Kang Yo Han who is in the afterlife!
Wow. What a lovely atmosphere.
Seeing you all gathered...
is very emotional.
I'm pleased to see you too!
Thanks for the gesture, Chairman Park.
- What? - How does he know?
You're alive.
Is this live?
How is this possible?
He's dead.
What kind of prank is this?
It's a prank? That hurts.
It's a solemn trial.
A trial?
What's he saying?
You blocked the newspapers, broadcasting, and the internet,
but there's one thing you forgot.
Hang on.
The DIKE App!
Bingo!
We'll start the live broadcast right now.
Dear fellow citizens. Your final trial will start now.
(Live Court Show, The final trial will start now!)
(DIKE)
(DIKE, Live Court Show)
First, let me introduce you to today's guests.
Park Du Man, chairman of Saram Media.
Pi Hyang Mi, the financial manager of Saram Media.
- What? - Oh, my.
Kim Sang Sook, director of Minbo Group.
(Kim Sang Sook, director of Minbo Group)
Min Yong Shik, chairman of Minbo Group.
(Min Yong Shik, chairman of Minbo Group)
(Do Yeon Jung, the current first lady of South Korea)
Do Yeon Jung, the first lady of South Korea.
Heo Joong Se, the president of South Korea.
Why is he including me?
They are the people who move this country.
- Honey. - Why don't I have reception?
Honey. What's going on?
I don't have reception.
This is an act of terror against the chief of state!
This is a crime!
Yes. This is a crime. I'm a criminal.
But what about you?
Aren't you a criminal too, Mr. President?
(Footage from the inside of Dream Home Medical Center)
Dear citizens. This is the truth behind the Dream Home Project.
Is this the despicable thing you were doing behind my back?
Did you know about it?
- You crazy wench! - Isn't this incredible?
They used a nonexistent virus as an excuse to drag people away,
and they sold them to conduct experiments on human bodies.
This is only something that a creative lunatic could come up with.
- This is all fake... - I admire you, Mr. President.
This doesn't make sense. Hold on.
Dear fellow citizens whom I love and respect.
This video has been fabricated!
This is an anti-national act conducted...
in an attempt to overthrow the current administration.
- As I always say, - Okay?
human lives come first.
Take a look around.
Do you know how much money each person is worth...
in clinical trials?
It's beyond your imagination.
And when they die,
we remove all the functioning organs.
It doesn't end there. From hair to blood,
we collect and export all the by-products as well.
Absolutely nothing goes to waste.
And...
You look good on camera. It must be because you were an actor.
These people died in the hands of Jung Sun Ah,
the board chairman of Social Responsibility Foundation.
She killed innocent people...
to fulfill her ambitions...
and to attack me.
And the newly appointed Chief Justice, Min Jung Ho,
is a hypocrite...
who acted as Jung Sun Ah's informant for his personal greed.
He betrayed Lieutenant Yoon Soo Hyun,
who was like a daughter to him,
and joined forces with her murderer, Jung Sun Ah.
(DIKE Live)
Isn't this surprising?
Go...
and live in misery for the rest of your life.
Your name will go down in history.
Just like you wanted.
Dear fellow citizens.
Are they guilty?
(What's your choice?)
(You have cast your vote.)
(National Vote Status)
(Innocent, Guilty)
- Darn. - No.
I'm being falsely charged.
Then we need a proper sentence.
What is that? Where is that?
Is that here? Look at that.
Honey. What is going on?
If you try to leave this place,
this bomb will go off.
- He said there's a bomb. - Go check!
Oh, no. Honey!
It's real!
Oh, no!
Dear fellow citizens. You should judge them yourselves.
Our president received ten million votes during the election, right?
The moment the votes on the DIKE app reach that number,
you will get to watch magnificent fireworks.
It'll be to celebrate the victory of democracy.
(Number of Voters)
(What's your choice?)
What should we do?
(Number of Voters)
I'm going to go now.
Where will you be going?
To the stage.
The door to the left when you're facing the bench.
What is this?
(Number of Voters)
Honey.
Kang Yo Han, that jerk.
Is it locked?
- It's locked. - Darn it.
Darn it!
Oh, no.
Oh, my. Oh, my goodness.
- Kang Yo Han! - Oh, my.
If you take one more step,
I'm going to blow this place up right now.
(Number of Voters)
Dear fellow citizens.
The footage of the inside of the Dream Home Medical Center...
was taken by Judge Kim Ga On, who risked his life to film it.
Once everything is over,
Judge Kim will testify and tell the whole truth.
The evil people who are with me...
will go to the afterlife with me.
No.
Honey.
Judge Kang. You have to let me live.
I did everything you told me to do.
I brought everyone here!
Hello?
It's been a while, Chairman Min.
You're... How did you...
I'll get straight to the point. Listen up.
I need you to do something for me.
On the day of Min Jung Ho's inauguration ceremony,
bring every member of the foundation to the court.
What?
- Have you lost your mind? - Otherwise, you're dead meat.
You pocketed the foundation's funds to save Minbo Group from bankruptcy.
I have the evidence.
You're lying.
If you can't believe me, check your desk drawer.
I put a copy in there.
You had the audacity to steal their money.
Save me.
When that gets out, they'll kill me.
If you want to live, do as I say.
Right now.
You piece of...
You crazy little...
Get off me. How dare you?
You crazy clown.
Save me.
You have to save me!
All right. Since you made a deal with me,
I'll give you a chance.
- The door opened. - The door is open.
This situation...
(Number of Voters)
Isn't it familiar to you?
Just like you did ten years ago at the church,
run for your life.
Only the fastest person survives.
What?
(Number of Voters)
Gosh.
No!
(Number of Voters)
Yo Han.
Isaac.
- Honey! - You jerk!
Hold on. Quiet, everyone!
Hold on a second. Kang Yo Han, listen.
I'll offer you a deal.
Quiet, everyone! Attention!
Yo Han.
I'm the only person you should save.
I'm the commander-in-chief.
It'll be a win-win for both of us.
The others are just a bunch of businessmen and women!
I'm different.
Without me, what will happen to the country?
I'm the Republic of Korea, for goodness's sake!
I'm an artist and leader.
Save me this once.
For this country! Please!
I'm the king of this country!
Please! I'm the king!
I'm the king! Don't you know?
(Number of Voters)
Gosh, the jerk talked too much.
Shoot him! Shoot him right now!
- Shoot him! - Shoot him!
Shoot him! Please!
You can do it. Shoot him!
Shoot him!
Is it you and me in the end?
Come with me, Sun Ah.
Bye,
Master Yo Han.
Gosh, this is so annoying.
It's okay, Sun Ah.
It's okay.
You know what?
I really liked you, Master Yo Han.
Please, let us live.
- Sir, help us. - Help us.
- I'm sorry. - Help us.
Please let us go.
I'm sorry. Let us go.
I'm sorry.
Chief.
Don't move.
Why did you come here?
Don't do it.
Will you leave Elijah behind?
And die with these jerks?
I have no choice.
Once the performance ends, the actor must disappear.
- No! - Help us!
- Let us go! - Judge Kang!
Don't kill us!
(Explosive Ordnance Disposal)
(Number of Voters)
I'll go with you.
You'll be a hero.
There need not be...
more than one devil.
Chief. Wait.
Chief!
- Chief! - It's too dangerous.
Kang Yo Han!
(Number of Voters)
- Judge Kang. - I'm sorry.
Don't do it!
- Don't do it! No! - No!
Kang Yo Han!
(Number of Voters)
(Fire Department)
(Ambulance)
Ga On, are you okay?
The ambulance is here.
Let's go. Can you stand up?
Elijah.
Elijah?
How's this?
Are you okay?
You thought I'd bring it down, didn't you?
(Blueprint)
(Secure exit, check exit time, time until explosion)
(Watch pillars, safest location, must check distance)
What is concentrated is also easier to bring down.
Once the show is over, the magician must exit.
The cleaning is done.
Now there must be something for you to do.
(Now there must be something for you to do.)
Ms. Ji.
Master Yo Han was here.
What happened? Where is Elijah?
Well...
Master Yo Han.
You're alive.
Were you worried?
Do you even have to ask?
Ms. Ji. You're fired.
What?
Leave this house and be free.
No one will live here anymore.
What do you mean?
But...
Master Yo Han.
Is Elijah in her room?
Yes.
Master Yo Han.
Elijah.
Yo Han.
Are you out of prison?
Are you okay?
Yes.
You don't have to worry about me. I'm fine.
Now we're going to move to somewhere safe.
Somewhere safe?
Do you want to see where it is?
It's a rehabilitation hospital in Switzerland.
I wanted them to find a way to make you walk again.
So I've been donating to them.
Would you like to go there?
Just the two of us.
Yo Han...
So he was alive.
Thank goodness.
It seems I'm going to get a lot busier from now on.
Excuse me?
Master Yo Han gave me a healthy food shopping mall...
as a retirement gift.
He told me to sell healthy food that doesn't taste good.
Should I take it as an insult?
- You'll go back to your hometown? - Yes.
It's unfair only the people in Seoul can see how charming I am.
You're right.
I volunteered to the department in charge of juvenile cases.
I want to scold some troubled kids and help them.
I think I'll be good at it.
I'm sure you will be like you've always been.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you too.
Call me when you're in town.
(Public hearing for judicial reform to overcome Kang Yo Han's case)
Well, the new ruling party...
will never repeat the same mistake...
the Heo Joong Se administration made.
In order to ensure the rule of law,
we are gathered here today.
Today, a national hero is here with us.
It's Kim Ga On. Let's give him a big hand.
(Public hearing for judicial reform to overcome Kang Yo Han's case)
Judge Kim.
To avoid a shameful incident from happening again,
what should we do? Do you have any idea?
Was it a shameful incident?
Kang Yo Han isn't a hero.
But he's not a criminal.
Do you think people were too naive and easily shaken?
Do you think that's why they went enthusiastic about him?
I can see that you're a vigorous young man.
I think you're trying to say we need to find the fundamental problem.
But can we fix it easily?
I think we need to find a solution to settle the public sentiment.
You're right.
The prosecution wants...
to strengthen the screening process in selecting the judges...
so that we can eliminate dangerous ones.
The Ministry of Justice should be in charge of selecting the judges.
What kind of nonsense is that?
It's a violation of judicial independence.
Sir, I have a better idea.
Kim Ga On is gaining a lot of popularity from the public.
So why don't we make him the presiding judge...
and make another live court show?
If you have time for this...
Excuse me?
Don't you think we should do our job first?
(Judicial Reform Committee)
(Chairman of Legislation and Judiciary Committee)
My apologies.
It might be rude to say this, but if I may, I would like to say this.
Forgive me for saying this.
We are the people...
who were empowered by the public to do our job.
We should make sure no one feels resentment...
and no one sheds tears of blood.
And the ones who make other people shed tears of blood.
We should make sure they pay for their crimes.
Isn't that what we're supposed to do?
I became a judge to do that.
But if we don't do our job,
someone has to suffer. And that suffer...
will create a monster.
People go furious...
for a reason.
Those were great comments.
Young people should be vigorous like you.
I respect that.
But I think we heard enough of Judge Kim's comments.
Now why don't we have a discussion...
to come up with solutions that are more practical?
Certainly.
You just talked about...
the screening process of selecting the judges.
Shall we continue to...
We still need to...
It's still the same.
Nothing has changed at all.
What should I do now...
to make the world that doesn't need Yo Han?
Do it well.
If you don't, I'll come back.
Chief Kang.
Kang Yo Han.
(The Devil Judge)
(Special thanks to Park Hyung Soo for his guest appearance)
(Thank you for watching The Devil Judge.)