[English subtitles are available]
[Plot Love]
[Episode 3]
I've always been nice to women,
so if you drink up these three shots,
I'll pretend nothing has happened.
What? You're afraid?
Then don't bother.
I'll talk to Mr. Lu then.
Gu Chengze is obviously trying
to make things difficult for Su Bei.
So Mr. Gu is saying
as long as I drink these three shots,
we can move on
and continue
our cooperation, right?
I'm in charge of Gu's Group,
so of course I'll keep my word.
Very good.
Ms. Su,
let me drink it for you.
No you can't.
Mr. Gu said
if I drink it,
we'll get
the endorsement.
Interesting.
Now I really regret that
I didn't go all the way with Eminence
to get you to work for me.
Mr. Gu,
if I were working under you,
you'd be paying me for cooperation.
But now,
I'm doing whatever it takes
to beg you for cooperation.
Which is more satisfying?
You know it very well, right?
By the way,
this is our new model Liu Qianying.
Nice to see you, Mr. Gu.
Kong's target customers
are the young people.
And Qianying can be
a perfect brand ambassador for that.
I'll definitely take Annie's recommendation
into consideration.
Let's talk about it tonight.
Mr. Gu,
please take care of my sister.
Zhao Long,
give her your contact number.
Ms. Su,
are you all right?
Stop faking it.
You convince a man with just a few drinks.
I'd like to see
whether Mr. Lu will still want you
when he finds out what you really are.
Ms. Su,
are you all right?
I'm fine.
I...I'll go and have some tea with you.
Come.
Take it easy.
She tried to turn it around by drinking.
I don't think
she really has what it takes to be a good agent.
You may not have feelings for Su Bei now,
but officially she's still your wife.
A wild wife makes you a cuckold.
Nice chandelier...
Mr. Lu,
before you get in the car,
I have a favor to ask.
Say it.
No matter what you see later,
don't get mad.
What's in it?
I won't tell until you promise me.
Alright.
I'll take that as a yes
if you don't say anything.
How dare you
let her get into my car?
She's drunk and
insisted to get in the car, and
I couldn't stop her.
Besides, I would feel bad
to leave a drunk woman in the garage
in case that something happens to her.
Get her out of the car
right now.
That...
That's not very nice.
Get a drunk woman out of the car
and leave her on the side of the road.
I'm too much of a man
to do that.
Besides,
if someone takes a picture of that and makes it public,
it will be a disgrace for me!
You'll have to deal with this woman yourself later.
Alright.
Well...
I just remember that
I have something to do at home.
I have to go now.
Yunfan!
What about her?
Deal with her yourself.
Love you!
Don't vomit in my car
or you'll be finished	.
Out!
It hurts!
It stinks!
Why on earth did I marry her?
Who are you?
Why are you so ugly?
You say I'm ugly?
Don't lie down yet.
Get up.
Here.
Vomit here.
Don't make my couch dirty!
Where did he put the fragrance brocade?
[Oxiracetam]
Why does he take this?
What?
Water, water.
Nuts!
Get up!
What's wrong with me?
What are you doing here?
Now that you're awake,
get out of my place.
I'm having a serious headache.
So
you want me to throw you out?
Don't bother.
I'll leave myself
when I'm sober.
But
I'm not feeling well right now.
I need to have a rest.
It's a big world out there.
You can rest as much as you like.
Then I'll use Mr. Lu's place to wash up.
Is that okay?
Sorry, no.
You tried to solve a problem in business by getting drunk.
That's your competence
and value?
As long as the problem is solved
it doesn't really matter what I do to achieve that.
Mr. Lu,
you sound more like
you're jealous.
Get out!
Thanks for taking me in last night.
Su Su,
as a woman,
if you want to get close to Lu Nan as soon as possible,
you have to use your womanly charm
to trick him.
I don't think
he can be totally cool, calm and collected
when his wife
is so attractive.
But I must do it in the right way.
He's very wary of me now.
If I just go for him without a strategy,
then all our plans
will be to no avail.
Fine.
It's up to you.
Did you hear anything
about Lu Nan's health
while I was away?
No.
But I found medication at his place
that treats brain damage and neurological deficits.
[Oxiracetam]
Brain damage?
Is the medicine for himself?
I'm not sure,
but it's true that
Lu Nan does forget about me.
So why don't you
look into it?
By the way,
is Zhang Yuan going to be released soon?
I'm keeping an eye on him.
Zhang Yuan not only
embezzled the company money,
but also caused a huge loss in the company.
I didn't expect Lu Nan
to let him off so easily this time.
What exactly
is he trying to do?
[The top model agent is a "sleeping beauty"]
What happend?
Oh no.
What a surprise!
[Su Bei of Eminence Starlight
leads a slutty life]
[Private and intimate meeting
with an executive from Gu's Group for drinks]
Check it out!
Come!
Breaking news! Breaking news!
Holy cow!
Yeah.
No way!
[Top agent flirts with multiple men in one night
and sleeps her way to the top]
[It's clear that Su Bei is a wild girl]
Tell PR to remove all the negative news.
What's wrong
with Su Manni?
She thought she could put down Su Bei
by spreading this
and she could hype up
what's between with you and her.
But if those people online find out
that you're actually married with Su Bei,
then Su Manni's plan would backfire.
You think Su Mannii is behind all this?
Of course.
You...
You think it's Su Bei?
Very likely.
She's the one who's going to benefit the most
if our relationship is known by public.
Sleep her way to the top.
That's mean!
I thought Su Manni did it.
Even if she's the one who did it,
Su Bei is the mastermind behind her.
[Su Bei of Eminence Starlight
leads a slutty life]
[Private and intimate meeting
with an executive from Gu's Group for drinks]
Is everything set?
Everything is going
as we planned.
In less than 12 hours,
the news will go completely viral.
We're about to
give the public a big surprise.
Take this opportunity to get the word out.
Poor Manni.
She must think
she's got the upper hand now.
What's going on
with Su Bei?
Apart from asking PR to remove the trending posts,
she hasn't done anything else.
If you're right...
You must be right.
Su Bei
is really something.
She's too good
at convincing Gu Chengze.
I heard his father
gave that idiot a dressing-down,
and he's grounded now.
You're awesome,
and your cheeky wife is awesome too.
So...
Shall we go ahead to remove all the news?
Sure.
That's necessary.
But
don't do anything about Su Bei
for now.
If your relationship is exposed,
won't it affect you?
If she really wants it to be exposed,
we can't stop her.
Instead of
forcing her to change tack,
we'd better just let her be
and see what she can do.
Got it.
Mr. Lu.
Can I help you?
Explaination.
I don't know
what kind of explanation Mr. Lu is asking about.
You've made
all the celebrity headlines now.
Who doesn't know that Eminence
has hired a sleeping beauty?
Currently,
Manni is back in the trending topic,
and Qianying has got a new deal.
So I think Mr. Lu
should be happy with what I've done.
As for the negative news about me,
I'm sure
Mr. Lu is well aware
who did it.
Should I give you an award for this?
I think I deserve it
if you do.
I'll give you 24 hours to deal with the issue
before your news
affects Eminence's reputation.
So that's the way you think of me?
I don't care what you do
as long as
it doesn't affect the company.
Wait a minute.
After all,
I'm still your wife, legally speaking.
As my husband,
aren't you supposed to
show some care and trust
to me?
A woman I haven't seen in seven years
claims that
she still has feelings for me,
and yet she's acting quickly
to divorce me and get a share of my assets.
Do you think
you deserve my trust?
Lu Nan.
Have you forgotten
how I left China?
Yes, I have forgotten,
so don't expect me
to be nice to a stranger.
A stranger?
Yes,
you've forgotten all about the past,
all the good you've done to me,
all the promises you've made to me,
and
all the things you've done to me.
What kind of a husband
would forget everything
about his wife
who went through so much with him?
Don't try to make me feel guilty.
You just want more of my money.
You can keep dreaming.
I forgot.
The last thing you have is a sense of guilt.
Don't worry.
Annie is capable of
handling problems like this
within 24 hours.
[Eminence Group]
[Nanxi Second Detention Center Examination Room]
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
-Hello?
- Let go of me!
Hello?
Zhang Yuan was taken away by somebody else. I didn't catch up with them.
Get the surveillance video then.
I'll try.
Don't worry.
I'll find him as soon as possible.
Have you let the word out?
Yes.
It's up to you now.
Sister Manni, bad news!
More scandals about Eminence Group.
[More scandals about Eminence's agent
and the truth is yet to be revealed]
Annie, the famous model agent
not only sleeps her way to the top
but also gets herself
a senior position in Eminence
thanks to her husband.
The truth is shocking.
She's been married to Lu Nan, the CEO of Eminence
for seven years.
Rumor has it that
Lu Nan and Su Manni, the model of Eminence, are together.
That's complicated.
Half jokingly, people comment online that
in rich families, anything is possible in their love life.
[More scandals about Eminence's agent
and the truth is yet to be revealed]
Don't follow Lu Nan's example.
We're in big trouble.
We should have known she was going to throw dirt on you
and stopped her earlier.
Now the shareholders are waiting for your explaination.
This woman
not only wants me to acknowledge our relationship
but also forces me to act like a loving couple with her.
Because if I don't,
I can't clarify what's between me and Su Manni.
At this moment
when Eminence is ready to go public,
I have to do it her way.
She's something.
I was wondering why Ms. Su rose so quickly to the top.
Now I see she did it by sleeping with the important person.
Oh my god! What an asshole!
Two women for one man!
She's here. Hurry up.
Did you do it?
Which one are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me.
Who are you to question me?
A home-wrecker of your own sister's marriage?
You...
Mr. Lu.
Su Bei bosses me around again!
Sit down.
Ms. Su,
you should explain to us about what happened today.
My bad.
I've put on your desks
a contingency plan
for the negative news
based on my discussion with the PR department.
Check it out.
The trending topics last night
are not top searches any more.
And Ms. Su put other news out
to deflect the criticism towards us.
But we didn't expect that
another post about you went viral this morning.
So I'd like to ask Mr. Lu to decide
which plan we should go for.
The longer it takes, the more damage Eminence will suffer.
I promised Ms. Su that
I wouldn't interfere with any decision you make
about our subsidiary.
Mr...Mr. Lu.
You can't agree to this! I...
Thanks for your trust, Mr. Lu.
Then
let's go for the last option.
Within one hour,
we'll have the legal department issue
a letter of recourse
and post the following statements
on our official account.
First,
we acknowledge that we're indeed married
and we keep it private for personal reasons only.
There is no marital discord,
and no separation.
Second,
upload a photo of me and Su Manni,
denying the rumors of cheating
and sisterly discord.
Third,
mention and warn those
who have spoken out of turn online.
Last,
you will
make a video
of your alleged affair with Mr. Lu
and post it on Weibo to explain yourself.
Make it short and simple.
I'll send you
exactly what to post later.
Before the criticism subsides,
I'll suspend all of Su Manni's endorsements
in the domestic market.
No! Mr. Lu,
I just got the endorsement for L.
Do as she said.
-Ms. Su, please stay. You can leave now.
- I...
Let's wait and see!
I know what Mr. Lu wants to ask.
I was the one who let out the word about our marriage.
The reasons are simple.
First,
In Eminence Starlight,
I'm Annie,
and I can't let Manni take the lead over me.
Otherwise,
I won't be able to manage the company in the future.
Second,
with the power of the internet,
it's only a matter of time
before they can find out about our relationship.
So I must take preemptive action
to turn the tide.
If you were in my position,
you'd do the same thing.
So Ms. Su had already forseen this.
I admire capable people,
but I loathe scheming ones.
I'll be cooperative
and make public our marriage.
But at the same time,
please behave as Mrs. Lu.
We've come this far.
There is no way
you can deny our relationship anymore.
Have you found Zhang Yuan?
No. I'm still looking for him.
[Eminence Group]
-Yeah. Why hasn't he come out?
- What's wrong?
-It's been a long time.
- Right.
Yeah?
I've checked it.
Here they are!
[Eminence Group Co., Ltd.]
- Here they are!
- Mr. Lu!
- Mr. Lu, tell us!
Tell us!
- In response to the news about me,
- Mr. Lu!
I have two points to declare.
First,
I have been married to
Ms. Su since seven years ago.
We have trusted each other
and supported each other all the way,
and we have never betrayed each other
because of our long-distance relationship.
Second,
There's nothing
between me and Ms. Su Manni.
For the smear and rumors
about our marriage,
Eminence will take legal action
to pursue the matter to the end.
Mr. and Mrs. Lu,
since you're so much in love,
then why did Mrs. Lu
spend the last seven years living abroad?
-Right.
Tell us.
-Tell us.
Tell us, Mr. Lu.
Tell us.
I would like to thank Mr. Lu
for giving me seven years to grow myself
into Annie.
Now I return to Eminence as a top agent.
All our effort is worth it.
I hope my wife
can achieve her dream
and contribute to Eminence Starlight.
Take pictures!
-What a loving couple!
-Right!
-So sweet!
So sweet!
Yeah.
Here! Look at me!
Take more pictures.
-Here!
What are you doing here?
It's rare to see you so disturbed.
You're trespassing my place.
I can call the police
to arrest you for
trespass.
We are legally married
and here I am at my home.
But my husband is going to
accuse me of trespassing.
If the police found out about this,
will they charge you
with obstruction?
Su Bei,
I know it's impossible
to find a man
as perfect as me in this world,
but you can't force me to love you.
So
if you want me
to show you any respect,
then go back to wherever you came from.
Mr. Lu,
everybody knows we're married
and we're in the spotlight now.
If those journalists find out
we're not living together
and word gets out that we don't really get along,
don't you think it will
affect Eminence's IPO at this point?
You and I both know
what's more important at this moment.
Co-habitation?
You really like me, huh?
You're trying very hard.
And you want a lot, don't you?
You'll get all the other party's assets after a divorce.
If you're not happy with it,
you can change it.
This clause binds both of us.
Even if we do get a divorce,
the law will decide who gets what.
Remember,
I only let you move in
for the sake of the company.
[Man's signature: Lu Nan]
Your room is on the second floor.
You're not allowed to be in my presence
as long as I'm around.
Mr. Lu,
that's too much to ask for.
The door is right there.
You can leave if you don't like it.
Go!
Grandma, why are you here?
Grandma?
Open the door!
Verification failed.
Su Bei!
Open the door!
Mr. Lu.
Su Bei!
Open the door now!
Or I'll let you pay the price!
Sorry, Mr. Lu.
I locked the door by accident.
I'm really sorry.
Su Bei!
But there's something wrong with the door
and I can't open it.
I'm asking you as your boss now.
Open the door right away!
It's not working time.
So I won't listen to you.
I really can't open it.
You must know the consequences of doing this to me!
Mr. Lu.
I have a stomachache.
I must use the toilet.
Please wait outside for a while
and breathe
some fresh air.
See you!
Don't ignore my warning!
The password is Lu Nan's birthday?
Verification failed
Su Bei, open it!
Shit.
Lu Nan.
What's wrong?
Why are you here?
Su Bei said something's wrong here.
You...
What happened?
Is the password grandma's birthday?
Verification failed. Please re-enter.
It's neither Lu Nan's birthday
nor grandma's birthday.
What is it exactly?
No.
If I put the wrong password again,
it may call the police automatically.
If you dare to laugh,
I'll send you to Africa tomorrow
and let lionesses entertain you.
Su Bei has gone too far!
How dare she push you around!
We must teach her a lesson.
Kick her out of my house tomorrow.
You...even you can't handle her,
let alone me.
Then I'll fire you.
Don't!
It's hard to find a job now.
You can't take it out on me.
Hello?
Ye.
I found a safe at Lu Nan's place.
I entered the wrong password twice.
If I make it wrong for the third time, it will probably call the police.
I want you to
prepare some things for me.
I'll send you the list on Wechat.
Alright.
Besides,
it's good to let her live with you.
I mean,
it's a good idea to have her around
so we can find out what she's up to,
right?
Why don't you just come over to my place
for the night?
Tomorrow we'll teach her a lesson.
If you tell anyone
about what happened today,
you'll be fired.
Don't worry.
I'm a fish.
My memory only lasts for seven seconds.
Fei, you know what?
In one day,
I've already had six partners to cancel my contract!
And your brother listens to everything she says.
No way.
My brother promised grandma
that he'd divorce Su Bei.
And the divorce agreement...
Are they really going to get a divorce?
Why?
I don't know.
I heard from grandma about it.
You must not tell others.
Why don't you tell me everything?
You know me very well!
Is your brother going to...
Of course not.
He's hurt so much by Su Bei
and determined to divorce her.
They're negotiating the share of assets now,
but they haven't reached an agreement yet.
But they're getting divorced,
and still living together.
They're still a couple,
so of course they live together.
What I'm worried about is that
although grandma doesn't like Su Bei,
as long as Su Bei is pregnant,
she'll have to accept her sooner or later.
It's time for brother to have a kid.
I don't want the mother of the child to be Su Bei either.
But as long as she gives birth to an heir for the Lu family,
I have to accept her.
Fei, how can you think that way?
Su Bei is just pretending to be pathetic
to make your brother fall for her.
I don't think
if your brother knew the way she really is,
he would still like her so much.
Manni,
take it easy.
I'll go to my brother's place
in a few days
to see what's going on.
Verification failed.
I've changed the password.
Mr. Lu, is this a retaliation?
No.
The air outside is fresher, right?
Enjoy!
Honey.
How did you get in?
Through the back door.
You don't know your own house?
Su Bei, watch your language.
Who told you you can call me honey?
The government!
The marriage certificate says we're husband and wife.
Mr. Lu, please don't be mad at me.
I didn't mean to keep you out yesterday.
I wanted to ask Yunfan to open the door for me.
But when I came out of the bathroom,
you were both gone.
Stop it.
Don't think you can get my attention
in this way.
I'm telling you the truth.
I apologize, okay?
This bitch is making fun of me.
Lu Nan, what are you doing?
Come here.
Lu Nan.
It has been a while.
I need some time to get used to it.
You can't get enough of me, can you?
I will make you happy.
What?
You can't wait
to rekindle our love, can you?
Do you like it?
You think I'll fall for
a body like that?
If you have any self-respect,
don't strip yourself naked
in front of your wife,
whom you say you want to divorce.
You're a lousy man!
Lousy?
Then let me show you something.