[English subtitles are available]
[Love Unexpected]
[Episode 22]
[2012]
Durian, here I come!
Did you buy durian in secret again?
I did not.
If you don't admit,
I'll throw away your half pack of durian.
You should take a shower.
I haven't had durian for a month.
Let me have one more bite.
-Just one bite!
-It's time for shower.
It's time for a shower.
Fine, I will take a shower.
In that case,
what are you doing here?
Get out.
Why should I go out?
Are you
shy?
I am not.
Just get out.
All right.
Close the door.
Sure.
♫ A little bit caught in ♫
♫ A little about jokes ♫
♫ Life seems to be a strange riddle ♫
♫ I don't know who to tell the story ♫
♫ And I don't know why
you just disappeared suddenly ♫
♫ Better slow it down ♫
♫ Or else my heart
will break to pieces ♫
♫ Because it is too much.
It is a lot ♫
♫ To lose somebody like you,
I can't get it through♫
Why are you smiling?
Why are you smiling like a fool?
♫ You said I am a fool who is not loved ♫
Why are you smiling?
♫ Because I just can't forget you ♫
♫ And I can't forgive you
for what you have done ♫
♫ You leave me alone ♫
What do you think?
♫ In a mysterious room without sunlight ♫
You...
Put me down.
I'm getting late to work.
Come on.
♫ Go tell the world
that I still love you ♫
Don't panic.
We still have plenty of time.
♫ I can't get you out of my mind ♫
I have warned you
not to drink so much.
It's a happy occasion.
I'm getting you a glass of water.
No.
Don't go.
Don't leave me, okay?
Don't ever leave me again, okay?
♫ Love can be ♫
♫ Hurting sometimes ♫
It's time to eat!
What are we having today?
♫ Love can be ♫
Scalded Prawns.
♫ Healing every wound ♫
I'm so grateful that my girlfriend
is a nutritionist.
♫ But for you ♫
Tell me.
Did you pursue me
♫ I'm willing to be brave ♫
just for free nutritious meals?
How did you know?
♫ Taking the risk,
no matter what they say ♫
Liu Ruo Chen!
♫ When life gets hard ♫
I have never peeled shrimps for anyone.
You are the first and the last.
♫ Please think of the old memories ♫
That's more like it.
♫ When you feel lonely ♫
Get me a drink.
♫ Please think of my whispers ♫
Now,
you have started to boss me around.
♫ Whenever your dream
is falling apart ♫
But
since you peeled shrimp for me,
I'll do it.
♫ I will be on my way ♫
♫ To ignite the fire of hope ♫
♫ Oh, my love ♫
♫ Oh, my dear ♫
♫ Oh, my heart ♫
♫ Underneath your breath ♫
♫ I feel the warm ♫
♫ Maybe one day ♫
♫ We will be lost ♫
♫ In the mist of this cold world ♫
Do you like it?
♫ Just remember ♫
Why?
♫ My whisper ♫
Because you deserve it.
If you like it,
I'll get it for you every day.
♫ When life gets hard ♫
♫ Please think of the old memories ♫
♫ When you feel lonely ♫
But
it is such a waste.
♫ Please think of my whispers ♫
As long as you like it.
♫ Whenever your dream
is falling apart ♫
♫ I will be on my way ♫
♫ To ignite the fire of hope ♫
How long will it take?
I'm sleepy.
The semester is coming to an end.
That's why I'm slightly occupied.
Go to bed if you are sleepy.
No.
I want to wait for you.
Why don't you watch some drama series?
Let me go through this document.
Get it done quickly.
I have downloaded an interesting movie.
I'm waiting for you.
Okay.
Once I'm done,
I'll spend time with you.
Finally, I can spend time with you!
Do you prefer resting early
or watching movie?
Didn't I say I wanted
to spend time with you?
What movie are we watching?
Switch off the light.
Is it necessary?
Here comes the best part.
Is the movie
you're talking about a horror movie?
You know
that I'm afraid of it.
Didn't someone
once claim
that he is not afraid of horror movies?
All right.
I'm here for you.
Don't be afraid.
End the movie.
Let's end it.
Fan Fan,
can we watch other movie?
Choose something
that is romantic
and soothing.
Let me show you something soothing.
Is it soothing?
This is...
It's worse than watching the movie.
Fine.
Fan Fan.
I...
I really can't take it.
-You said you wanted to watch movie.
-I can't take it.
Is it nice?
-Fan Fan, don't go too far.
-Is it nice?
Liu Ruo Chen!
Are we still watching the movie?
Yes or no?
Liu Ruo Chen.
No. Stop.
Let me show you the real horror.
It's time to wake up.
I'm so exhausted.
Let me sleep in.
No.
You need to wake up by 9am.
Wake up.
Hello.
Lu Fan Fan.
I told you before.
You gave me a hard time.
As such, I won't let you have a good time.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
You gave me a hard time.
As such, I won't let you have a good time.
Gao Ru Wen.
You are Gao Ru Wen from the year of 2024.
You are quite smart.
Lu Fan Fan.
Nice to meet you again.
What do you want?
Are you afraid?
Don't worry.
You won't be suffering for too long.
I will put an end to everything.
Tell me.
What do you want?
Hello?
Gao Ru Wen?
Has he escaped?
It's someone scarier than him.
It's Gao Ru Wen from the year of 2024.
Who would have thought
this would happen.
Gao Ru Wen is the kind of person who'll
seek revenge for the smallest  grievances.
He will surely
seek revenge against Fan Fan
in every possible way.
He is so terrifying.
When I think about it,
he did that to me even though
we did not have any conflict.
He will do something worse to you.
Well...
Even if he is a fool,
I don't think
he will throw himself in our way.
Never lower your guard.
A baited cat may grow
as fierce as a lion.
Don't forget that Gao Ru Wen is a felon.
With his intelligence,
in the coming days,
he will try to escape at all cost
and find a breakthrough
to his advantage.
Are you saying
I'm the breakthrough?
Judging from the current situation,
he called you
because of that.
That...
That's so arrogant of him.
Do I look like
a pushover?
I...
What about this?
Move in with me.
Qin Yang.
Yi Xiao.
Move to my place.
We should stay together.
If you stay at home,
he won't stand a chance
even if he aims to attack you.
Under the circumstances,
this is by far the best way.
Enjoy while you can.
Tomorrow is another day.
Not bad.
What were you doing?
We were exchanging code words
that was fresh out of the oven.
If someone can't answer the code words,
don't open the door.
I see.
It's quite easy to remember.
Come on in.
Yi Xiao.
Give me the suitcase.
Did you encounter
anything unusual tonight?
I came here by taxi.
I came here right after
picking up Yi Xiao.
I have verified
the vehicle registration number
and the license.
He is just a normal driver.
I didn't notice anyone unusual either.
When did you do that?
I didn't notice it at all.
Of course I had to do that in secret.
That...
That was so exciting.
It's as if we were in a spy movie.
It's not that exciting
but
it's better to stay cautious.
You have reminded me of something.
It's a little to passive
to guard against Gao Ru Wen.
Moreover, Yi Xiao and Fan Fan
are easy targets for him
as they are ladies.
In that case,
what should I do?
How about
I pretend to approach him?
Anyway, I have no money,
but a life.
If you lose your life,
what should someone do?
You are right.
Fan Fan and I
will stay together
until death do us apart.
Well,
don't you forget about it.
When you girls are outside,
you need to protect yourself.
If you encounter this kind of situation,
what should you do?
Lu Fan Fan.
Are we
going to learn this?
Of course.
This is self-defence
martial arts for ladies.
If you master it,
Gao Ru Wen is all alone
and he won't be able to defeat us.
Ruo Chen,
are you sure
this is useful?
I think it's not too useful
but we can't give up.
Actually,
we can
carry weapons with us.
For example,
pepper spray.
I have it.
Alarm.
I have it too.
Stop.
Did you forget
Gao Ru Wen
is good at hypnotising?
All he has to do
is to stare at you
and you will pass out immediately.
Give it to me.
Qin Yang.
Come out.
Put your hand on me.
If you encounter this situation,
lift your left hand.
Then,
in the next second,
in the blink of an eye,
press his wrist,
lift your leg
and attack him with your elbow.
That's a complete demonstration
of the move.
Next.
The next move...
Ruo Chen.
This...
I don't think it suits us.
What about...
Let's play a game.
Sure.
What is it?
Water carry game.
Water carry game,
as suggested by its name,
means carry a bowl of water horizontally.
What we have to do is
pour water from one cup to another.
The first person to spill the water
is the loser.
The loser...
The loser will have to
clean the kitchen
and do dishes!
Sure.
It sounds simple.
Let's begin.
Who wants to be the first?
Fan Fan is the focus of the day.
Let Fan Fan go first.
You are so mean.
After all, it's a game.
Come on.
Mr. Qin.
I got it under control.
Come on.
It's easy.
You guys are
working together to trick me.
Good luck.
You are something!
This...
I can do it.
Ruo Chen.
You lose.
I was giving way to you.
Harm set,
harm get.
It seems that
the kitchen
belongs to you today.
A bet is a bet. I admit defeat.
Thank you for the hard work.
All right.
Take your time.
I'm going out.
No way.
It won't be long.
I will come home soon.
Like I said, it's very dangerous.
No way.
But...
I need to buy something.
What thing?
I'm on period.
I need to buy
that thing.
You...
What thing do you mean?
Something for ladies.
That thing.
What is it?
Sanitary pad.
I...
I got it now.
Well...
I can get it for you.
Give me a minute.
Goodness.
He is so handsome.
He looks even more handsome
than the actor in the drama.
There are so many brands.
This...
They are alike.
Which one does Fan Fan use?
Sir.
Do you need help?
Are you buying pad for your girlfriend?
If she has a heavy flow,
I recommend this one
and this one.
It can prevent period leaks.
There is an ongoing promotion.
You can buy one and get one free.
If you want something comfy,
you may choose this.
Which one
do you need?
Come in.
You...
Thank you.
I'm going to meet Qin Yang.
[Stay tuned for the post-credits scene!]
What are you drawing?
Give it back to me.
You remember everything.
I always remember it.
In that case,
let me keep you company forever,
okay?
What are you drawing?
Can't you tell?
It's a cello.
It's the instrument that you play.
Does cello look like this?
It looks like a bee.
I think it looks like cello.
No way.
Why are there antenna?
Silly girl.
You should draw like this.
Like this.
To the left.
Followed by a curve.
And lastly,
draw this.
That's right.
Right?
♫ Watch the clear blue sky
from the window ♫
You forgot it.
Will you teach me how to play cello?
♫ All I hear is your whispers ♫
You want to learn it?
Sure.
♫ Living under the same roof ♫
Lower your hand.
Like this?
♫ Your presence
is a whole new experience ♫
That's not how you hold the bow.
♫ Just like yesterday,
memories push me forward  ♫
Lower your hand.
♫ It reminds me of a wish
I made many years ago ♫
♫ Your backlight makes you glow ♫
Like this?
Yes.
♫ I can never forget your smile ♫
What about this?
Be serious.
♫ You are the stars
lighting up the long night ♫
It's so hard.
I don't want to play anymore.
♫ I wish I could go against time
and grow up with you again  ♫
You have never changed.
♫ The street that we passed by
when we were kids ♫
By the way,
I got you a present.
♫ It has aged gracefully
as time passed ♫
What is it?
Back then,
you always sat by my side
♫ My childhood is all about you ♫
and watched me play cello.
But
♫ I collect the fragments of memories ♫
I haven't played cello for you for long.
Would you like to hear it?
♫ You are my one and only ♫
[Fan Fan,]
[thank you for getting my brother back.]
[I am really happy now.]
[I hope you are happy too.]