(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
Previously on The Penthouse 3.
Are you okay? Can you hear me?
We will now start auditioning...
for the Cheong A Arts Center resident musician.
Bae Ro Na's talent was top-notch.
You were the one who invited Clark, Shim Su Ryeon?
This place is for orphans. Just like you.
I did everything you asked, so why?
Seok Kyung and Seol A are twins?
Do you not care if you never see your biological child ever again?
Don't look for me anymore. I won't let Dad catch me.
Shim Su Ryeon. Why not leave her to me this time?
What does it say on that trash can next to Logan?
- Penthouse? - Ordering Baek Jun Ki...
to blow up Logan's car and keeping him locked up like this.
I didn't know you were such a scary woman.
(Episode 9)
Hi, Son.
What are you doing here?
I thought you should know.
Your mom did something horrible.
She had...
locked up Logan in the penthouse.
Isn't Logan dead?
He's barely breathing.
In the penthouse's helper room.
Didn't you think something was off?
Not at all. Why would Mom do such a thing?
She has a good reason.
Logan took Min Seol A's bone marrow...
and abandoned her.
Logan was nothing more...
than the target of revenge for Seol A.
Anyway, I plan to move back into the penthouse soon...
since this was originally my home anyway.
I should get the bedroom redone.
I'm going to hop in the shower.
Please pick up, Mom.
The person you have reached...
(Living Gositel)
James knows I'm here.
Give me a minute.
That was brave of you.
You conspired with Su Ryeon to kill Logan?
Did she lure you with money?
Or did you hope to become her new lover?
You were the one who dragged me in there.
Why did you get me out of prison?
Was this your plan all along?
How could a mom use her daughter to threaten me?
- And you call yourself a mom? - What about you?
Did you stab me in the back for Eun Byeol's sake?
Because of you,
she lived with that monster.
You betrayed me and split us up,
so you must pay the price.
That is...
poetic justice.
You killed Yoon Hee, didn't you?
Yoon Hee?
Didn't you kill her?
Because you betrayed her and dumped her.
Carry that guilt with you for the rest of your life.
If you survive, that is.
Seo Jin. I will never forgive you.
Seo Jin. I'll get you for this!
Seo Jin!
(Living Gositel)
Let him go.
Please, sir. Do get in the car.
I'll explain everything on the way.
You're really something, Cheon Seo Jin.
You really tricked James.
Is it now time to celebrate?
No wonder...
we make such great partners.
That's right.
There's one thing I want to know.
Why do you want to get at Shim Su Ryeon so badly?
The almighty Cheon Seo Jin.
She was the one woman who really made me care.
Shim Su Ryeon.
Will there ever be a day better than this?
I panicked when I heard that Logan was alive,
but thanks to that, we got rid of Su Ryeon,
Logan Lee, Jun Ki, and Yoon Chul all in one fell swoop.
We got rid of everyone who was a nuisance.
I'm going to drink until I get drunk.
You're sure...
Logan won't wake up, right?
I personally injected him with the poison.
His heart stopped. He won't last a day.
He was going to die anyway.
That's right.
What did you do with Jun Ki?
I told a certain someone that he desperately missed...
where he used to be.
Do you mean the mental hospital in Japan?
Yes.
But then again,
that's a better fit for him.
It was a great move...
to tie Su Ryeon and Logan together.
You really are impressive.
So you were the one behind Jun Ki coming here.
You found out that I planned to kill Logan...
and got him out and locked him up...
and made a deal with Logan's family?
You are psychotic.
You'll end up killing me if I don't kill you first.
I need to stay on my toes.
Was the view from the penthouse this nice?
Su Ryeon...
enjoyed a lot of pretty things,
so she should have no regrets in this life.
You're next, Dan Tae.
Enjoy this as much as you can.
I'll take everything you have very soon.
Logan.
Su Ryeon.
I've missed you.
Is it really you?
Yes.
What happened?
Why didn't you tell me if you were alive?
How can I die and leave you?
I'll explain everything.
I'm sorry it took me so long to come.
You're alive, so it's fine.
I prayed so earnestly...
that you'd be alive in any shape or form.
Dr. Ha. What are you doing here?
He helped me...
meet you.
You did well so far, Logan.
In just 24 hours,
you will feel very comfortable.
Maybe I imagined it.
So why did you waste your precious life...
by falling in love with someone like Su Ryeon?
What a waste of your money and youth.
But don't be too upset.
I'll send Su Ryeon to you very soon.
What happened? Who did this?
This causes heart failure.
Let me give you an antidote. Hang on.
Stay with me, Logan.
It was Seo Jin.
What?
The person who locked me in here...
was Seo Jin.
Seo Jin?
Alex.
Please call Alex.
Logan.
Wake up, Logan.
Darn it.
You can't die.
Hey. What is going on, man? Where's Logan?
The situation is bad.
I gave him an antidote immediately,
but he was poisoned.
What? Poisoned? Who?
Cheon Seo Jin, that crazy lady?
Oh, no. I'm going to kill this woman.
I won't let this happen.
Calm down. You won't find out anything this way.
I'm not waiting any longer.
What if Logan dies?
You're going to be held responsible?
Darn it.
Think why Logan told me to tell just you.
If you get carried away, you'll ruin all of Logan's plans.
He cheated death many times to get this far.
Please. Let Logan do what he wants.
Darn it.
Cheon Seo Jin will do something tomorrow.
I think she'll move Logan somewhere.
I don't know where that is.
Right now, all I can do is wish he gets through it.
Cheon Seo Jin. And Joo Dan Tae.
I'll kill them all.
I'll use all my family's money,
down to the last penny if I have to,
to make sure they're both dead.
I swear!
Bring that this way.
Okay.
What's that?
What's going on?
Is that furniture?
Did you get a new couch? Which one?
It must be a new model.
I'm so jealous.
My gosh. How can something look so luxurious?
I just changed the couch.
It's luxury at its peak.
It totally upgrades the whole house.
The interior looks so different.
Smile a bit, Su Ryeon.
Ms. Cheon, he was just brought in.
He seems to be unconscious.
Good job.
At exactly 7pm, bring Su Ryeon to the helper room.
You must be on time. Make no mistakes.
I'll compensate you handsomely.
Ma'am, you need to come over.
There's a weird smell coming from behind the hall.
There is?
[VIU Ver] SBS E25 'The Penthouse 3'
"Logan Reunites with Su Ryeon"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
- Who are you? - Shim Su Ryeon.
You revenge your daughter's death...
by doing this to our Logan?
Logan?
Logan? What are you talking about?
I didn't know you were such a scary woman.
Poor Logan.
Tricked by the woman he loves.
Logan!
His heart stopped.
Take him to the hospital!
And bring her too!
Come on in!
Let me see Logan.
Please let me see Logan!
Logan! Let me see him!
Let me see him!
Logan!
- Logan. - Turn the ambulance around.
What's going on?
Call Alex for me.
Don't tell the rest of the family.
Tell Alex to do as I asked.
Do not touch a hair on Su Ryeon's body.
Hey. Thanks for making it, little bro.
But do we really have to keep this a secret?
For now. You know what our parents are like.
If they know it was Dan Tae and Seo Jin,
would they let them live?
My plan will become a mess.
All right. But we should still tell Grandma, though,
because, you know, she's pretty upset.
Leave it to me.
All right.
And don't worry about this place,
because I got this place on lock-down, all right?
Nobody can get in here besides me and my people, all right?
Thanks, bro.
Yes.
Let go.
You're being fooled.
Please take me to Logan.
I need to see how he's doing with my own eyes.
I beg you.
You must've been in so much pain.
How could they do this to someone?
I'm fine.
I'm alive.
Seeing you...
made it worthwhile.
Joo Dan Tae and Cheon Seo Jin.
I can never forgive them.
There is no more mercy.
They went after the wrong person.
I will make them regret it.
I never imagined that the person who confined me...
was Cheon Seo Jin.
Even less that she'd rope in Dr. Ha.
In return for springing me from prison,
she made me work for Dan Tae.
Then she told me to treat Logan.
To keep him barely alive.
To hide her identity,
she even used Eun Byeol to blackmail me.
How could a human being do such a thing?
For now, let's pretend I'm dead.
Do as you planned.
What will you do?
I have to find Seok Kyung first.
Seok Kyung is...
my real daughter.
Seok Kyung?
Dan Tae killed Yoon Hee because she tried to reveal that.
I'm not positive,
but I think Seo Jin's involved too.
It's all my fault.
I asked Yoon Hee to find your daughter.
Because of me,
she's dead.
So that her death isn't in vain,
we must reveal the truth.
In my own way, I will get revenge that will devastate them.
Count me in.
Let me help.
Mr. Lee.
Seok Hoon.
Mom. Are you all right?
Is everything okay?
What on earth is going on?
What happened to Mom?
I wonder.
Considering what she did to Logan,
his family won't let her off lightly.
She went way too far.
All because of a dead girl.
This penthouse...
is in our name, yours and mine.
Now only true family members are left.
You promised never to hurt Mom.
Don't forget that.
Don't you worry. I didn't touch your mom.
I couldn't, even if I wanted to.
Logan's family took her.
Be careful so your dad doesn't suspect you.
He'll trust you because you're his only blood.
Do not make the first move.
Be careful until we find Seok Kyung.
So...
Shall we get to work?
Did Seok Kyung call you?
I still can't seem to reach her.
I assume she's busy getting used to her life abroad.
I'm sure she's doing fine.
You really are my son, with that tender heart of yours.
Don't worry about trivial things.
Just enjoy what you will soon have.
You're the only one I trust, Dad.
Yes. Where's Seok Kyung?
You still haven't found her?
I'm sure she'll come crawling back since she's out of money.
Come down now.
What are you doing?
What about you?
You think you can kill your father with something like this?
- Come with me. - Let me go.
- Come with me! - Let go!
Who are you to intervene in my life?
Let go!
Seok Kyung.
Take her to the hospital first. She seems like she's hurt.
I didn't bring her in because I like her.
I just didn't want her to get hurt at Hera Palace.
Thank you.
Where are you hurt? How much?
You look horrible.
Let's go to the hospital.
It's nothing.
It is something.
None of my bones are broken, and I'm not bleeding!
Why are you making me worry?
Do you know how worried Mom and I were?
Why didn't you call?
Where have you been?
You should have come looking for me if something had happened.
Why are you worrying about me now?
You wouldn't have cared if I died.
Don't say that.
I'm not even your birth sister.
You...
How did you...
Dad told me.
That's why he did this to me.
Because I'm not his daughter.
It's why he sabotaged my relationship with Mom.
It's why he used me to take over the penthouse.
It's why he took all the money under my name.
That was why.
Because I'm Mom's daughter.
Shim Su Ryeon's daughter.
Because I'm Min Seol A's twin.
So what?
That doesn't mean anything.
How is it nothing?
It means you and I are strangers.
We walk different paths.
That changes nothing.
You're my sister till death. I'll protect you no matter what.
Dad will never hurt you.
I won't let him. So listen to me!
I know you're working for him.
Are you planning on inheriting it all yourself?
Is that why you kicked Mom out...
and are staying by Dad's side?
I know you don't mean that.
You know me better than that.
Does saying that make you feel better? Are you stupid?
Let go!
I said let go! Please!
It was me.
It's okay. I know it was hard.
Who owns...
Dohae Construction again?
It was bought by Logan's company.
Shim Su Ryeon is sure you're the man behind it.
Which is why we helped her.
As promised,
I will give you the development rights...
for Cheonsoo District.
Then can I assume that from today...
Dohae Construction will no longer be involved with Cheonsoo District?
Of course.
That was clean.
I'm sorry about Logan.
I really wished he would survive and let the truth be known.
Still...
I'm relieved...
he was able to die in the care of his family.
My family...
is planning on returning to the States now.
How are you going to deal with...
Shim Su Ryeon and Ha Yoon Chul?
My family will deal with that.
Alex,
Logan's brother, will be taking care of it.
The punishment won't be light.
Sorry for misunderstanding you all this time.
You two will be rewarded soon.
How did everything work out so smoothly like this?
Chairman Joo, you continue to astound me.
When Cheong A Constructions is chosen to lead the Cheonsoo project,
Cheong A group's stock price, which has been falling,
shall also rise again.
I will try my best...
to make it hit the highest price in the country.
Some say it's already been decided as a land transaction permit area.
Okay, then.
Thank you for all your work so far.
Doesn't money smell great?
What about Yoon Chul? Don't you have anything?
That's right. Did something happen to Dr. Ha?
I can't seem to reach him.
I think by now...
he's become fish food in the middle of the Pacific Ocean.
Fish food?
It was Shim Su Ryeon...
who blew up Logan's car.
It seems she had locked him up in the penthouse and tortured him.
Logan was the last target...
for her daughter's revenge.
And Ha Yoon Chul helped her.
- What? - Wait.
That doesn't make any sense.
Forget Shim Su Ryeon for a second.
Why would Ha Yoon Chul do that?
What did Logan ever do to him?
I'm sure it was for money.
Shim Su Ryeon offered him a great deal of money.
How bold of her to do that...
to an American who is part of a conglomerate.
How sad.
Although we did end up with more money thanks to that.
I heard you both worked very hard.
I hope you can keep it up until the construction ends.
And this is an extra gift from Cheong A Group.
This couple sure is generous.
They really know how to play.
Cheers. Here.
Stay here for a while.
It'll keep you out of Dad's radar.
How's the wound?
I told you I'm fine.
Go now. I want to rest.
Let's meet Mom in the evening. I'll call her.
- I don't want to. - Why?
You want her to keep worrying?
We looked all over the retreat center that day because of you.
Mom's in a dark place right now.
After Ro Na's mom died,
she's been fighting Dad day and night.
Is this about her again?
Stop talking about Ro Na's mom. I'm sick of hearing it.
It's not like I killed her.
You didn't, but you played a part.
She found out you were Mom's daughter...
and was chased by Dad. That's how she passed away.
What?
You of all people...
shouldn't talk that way about her death.
She was even falsely accused of kidnapping Eun Byeol.
Because of Ms. Jin's lie.
Ms. Jin?
How about that tteokbokki?
What are you doing here?
Let go of me. I'm busy.
Ha Eun Byeol.
Are you looking for her?
Do you know where my Eun Byeol is?
I told Ms. Jin that...
Eun Byeol was at Ro Na's place.
What?
I also kept you and Ro Na at that tteokbokki place for her.
If only I hadn't told her, none of this would've happened.
Did Ro Na's mom die because of me?
Did you really do that?
Tell me exactly what happened.
You tell me.
Is Mom in danger?
What did Dad do to her?
Why isn't Su Ryeon picking up?
She handed over Dohae Construction's development rights so suddenly too.
Gosh, you startled me.
What are you doing? I'm busy.
Hey!
Let go.
I have nothing to say to you.
Unless Joo Dan Tae threatens to kill me,
I'll never make a deal with you.
What's all this?
Let's flee.
What?
I already booked flights.
I also found a school for Jenny.
With this money, we can support Jenny abroad.
We'll make a fresh new start...
where no one can find us.
Don't tell me this money is from Joo Dan Tae.
Did he give away money to celebrate his new rights?
Cheonsoo District was going to be developed by Cheong A anyway.
That way, we can sell our land at a higher price too.
Cut ties with Shim Su Ryeon. We're leaving this place.
(Korea Air, Passport)
Are you even human?
After destroying a family, what are you saying now?
"We'll make a fresh new start?"
I still can't face Ro Na.
I feel too guilty.
I only care about my own child.
We'll pay Ro Na, okay?
A person died!
To Ro Na, Yoon Hee meant the world.
With her whole world gone, what meaning does money have?
- Ma Ri. - Su Ryeon is missing.
You know where she is, don't you?
Joo Dan Tae, that jerk, might have kidnapped and blackmailed her.
Otherwise, why would Dohae Construction give up so easily?
What does that matter when we can keep the money?
No way.
Have you been working with Joo Dan Tae for money all this time?
You're a jerk!
You can never flee.
Pay for what you did to Yoon Hee first.
Confess everything Joo Dan Tae has ever done.
If anything happens to Su Ryeon,
I'll put you behind bars with my own two hands.
You're becoming just like Joo Dan Tae.
Get it together!
The person you have reached is unavailable.
Why isn't Ms. Shim here yet?
Her phone is turned off too.
- Goodness. - This is bad.
Well...
I'm not sure if I should tell you this,
but Ms. Shim is...
being suspected of murder, kidnapping,
and holding a person captive, and is on the run.
- What? - My gosh.
In addition to the shameful fact that she used to work as a hostess,
if this gets out to the press,
Cheong A Foundation's reputation will be irreparably harmed.
There's no point in waiting any longer.
Let's take a vote already.
If you think Director Shim Su Ryeon should be dismissed,
raise your hand.
All right. By unanimous consent,
Director Shim Su Ryeon is dismissed.
Let's elect the new director immediately.
Our former director, Ms. Cheon, is with us anyway.
- That sounds good. - Great.
Me?
If you give me a second chance,
I'll devote my body and soul to Cheong A Foundation.
Put this office back...
to its original state before my inauguration ceremony.
Yes, ma'am.
Welcome back, Ms. Cheon.
We should work together...
- to grow Cheong A Foundation. - I know.
(Cheon Myung Soo, Sixth director)
Father, I'm back...
at Cheong A Foundation that you left for me.
It's not me.
I swear!
This was all set up by Cheon Seo Jin.
I just did as she said.
I was fooled!
Are you confessing?
- Logan. - What?
Are you surprised?
Because I'm alive?
How could you...
betray my trust like this?
I was trying to help you.
Killing Joo Dan Tae was never your plan.
You weren't the least bit interested in your parents' revenge.
Did you only pretend to want to kill him...
to approach me?
Why? Were you after my money?
Is that why you teamed up with Cheon Seo Jin?
No.
I was grateful to you for getting me out of the loony bin. I mean it.
But Cheon Seo Jin's offer...
was hard to resist.
Did she pay off your gambling debts?
She promised half the profits.
If everything worked out,
I thought it could make up for all the injustice in my life.
You and Joo Dan Tae...
didn't just share a name.
Both of you are...
scumbags.
So I'm thinking of sending you back there.
Yes, there. That place.
Do you understand?
You'll rot there for the rest of your life.
You're crazy. You're out of your mind.
I'm sorry, Logan.
Take him away!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Logan.
No.
Logan! I don't want to go back there.
Logan!
Don't lock me up again!
No!
[VIU Ver] SBS E26 'The Penthouse 3'
"Back on the Throne"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
You found Seok Kyung?
Where is she now? Bring her to me right now.
No. I'll come to you.
She's not ready to see you yet.
She's very confused. Give her some time.
How can she not be ready to see her own mom?
Tell Seok Kyung this.
I'm waiting for her like I always have.
She can come to me anytime.
By the way, Seok Kyung told me something important today.
On the day Ms. Oh died,
Seok Kyung met Ms. Jin.
It's certain that Ms. Jin kidnapped Eun Byeol.
Seok Hoon?
I'll call you back.
Finally.
Finally, this place became mine.
I'm going to tear down this shop...
and build a Cheonsoo District landmark here.
Why does it have to be here?
This is...
where I used to live.
Your paternal grandmother...
lived here.
My paternal grandmother?
Wasn't this my maternal grandfather's land?
No.
It's where my family and I lived.
At 27 Cheonsoo District.
And...
this is where my mother...
is buried.
Mom.
Jun Ki.
You must stay alive.
Make lots of money and succeed.
Build a big house for all to see,
and you must live...
as a rich man.
No. Please, no Mom.
Don't die.
You can't leave me.
Jun Hee. Please, wake up.
Breathe.
Everything began here,
and it's time for me to complete it.
First, I plan to erect...
a Zeus Tower in memory of my mother.
It will be lit 24 hours a day...
and visible from anywhere.
It'll be the tallest building in the world.
And all of this...
is yours, Seok Hoon.
Picture it.
How amazing is this?
Aren't you thankful you were born as my son?
We must find Jin Bun Hong first.
She holds the key to the truth of that night.
Do you know where she lives?
No, I don't. But I know how to find her.
Leave it to me.
I have a question.
Why did you help Logan?
Because of Yoon Hee.
Because I felt like...
that was what Yoon Hee would've done.
The person you have reached...
Eun Byeol, pick up.
Eun Byeol, where are you?
Eun Byeol, why can't I reach you?
Is something okay?
I'm at Hera Palace. Make some time for me.
(Eun Byeol, pick up.)
(Eun Byeol)
Eun Byeol, I heard you failed the Cheong A Arts Center audition.
An SNU grad lost to a high school grad?
I heard Ro Na was amazing.
Did you see the posts by the kids who were at the audition?
Want to see a video of her audition?
Yes.
(Cheong A Arts Center Artist in Residence Audition)
Awesome, right? Isn't she incredible?
She's really good.
(Cheong A Arts Center Artist in Residence Audition)
Eun Byeol! Please wake up!
Eun Byeol!
No! Please wake up, Eun Byeol!
We'll die, Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol! Please!
Eun Byeol! Please wake up!
What's wrong? What is it?
Look at me.
Are you okay?
When did you all get here?
What do you mean? We've been studying for finals.
What? I was?
Wow. Look at you weaseling out of this.
- You're a great actress. - You guys...
Eun Byeol! Are you okay?
Ms. Jin.
Drink up.
Why are you so pale?
Have you been eating?
This just won't do. Let's go to my place.
I'll make you all of your favorite foods.
Ms. Jin. Can you get me some more of that drug?
The drug?
Well... It's not that easy.
Please. For me.
No one cares about me as much as you do.
I feel like my head will explode without it.
Please get it for me.
Okay, I will.
There's nothing I won't do for you.
Don't worry. I'll get it for you.
They stopped the clinical test because that drug was too dangerous.
People showed signs of early dementia.
It's too dangerous.
Do you know that?
Why do you care? I said it doesn't matter.
Get me as much as you can next time, got it?
You knew that, but you gave that garbage to my daughter anyway?
What? Dr. Ha?
Eun Byeol wanted it.
She asked for it first.
Don't lie to me.
Do you think I believe you?
You ruined my daughter.
Her parents ruined her.
She's miserable if she's with the two of you.
I'll protect her. I won't lose her!
Hey. What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be making dinner?
I don't want to go home because I don't want to see Kyu Jin,
but I have absolutely nowhere else to go.
My life has been in vain.
I had to serve my in-laws...
and support my husband all my life, so I don't know how to have fun.
And I don't know how to do anything.
Why did I live like this?
Listen to this woman.
I want to make him pay big time,
but I have no clue what I should do.
Get up.
- What? - I'll teach you, so come with me.
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
This woman...
Does she know what time it is?
Her child and the family were all she ever knew.
But now, she's always out...
and doesn't keep house at all.
What is wrong with her?
Honey! Where are you?
What?
Hey! Where are you?
I'll come to you right now...
Do you think that jerk will care just because I do this?
See? Your phone is blowing up.
Goodness. He is going crazy.
Stay here for two hours, okay?
What is this?
Soju.
You need to smell like alcohol...
to make Kyu Jin mad.
Yes. Ma Ri!
Gosh.
I've already looked up to you...
May I love you?
My gosh! Ma Ri!
Who are you people? Why did you bring me here?
Do you want to die? Untie me!
What deal did you make with Joo Dan Tae?
Did he promise to give you Eun Byeol...
if you do as he says?
What deal would I make with Joo Dan Tae?
Why would I do business with that fool?
Eun Byeol is my daughter anyway.
Do you think you can take her from me?
I'm the one who loves Eun Byeol more than you two.
You never visited her since you were released from prison.
All you cared about was getting revenge.
- You crazy... - That day,
you abducted Eun Byeol,
and Yoon Hee died trying to go after you.
Tell me everything you know.
- What happened that night? - I don't know.
- Tell me! - I don't know anything!
I had nothing to do with Oh Yoon Hee's death.
Long time no see.
Ms. Jin Bun Hong.
Logan?
You're alive?
I am.
Thanks to these two here.
Who did this to you?
Joo Dan Tae.
He set a bomb to get rid of me.
You sided with someone like that,
talked to the press,
turned Oh Yoon Hee into a criminal,
and even tarnished my reputation.
How could you...
betray me of all people?
How could you?
Didn't you come to Korea to help me?
I really had no idea...
that Joo Dan Tae would do something that dreadful.
The only thing I wanted was Eun Byeol.
I know.
It's because of Michelle, your dead daughter.
But guess what?
Michelle didn't die because of you.
That night, the person who left her outdoors...
was your drunk husband.
No.
She died because of me.
I ran away.
Because I was scared of my husband.
I left the poor thing behind.
Her hands...
Her face was so cold.
If I'd gotten to her sooner, I could've saved her.
I won't leave her alone ever again.
No. Eun Byeol can't be alone either.
I must go to her!
Pull yourself together, you lunatic!
Eun Byeol isn't your daughter!
No! She is my daughter!
She sleeps in my arms,
she smiles brightly at me,
and she tells me everything.
She likes the food I cook,
and she waits and waits for me.
You are out of your mind.
I won't let you near Eun Byeol again!
Logan!
Logan! Please help me.
Let me see Eun Byeol.
She means more than my life.
Please help me, Logan!
That...
depends on what you do.
Tell me everything that happened that day.
Tell her, Ms. Jin.
That day...
Oh Yoon Hee drove after me.
So I called Joo Dan Tae.
I found Eun Byeol.
I'm being followed by Oh Yoon Hee.
Help me.
Oh Yoon Hee is there?
Then I should, of course, help you.
I'll send you an address. Lure her there.
I met him in an isolated spot.
He suddenly tied me up and took me somewhere.
- I don't know what happened next. - Let me go!
Don't lie!
Your car was found where Yoon Hee died.
I really don't know!
I was locked up somewhere.
He let me go under the condition that I talk to the media.
That's all.
I can't believe this woman.
That day, when the car was pulled from the water,
the dashboard camera was already gone.
Ms. Jin. Look into my eyes as you answer.
That dashboard camera.
Do you really not know where it went?
I don't know where it is. You can ask the police.
Jin Bun Hong!
Tell me honestly.
I'm giving you one last chance.
The police don't know either.
To hide the fact that I'd kidnapped Eun Byeol,
I hired someone to get the dashboard camera,
but I haven't seen the footage either.
It's company property, and I couldn't get into the system.
Then tell me...
where that dashboard camera is now.
It has been six months.
Do you think the video's still there?
If it's the last video before the accident,
it'll be there.
Because there's no new footage to be taped over it.
(Login ID, Password)
(Record List)
Eun Byeol!
Get it out!
I'll jump aside once it's out, so get it out!
Free your hand first.
Eun Byeol, wake up.
No, Eun Byeol...
No!
Let go.
It was Cheon Seo Jin.
She killed Yoon Hee.
She's crazy.
Why would she... Why?
She killed Yoon Hee...
and wanted me gone too.
To take everything.
Do you think Dan Tae and Seo Jin are working together?
No.
Dan Tae will think he killed Yoon Hee.
But that doesn't cancel out his crimes.
To put pressure on Yoo Dong Pil,
he used Yoon Hee's corpse.
He killed her twice.
Did Eun Byeol see all this?
Is that why she asked Jin Bun Hong for the pills?
Cheon Seo Jin...
She got Eun Byeol in this mess.
I will not forgive her.
Never.
They will see...
what torture is like.
Mr. Yoo, are you all right?
Don't mind me.
You know that Jenny's now Cheong A Arts Center's...
Artist in Residence, right?
It would've been nice if you'd attended the party.
Why are you...
always interfering and meddling?
Jenny did really well that day.
Look. You wanted to see, didn't you?
She was dazzling at the audition.
(Official Video)
Jenny always said she's like her dad.
That's why she's loyal and softhearted.
A daughter takes after her dad.
Would she take after a passing dog?
Jenny likes you a lot.
She always looks at her photo with you before bed.
She misses you.
I don't know what's going on,
but if you speak earnestly to her and Ms. Kang,
won't they understand?
Tell me whatever you need. I'll help.
You shouldn't drink too much either.
You jerk.
Yoo Dong Pil.
You are the biggest scumbag.
I don't deserve it,
but I'm going to be your father for once.
Just this once.
Kang Ma Ri.
What should I do first?
I'll do whatever you tell me to.
Then I'll gladly be punished.
(115 posts, 237 following, 98 followers)
Mom, let's take a photo together.
Sure.
One, two, three.
No rabbit looks like that.
Isn't it adorable?
It's cute.
Where have you been?
It's too early to be walking around.
If Joo Dan Tae finds you...
Can I ask you for a favor?
I saved this money...
for Ro Na.
Please hand it to her for me.
Why don't you do it yourself? Even though you're late.
You can still be her father.
I heard from Yoon Hee.
I don't deserve to be a dad.
Ro Na wouldn't want that either.
However,
I will spend the rest of my life trying to destroy...
Joo Dan Tae and Cheon Seo Jin for Yoon Hee.
I'll do whatever it takes.
I will avenge Yoon Hee's death with my own hands.
At least Yoon Hee won't be lonely.
You and I both want to pay her back for what we owe her.
If anything happens to me,
promise you'll take care of Ro Na.
Stay by her side till the end.
(Caller ID blocked)
Hello?
Hello? Are you there?
Seok Kyung?
It's you, isn't it?
Where are you?
I'll come.
- We should meet... - I have something to tell you.
Director Cheon Myung Soo...
didn't die of a heart attack.
Someone killed him.
It was Cheon Seo Jin.
What are you saying all of a sudden?
I saw her in the video.
Eun Byeol had it.
Eun Byeol is the witness.
I hope you succeed in whatever it is you're trying to do.
Seok Kyung.
[VIU Ver] SBS E27 'The Penthouse 3'
"The Dashcam Footage"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Eun Byeol, you'll come to my inauguration party today, right?
What are you doing?
Can't you see I'm eating?
I'm starving. I haven't eaten anything since yesterday.
What are you talking about?
You just ate. You ate a whole bowl of curry.
I did? When?
Eun Byeol!
Get Eun Byeol out first!
Quickly!
My leg!
I'll jump aside once it's out, so get it out!
Quickly! Cheon Seo Jin!
My leg!
Eun Byeol!
Don't touch me!
What's wrong with you? What are you saying?
What did I just say?
You don't remember?
My head's been hurting lately.
Right, it's your inauguration today.
Be pretty.
I should go get ready as well.
Eun Byeol, why this again?
I thought you'd forgotten it all.
It's all because of the stress from that audition.
Because of Bae Ro Na.
It's going to be fine, right?
Yes.
Everything will be fine soon.
My Eun Byeol...
is meant to lead the Cheong A Foundation.
(Inauguration Celebration for Cheong A Foundation's Cheon Seo Jin)
Thank you.
Today, I was born again.
When I stepped down as the director of Cheong A Foundation,
I thought I died.
But you've brought me back to life.
I will think of the rest of my life as something extra...
and sacrifice myself for education.
From now on, Cheong A Foundation will be even better than before...
and grow into the best private foundation...
in all of Korea.
(Inauguration Celebration for Cheong A Foundation's Cheon Seo Jin)
- Bravo! - Bravo!
- Congratulations! - Cheers!
Thank you.
Why did you want to come here?
We have nothing to do with the Cheong A Foundation anymore.
The kids have graduated.
Has following me ever done you any harm?
No.
Then just pay close attention.
Something fun is about to happen.
Right, how's your husband doing?
(58 missed calls)
Goodness, is he obsessed with you?
(Cheonsoo District New Town Groundbreaking Ceremony)
The place will be full by the time we start.
We will now start the ribbon cutting ceremony.
One,
two,
three.
(Cheonsoo District New Town Groundbreaking Ceremony)
(Beyond Gangnam, Nation's Most Prestigious Town)
Cheonsoo District has finally...
recorded the nation's highest price.
We will soon be welcoming some of the most prestigious schools...
as well as an express train line...
that will take us...
to Jongno within 20 minutes and Apgujeong within ten minutes.
(Cheonsoo District New Town Groundbreaking Ceremony)
To live up to its reputation, Cheonsoo District will be reborn...
as the nation's largest, most luxurious new town.
Cheong A Constructions will not stop investing...
until Cheonsoo District becomes a world-class town.
- Yes! - Let's do this!
- Nice! - Congratulations!
Cheong A Group's stock prices skyrocketed today.
Congratulations.
But why is Ms. Cheon Seo Jin not here?
Her inauguration ceremony happens to take place today,
so she couldn't make it.
But she sent me a congratulatory message.
Let's see it together.
(Beyond Gangnam, Nation's Most Prestigious Town)
Congratulations on the groundbreaking ceremony.
What's that?
What's going on?
What happened?
(Joo Dan Tae killed Logan Lee.)
- "Joo Dan Tae killed Logan Lee?" - What's that?
- What's going on? - Unbelievable.
- What's going on? - Who did this?
- My goodness. - This is awful.
What happened?
What's wrong?
I hope you like what I prepared,
Mr. Joo.
Gosh.
Cheon Seo Jin, that crazy...
Mr. Joo, what happened?
Can you say something?
Please explain!
Say something!
Explain what's going on!
Mr. Joo!
Mr. Joo's present just arrived.
He didn't have to.
Dear Director Cheon Seo Jin, my beloved wife.
You're my joy and happiness.
Love, Joo Dan Tae, your husband.
My goodness.
I'm curious what he sent you. Show us.
Shall we do that?
(Inauguration Celebration for Cheong A Foundation's Cheon Seo Jin)
My husband, Chairman Joo Dan Tae, sent me a precious gift.
Its price is 450 million dollars.
"Salvator Mundi" by Leonardo da Vinci.
Let me present it to you.
(Cheon Seo Jin killed Director Cheon Myung Soo.)
- What's that? - Oh, my.
- What's going on? - What's that?
Is that true?
Can you give us a comment?
Did you really kill Director Cheon Myung Soo?
Who is it? Who did this?
Say something!
It's not true. Never.
It's far from the truth.
Please stop taking pictures. It's not true.
It's not true.
Joo Seok Kyung. Did she open her mouth in the end?
- Is it really true? - Please explain!
It's not true!
Move. Get out of my way.
My gosh. What is that?
Ms. Cheon killed her father?
What did I say?
I told you something fun was about to happen.
Joo Dan Tae!
Cheon Seo Jin!
How dare you mess with me?
Look who's talking.
Didn't we agree to bury that for good?
After asking me to get rid of Baek Jun Ki,
how could you stab me in the back like this?
Ruining my ceremony...
would harm Cheong A Group too. Don't you know that?
That's nonsense!
Why are you digging up the past then?
Do you have proof that I killed my father?
Get off me!
Let go!
(The Penthouse 3)
We're all here to punish Joo Dan Tae and Cheon Seo Jin.
- Wanted? - You have three days.
- It's Baek Jun Ki. - I'm going to die?
Are you scared? That mean witch.
- What brings you here? - I want to take you somewhere.
My sweet girl. I miss you.
- It's 500 million dollars. - Five hundred million dollars?
I'm not going!
The fight is on.
I trust neither the police nor the court.
I'll punish them myself.