[English subtitles are available]
[Begin Again]
[Episode 12]
Ms. Lu,
are we just eating bread for dinner?
Yes.
Eat up.
Don't choke on the bread.
Thank you.
Ms. Lu,
would you like to eat something else?
Ms. Lu, you...
What's wrong?
Are these bread so delicious
that it moved you to tears?
It tastes normal.
Even this kind of bread tastes bad
when you eat too much of it.
How awful Ling Rui must felt
when he had to keep eating those bread?
Come on.
Don't stop, keep eating.
We have to choose
the best bread.
I'll buy it for Ling Rui
when he comes back
from his business trip.
You're trying to force Dr. Ling
to recall his past misery
to accentuate his current happiness?
How can that be?
I'm replacing
his previous bad memories
with delightful flavors.
No, Ms. Lu.
In life,
there is countless great food.
Eating bread
is definitely not Dr. Ling's
dream.
You've gotten smarter.
How can eating bread
be a person's
lifelong dream?
I'm going to write
a wealth plan that generates
a million yuan income a year.
Ms. Lu,
can you write one for me first?
That'd be too slow.
Shall I give him some shares?
My fortune?
I'll let Gao Erfan do some checking.
No, no.
If you do that to Dr. Ling,
he'll be scared.
Girl, you're naive.
I'm trying to give him
a strong sense of security.
Previously,
I always thought that.
Ling Rui was a warm person.
But it turns out that
he had been through such painful days.
Ms. Lu,
are you sick?
What are you doing?
No, no.
I mean,
you love Dr. Ling so much.
Love?
Don't tell me that
you don't feel anything.
Ms. Lu,
do you know what you're doing?
I'm...
I'm just...
taking care of
the father of my future baby.
Only when my baby's father is in a good mood,
can the baby
be in a good mood.
I'm considering it from
a genetic point of view.
Let me put it this way.
Even if you're lying to Dr. Ling that
you don't want a baby.
But what about then?
Having a baby
is not what Dr. Ling wants.
Will you force him?
Ms. Lu,
have you ever been in a relationship?
Don't tell me you have been single since birth?
What?
Single since birth? What do you mean?
It means that
you've never been in love
ever since you were born.
How is that possible?
Tell me about it.
How many times have you been in a relationship?
Or I wouldn't believe you.
This many?
One.
Strictly speaking, it's one point five.
Why is there a decimal point?
It's the kind of situation
where he thought he's in a relationship with me.
But I was actually taking him as a subject.
His family sells soy sauce.
Okay, okay, this doesn't count.
What about the remaining one?
That was a
serious relationship.
Later on,
because of some reason,
we broke up,
I was even a little sad.
At that time,
he confessed his love to me
and gave me a box of chocolates.
I gave him a gift back.
What did you give him?
I don't know if you've bought one before.
Those stickers,
the puffy ones.
Not the normal kinds.
I remembered it was quite expensive.
Five yuan for one sticker sheet.
Did you buy one before?
I did.
How old were you?
Seven or eight.
I can't really remember.
It happened when I was in Grade 3.
That can't be counted as a relationship.
It doesn't count?
What is love then?
Love is when I...
He...
You're back.
I'm cooking.
♫ Even the pedestrians look like him ♫
♫ Even the sky won't stop crying ♫
What's the matter?
You're really back?
How come you are back?
They were conducting air traffic control today.
The flight was canceled.
We had conference calls
the whole day.
You are cooking.
I bought some vegetables
on my way back.
How's your day today?
How was work?
Pretty good.
We exchanged many new technologies
with specialists in pancreatic diseases.
I heard that in Germany,
they have new adjuvant therapies
and there have been successful cases.
I'm so glad.
Will you feel bored
if I talk about these?
No, I won't.
I like it.
What else did you do?
I had lunch with my colleagues.
In the afternoon,
we had a brief exchange.
Nothing else.
How about you?
I...
I was busy making money.
Nothing much.
You must be tired
after having a long day.
You don't have to cook.
Let's dine out.
It will be my treat.
Do you want Japanese or French cuisine?
Well...
If you don't like it,
you can treat me, too.
I'm fine with whatever you like.
I like the feeling of
eating with my family.
I'd like to cook for them.
I won't get tired of that.
Well then, I like it too.
What's the matter with you today?
Why do you keep looking at me?
You cried?
No.
Probably because that
I haven't rested well these two days.
I suppose so.
No one would dare to bully you.
Except for you.
Nothing.
Ling Rui.
Today,
I really, really
want to hug you today.
Can I hug you?
Sure.
I have to get some ingredients.
Okay.
Fangning,
why are you acting
like a child today?
Come on.
I can't cook like this.
It's fine.
Go on.
Fangning, come on.
Come.
Here.
Stand still.
Stand against the wall.
Don't move.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Put your back against it.
Don't let it fall off.
Hold these.
Grab tight.
Don't move.
Dinner will be ready soon.
Just wait a bit more.
Be good.
If... If you do this,
I can't move.
That's the point.
Or there's no way I can cook.
Well then...
What can be called as
love?
Love is when you care
if the person is happy or not.
All your emotions
are influenced by him.
Is he really not a fool?
I don't want to force him
to do what he doesn't want to.
You want to help him realize all his wishes.
You want to give him your most important things.
All of it.
Ling Rui,
I would like to officially inform you that
I want us
to start...
I'll open the door.
That's fine.
I'll go.
Who's that?
Who?
Lu Fangning,
you are just forcing him!
Tang Pingping,
why are you making a scene here at my house?
I didn't expect that
you would use their family debt
to force him to marry you.
I'm warning you.
Slander is also a crime.
I did not slander.
I found out about everything.
Your marriage with him
was fake from the beginning.
You're not saying anything?
You're admitting it?
Shut up.
You forced him with money.
You don't love him at all.
Who gives you the right
to speculate
my feelings?
Tang Pingping,
listen carefully.
How did Ling Rui and I meet
is none of your business.
Besides, I'm telling you.
My feelings for him are real.
As long as he's happy,
I'll be happy.
If he is not,
I'll try my best to make him happy.
I won't let him do anything
that he doesn't like.
On the contrary,
I will give him
my most precious things.
For the first time since I was a child,
I now understand
what it is like to truly love a person.
That's right.
Yes.
I love him.
♫ My dear, I have three hearts for you ♫
♫ Listen to this carefully,
this shall not be done half-heartedly ♫
I finally said it.
It feels so good.
Dr. Ling...
Ms. Tang,
Fangning and I have a happy marriage.
Thank you for your concern.
Sorry for hurting your eyes.
Are you satisfied now?
Now,
please...
get out of our house.
Your hand.
I hate you!
Close the door.
Darn it.
Lu Fangning,
just wait and see.
I will definitely
get Ling Rui back!
I won't lose to you.
♫ I'm moved beyond my expectation ♫
It's cold.
How dare you chase me out?
One day,
it will be your turn, Lu Fangning!
Hmph!
You...
don't hate vegetables anymore?
I'll buy more vegetables tomorrow.
No.
Anything is fine.
I'm fine with anything.
Ling Rui,
don't you...
have anything to say?
Like what?
About my confession
to you tonight,
don't you have anything to say?
Isn't that
an excuse
to make Tang Ping give up?
I have thousands of other reasons
to make her give up.
Why would I bother to say all those things?
Perhaps
that is the most convenient one.
Ling Rui, look at me.
Look at me.
In all seriousness,
I'll tell you once again.
I love you.
You've said that many times.
This time...
I really love you.
I mean it. It's true.
No,
you were just being impulsive
to upset Tang Ping.
I don't know
what happened to you today.
But love
is not something so casual.
I'm full. I'll go back to my room.
Tell me when you're done.
I'll clean up.
You are so stupid.
Who wants to have a baby with you?
You get what you deserve.
This time,
I really love you.
I mean it.
It's true.
[The CEO's Sweetheart]
I've tried everything.
What do you want me to do?
Ling Rui,
I love you.
Ling Rui works in the hospital every day.
I think he's probably
fed up with a white coat.
No.
This is good.
I'm not wearing anything under this.
It looks sexy.
Ling Rui.
No.
It will bring back
all the bad memories to him.
Why?
Why do I have to dress up like this?
[Even if she said she was not being impulsive]
[or because she wanted to win,]
[but it's because]
[everything feels new when she's with me.]
[It will fade away soon.]
The wealth plan that generates
a million yuan income a year?
Half of your fortune?
All of your fortune?
Aren't you the one
who suggested them, Ms. Lu?
It worked before.
How come it doesn't now?
That's right.
It worked before.
How come it doesn't now?
Did you get rejected
by Dr. Ling?
I mean...
Ms. Lu, your love for Dr. Ling
has gotten deeper.
The more you care about him,
the more insecure you feel.
Insecure...
I never thought that one day,
this word
will be related to me.
You know what?
Even if I gave Ling Rui
the wealth plan
and all my fortune,
Ling Rui won't accept it.
Why?
He has such a great personality.
His job is to heal the wounded
and rescue the dying.
After he gets off work,
he continues to do that.
He saves more people
and treats more wounds.
More importantly, it's for free.
So,
compared with Ling Rui,
I'm nothing.
From now on,
I want to be like him.
Be a warm person,
a noble person,
a perfect match for him.
A woman who really matches him.
I want to be
an angel.
Ms. Lu,
you are an angel.
Do you lack money?
Do you want the watch?
I see you haven't
had a watch.
-This watch is expensive.
-No, Ms. Lu.
Dad.
Come on.
Daddy.
How much do you want?
80,000 yuan?
No.
8,000 yuan? No problem.
IOU.
I, Tang Ping will borrow four million yuan
from my father, Tang Dawei.
I will definitely pay off the debt.
Debit holder, Tang Ping.
Right.
Pingping.
Tell me honestly.
Did you do something
very bad?
I didn't break the law.
That's right.
You are not capable of doing that.
But,
you're not that capable,
someone else can be.
Tell me the truth.
Did someone deceive you?
Did they brainwash you?
No.
What are you talking about?
Are you lending me or not?
If you are not, I'll go to uncle Lu.
You didn't break the law?
No.
You must have been deceived then.
I told you earlier
that you're not clever.
You don't believe me.
Did some jerk
ask you for four million yuan?
Is it?
Jerk?
Yes.
Tell me, what kind of man
would simply ask a girl
for four million yuan?
Doesn't that make him a jerk?
Lu Fangning gave Dr. Ling
four million yuan.
That makes Dr. Ling a jerk?
If I told Uncle Lu
and everyone the truth,
they will think that
Dr. Ling is a jerk.
I can't say anything.
Are you lending me or not?
No.
No!
Yes or no?
Where is that jerk?
Ask him to come here.
I'll give it to him.
I'll give him four hundred slaps!
There's no one like that, no!
It's not like that!
What is it then?
I want to get plastic surgery!
To look like Lu Fangning.
All right?
Plastic surgery?
To look like Lu Fangning?
Any amount of money will do.
You are giving the goods to me now?
Can I resell it?
I need money urgently, you know.
I just want to resell the goods.
Can I do that?
I have to go now.
Dr. Ling.
Ms. Tang.
About what happened last night,
I hope...
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
For your reputation.
For your fame
and your future.
I won't say anything.
Thank you, Ms. Tang.
For letting me and Fangning
take care of our personal affairs.
From now on,
let's get down to business.
Dr. Ling,
I know your present situation.
You can't be with me.
Not to mention...
you can't even
show your true feelings.
But you'll be able to do it after a year.
A year later,
you'll divorce Lu Fangning.
By that time,
I'll be the first candidate
to be your girlfriend.
Ms. Tang.
All right, I know.
You don't have to
promise me anything now.
I'll be waiting for you.
Because...
I
love
you.
I
love
you.
Ms. Tang,
you don't have to wait for me.
Neither will we, in the future,
have any kind of relationship.
Of course, you would want your father
to be healthy.
So,
we don't even have to maintain
our doctor-patient relationship.
I said that
I don't need you
to promise me anything.
I just want
what you wore at the hospital.
The ID tag
belongs to you only.
I'm leaving.
Dr. Ling.
Okay, okay.
I won't talk about love.
I'll make money to
set you free from Lu Fangning.
Dr. Ling.
Don't get deceived
by Lu Fangning.
She has always like to steal from me
since we were little.
Pingping, Fanfan,
Liangliang, Dingding.
She stole
everyone I liked from me.
Therefore,
you must
try your best
to persevere.
Dr. Ling.
I love you.
All right.
She stole
everyone I liked from me.
Dr. Ling,
you can't be deceived by Lu Fangning.
the operation is all ready.
All right.
Dr. Ling?
[Ling Rui, Shenzhen Huiren Hospital]
You can draw a bit more on this side,
right?
Yes.
Right?
Xinbao, you're drawing?
Dr. Ling.
Xinbao is drawing your portrait.
He said he will participate in
the charity auction this afternoon
with this painting.
Really?
You're drawing my portrait?
Can you show me?
That's not how the game works.
The nurse said that who gave the most money
will be able to see it.
Okay.
I'll come to the auction this afternoon.
At that time,
I'll look at your painting.
Really?
Yes.
Dr. Ling,
I love you.
All right, Xinbao.
Dr. Ling
has other things to do.
Let's not disturb him,
okay?
Okay.
Come on, let's go on.
Hello?
Ms. Lu,
the charity auction is in the afternoon.
I'll talk to him in a minute
and I'll remind him.
No problem.
Let's play it by ear.
I told you
you got the wrong number.
Someone dialed the wrong number.
The charity auction in the afternoon,
don't forget to attend.
I know, I'll be there.
It can help sick children
and I can get close to Ling Rui.
I, Lu Fangning,
am definitely an angel.
An angel.
Let's welcome our great charitarian,
Ms. Lu Fangning.
All right, let's welcome her
with a round of applause.
Hi.
[Little Painter Charity Auction]
Hi, everyone.
I did all of this
to help
the children who are struggling
with their illnesses.
Of course,
it's also for one person.
He is...
[Shenzhen Huiren Hospital welcomes you]
No.
Ling Rui doesn't like that.
Does it seem like
I'm flaunting?
Be anonymous?
Doing good deeds without leaving a name.
It's not my style.
Forget it.
Nice drawing.
Fangning, you are on low profile today.
It's not like your style.
Change of plan.
We'll go with plan B.
You'll bid in my stead.
After that, try to be unintentional
and as natural as you can
when you disclose it to Ling Rui.
Tell him that
I'm the one behind everything.
You're so considerate of Ling Rui.
I am relieved.
He'll appreciate me more
if I did something like this, right?
Okay, dear friends.
Our Little Painters
Charity Auction
is about to begin.
Thank you
-for supporting us.
-Let's begin.
Go.
Please do not wander around.
For this auction,
the first painting
is from the third ward,
our little friend, Chengcheng.
This painting
is called the Dreamer.
-It's very nice.
-The starting bid
for this painting is 100 yuan.
The bid increment is 50 yuan each time.
Feel free to place a bid...
150.
Yes, this gentleman here
offered 150 yuan.
150 yuan.
-Charity?
-Any higher bid?
Does anyone want to bid?
200.
The gentleman behind offered 200 yuan.
300.
1,000.
1,000 yuan.
The lady offered 1,000 yuan.
What do we do?
Raise your hand.
Well... 1,050.
How stingy. Forget it.
2,000.
The young lady offered 2,000 yuan.
2,050.
Okay, 2,050.
5,000.
This lady
offered 5,000 yuan.
Any higher bid?
5,050.
5,050 yuan.
-6,000.
-Shall we stop?
6,000 yuan.
Let it be.
Any higher bid?
Okay, 6,000 yuan, going once.
6,000 yuan, going twice.
6,000 yuan, sold.
Congratulations to this pretty lady.
You get the painting.
Change of plan.
Plan C.
Thank you, young lady.
Okay, let's move to the next painting.
What does plan C mean?
Plan C is where
we just keep raising the bid.
When it's gotten high,
let her get it.
Tang Ping likes to show off.
Let her enjoy this.
In the end, just remember
to tell Ling Rui that
I did these all on purpose.
The purpose is
to raise more money
for the kids in this hospital.
She's trying to fight with me.
I'll let her have it.
Congratulations, this gentleman.
Here is
the next painting.
It is a drawing
by our Beibei.
For this painting,
the starting bid is still 100 yuan.
1,000.
4,000.
4,000. Any higher bid?
5,000.
-5,000 yuan.
-Let her have it.
5,000 yuan, any higher bid?
5,000 yuan, going once.
5,000 yuan, going twice.
Okay, deal.
Congratulations again
to this beautiful young lady.
All right.
So the third painting...
Is this what you mean?
Right.
Is right here.
This painting
was created by
an 8-year-old kid.
2,050.
5,000.
Congratulations to this beautiful young lady.
As for the next painting,
it's interesting.
Van Gogh's sunflowers.
4,000.
6,000.
Deal!
Okay, the following one.
This painting
was created by a 6-year-old kid.
It's titled Underwater World.
4,000.
8,000.
Deal!
Congratulations again
to this beautiful young lady.
She got another painting.
Beautiful young lady...
All right, the next painting.
Here comes
the last painting of this auction.
The creator of this painting
is Xinbao.
He's also here with us.
Let's give him a round of applause, all right?
Well done!
Okay, Xinbao.
About this painting,
I'd like to ask
what is the title of this painting?
It's
My
Dear
Dr. Ling.
An angel.
Holy light.
Ling Rui.
Get this painting for me.
Xinbao.
How much are you going to start
for this painting?
100 yuan.
All right. Staring bid, 100 yuan.
5,000.
5,000 yuan.
6,000.
8,000.
8,000 yuan.
-The young lady offered 8,000 yuan.
-Double it.
16,000.
Are you happy now, Xinbao?
20,000.
Stop competing with me.
Fangning, what should I do?
50,000.
I...
I said 50,000.
60,000.
80,000.
100,000.
200,000.
500,000!
Stop, stop!
Can you both give it a rest?
I can draw one for you, my sister-in-law.
Let me draw one for you.
I'll draw one for you, too.
How's that?
I'm sure all of you can feel
their generosity.
Xinbao, do you feel it?
Yes.
Right. Of course,
the way we show love
may not just through
this auction.
I'm sure there will be
other ways
and opportunities
waiting for both of you.
You're right.
Therefore,
I hereby announce that
I've decided to fund
one-year medical expenses
for ten poor children
in this hospital.
I'll fund 20 children!
30 children.
Dr. Ling.
Xinbao.
I would like to have this painting, too.
But...
I only have 2,000 yuan.
Can I have it?
Xinbao,
what is your decision?
Okay.
I drew a portrait of Dr. Ling.
So I'll sell it to Dr. Ling.
2,000 yuan, deal. Congratulations!
Now, let's have
all the successful bidders
come up on stage for a group photo.
Why do we have this session?
What's wrong with this session?
Don't worry, my sister-in-law.
Don't worry.
I'll make sure to tell everything
to Ling Rui.
Okay, let's give them a big hand.
Listen.
I can paint, too. I sell it for 500 yuan.
I'll give you 1,000 yuan to shut up.
Bye, Dr. Ling.
Fangning.
Bye.
It's okay.
I'll get back to work.
You should go as well.
Ling Rui, actually I...
I'm very busy.
Let's talk about it when we're at home.
No, we'll talk about it next time.
That's it.
I'm returning to my ward.
That's it?
Forget it, okay?
Why?
Because I don't like it.
I don't like that
you could say those three words so easily.
I don't like that you are competing
over such things.
So let's just drop it, okay?
Why would you think so?
Who told you that?
Who told you I was being insincere?
Tang Ping?
Why did you choose to believe her
but not me?
I don't believe her.
I believe what I know about you.
Who are you
to judge me?
I've never done that
to anyone else.
I was not acting recklessly
or competing with anyone.
What can I do
to make you believe me?
Should I sponsor more patients for your sake?
Is that okay?
I'm... I'm sorry.
Did I say something wrong again?
Ling Rui,
I did all of these
because I want to
get closer to you.
I hope you can truly
fall in love with me.
I admit what I did to you before
was on the spur of the moment.
But when these spontaneous moments
come together,
it then becomes an indisputable fact that
I love...
Believe me.
When you're no longer impulsive
and competitive,
you won't feel the same anymore.
Don't say anything
that you're not sure of.
That's all I'm going to say.
I'm leaving.
Our brand
is the leading brand
in the home furnishing industry.
We have the ability to
lead the main trends of the market.
Compared to our brand,
our competitors use crude materials
and apply irrational structures.
In contrast,
Infinity
is the lightest and strongest.
Adjourn.
That's it for my love life?
It wilted before it even started.
Where's my next episode?
Where is the next episode?
The next episode is coming.
Director Lu.
Lin Qi.
Siyu.
You've got something to say?
Carry on with your work then.
Go on.
The proposal that you just gave me
is not like what you said.
Have a look at it.
Sure, I'll check it.
I'll hand it to you in a while.
Yes, please do.
I'm sorry.