[English subtitles are available]
[Begin Again]
[Episode 06]
Ling Rui.
I don't know what's going on
between you two.
But listen to me carefully,
I won't let anyone
have any chance to hurt her.
Lu Yiyao,
I don't know what's going on
between you two, either.
But listen to me,
the one who hurts her
definitely won't be me.
Thanks for your milk.
She founded Infinity
because of her past experience.
Throughout all these years,
she has always insisted on
founding Infinity.
That means she's never let it go.
It seems that she doesn't trust you
as I imagined
although you're already married.
Good night.
What are these?
No.
I must have misheard.
Yeah, I must have.
Shameless, stupid
brazen-faced, and ordinary,
damn Tang Ping.
You know a lot of
professional idioms.
Listen to me,
it is still my wedding
even though
it's only a contract for a year.
I'm not interested
in gossip at all
although I'm an entertainment reporter.
Whether you're really married or not,
or when you're going to divorce.
I really
don't want to know.
Cai Siyu,
if you still can't dig up any big news,
you can just quit your job.
What should I do?
You did sleep well.
You slept like a pig.
You're the one who should take initiative.
How come
he put you to sleep?
Is it so difficult to get pregnant?
Harder than
creating a new brand?
The fourth guideline of a happy marriage,
morning is the best timing.
Okay.
Ling Rui.
I can't have the zipper
on the back of my dress zipped up.
Two days?
I prefer a week then.
I'm okay with that.
No problem at all.
Okay, I'm hanging up.
Fangning.
Something happened in the hospital.
What happened?
I may be occupied the next whole week.
I may not
sleep at home.
For a week?
What should I do alone
without you?
What do you want?
I mean
we're newlyweds.
Being intimate is
what we should do.
How should I explain to my family
when you're gone?
Then, I'll go talk to Dad.
I'm sure he'll understand.
Wait...
This is good actually.
We've had a hard time
staying under the same roof,
and pretending.
It can be easily seen through.
This is a good chance.
We have a fair reason to be apart.
But I still have a lot of plans.
Like what?
Just now,
you said your zipper...
No. Nothing.
Off you go.
Okay, I'll go to work then.
[LM Deer Sing Group]
How is it going?
Are there any changes?
Nothing.
Everything's normal.
Rogue!
Wait...
Security!
How could you let people like that in?
Simon,
are you okay?
What are you looking at? Go back to work.
Thank god I was quick-witted.
Otherwise, it'd be so awkward.
I didn't talk with Ms. Lu
about the recording.
Where is my recording pen?
Bread for breakfast,
for lunch,
and even for dinner.
Why not let me be
a bread tester?
Bless me! Just let me meet
this month's target.
Please give me a piece of big news,
Lu Fangning.
Since I'm here now,
it won't be too much
to take a photo with Ms. Lu, right?
Shameless, stupid
brazen-faced and ordinary,
damn Tang Ping.
You know a lot of
professional idioms.
I seem to know the owner
of this recording pen.
I'll give it back to her.
Let's go see
your new office later.
I'm screwed.
My exclusive news
and my recording pen are both gone.
My rent, my meals, and my boyfriend
are all gone too.
Why are you here again?
-I...
-Leave.
Wait, I...
I lost something important
inside.
How can you do this to me?
Will you save me some face?
Go away. Don't come again.
I don't want to see you, either!
Hello?
Ms. Lu?
Don't you want to check it?
Excuse me.
Okay, you can go on.
Why did you ask me
how much money I can be bought with?
If you didn't take the picture
of Zhou Yijian
or Sister Lu,
you'd be thankful
if she gives you 10,000,
let alone 100,000.
Please don't listen to her nonsense.
I can't be easily
bought off.
Being a journalist is a sacred job.
My dream is
to win a news award.
You don't have to worry.
I won't stain
your sacred dream.
Because I didn't mean
to give you even a penny.
I've erased
all the recordings in it.
There isn't much
besides learning about
what you like to eat
everyday.
-Food means...
-Although the recordings
have been erased,
but the things in your head...
Wait a second. What are you going to do?
I'm telling you.
Even though I'm only a young reporter,
I have some connections too.
Even though LM Deer Sing Group
put your ads on
those top-ranking platforms,
but small platforms like us
are extremely good at hyping news.
If you dare hurt me,
I won't let you go.
Okay, go on.
What is there to say?
Criticize the Deer Sing's ads.
Go ahead.
Was that a criticism?
I was threatening you.
And,
you always put ads
on our entertainment section.
Who says the effect would be better
with more views?
Celebrity gossip is so interesting.
Who will have the time
to see a mattress ad
overlapped on a celebrity's face?
Even if I click it by accident,
and the official page
of your company pops up.
Where are the products?
Where should I find it?
Reading gossips is more fun.
You've spent five whole years,
yet you're still
reporting celebrities' tidbits.
You would never win
Pulitzer Award in your lifetime.
Why don't
you join my company
and work in the Planning Department?
Just focus on earning money.
What do you say?
You...
How can you attack me like this?
I'll double your pay.
Extra bonus
if you achieve your KPI.
I can give you
one third more personally.
In the long run,
it's much better than
your present job.
As for the secret,
you have to
erase that
from your brain.
Understand?
[Boss Dog]
Wait a second.
Hello, boss.
Cai Siyu!
Where are you?
Where is the news?
You can resign
if you don't want to work.
I'll approve it now!
She has resigned, and you have approved.
Cai Siyu.
-You'll start the day after tomorrow.
-What did you say?
Repeat it.
Cai Siyu!
What did you say just now!
Repeat it.
Didn't you hear it?
I'll say it again,
I quit!
Screw your 996 work schedule!
Screw your paparazzi!
I'm sorry.
Sorry, sorry.
[Shenzhen Huiren Hospital]
I know you're newly-wed.
But, young man,
don't overindulge yourself.
Don't spread
the news about my marriage.
What? Do you want to keep it hidden?
But you married Lu Fangning,
I think you can just hide instead.
Her identity is quite special.
She doesn't want our marriage
to be widely known.
I also don't want it to
interfere with my work.
So,
keep your mouth shut.
Fangning.
Ling Rui really
won't come back home tonight?
He said
he had to work overtime in the hospital.
But...
Alright.
I know what you wanna say.
It's not good to work late
on the first day of marriage, right?
You forgot that
I went out for a business meeting
the first day we got married?
I even closed the deal.
You were so pleased.
You said we earned money
and it was you who brought me luck.
Did you forget that?
Earning money is a daytime thing.
How precious the night is.
Fangning.
You should take it into account.
Oh!
Look at this.
Fangning.
Here.
This is the soup I boiled
especially for you.
It saturates three bowls into one
and is very nutritious.
Drink this.
No more wine.
A little bit of wine is okay.
That calms her down. No harm.
One last time. Last time.
It's bad for the baby.
Do you take folic acid?
That should be taken in advance.
Also,
do you like girls or boys?
I feel like
you would better
have a girl.
Girls look like their fathers.
Why should I be the one
who suffers all these?
Why?
Dad,
when can I be freed
from this "prison"?
This is your home.
You're well-served here.
How is it a prison?
No Wi-Fi, no cell phone.
Isn't it just like a prison?
I just went to the wedding ceremony
in a wedding dress.
Why?
I didn't look as pretty
as Lu Fangning in a wedding dress?
Pingping.
I am ill.
Dad, you're not.
No.
I am.
But, I don't have medicines.
Dad.
I wanted
to see Dr. Ling last time,
so I said you were sick.
Stop acting.
No, I'm serious.
The hospital called me.
I'm not lying this time.
I'm really sick.
Ling Rui.
Here she is.
I'll leave you two here.
Peng Bo.
You stay here. Wait for a moment.
Dr. Ling, please help my dad.
Your father now has
congestive splenomegaly.
So I suggest
to receive a radical treatment
through surgery.
Is it very serious?
We can't make judgments now.
But if it's spleen lesions,
he should get diagnosed
and receive treatment as soon as possible.
I'll take your advice.
We'll do the surgery.
Okay.
I'll make you an admission notice.
Dr. Ling,
are you still willing
to do the surgery for my father?
Of course.
He is the patient. I'm a doctor.
It's my job to save a patient's life.
Alright, you've got
the patient ID card, right?
Go pay the fees.
How much should I give you
personally?
Are you a fool?
How could you say this in front of me?
I said I should go.
Don't listen to him.
We won't accept that.
Take this.
Go pay the fees.
Good for you.
Separate work from private interests.
Nice.
[Send to: Ling Rui]
Will you
come back tonight?
The condition of the patient at bed 22
is quite special.
His liver is normal
in size and shape.
But you see, it has a smooth
and neat contour,
as well as a clear membrane.
So be sure to observe closely
and pay attention to his temperature.
Keep an eye on him.
Dr. Peng, who is this woman?
She seems to have an unusual relationship
with Director Ling?
Another crazy fan of him.
Haven't you got used to this?
How many fans does he have?
This is not the same.
How?
She is
more stubborn,
and may directly affect
our director.
Affect our director?
They have a personal relationship?
Anyway,
this is
where we work, right?
Don't let others pry into
our Director Ling's
personal life,
got it?
I got it.
Fangyu,
why are you playing with your phone again?
Your mom said that
you got this sickness
because you played with your phone
too much.
-Dad.
-You're can't be cured.
Dad, I'm not sick at all.
What are you talking about?
I won't ask you.
You won't tell me the truth.
I'll ask Ling Rui.
I felt like there is someone absent.
Where is Ling Rui?
Fangning, where is Ling Rui?
I have to say something.
Did you have a fight
with Ling Rui again?
Listen,
you can't do that.
You're now
married.
If you go on acting like this,
no matter how good a man he is,
your life would go wrong one day.
Ling Rui is such a good man.
He is a doctor.
Right?
Brother-in-law.
Dad,
you're looking for me?
You're at home?
I just got back.
Fangning said
you wouldn't come back tonight.
I wasn't going to come back.
But temporarily decided
to pick up some clothes.
I'm leaving again later.
Have dinner first.
I really can't.
I still got work in the hospital.
Dad, I'll go talk to Fangning.
Take your meals regularly.
After I'm done with the work,
I'll make it up to you.
Okay.
Dad, aunt, enjoy the meal.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Ling Rui,
don't miss your meals no matter
how busy you are.
Also, come back early.
Okay.
Go ahead.
[Nurse Station]
Um...
Nice contact lenses.
I am not wearing contact lenses.
Then you really have beautiful eyes.
You are?
I'm...
Patient's family member.
Are you here to see Director Ling?
Yes.
No, no.
What Director Ling?
Look, these are
food I bought
for the doctors and nurses.
-Thank you.
You're welcome.
Alright, I see.
No one is allowed to eat this.
Let me see.
Wow.
Yang Jin, you freak.
How can you fight with us
for this heart-shaped cake?
That's right.
This is for Director Ling.
Be smart.
Freak.
He didn't answer my message,
but came back all of a sudden.
He came back,
but didn't stay the night.
Guidelines of a happy marriage?
But, where is my husband!
Sister,
I heard nothing just now.
Did you knock at the door?
Come in.
Your hearing is good.
Why don't you quit the job in the mall
and be a telephone operator?
Sister, I think my job is good.
I don't want to be an operator.
By the way,
I just called
the hospital.
Actually,
brother-in-law isn't on duty tonight.
I think he just said that because
he didn't want to
make things awkward for you.
It was his fault anyway.
Sister.
Why don't you be proactive this time?
I heard from brother-in-law
that there is a nice restaurant
nearby the hospital.
Why don't you
deliver the food there in person
to impress him?
Sister,
I'm also a man.
I know what men like.
Lu Fangyu,
I can let you
get out right now,
you know?
-I know, I know.
-Get out.
Now.
Get out!
Okay, as you wish.
Sister, I'm your brother.
I'll definitely help you!
Get lost!
A man who said
he would obey the contract
hasn't come home
for two days in a row.
Should I stay at home,
waiting for him to break the contract?
Of course, no.
I have the duty to
remind him
and help him.
Tang Ping?
Why are you here?
Dr. Ling
specially arranged the surgery
for my father right away
after he heard that my father was sick.
And, he stressed that
he'd do it personally.
He knew that
I don't like being around
too many people.
So,
he arranged
a single ward for my father.
So sweet.
What are you doing?
This is a hospital.
Behave yourself.
Listen, Tang Pingping.
Our Ling Rui is a doctor
who is considerate and responsible.
It's his duty
to take care of his patients
and their families.
That's nothing.
Single ward?
Let alone Ling Rui,
even Uncle Tang won't request that.
But you are quite good at
wasting national resources
without contributing.
-You...
-Alright.
Since I'm here,
just bring me to visit Uncle Tang.
No, let go of me!
Didn't you hear from them?
Both the man and the woman
are not married.
People in this hospital
don't know
he's married.
You say,
why didn't he tell others?
He doesn't want any trouble
when you get a divorce later, right?
Dr. Yang.
Tell her who I am.
The family member
of the patient of bed 2.
Be more specific.
A special family member of Director Ling.
Fangning, why are you here?
Sure enough, he isn't wearing the ring.
One-year term.
You remember that very clearly.
What do you mean?
You always say
that you will
obey the contract.
You accepted
another woman's cake
and be kind to another woman.
Is this how you
obey the contract?
Fangning,
can we have a talk calmly?
Am I talking to the air
right now?
Do you know that
when I'm alone at home,
all the people asked me
where you went
and when would you come back?
What can I tell them?
How come a newlywed husband
gets tied up
and can't come home?
I'm just worried that
we would be caught in a lie.
What about today?
I told everyone
you wouldn't come back,
and you showed up suddenly,
that embarrassed me.
Do you know that?
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
It's my fault.
That's all?
Ling Rui, let me ask you.
At the present time, do you ever
keep it in mind that
you're already married?
Do I have to?
Of course!
Newlyweds don't just say that
they love each other
and hold hands!
Look at us,
we don't look like
a newlywed couple at all!
I'm telling you,
if our lies are exposed,
it's your fault.
You're breaking the contract!
My fault?
I can finally work in
a splendid office building.
They are really elites,
looking so fancy.
But why should I
dress like this for work?
My feet ache.
Cai Siyu, you can do this.
Come on.
I'm coming.
There, falling, careful.
Good luck.
Missy,
are you from the "rookie village"?
You are not proficient
in your "equipment".
Mind your mouth, okay?
Don't hit on me.
I didn't.
Let me help you?
No need.
We're colleagues, let me help you.
Don't touch me.
Don't touch me!
-You...
-Shut up.
Director Lu.
I'm sorry.
You saw that.
She pushed me.
-She pushed me.
-Director Lu?
What are you talking about?
Why would I push you
if you didn't touch me?
I meant well.
Director Lu, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Well... I'll go bring the cleaner over.
You!
Cai Siyu?
Director Lu.
Why are they together?
Cai Siyu.
What are you doing?
Why are you two together?
Oh my.
Did Ms. Lu misunderstand?
Simon.
-What's wrong with you?
-Ms. Lu, I...
I didn't do that.
Alright. Quit it.
You embarrassed the director
on your first day.
No bonus this month.
Let's go, Simon.
Go get it changed.
Tissue.
Ms. Lu...
I had my bonus canceled on my first day,
what should I do next?
Cai Siyu,
do you know why
I asked you to stay?
I don't really know.
The employee was sent by Ms. Lu.
How come it's you,
a rookie?
You dared spill coffee
all over Director Lu
on your first day at work?
No, I didn't do that.
You didn't, then I did?
How dare you slander me!
I did that, I did.
Stand up.
Have a seat.
You have a good attitude.
I'll just let you go.
Anyway, you'll be in
my Planning Department.
I'll back you in the future.
Thank you so much.
Hold on.
My last name is Lin. I'm Lin Qi.
You can call me
Leader Lin.
Hello, Leader Lin.
You can come to me
if you have any problem
about the company
in the future.
But,
you may not have the chance to do that.
You just pissed Director Lu off.
I assume you will not stay here
for a long time.
Is Director Lu
terrifying?
Terrifying?
More than that.
He is a legend, okay?
Legend?
Yeah.
What legend?
First,
there are two subordinates
who've worked with him for over a decade.
They've been sticking by him
no matter at home or abroad.
A leader's glamor.
He must be broad-minded then?
Not necessarily.
Second, although his last name is Lu,
he is not
relevant to the Lu Family.
He was adopted by Chairman Lu.
But he has helped our chairman,
and done many things that
our chairman wanted to do
but dared not do.
The mystery of his lot,
complicated and mysterious.
Exactly the standards of a male lead.
What else?
Just listen to me.
Third,
ten years ago,
he suddenly broke up
with his fiance
who was about to marry him.
No one knew what happened
and why.
Later,
Lu Yiyao went to Sweden for ten years
and never came back.
He was
traveling the world for love.
A rare love fool.
Anything else?
No more?
Except for the two subordinates
and the fiance,
no more juicy gossips
about Director Lu?
What's wrong with your eyes?
Well, Director Lu, I...
You're fooling me again.
Well done.
Come on.
What else do you want to know?
I can tell you in person.