[English subtitles are available]
[Begin Again]
[Episode 02]
Here.
Check.
Uncle Hua?
-You are back.
-Having a walk?
Ling Rui is back.
I'm back.
-Ling Rui.
-Hello, Aunt Li.
Change another hand.
Sister Fang.
Use your left hand.
This way.
Then, use this.
Yes.
-Aunt.
-This shoulder.
You're off early.
-Yes.
Your mother
is promoting health knowledge again.
-Forward.
-Call her.
Revise what I taught today.
Mom!
Mom, are you done?
Yes.
Let's go home and have lunch.
Okay, where's my musical instrument?
My bag?
The bag's here.
-Don't forget to practice.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Repeat 20 times.
Let's go.
Look at how bad this woman is.
I told you.
I know the ending will be like this.
Look.
What's it, little aunt?
Ling Rui,
I'm going to die.
So, you are saying that
the one who owed you four million yuan
is the aunt of Dr. Ling Rui.
Yes, sister.
Sister Yazhi told me that
she has a nephew named Ling Rui,
working as a surgeon in the city hospital.
And Sister Yazhi
is really good.
So, she is not going to
deny the debt.
And, their aunt...
Shut up!
I took the little asset
your former uncle-in-law gave me
before the divorce.
And, I did some investment.
I lost all the money in it.
I also...
-Also...
-I also...
What?
I also owed four million yuan.
Now, they are urging me to return it.
I don't have the money.
Ling Rui, don't...
Don't tell your mother
and my sister.
If they find out, I am doomed to die!
Okay, little aunt. Don't worry.
I will
deal with this.
Okay, okay.
Okay. No problem.
Okay. Goodbye.
Did you make an appointment with him?
Yes... Yeah.
He said we could meet tomorrow.
Well, sister.
Do you have any other orders?
This is the company.
Call me Ms. Lu.
Okay.
I'll pay attention to that in the future,
and call you Ms. Lu.
Four million yuan. Good job.
Sister...
It's so generous of you
by spending money like water.
Do you know how hard
your sister works?
Sister... Ms. Lu.
I was wrong
I'll go work at the store
right now.
I promise that
I'll do my best, for Deer Sing,
dad and you, with a
down-to-earth attitude.
Did you forget about your mother?
Yes. For my mother too.
For my mother,
I need to put my life on
competing with you for the inheritance.
I'll give you
a great sense of accomplishment
in the process of defeating me.
Okay.
Just leave.
Sister...
Can I have my credit card back?
Get out!
Okay.
I'll get out of here right now.
Bye bye.
[Ling Rui]
Ling Rui.
[Aunt: Ling Yazhi]
You have nowhere to run.
[LM Deer Sing Group]
Lu Fangning,
General Manager of LM Deer Sing Group,
Lu Fangyu's sister,
and the creditor of your aunt, Ling Yazhi.
I'm the one you are responsible for.
Ms. Lu,
I'm willing to
bear all the debt
on behalf of Ms. Ling Yazhi.
But, because the amount
is relatively huge,
it may take a while to pay off them.
I totally understand.
So,
can you give me an extension?
I came up with
an overall plan
for this problem.
An overall plan
that benefits both of us.
Let's make it to two million.
But, you need to marry me
for just one year only.
The two million
can be offset after a year.
You don't have to thank me.
I need a marriage
to deal with my family.
And, you're the right guy.
You don't have to thank me
for giving you this chance.
I'm sorry. I reject the offer.
Two million five hundred thousand yuan?
It's more than half of the debt.
Three million.
Three million a year.
It's several times your annual salary.
Think about it.
If we cooperate happily,
this will make a win-win situation.
Smooth.
Four million, all of it.
You just have to keep up
a year's marriage with me.
One year later, the debt will be
canceled.
I think I'd better go.
Later,
I'll think about
the specific repayment plan.
Then, I'll inform Ms. Lu.
You won't lose anything.
Wait! Wait!
Lu Fangning,
apologize to me.
This is a workplace.
Influencers are not welcome here.
I'm not an influencer. I'm a celebrity.
They are the same.
Don't be too arrogant,
or I'll ask my father not to vote for you.
I'm so scared.
You!
Security.
Don't call security.
Don't do that.
Security.
Get this madman away from me.
How dare you say that!
Tang Pingping.
-Dad.
-Pingping.
You're looking for me?
-I...
-You're in the wrong place.
I was just there.
Fangning, you are here too.
Look at my silly girl.
She can't even remember where my office is.
Let's go.
I won't go.
I want her to apologize to me.
She broke my arm.
It really hurt!
Apologize for what?
Didn't you just twist it?
It's alright.
No.
Dad.
Don't vote for her.
Okay, okay.
I won't. I won't.
Fangning, don't worry.
I'll definitely vote for you
at the next board meeting.
-Thank you, Uncle Tang.
-What did you say?
You!
-It hurts.
-Dad!
It hurts!
Mister, sit over there.
It hurts.
-Sit down first.
-Dad.
Come here.
-It hurts.
-Sit down first.
Mister,
are you feeling the pain in the upper chest
or the lower end?
Do you feel stuffy or tight?
I... I...
I didn't sleep well.
I'm afraid of getting angry.
Uncle Tang, drink some water.
-Thank you.
-It's okay.
Doctor,
how is my father?
You'd better take him to the hospital
as soon as possible
to do some detailed examination
in thoracic surgery
and internal medicine department.
So, you can know what's going on.
It hurts. It hurts.
Which department are you from?
I'm from the General Surgery Department.
General Surgery Department?
Then,
when are you usually at the hospital?
Dr. Ling,
I think
you can help with nothing here.
You can leave.
Mister,
remember to go to the hospital for a check-up.
Thanks.
Lu Fangning.
You brought such a
handsome guy here.
Do you have any agenda?
I'm asking you.
Why don't you come with us tonight?
I told you many times.
I'm not going.
Just go with me.
And it's me
who'll pay for it.
It's just a blind date.
I'm not going.
Okay.
What are you doing?
What are you doing with my food?
You don't eat the meat every time.
And, I don't have enough to eat.
It's not a big deal for me to eat some.
But, I have to eat it too.
But,
it's reasonable that nobody can get you
the most handsome guy of
General Surgery Department
merely through a blind date.
Especially, you're the most handsome guy
who is dedicated
to the medical cause.
Am I right?
Tell me something about it.
The lady behind the curtain...
Who is she? Why don't I know her?
She shouldn't be from our department.
Because I don't even know her.
And,
she shouldn't be a patient's next-of-kin.
You're not a person who does such a thing.
Stop it! Just eat.
Did anything happen at home?
I haven't seen the look
for a long time.
There's something wrong indeed.
It's the same bank account number, right?
What are you doing?
I'll send you the money.
The most probable cause to your problem
is money.
You don't have to do that.
A huge amount?
More than your mortgage.
And, you're still in the mood to eat?
You...
Food is essential.
I don't want to waste it.
So what are you going to do?
I've already figured it out,
although
it's a little tricky.
Come on.
Let me send you some.
Or what if
you disappear someday.
If you, the most handsome guy
in the hospital, disappear,
where can I find you?
Why do you talk so much?
Don't talk nonsense and just eat.
You should know
to never trust repeated criminals.
Look at you.
What's the use of being so handsome?
It will be nice if a female boss
marries you one day.
Gao Erfan,
what do you think of my negotiation skills?
How is it?
There is no contract that you can't win.
Did my skill deteriorate?
You mean
yesterday's negotiations with
representatives of Yi Rui?
I think your performance
is perfect.
And all the terms
correspond to our goal.
I don't think there's any problem.
Then, who has a problem?
Ling Rui?
Dr. Ling?
What's wrong with him?
I offered to marry him
by raising the condition from
two million to four million.
But, he didn't want to accept it.
Why?
Well.
Say it.
In my humble opinion, Ms. Lu...
You were negotiating a marriage,
not a business.
Imagine it.
If a man
tells you
how much money
he can give you
and how can both of you
make a win-win situation
when he's about to marry you,
will you feel happy?
I will.
Why not?
Bravo.
Then I...
Say it.
Ms. Lu,
my holiday and bonus for next month...
Say it.
Anything but money.
How and what to negotiate?
Sure enough, about true feelings.
Show him your true feelings
and enthusiasm.
We won't go to the company.
How about my bonus?
Where are you going after work?
I have something else
and I have work to do
afterward.
What can you have?
You are going home to work?
Come on.
Where are you going?
Dr. Ling.
Hello.
You...
I'm Tang Ping.
Ping is the...
An apple (Ping Guo) a day.
I remember.
Ms. Tang,
what can I do for you?
After you left,
I thought
I have a lot
to say to you.
Then...
You two go on. I'll go first.
Okay.
Ms. Tang,
you're not my patient.
If you're in need,
you can go to
the medical management department,
on the fifth floor of the East area.
We're leaving.
Dr. Ling.
No.
See.
I made this for you myself.
I'm giving it to you.
Thanks a lot.
Well...
Actually, it's not that good.
Bribery is
against the rules everywhere, right?
It's not for you.
We have work to do. We'll leave first.
Dr. Ling,
can't we just
be friends?
I'm afraid not.
Don't go.
Peng Bo, let's go.
Dr. Ling.
Lu Fangning, why are you here?
Such a coincidence!
You are not friends, are you?
Let me introduce her to you.
This is Tang Ping.
The ordinary Ping.
It's obviously the Ping
who likes him at first sight.
Nobody knows what you're saying.
You!
It's just the pretty Ping.
The ordinary Ping!
And, this is my man, Ling Rui.
What?
-I'm not. -That's impossible.
He... I like him first.
Then, why don't you build a castle
for him?
Tang Ping.
How dare you
snatch my "future husband"?
What can you do about it
even he's your "father"?
Tang Pingping.
You're really getting bolder and bolder.
That's who I am.
Dare you touch me again?
-Okay!
-Again?
Okay!
-Hey, ladies.
-Okay!
-Ladies...
Ladies, we're at the hospital.
Shut up!
Stop acting.
He's neither stupid nor blind.
He can see through your acting skills.
Dr. Ling.
Today, I am here
to talk about
the unfinished topic
last time.
This is for you.
Come with me.
Did you hear that?
He asked me to go with him.
Don't be arrogant!
Come back.
This patient...
How about
I'll take you to
the medical management department
or the Orthopedics Department?
No, thank you.
Get out of my way.
Please, marry me.
Ms. Lu.
I think
I've made it very clear before.
You can ask me some
normal questions now.
For example, why did I choose you?
Never mind. You don't have to talk.
Let me tell you.
We met three times before.
You have a good personality,
body, and vigor.
I'm very satisfied with...
I'm moved.
Ling Rui.
I'm being serious.
The heart is on the left.
Ms. Lu.
I still want to discuss my repayment plan
with you.
Are you serious?
This isn't
a simple thing.
I can't believe there's someone
who takes the initiative
to pay back money these days.
Why?
Your dignity?
Actually, you don't have to do this.
In the matter of gender equality,
we can try
to materialize it.
I know you don't have much savings.
All of your money
has been donated to charity
in various names
since you started working.
But, it doesn't matter.
I allow you to use me,
in the name of Lu Fangning's husband.
Thus, we can help more people
to get more the help they need.
I know you are going to Germany.
-We can...
-Ms. Lu.
I do want
to help more people
and realize
my dream.
But I won't
break my rules for this.
Marriage is not a business.
There's no shortcut to anything.
Marriage is originally the reorganization of
two families.
This isn't a shortcut at all.
This is for the better.
You should render great love in your heart.
You should render
the spirit of sacrifice and dedication.
So I have to sacrifice my marriage?
To you?
Definitely.
Thank you for helping my family.
Also, please.
Stop mentioning it again
in the future.
I'll pay you back as soon as possible.
And,
Ms. Lu,
please don't tell
my family about this.
I don't want them to worry.
This flower
can't be put in the ward.
Ms. Lu, please take it back.
Thanks.
Sure enough, it's fragile
and useless.
Just a waste of money.
Ms. Lu.
Do you want to call Lawyer Deng?
Lawyer?
Yeah.
It's natural
to let lawyers handle the debt collection.
Let me think about it again.
Go out.
So embarrassing.
Pingping.
Let dad tell you something.
Don't go to the company
when you're free.
Don't act perfunctorily!
If you go a few more times,
my heart, liver, and my lungs
can't stand that anymore.
Dad, you're not that weak.
What's the matter?
What did you just say?
I said
my heart, liver, and my lungs... What's wrong?
Dad,
you are ill.
No.
I'm just getting old
and feel a bit out of breath.
The great doctor
said before
that you were really ill.
I am fine.
I eat and sleep well.
There's nothing wrong with me.
You're ill. You have to go to the hospital.
I'm not ill. I'm not going to the hospital.
You are. You're going to the hospital.
I'm not ill.
No. Let's go to the hospital.
Just go. You're ill.
There isn't much problem.
Just go home and have a good rest.
Okay. Thank you, doctor.
Dad, come in.
Dr. Ling.
Hello.
You...
Didn't you ask my dad to see a doctor
last time?
So, I brought him here.
Have a seat.
But this is the General Surgery Department.
You're so skillful.
Of course, my father trusts you.
Isn't that, dad?
Yes.
Alright.
I'll help mister to make an appointment
for some examinations.
And we'll know which department to go to
after the test results come out.
Okay. Thank you, Dr. Ling.
You're welcome.
Dr. Ling.
I brought you
coffee.
I can't take this. Thanks.
It's just a cup of coffee.
This is my sincere thought.
Can't you even accept it?
You can leave it here.
Thanks.
Okay.
Not me,
but Tang Ping?
Gao Erfan, get in here.
Ms. Lu.
Call Lawyer Deng.
Now.
[Reciprocal Account Name: Peng Bo]
Don't come in.
If you dare to come in,
you are trespassing.
Stop.
I will tell the TV station to expose you.
Yea.
You... Don't move.
If you dare touch me,
I'll sue you for sexual harassment.
I have filmed it.
What's the matter?
Mr. Ling Rui, right?
Yes, I am.
Hello, Mr. Ling Rui.
I'm entrusted by my client
to collect
Miss Ling Yazhi's
debts of four million yuan.
Given her financial situation,
we think it is necessary
to know about her family's repayment ability.
If it's determined that
she is incapable of repaying,
we'll bring up a reasonable lawsuit
shortly.
What?
What... Four million yuan?
What's going on?
Ling Yazhi, you...
Where's your client?
My client is downstairs.
You have her business card.
You should know what to do.
What's going on?
Lu Fangning.
Yes?
Do you want to punch me?
Ling Rui.
Usually,
I don't give
anybody a second chance.
But, I can make an exception
for you.
No.
This confirmed
my decision to reject you.
You only want to achieve your goal
and impose your will on others.
You keep saying that you want to get married.
But do you know the feeling of
love and being loved?
Do you know
the importance of family to a person?
You only think about yourself.
But you disregard
other's feelings and wishes.
If you care,
you won't easily
hurt other people's families.
You're a debtor.
You've no right to judge me.
Lu Fangning,
you are a selfish and
childish person.
Fangning,
will you stop
being childish?
Enjoy your food.
Let's eat.
A great day begins in the morning.
I got up early in the morning
to prepare this.
But all of you don't even appreciate it.
Even you're worried,
you have to eat.
Am I right?
Mom!
You always say
people live on meals.
I promise you, okay?
If it doesn't work out in the end,
I will ask you for help.
I was waiting for you to say this.
I've thought it through.
I... I have to find another house.
Or we'll have no space
for these things
if this house is mortgaged,
am I right?
Zhang Aidi has a house.
It seems that I have to
talk to this woman again.
I did some math.
I can help gather a little
by withdrawing the investment money.
Ling Rui can earn it back
for me.
Am I right, Ling Rui?
Sure enough.
All right, let's eat.
-Let's eat.
-Enjoy.
Let's eat.
Aunt,
there are the freshly made fried dough sticks.
Try it.
-Okay.
-This is freshly made.
The dumpling looks tasty too.
I'll start with this.
It's delicious!
Is it delicious?
Yes.
-Nice?
-Ouch.
-Mom, why are you pinching me?
-Does it hurt?
-Harder!
-It hurts!
-It should hurt.
It hurts!
Let him remember this.
I tell you.
He should tell us
whenever he's in trouble.
If you dare lie to me again,
I'll force you to marry
the cousin's daughter of
the aunt who lives next door to Zhang Aidi.
Believe it or not?
I believe!
-Do you? Do you?
-I do!
-Stop pinching.
-Does it hurt?
It really hurts!
Aunt Wang's
uncle's daughter?
Another aunt's daughter
is okay too.
Okay?
I was wrong.
What about me?
It was my fault.
Why didn't you scold me?
You can beat me too.
Nice try.
Do you know
what's the worst punishment?
It's that you obviously made a mistake,
but you don't get punished, right?
How hard it is for you!
Think about it.
Yes.
That's the greatest pain
in the world.
Let's eat.
Mom, eat the bamboo shoot.
Delicious.
You just ignore me. I'll eat by myself.
Come.
Little aunt, eat this.
It's delicious!
The shrimp dumplings are made very well today.
Right?
Mr. Yang.
Ms. Lu.
It's been a while.
Have a seat.
What would you like to drink?
Two hot lattes.
Okay, just a moment, please.
Stop touching your "glib tongue".
Can you look at the waiter and talk?
Didn't anyone teach you manners?
I don't want to drink a latte.
I've been looking for a chance
to talk with Ms. Lu.
What for?
Ms. Lu,
you run Deer Sing Group so well.
But a woman like you
may not truly understand about
how to run a business.
Ling Rui wouldn't say such stupid things.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Oh, no!
I'm starting to hallucinate.
Professor,
we've been in the hospital all-day.
But you asked me to come here after work.
Is there anything you want to say to me?
You should be the one
who has something to say to me, right?
Peng Bo told you?
You should have told me first,
not him.
He barely has spare money.
Don't worry.
About money,
I'm not very good at it,
but
my wife manages it well.
Take it.
Thank you, sir.
But I can handle this
by myself.
You're still so stubborn.
I knew it would be like this.
I...
I'm just trying to carry out my duty.
I know.
You can deal with everything.
Okay.
Let's get down to business.
How is
the German Institute going?
A new subject
has already been declared.
Then, there can be no further delay.
Pancreatic cancer has always been
a difficult problem to overcome
for General Surgery Department.
Your father's illness
is also the root of your medical study.
Over the years,
you always want to
do research there.
Don't be distracted by other things.
Ms. Lu.
Is there anything
you want to say to me?
Ms. Lu.
I came here because
I hope that you and Director Yang
can vote for me
at the board meeting.
I knew it.
What can I get in return?
I can assure you
after Infinity passed the voting,
the company's profit
will at least double in the next year.
Don't tell me these baseless things.
No one can tell what will happen next year.
How about this?
I'll sign a contract with you in private.
If I can't achieve
our goals,
I can give you
a share of my equity.
Fangning.
You know what I want.
You know that.
I don't know.
I have a proposal
that satisfies both parties.
I've no idea.
Would you like to hear it?
Well, maybe I can help you.
Go to my penthouse
and I'll tell you in detail.
By the way,
did you put the drugs on the nightstand?
You should know
I made an appointment with Lu Fangning,
right here at the penthouse.
Yes.
I'll use it later.
I'll grab a bottle of wine before I go up.
And let her have a "taste".
Okay.
Fangning,
I rent
this room all year round.
How's the environment?
Do you like it?
Pretty good.
Come, drink some water.
Thanks.
By the way,
Mr. Yang, the idea you said
that can satisfy both parties,
what is it?
We're not rushing.
Since we're here,
let's talk about something else.
Drink some water first.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Ms. Lu.
There's an appointment with...
I'm in a meeting.
I know. I will be there.
Send me the exact time
and place.
Okay, don't worry.
I'm hanging up.
Ms. Lu is really busy.
Indeed.
So, let's make a long story short.
Mr. Yang, can you tell me
the proposal now?
Let's get married.
Get... Get married?
Don't you have a wife?
It doesn't matter.
As long as you agree,
I can divorce her.
But...
Fangning, don't hesitate.
I know your dad
always forces you to go on blind dates
and wants you to give birth to a child.
Instead of marrying a person
you don't like,
you should marry me.
We can cooperate and run the business well.
Think about it.
Your current shares in Deer Sing
and the Yang family's share
can bring LM Deer Sing Group
a bright future that is under our control.
Forget about Infinity.
We can create ten of them,
and still have a smooth sail.
But,
there are no feelings between us.
Marriage is not necessarily
based on feelings.
You get what you want,
and I get what I want.
Isn't that quite good?
Let's work together.
Ms. Lu.