[English subtitles are available]
[Begin Again]
[Episode 22]
General Assistant Gao,
this is the purchase record you want.
I'm so sorry that
we made you come yourself.
No worries. It's my duty.
[LM Deer Sing Group, Product Department]
[LM Deer Sing Home Furnishing Store's Purchase Record]
How is your preparation?
Morning.
Let me see
if I'm dreaming now.
Dreaming?
You should pinch yourself.
If I pinch myself too hard,
won't you feel bad?
Perhaps
you can do this.
Are you dreaming?
There're no feelings.
One more time.
I want to stay in the bed with you.
That's so nice.
I want to be like this, too.
Cai Siyu and the team
are coming today, right?
Let's not bother them.
I'll ask them to go back.
I'm the boss anyway.
It seems that Ms. Lu
wants to be a foolish ruler.
Then you praise me.
What to praise you?
Praise me
for being extremely beautiful.
Extremely beautiful.
Chic and imposing.
Little White Dragon in the Waves.
The White Queen in the Golden Forest.
Little White Dragon.
-White Queen.
-Little White Dragon.
White Queen.
Little White Dragon.
You turn it again.
It looks good.
It's beautiful.
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
Ms. Lu.
Be cautious.
Be careful.
Ms. Lu.
You're dressed to the nines today.
How's the preparation?
Perfect.
Come take a look.
Later on, we'll...
Enough said.
Don't talk to me.
Talk to Ling Rui.
I'll go there first.
Cai Siyu,
come over.
This time around,
I want to praise you particularly.
Before I came,
I thought in the first place that
these sets of clothes
you prepared
weren't quite suitable for me.
But
it turns out that
they're both decent, elegant,
and make me look very friendly.
It's good that you're satisfied with them.
You have to look beautiful.
How have you been during these two days?
It's been so-so.
What do you mean?
What's wrong?
You look a bit down in the dumps.
You and Simon...
Because of the recorder?
Is it because of the recorder?
Ms. Lu.
Regarding this matter,
I haven't apologized to you yet.
If it wasn't because of my recorder,
there won't be so many troubles.
Why do you have to apologize to me?
Those are essential facts.
I dare to take responsibility for what I've done.
It's not a big deal.
Don't be like this anymore.
Show me a happy face.
How about
I give you a pay raise afterward?
And double bonus.
Thank you, Ms. Lu.
Why did you think
that I'm suitable
for that kind of mini skirt for a lady?
You look good in whatever type of costume.
Today's light
will probably make them look good.
Why are your hands so cold?
Are you nervous?
I've never taken part in this kind of photoshoot before.
It's my first time,
so I'm feeling a bit nervous.
It's actually my first time, too.
But
I have you here,
so I'm not nervous.
Great.
Then shall we start?
♫ I have a secret about you ♫
♫ It's like entering a game, recalling the warm memories ♫
♫ There's you and my hope for the future ♫
♫ There's no distance between you and I ♫
♫ You won't forget if you're aware of it ♫
♫ It's full of happiness in my eyes ♫
♫ Despite being treated unfairly, with you, I'll have the strength ♫
♫ This is the meaning of getting used to it ♫
♫ I'm used to living with you ♫
Change the angle.
Okay.
♫ I don't really want much at all ♫
♫ As long as you're willing to listen to me nagging ♫
Women...
What is it?
They really are scary creatures.
Look at Ms. Lu.
She wasn't like this before.
After she's fallen in love...
Okay.
Thank you for the hard work.
-Thank you for the hard work.
-Thank you.
It's my duty.
-Are you tired?
Are you tired?
I'm not tired.
How about you?
I'll no longer be tired after you've kissed me.
So many people here are watching.
I pay for their salary.
It's okay to let them gossip.
Come and kiss.
A hug will do.
It's not exactly what I want.
Our work here...
Let's go back for the exact one.
What can I do here?
Enough said.
Work is not easy for me, too.
I can't stand it anymore.
Look at them.
♫ You won't forget if you're aware of it ♫
♫ It's full of happiness in my eyes ♫
Ms. Lu, you have a call.
Gao Erfan?
Hello.
Okay.
I got it now.
What happened?
There was a quality inspection.
The products of a brand in LM Deer Sing Store
were found defective.
This time around
is just a routine inspection.
They didn't regard LM Deer Sing Group
as a typical one.
We've already contacted
the merchant
to see how to deal with it.
Ms. Lu
has been notified.
She'll go directly to the store.
You might bump into her
in the store.
How's the situation?
This is the inspection report at the time of purchase.
Leqi has entered LM Deer Sing Store
for three years.
Product quality
has never been a problem.
The procedures are also very complete.
Before entering the store,
the company had also conducted random inspections,
and no problem was found.
How about Leqi's side?
We've already contacted them.
They said there was no problem with the products.
I guessed they would say so.
We can only know the actual outcome
after checking.
Gao Erfan,
you sorted all the people
who had dealt with
this batch of products before.
There must be a detailed review of all the procedures
to identify
the exact problem.
Also,
we'll announce publicly that
Lu Ming will treat
this matter seriously
and give the public an explanation.
Tonight
might be a bit hard for us.
We need to check
all the products in the store again
to make sure that
there won't be another Leqi.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I've told you that
you don't have to come with me.
I'm in a hurry.
I can't return home
in awhile.
I'm fine.
It's good that you can handle it.
I also have to go back to the hospital first.
Be careful.
Thank you for your hard work, Simon.
I'm leaving.
Peng Bo.
Is everything okay in the wards during these few days?
You're back.
Nothing happened.
[To Ling Rui]
Are you exhausted
after going back this time?
When is the express delivery?
This morning. What happened?
[Interview notice]
Your expression...
What is this?
Ling Rui.
You've received it, right?
I heard that this time around,
you should be on the list.
Professor.
Great.
That's great.
This is the notification letter sent
by the Pancreas Institute
in Germany?
My goodness, Ling Rui.
Finally, you're going to succeed.
This fellow...
What kind of expression is this?
This is something to be happy about.
Why didn't you even smile?
Of course I'm happy.
When will you
join the orientation?
They asked me
to attend an interview in Germany in a week.
Why do you need to go for an interview
when you've received the notification letter?
You know nothing.
The person in charge of the project
which Ling Rui will join this time around
will be his mentor in the future.
Of course he needs to visit him.
Don't worry.
It's just part of the procedure.
There won't be any problems.
Besides conducting research normally,
Professor Cliff
is just a simple-minded person.
He's one with a kind personality.
When are you leaving?
Do you need to apply for leave?
I can sign now.
You can go now.
Professor Luo.
It's a week later
for the interview.
He's been waiting for so long.
I hope that he can go right away.
Right now.
Immediately.
Professor.
He has a family.
No matter what,
he needs to inform his family.
Moreover, he'll leave for three years.
How can he leave now?
It'll delay his plan of getting a baby.
Gosh.
Don't bother him
at this time, okay?
This is really a big deal.
Hello, it's me.
How's the preparation
for the next action?
Okay.
Always get ready.
Listen to my signal.
Dr. Ling.
Ms. Lu is inside.
You can go in.
Okay, thank you.
Hello, this is the general manager's office.
You're here.
Have you had your meal?
Not yet.
Here's the food delivered to you by me.
Let me answer it.
What's it again?
Ms. Lu.
Two brands
wanted to withdraw from our store.
Hold them up for now.
Ask them to hold their horses.
Okay.
What's the situation now?
I can still handle it.
How about you?
You went to work today.
Did any young nurse harass you?
I'm always cold.
I didn't give a smile at all.
Really?
How is it like? Show me.
Your eyes are still smiling.
Change to another look.
That's more like it.
You're so good.
Thank you.
Fangning.
I have something to tell you.
What happened?
Today, I received...
Oh, I'm doomed.
I asked them to go and check the store,
but I forgot to tell them
that the newly entered brands
also need to be checked.
It'll be miserable if there's a mistake again.
I have to go to the store.
Did you just say
that you want to
tell me something?
There's nothing.
You go ahead.
I'll tell you again
when you've done your stuff.
Then I'll make a move now.
Wait for me.
Leave me some.
I'm leaving.
Bye-bye!
I'm sorry.
There were even more things to settle when I reached the store.
Why are you still here?
Were you asleep?
I'm really sorry.
I'll still have to be here
and wait for updates from the store.
I can't go back yet.
You go back first.
You still have to go to work
in the hospital tomorrow.
How can you work without energy?
Listen to me. Hurry up and go back now.
Okay then.
The food is cold.
Remember to let Gao Erfan warm it up.
Rest assured.
Go now.
Come back early then.
I'll leave first.
Go to bed early.
Wait for me to go home.
I'm leaving.
[Interview notice]
Ling Rui.
You're back.
You worked all night again.
What can I say?
I've made breakfast, do you want some?
Wah.
You're so nice today
that you made me wonton.
Then you go and rest only after eating.
I'm sorry.
I said yesterday
that I'd be back soon.
It's fine.
I know that you have a hard time at work.
How is it going?
The company's issue.
How did it go?
Well...
It's been alleviated temporarily.
It should be fine later on.
That's good.
By the way,
what did you want
to tell me last night?
We'll talk later while eating.
Hello.
Hello, Ms. Lu.
Hurry up and watch the news.
Something happened.
[Following the reveal of the problem]
[with Leqi in LM Deer Sing Home Furnishing Store]
[yesterday,]
[the media has received more]
[complaints and reports from consumers again.]
[Reporters went to LM Deer Sing Store]
[for secret inquiries.]
[LM Deer Sing Group is being complained again, the eco-home's concept was questioned]
[The problem of data fraud]
[was also found]
[with Hanping Home Furnishing's store.]
[LM Deer Sing Store's]
[management of the brands entered]
[is greatly questioned.]
[The so-called eco-friendly furniture]
[has become]
[a fake selling point.]
Why has something happened again?
The stock won't fall again, right?
Surely not.
Fangning is so capable.
There won't be a problem.
Nothing will happen.
Accidents happened twice in a row.
There must be someone behind all of these.
Let Fangning look into them.
You think too much.
They're not that serious.
Get me a glass of water.
Okay.
LM Deer Sing Store's
management of the brands entered
is greatly questioned.
I can guarantee you
that other brands in LM Deer Sing Store
absolutely conform to the
country's inspection standards.
And for these two brands,
I'll hold them accountable.
Don't worry about this.
Hello.
Don't worry.
We'll take care of it, okay?
Lu Yiyao.
Tell me.
Does Lu Fangning now
understand the situation?
Two bad news were out
one after another
in just two days.
The company's stock
has fallen terribly now.
Please give me a reasonable explanation.
Can you propose
a feasible solution?
If you can't, I'll convene
a board meeting at once.
Okay, I'm heading there now.
Lu Yiyao. You...
These two factories
had problems consecutively,
which were revealed swiftly,
causing the public
to have a bad impression on LM Deer Sing.
Moreover, many brands
have terminated their cooperation with LM Deer Sing Group one after another now.
Today's stock price reached a limit down.
If things don't get better,
the shareholders
will definitely create chaos first.
This matter was exposed too quickly
with too many coincidences.
I've asked someone to look into it,
but it takes time.
The most important thing now
is to prevent the news from spreading like wildfire.
I'll personally go to Leqi
and Hanping's factories.
It's indeed better
for the manufacturers to give an explanation.
I'll go with you then.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Director.
Is sister-in-law okay?
When I took the subway this morning,
I heard from the news,
they were all talking
about her company's issue.
It's a big mess.
Yes.
Go away.
There's nothing to gossip about. Go away.
I'm concerned about the director now.
Well,
you go over there.
I have something to talk to him about.
Just go over there.
Regarding your studies in Germany,
you haven't told her, right?
You said an affirmative sentence.
Based on what I understand about you,
you'll never say at this time.
Bro, can you say something?
You've already said an affirmative sentence.
What do you want me to answer?
You always bottle things up.
When are you going to tell her?
The interview will start in two days.
Okay.
What are you thinking?
Have you booked the flight ticket?
Have you got in touch with Germany's side?
Yes, this interview is only part of a procedure.
But you don't even go through the procedure.
Doesn't that mean you're giving up?
I think Lu Fangning is quite capable.
It's no use for you to worry here.
Since you have the time,
you should think
about your future.
Oh my goodness, bro!
I...
I'm so worried about you.
Just eat,
it's all yours.
[Leqi]
Ms. Lu,
I really don't know
where the problem lies.
We've always kept our feet on the ground
while doing our jobs.
We've also received
a lot of returned orders now.
It's also not a small loss.
Now is not the time to talk about this.
The most important thing is to figure out the solution.
What say you?
I have a solution here.
That's to recall all the products
in the same batch.
As long as the customers have inquiries,
we'll refund them,
no matter if they think
the product is defective or not.
I've allocated all my funds
for the expansion of the factory
and the import of new equipment.
Aren't you causing difficulty for me now?
That's the only solution for now
which can regain
the customers' trust towards us in their minds.
It's worth it in the long run.
For Hanping's side,
I'll also go
and discuss it with them.
Ms. Lu,
I know that your solution
is also good for us.
But
Hanping is the same as us.
We're all emerging companies.
If you want us to utilize the cash flow
for the refunds,
my whole factory's operations
can only be discontinued.
Look.
I'm raising so many people.
If we stop production,
my business
will be considered going bankrupt.
Ling Rui.
I got you.
What brought you over?
How did you know that I'm here?
I went to the company and couldn't find you.
I guessed you would be here.
Is it difficult to solve
LM Deer Sing Group's crisis?
In fact, it's not impossible to solve it.
It should be all right for Lu Ming
to get through this crisis.
It's just that those two factories
may no longer
be revived.
Do you think
if I should lend them a helping hand?
If you happen to save them,
will you encounter any difficulty?
Those two factories
hire hundreds of employees.
I thought
that you surely would ask me
to help them.
I'm not that holy.
The Savior needs to save himself first.
Moreover,
LM Deer Sing Group's survival
is also related to many people's lives.
You're running a business.
The concepts of conscience,
original intention,
and compassion
can only be practiced
with the premise that the company can survive.
Besides,
if you have a way to protect yourself,
you don't need to think about
the temporary gains nor losses.
After all,
it'd be a good deed
if you can help others.
Okay.
[Yu Shiyi, waiting for the call to be answered]
Hello, ex-boyfriend.
Why did you suddenly think of contacting me?
I have something to ask for your help with.
I knew it.
If you don't have
something serious,
you won't contact me.
But if I remember correctly,
shouldn't you appear
at the institute six days later?
Are you asking me
to help you pack your luggage
by looking for me at this hour?
Can you please contact
Professor Cliff for me?
I want to change the interview time,
or we can
schedule a video call first.
I have something to handle here for now.
I mightn't be able to go there right away.
You're really troublesome.
But I can't guarantee
that I'll succeed.
You know Germans.
Let me try first.
Thank you.
Cut the
civilities out.
I'm hanging up.
Bye-bye.
[LM Deer Sing Group]
You ask me to come over.
Is there any solution?
I'm thinking to let LM Deer Sing Group take
all the responsibilities for now.
What do you mean?
Before the issue
gets worse,
I want LM Deer Sing Group
to bear all the losses in advance.
To meet all the needs of customers,
including returns, refunds, and even compensation.
For the products' environmental issues,
the direct responsible parties
are their brand manufacturers.
After all,
LM Deer Sing Store is just
a sales platform for these brands.
We shouldn't take all the responsibilities.
Of course I know.
I'll also hold those
manufacturers accountable for these.
But the point
is they totally don't have
the ability
to afford all the compensation.
There's only a dead end for them.
Moreover, the key to the problem
is to appease public opinion
by meeting customers' needs.
What I worry about is that if we do so,
we'll need to contribute a lot of funds.
That's too risky.
Is there any better way?
Let's issue a statement publicly
that we'll strictly check for the parties responsible for these.
As long as we dare to face the problem,
LM Deer Sing Group's reputation will soon be rebuilt.
How long is required?
It's feasible.
But you need enough
funds to support the effort.
Also, it's not that
you can execute it
after Simon and I
have agreed.
What about the board?
Have you thought about it?
Of course I know that
there's a huge risk for this.
But LM Deer Sing Group's credibility
must be rebuilt immediately.
I've asked Gao Erfan to contact
all the investors
who approached us before.
I'll also filter out those investors
who are competent enough
and are willing to help us as soon as possible.
I believe that we'll have a bargaining chip
in front of the board.
For my side,
there're also a few trustworthy
investors who are close with me.
I can convince them.
Okay.
I'll go and ask
those investors
to see if they're still interested.
According to the current
situation of our store,
we must filter out
the most suitable
investor within two days.
Little bear,
thank you for eating with me.
Come on.
I toast you.
Bottoms up.
Boss must be so worried
that her hair is even falling out now.
By thinking so,
we ordinary people
still live a more comfortable life.
Come on.
Let's clink first.
Okay.
In fact, I asked you out today
is because our...
Look at you.
You talk about the work from the beginning
when you invited me out for a meal?
Fine. Then
I toast you again.
I get drunk easily.
You may drink more.
Okay, I'll drink it.
Who is this woman?
Both of them are single.
What does it mean that they're eating together at night?
It's a difficult period of time for LM Deer Sing Group now.
I can't believe that he still has time
to dine with a woman.
Yiyao.
It's actually okay that LM Deer Sing Group can't hold on,
or
you can come to my company.
Although your last name is Lu,
this world shows us that
those long united shall be divided.
Why do you care so much?
How come you still touch him?
Lu Yiyao.
Don't you stay away from strangers?
Why did you change your mind now?
Come on.
Have a drink.
Okay.
Then I represent LM Deer Sing Group
to toast you again.
Cai...
Who is this?
This is LM Deer Sing Group's employee,
Miss Cai Siyu.
This is Ms. Xu.
We're here
to talk about the investment in LM Deer Sing Group.
Ms. Xu.
Well...
This is our first time meeting,
I'll toast you first.
Well.
Ms. Xu,
I'm sorry that
I was reckless just now.
I'll punish myself for a shot.
Well,
Director Lu
usually doesn't drink a lot.
I'm still quite okay with it.
I'll toast you on behalf of Director Lu.
What are you doing?
Ms. Xu,
I'm also an employee of LM Deer Sing Group.
LM Deer Sing Group has encountered such a huge crisis,
I...
On behalf of my colleagues,
I toast you,
hoping that you
can help us.
That's enough.
It's okay, Director Lu.
I'm still okay.
I'll treat you
well today.
If this is the case...
Waiter,
get us ten more bottles.
That's enough.
Let me drink it.
Director Lu, you can't drink too much.
I'll drink it.
Don't drink anymore, okay?
That's enough, don't drink anymore.
I'll drink it.
I'm still okay.
Don't drink it.
Give it to me.
Don't drink anymore.
That's enough.
She's gone.
Why did you come here again?
You were creating chaos here.
What are you talking about?
I did it for you.
If I didn't see you,
you may be with that Ms. Xu...
Right?
You scumbag don't appreciate it.
I just wanted to help you.
I was just here to talk about...
Just to have a talk?
Okay, if you want to have a talk, then drink it.
Drink it.
Okay, I'll drink it.
Let's see what will happen if I don't help you. Drink it.
Aren't you capable of drinking a lot?
Then you should drink it, too.
Okay, I'll drink it.
Come on.
Don't stop. Continue.
♫ The rose petals have a potent fragrance ♫
♫ I don't mind walking on the streets alone ♫
♫ The movies are always full of disappointment and farewells ♫
♫ But who will watch them with me ♫
♫ Slowly, we get closer ♫
♫ I like you ♫
♫ Only you ♫
♫ You're my one and only ♫
♫ Tonight, I'll let my mind wander ♫
Why are you swaying?
I drank too much.
We...
Where are we going?
Go to bed.
Go to bed?
Where to sleep?
Go there.
Go there to sleep.
♫ I want to travel to Paris and Tokyo, and eat chocolate by the sea ♫
♫ As long as I'm with you ♫
♫ We can lie on the beach and count the stars ♫