[English subtitles are available]
[Begin Again]
[Episode 28]
My waist...
What is your next plan?
You look like you're about to die.
Old man, stop following me.
Go back and rest.
Who says I'm about to die?
You can't keep up with us youngsters' pace.
Cai Siyu.
I'll tell you again.
I am not old.
If you don't believe me, try me.
My next activity
is not for you.
What activity is not suitable for me?
Dad.
Love you!
Hey, Siyu.
Hey, Tang Ping.
Let's come out and eat.
Hello?
Ling Rui knows about Youyou's existence.
Ling Rui knows about Youyou's existence?
Who?
Youyou?
Why does it sound like a child's name?
Fangning.
Fangning...
Get out of the way.
Did you come back
together with Dr. Ling's son?
You kept this from him for six years?
Yeah...
You're like the ex-wife who's back with their kid to look for trouble.
Lu Fangning...
You're more dramatic than I thought.
Cai Siyu.
Hey, Fangning...
Who...
You go.
Go!
Fangning.
Step aside.
Are you okay?
You have to take good care of your back.
Did you have a baby with another man
while you were abroad?
You're awesome!
Is he mixed?
Mixed-race kids are so pretty!
Another man?
Yeah.
Or else, why did you
keep it from Dr. Ling?
Do you think I'm stupid?
It's not that I think that you're stupid,
Tang Pingping, you are stupid.
What did I do wrong?
Pingping.
Come here.
Move aside.
Fangning, I know
you have your reasons.
You had no choice but to run away, divorce,
and keep everything from Dr. Ling, am I right?
Thank you, Uncle Tang.
Fangning.
How are you doing? How's your health?
Do you want me to introduce you
to a better doctor?
It's alright.
This too shall pass.
How much does it cost to see a doctor? I'll pay for you.
I can at least help with
this kind of small matter.
Fangning, what's wrong with you?
To think that
your Uncle Lu
only has this one daughter...
And now, she's...
My heart really...
Lu Fangning...
Don't tell me you're terminally ill?
Are you dying?
-Dad, please save her!
-Shut up!
What terminal illness?
Stop talking nonsense!
Fangning.
I know that you're a stubborn person.
If it wasn't for this,
you wouldn't have disappeared just like that.
Yes.
Dad.
But she even gave birth to a baby.
Can her body take it?
You're terminally ill?
Why did you
keep such a huge matter from us?
That's it. That's enough!
Enough!
Be quiet!
Youyou is sleeping in the room.
What if the kid hears all of this?
Fangning, you're at the wrong this time around.
It's not fair to
Ling Rui and Youyou.
Exactly. Are you stupid?
No, you're not stupid, you're just looking for trouble.
Yup.
You disappeared right after going bankrupt
and what else did you do?
Sacrificing for love silently.
What kind of old cliche is this?
Did you want to
chase a good husband like Dr. Ling away that much?
Exactly.
I always thought you were smarter than me.
Who knew you'd be like this?
Dad.
You can stop comparing us anymore.
We're of different levels.
Indeed you are.
Yup.
Fangning.
This matter
was a big blow to
Dr. Ling.
It's hard to make up
for the lost affection.
You're right.
Dr. Ling is such a good person.
How could you...
Why is it you again?
If you guys want to start
another round of attack,
it should begin from Simon.
Can't I cut the line?
If I knew you would abandon Dr. Ling,
you should have just given him to me.
To you?
Who are you glaring at?
You did this to yourself.
Yeah. You totally asked for this.
Where can you find
such a good husband like Dr. Ling?
Where can you find one?
And you kept
such a huge secret from us.
You kept it from us.
Do you even
see us as your good friends?
Enough, you two...
Why are you scolding my mom?
This... This child...
Baby, we were chatting.
We were just a bit loud.
They scolded you.
I heard them.
This is you and Dr. Ling's son?
So cute!
What a little angel!
Me first.
Me too, little angel.
Will you give auntie a kiss?
Pingping.
You should let me have
a cute grandson like this too.
I want him. I want him.
Enough.
Enough, you two.
[Youyou is our child?]
How old is he now?
Five years old.
[Why didn't you tell me?]
[I...]
[I just didn't want to]
[disturb your life.]
At night,
both of them were too tired to move.
But when Harry thought of Pooh
and their journey across the ocean,
there was a voice in his head
that was saying,
I shouldn't,
I can't.
But his heart made a decision.
Youyou.
If you can't sleep,
do you want to chat?
Mom is right.
If you can't sleep,
don't force yourself to.
Come here.
Then...
What should we chat about?
Come, sit properly. Let mommy ask you a question.
You...
Do you really want a dad?
Time is precious. Stop talking nonsense.
What if
dad doesn't want us?
I'm so cute.
Of course, dad would want me.
As for mom,
you'd barely make the cut.
Mom.
If he doesn't want you,
I don't want him either.
We can just
change a dad.
Oh my.
Why are you so hot?
How did I only notice it now? Youyou.
Do you feel sick?
Yes.
Let's go to the hospital.
Okay.
Come on.
Good boy. Come.
Come, give mommy a hug.
Hug mommy tight.
Good boy.
[Emergency]
Hello.
This is my ID.
Youyou, how are you feeling?
Feeling better?
Do you want to drink some water?
Youyou.
Hello.
Can I put you down for a while?
Let me make the payment.
Okay, I won't put you down.
Hello.
Sorry.
Youyou, you have to come down.
I need to take something.
Let me hold him.
You register first.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
He's having a fever.
All done.
Okay, thank you.
The clinic is over there. Let's go.
Next patient.
Dr. Ling.
-Hello, Dr. Ge.
-Hello.
The child has a fever.
Hi, little one.
Shall we take off
our masks together?
Okay.
Your relative's child?
He's pretty cute.
Little one,
do you feel weak?
Do you feel like your nose is runny?
When did he start
having the fever?
He only started
having a fever tonight.
But he actually
started coughing a little bit two days ago.
Oh.
He just came back
from overseas.
I was scared that he might not be used to it here,
so I took his temperature
every day.
-Please take a look.
-Let me have a look
I also noted down the medications
that he has taken in the past.
It's time to take your medicine.
Okay.
It's not a big problem.
He'll just need to stay in the hospital tonight for observation.
How did you know that
we...
Lu Yiyao called me,
saying Youyou was sick.
He had work.
It may be hard for you to take care of Youyou alone.
I'm really not a
very competent mother.
Youyou is very sensible.
You took good care of him.
By the way...
Youyou seemed to be just joking
when he called you 'dad' the other day.
After he gets better,
I will tell him
the true relationship between you two.
Sorry, Ling Rui.
He is asleep now.
I can handle him on my own.
You can get back to your work.
Okay.
Isn't my mom pretty
when she's quiet?
Can you carry me up?
Sure.
I've always known that
you were my dad.
You look a lot like my plushie.
So, besides hugging me,
you can also pinch me.
Mom really likes
to pinch my face.
I'm very cute.
Yup.
Dad.
Can you stay by my side?
I...
Just now, when the doctor asked
whether I'm your relative's child,
none of you denied it.
I felt so sad inside.
Actually, I really want dad too.
But I don't want to make mom sad.
I know mom misses you too.
You're such a good boy.
His temperature is normal.
He can go home now.
Dr. Ling,
your relative's child is so cute.
Thank you.
He's my son.
Well... Dr. Ling...
Your...
Your son is so cute.
I'll get back to work.
-Okay.
-Thank you so much.
Dad, I want a hug!
Sure.
Here's your hug.
Your hug feels much safer than my mom's.
[Breakfast with Tang Ping]
Do you love Miss Pingping?
Yes!
Is Miss Pingping beautiful?
Good. Three, two, one.
One more!
Another pose.
Now, the finger heart!
Okay. Really pretty.
All done. Let's start then.
Come.
You're welcome.
Miss Pingping.
Can I take a photo
with you alone?
Come.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
Thank you, Miss Pingping.
-We will always support you.
-Yup.
Let's do our best. Thank you.
The president said
we must have breakfast with you
because breakfast is cheap.
Then, we can
help you save money.
Having breakfast is pretty good.
It's just that
it's a bit hard to wake up for it.
Exactly. I couldn't wake up too.
It's all the president's fault
for coming up with this bad idea.
It's okay.
It's my treat today.
You guys enjoy the meal.
Have whatever you want.
Thank you, Miss Pingping!
Let's have a toast.
Let's raise our glasses and make a toast
to Miss Pingping!
-Okay?
-Yes!
Thank you, Miss Pingping.
Cheers!
Alright.
Delicious!
Really good.
By the way,
is 120 not here today?
I didn't see him.
-Didn't see him.
He's not here again?
Think about it. This president is the one
who comes up with all the ideas all the time.
But he's also the one
who's always absent.
He's absent because he's busy
with work again today.
Have you met the president before?
Ever since I joined the fan club,
I've never once met the president.
I don't even know if the president is a male or female.
I've never met the president either.
Do you think that
this president
is hiding a secret?
Is it because he looks really...
Don't say things like that.
It's not good to talk behind someone's back.
Okay.
Whether he looks good or not,
he is still my first fan.
To me,
he's very precious.
So, even if he looks very ugly,
I won't mind it.
Alright.
Let's start eating.
-Okay.
Let's start.
This one...
This looks so pretty.
This is so...
Hello.
You came!
This is my friend.
He's Peng Bo.
He is my father's personal physician.
We haven't seen each other for a long time.
So, I specifically invited him over to have a meal
Do you guys mind?
We don't mind.
That's great.
Welcome.
[So this is how everyone looks like.]
Peng Bo.
[This person bashed me in the chat group before.]
[This one.]
[He replies the slowest whenever]
[we assign ranking tasks.]
[And you...]
Peng Bo.
Miss Pingping.
Why are you calling me that?
Only my fans
call me that.
You don't have to.
[I want to call you that too.]
Okay. You can go ahead.
Welcome!
Come. Have a seat.
Have a seat.
Miss Pingping, let's eat.
Let's eat.
Peng Bo, I'll leave you on your own.
You can eat yourself.
Try this.
You've worked hard.
Thank you!
It's nothing.
[I want it too.]
-Thank you.
-Hurry and eat.
I think this must be delicious.
Do you know why?
Why?
Because
Miss Pingping
gave this to me.
I'll taste it first.
How is it?
Delicious!
It's really good!
[The patient of Bed 21 vomited.]
[I'm on leave today.]
[Is it your first time seeing]
[patients vomiting after having anesthesia?]
[Look for a nurse at the nurse counter.]
[Mengmeng is on duty today.]
[She's ignoring me.]
[Dr. Peng, she's breaking up with me.]
[So, this is the main point?]
[Dr. Peng.]
[You finally got it right.]
[Help me.]
[I gave everyone]
[a piece of toast.]
[This piece is yours.]
[I don't know]
[what flavors you like,]
[so I took a bit of everything.]
[Hope to see you next time.]
[Why are you ignoring me?]
[Are you having constipation?]
[Even you're leaving me.]
[I'm such a poor thing.]
[Bed 21 is fine.]
[Don't be too worried.]
[Mengmeng is still ignoring me.]
[Okay?]
[I'll tell Ling Rui]
[that your brain is constipated.]
[Ling Rui?]
Goodbye.
Remember to take your phones.
Your phones.
Goodbye.
Okay.
Goodbye, Miss Pingping.
Goodbye.
-Goodbye, Miss Pingping.
-Goodbye.
Goodbye, Miss Pingping.
Goodbye.
Miss Pingping.
We'll come again next time
to your birthday party.
Sure. Goodbye.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Goodbye, Miss Pingping.
Goodbye.
[Tell Ling Rui?]
[Caramel Apple 120?]
[Peng Bo?]
Stop there, Peng Bo!
Stop!
You!
Stop there!
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
It hurts!
Sorry... Sorry...
-It hurts.
-I...
Let me have a look.
Caramel Apple 120.
It's not me.
What do you mean it's not you?
How did you know
Caramel Apple 120
was a person?
No...
Not a person...
120...
Should I call 120 for you?
Why don't you have a check at the hospital?
Give me your phone.
No way.
Give it to me.
Hold still.
Let me see
whether you're
Caramel Apple 120?
Please give me back my phone.
Nope.
No. No.
Give it back to me.
Nope.
No.
Are you angry? Are you angry?
Enough.
Stop joking around.
I'm not joking around.
Have a look at yourself now.
What's wrong?
You are an idol.
You are an artist.
Aren't you scared of the paparazzi?
Am I right?
Do you think you're lack scandals?
Would you be able to do well
in your showbiz career?
Stick your foot out.
That one.
You're a celebrity.
You're an artist.
You need to be careful next time.
Okay.
Be good.
Be careful.
Caramel Apple 120...
It's you.
I really shouldn't have
let Lu Fangning read those novels.
She's living her life
as if it's a novel.
The beginning...
[Deadlift.]
[Deadlift, no problem.]
What a marvelous beginning!
Next...
[Chapter Two]
A marvelous experience.
[Lu Yiyao]
I, Lu Youyou, am officially informing you
that from now on,
I don't need you anymore.
Dad,
thank you for your company for the past five years.
But now I have found
my real-life dad.
What?
You're asking
whether I'm satisfied with my dad?
Make a guess.
Dad. Dad. Dad.
[Can we meet?]
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Sit down.
It's okay.
Uhm...
Do you want something to drink?
Excuse me.
One hot Americano, please.
Thank you.
Okay. Please wait for a while.
Uhm...
Ling Rui.
I heard Youyou called you 'dad'.
He's much smarter and sensitive
than I imagined.
Last night,
I watched him holding that doll
and kept calling it 'dad, dad'.
I was wrong
about Youyou's matter.
I...
I was too full of myself.
And because of that,
I've brought
nothing but scars and regrets
to you and Youyou.
I'm sorry.
Have a seat first.
It's okay. I'm more comfortable like this.
Here's your hot Americano.
Thank you.
I can try to
digest my emotions.
But Youyou is just a kid.
For the past five years,
he had to
live a life without a father.
Ling Rui.
I'm really sorry.
I will find a way to make amends.
I will make amends
for your father-son relationship.
How do you plan to make amends?
I have a way
we can make up for what we've lost over the past five years.
What's that?
I hope you can give me
Youyou's custody.
No way.
No... I mean...
Your business is just starting.
Plus, you're overseas most of the time.
The nature of my job
and living environment
is more suitable to raise a child
compared to yours at the moment.
Besides,
having a child with you always
makes it hard for you to find a boyfriend.
Your youth is wasted just like that.
I thought it through.
This is the best solution
at the moment.
I'm not looking for a boyfriend.
Ling Rui, I swear
I'm not looking for someone.
I will never do that.
I...
Ling Rui, you have no idea.
Youyou is at this age
where even dogs hate him.
You wouldn't want
to see him every day.
You would eventually lose
your love for him.
How about
you two meet more often?
Meet each other more.
Meet each other a lot.
One week each month.
Half a month.
Meet three-quarters of a month.
How about that?
Don't you have to
go back abroad very soon?
I won't go back.
I'll take root in my motherland and serve my country.
We don't live together.
My mother
and aunts are also old now.
It's inconvenient for them to move around.
I...
I'll deliver him to your doorstep.
I'll deliver Lu Youyou to your doorstep.
I'll personally
pack and deliver Lu Youyou to your doorstep.
Ling Rui.
Think about it.
Think carefully about it.
We really can't bring this to court.
Parents going against each other in a lawsuit
will only bring a negative impact
to our child's growth
and also his future.
I'll wait for you at home.
If you have nothing important to say, you can leave.
Peng Bo, my friend.
Where's your phone?
Who is this romantic person?
Which century are you living in?
You're still using
such an ancient tool of communication.
Oh my goodness.
Have a look.
Open it.
Yang, let me tell you.
I've understood the confusion
that you told me about last time.
Okay.
So?
So I made an arrangement.
From today onwards,
you and Nurse Liu Mengmeng's shifts
are all separated.
In our department,
either you or she will be here at a time.
Never together.
Dr. Peng.
I give you three seconds
to get out of my sight.
If you don't leave,
-I'll tell her that -Understand!
Everything
was just a scheme that you begged me
to separate her from you.
[To, Peng Bo. Contains bombs.]
[Your phone is with me.]
[But I don't know the password.]
[But I can try.]
[My birthday.]
[The day I acted for the first time.]
[The number of views]
[of my first drama.]
[After trying them all out,]
[I'll go through all your contacts]
[and tell them]
[that you are my 120.]
[You know how to contact me.]
How am I supposed to contact you?
All the numbers are on my phone.
[Tell him that his dad is a bastard]
[and he must choose mommy.]
[No, I can't.]
[I can't bring this]
[to the child.]
[Or I can just]
[send Lu Youyou back abroad]
[and get the old man to hide him.]
[No, I can't.]
[I can't do this kind of thing anymore.]
[In that case, I can only...]
Mom, I'm so handsome.
Are you mesmerized by me?
Baby.
What happened?
I'll have to ask you
to bear a short while for mommy.
I need your help to show
how great mommy is.
Mom, what are you talking about?
Youyou.
Do you want to know
how to please the three grandmas?
Yes!
Then, let me tell you.
Just show them
what a true devil you are.
Cry and throw tantrums.
No matter what they ask you to do,
you have to say 'no, no, no.'
No one would like
such a child.
This is what you don't understand.
Let me tell you.
You haven't been back for too long.
It is the difference
between Chinese and Western culture.
You always liked watching the news, don't you?
The grandmas here
love kids who cry, throw tantrums,
who are lively and rebellious.
This can stimulate
their motherly love.
Look.
You met Auntie Tang Ping before, didn't you?
Wasn't she just stupid and loud?
Am I right?
But doesn't mom still
accept,
tolerate and love her?
We have to allow everyone
to have different preferences.
Okay?
Okay!
Not okay...
Okay...
Are you okay with it or not?
Are you fooling me around?
I guess it really isn't okay.
How about we both take a step back?
Let's compromise.
Just promise me
that you'll do three things.
Three things?
Seventy thousand.
Pass.
Pass?
Hurry, your turn.
Forty thousand.
I won!
-Be gentle.
-I...
Sorry. Sorry.
I was just excited.
Did you forget that I have pharyngitis?
-I can't eat chili.
-I don't care.
Why didn't you say anything
when you forced me to eat it just now?
I can't eat it.
I'm still coughing.
I don't care. You have to eat it.
Not too much.
Ling Rui!
Yes.
They're bullying me.
Go and pour me a glass of water.
They're getting me to eat chili.
-Okay.
-Pour me a glass of water.
So much chili!
I'm coming.
How am I supposed to eat them?
I'll be coughing mad eating these.
Hurry and eat them.
I want to witness
this historical moment.
Hurry and get me some water.
Water is coming.
Sister-in-law.
-I'm not eating them.
-Hurry up.
No can do.
I'm not eating.
I need to drink water.
If you keep acting like this,
then we'll...
We'll draw your face.
I'll draw for you.
You owe me one.
Can I owe it?
You two are so shameless.
Next time, let's not
do eat chili then.
Keep your voice down.
Who is it?
I'll get it.
Come.
One more round.
Dad!
-What's wrong with you two?
-Youyou.
Where's your mom?
Why didn't she come?
Didn't she say home delivery?
Mom sent me here.
There's a kid.
-Then, she left.
-Who is he?
Who came?
We already know each other so well.
We don't need her introduction.
Good boy.
Go in.
Who is this?
A little baby.
This is actually...
[First thing.]
Scream as soon as you enter the house.
What happened?
What's wrong？
Are you sick?
[Mom only asked me to scream.]
[She never set the reason as to why I scream.]
How beautiful!
Youyou saw this house
and the three grandmas.
I think you are all so beautiful!
So good with his words.
This kid.
Are you auntie?
You're so young.
I should call you Sis.
Sis!
Then, you two must be Grannies,
am I right?
Yes, we are.
You're so beautiful too!
Thank you.
I just
got my hair done two days ago.
Of course, I'm pretty.
This child sure has an eye for beauty.
It's really rare.
He's so cute.
-This is...
So cute.
I want to keep him home.
Where did you get this baby?
-Big sister!
-How about you sit here?
So cute.
How come he looks kind of familiar?
Look at all the kids.
Aren't they all the same?
It's still very rare
to see such a cute child.
[Second thing.]
"Upside down".
After entering the house,
create a mess and turn the house upside down.
Okay?
It's not good
to touch other people's stuff
when you're in their house.
You're right.
Then, you can try to hold it in first.
Go into the house and
find a corner that you like.
Just turn that corner upside down.
Okay?
What did he find?
What is he doing?
What's going on?
It's normal for kids
to pull out all the things at home.
It's just curiosity.
This...
He's putting them back.
That's new.
It's the first time I see a kid
tidying up
after creating a mess.
What do you mean by 'first time'?
Well...
Ling Rui was like this when he was young.
He couldn't bear
even the slightest mess in his room.
Am I right?
Ling Rui.
Where did you pick up
such a treasure?
The two of them really do look kind of alike.
Yeah.
I don't count on you
to give me
such a precious grandson.
Youyou.
It's almost mealtime.
What do you want to eat?
[That was fast. We're at this time now?]
Third thing.
When grandmas ask you what you want to eat,
say you don't want to eat.
You don't want anything.
You only want pizza,
burger, fried chicken, and fries.
Pizza, burger, fried chicken and fries.
That's easy. I'll go and buy them.
-The soup is coming.
-Why did
she get all these
junk foods for him?
Soup is here. Soup is here.
The soup is here.
Here comes the soup.
Kid, drink the soup first.
Finish the soup
and then, you can eat these junk foods.
Did you hear me?
I don't want to.
Nevermind then.
Youyou said
he wants to eat these junk foods.
Kids love these.
Come.
Have some vegetables
so you can balance your diet.
I don't want to.
You don't want to?
Youyou.
I made these dishes myself.
Have a taste.
No!
One, two, three, chew.
Good boy.
-Chew, chew.
-He's eating vegetables now.
Keep chewing.
Another sip of the soup.
-What a good boy.
-Good boy.
Really good.
Have some veggie after the soup.
Very good.
Kid.
Let's not eat these junk foods
anymore today.
Okay?
Give it to Grannie.
Very good.
If you can not eat them today,
you can
not eat them forever.
Okay?
I won't eat them anymore.
Nothing tastes better
than the dishes made by dad.
Exactly!
-Good boy.
-Dad?