[English subtitles are available]
[Begin Again]
[Episode 07]
-I'm sorry.
-Director Lu.
I'm giving this rookie training.
This rookie really wants
to know about you.
It's not me. I didn't want to.
Bring me the planning case by Gavin
the major designer
of this year's design exhibition,
by Friday.
Okay.
Twice already.
No.
Three times.
Bad luck.
Twice.
No.
Three times.
What the hell?
Alas.
I'd like to ask that
where can I find the list?
Make a turn at the corner ahead,
go to the last room.
Okay, thank you.
The fever has subsided.
Other indicators are normal as well.
Surgery may
be arranged first.
Go inform them.
Okay.
And,
bring me the report
of the patient at bed 36
as soon as possible.
It's you.
Wait, you...
I... I don't think it's appropriate.
What? What did I do?
Yes.
I know Ling Rui is a good person.
But it's not proper that you follow him
all day long.
When did I follow him?
You have to mind your behavior.
You're a young girl.
Um.
How can you be so thick-skinned,
right?
Ling Rui is busy rushing from one place
to another every day.
He doesn't have the time to talk to you.
What the hell did I do to him?
Why do you treat me
like this?
Am I such a fool
without conscience
in your mind?
I'm still harassing a man
while my father is sick,
right?
Well. Who knows?
You...
I meant to ask
how to get there?
Thank you.
[Shenzhen Huiren Hospital]
How do you think
a honeymoon period for the newlyweds
should be like?
I don't know, director.
I'm not married.
But,
the couple must be an attachment
to each other,
and very much in love.
They only have eyes for each other,
like...
they wished they were
a pair of Siamese twins.
You can shut your mouth.
Attached, not attachment!
You can't even say it correctly.
Don't look at me.
I'm not married either.
I think,
at least you can't hide
the fact that you're married from others.
Stop nodding.
[LM Deer Sing Group]
Let the Design Department
do a few more sketches for you.
Mr. Ling, then I'll go first.
Thank you.
We're going to redo
the waterproofing test on
the goods we saw just now.
-Write that down.
-Okay, I will.
Where is the datasheet
for this batch of materials?
I'm sorry, Ms. Lu.
I'll go fetch it right now.
Let's check
over there later.
You can take a look over there.
Okay, let's go.
Why are you here?
I want to see what you
look like at work.
The work in the hospital must be heavy.
Don't you have to be on duty?
Anything important?
If no, I'll go to work then.
No, I'm off today.
Wait for me.
♫ My mind floats in the wind ♫
♫ The warm room doesn't look
much different ♫
♫ But, you're no longer by my side ♫
♫ The hollowness in my gaze ♫
♫ Everything I touch turns into emptiness ♫
♫ Desolation comes
when it's least expected ♫
Ask Ma to send the datasheet
directly to the B217.
-Let's go over there and check.
-Okay.
♫ The more you care, the more you hurt ♫
♫ But, you're no longer by my side ♫
[LM Deer Sing Group]
♫ My emotions don't matter anymore ♫
Why are you still here?
It's late.
You're done?
I just finished.
Right,
was there something
you wanted to tell me?
Nothing.
I'm waiting to pick you up after work.
Stop smiling.
Do you think I would
forgive you because of your smile?
Fangning,
I've given it a serious thought.
Why is the light off?
Sister, the light is off
and the door is locked.
That's all I can do for you.
What does he mean?
Lu Fangyu
must want to give
the two of us
a chance to be together.
Then, we...
Only in the morning
will someone come and open the door.
Then, we can only stay the night here.
Maybe.
Then I'll take you to
a comfortable place.
Let's go.
Slow down.
There it is.
What?
Nothing.
You're familiar with the place.
Of course.
I watched the place
as it was being constructed
little by little.
When I first joined LM Deer Sing Group,
I was once a store staff and a salesperson
I had to run up and down many times.
Of course,
now I also come here once a week.
So even with my eyes closed,
I can find the place I want to get to.
I told them last time
not to put the flower pot here.
Why is it still here?
Lu Fangning.
Wait for me.
Why are you running so fast?
I'm scared to death.
You scared me first.
I'm not frightened at all.
Me too.
Then, why are you grabbing me
if you're not scared?
I worry that you'll be scared.
Didn't you say we're almost there?
Why is it taking so long?
We're almost there, just a minute.
Don't be scared. I'm with you.
I'm not afraid.
Almost there.
Slow down.
We set this place
as a
Living Room Exploration Hall,
simulating a sense of being at home,
to make customers feel like they are home.
Sit down.
Our employees
usually rest here, too.
The sofa over there
is an exhibition.
But, it has been booked
by our customer.
So we can't sit there.
Just make do with it.
Sit here.
Never mind.
It's quite comfortable here.
Here you are.
Thank you.
We only have chips here.
Next time I'll ask my staff
to order
something more delicious.
It's okay.
It's good enough.
However,
we probably won't get to do this again.
Nothing. Enjoy it.
I'm so tired.
Shall we
find something interesting
to do?
Do...
Do what?
Come here.
Let's play this.
The winner can ask
the other person a question.
The other one has to answer truthfully
and can't hide anything,
so we can
learn more about each other.
I'm not in.
I don't wanna know more about you.
Come on.
So childish. I don't want to play.
I'll go first.
Your turn.
Pick one.
Have you decided?
Don't rush me.
Strategy matters.
Okay, take your time.
Be quieter when you eat chips.
I got distracted.
You lost. I win.
Ask me.
I am not
curious about you.
I don't know what to ask.
Okay, I got one.
What do you think of Tang Ping?
Tang Ping?
Not interested.
Then in hospital, you and her...
Her father had
an unexplained shadow in his lungs.
She took the X-ray there,
which is
exactly my specialty.
So I took him in.
No more?
-Yep.
-That's all?
Go on.
I win again.
Awesome people indeed
do well in everything.
Go ahead.
Why did you suddenly
decide to marry me?
Because I wanted to help you.
And?
Nothing.
Nothing again?
You...
You're not playing fair.
I'm not lying.
I'm not dodging it.
Go on.
You lose.
It's my turn to ask you.
Why did you want to
marry me so badly?
Was there any other reason
other than work?
Of course, I wanted to
have a baby with you.
But I can't let him know.
And I can neither lie nor evade it.
What should I say?
Because I want to
have a deeper...
A deeper connection with you.
Another round?
I...
I feel sleepy.
Okay then.
Let's stop.
Would you like to watch a film?
♫ The potent fragrance of the rose petals ♫
♫ I don't mind walking
on the streets alone ♫
♫ The movies are always full
of disappointment and farewells ♫
♫ But, who will watch them with me ♫
♫ Slowly, we get closer ♫
♫ I like you ♫
♫ Only you ♫
♫ You're my one and only ♫
♫ Tonight, I'll let my mind wander ♫
♫ Tonight is the night ♫
♫ I want to travel to Paris and Tokyo,
and eat chocolate by the sea ♫
♫ As long as I'm with you ♫
♫ We can lie on the beach
and count the stars ♫
♫ I like you because you put up with me ♫
♫ My unyielding stubbornness ♫
♫ It's all because of you ♫
♫ I like you ♫
♫ Only you ♫
♫ You're my one and only ♫
♫ Under the moon, on the bright street,
we'll hold our wedding tonight ♫
♫ Only you ♫
♫ You're my one and only ♫
♫ We need to learn no more,
we'll fall in love tonight ♫
Ms. Lu.
Darling.
Yes?
Let's go to work.
Okay.
Let's go.
Did you sleep well last night?
Pretty good.
I had a nice dream.
And you?
Me too.
I thought you were
already awake, right?
You pretended to be asleep.
It was so awkward.
[More brands and surprises upstairs!]
This is your place.
You're more suitable
to deal with the situation.
Wait for me here.
-Ma.
-Ms. Lu.
Before closing the door,
you must check
if there is anyone inside
to make sure
the safety of people and goods.
-Got it?
-Yes.
Done?
Do you have something to do later?
Why don't you drive me to the hospital?
I drive you to the hospital?
I mean...
How about we have our breakfast there?
What do you want?
Anything is okay, you decide.
You can taste
the grain porridge here
and some desserts.
Okay.
You go take a seat. I'll go get the food.
Let's go together.
Okay.
-Thank you.
-Thanks, Sis Li.
What else do you want?
Okay.
I can't.
Thank you.
-Do you know her?
-You go.
Go, you go ask.
Director Ling.
Yes.
-You're here for breakfast?
-Yeah, hello.
Thank you.
She is...
She's my wife.
You're married, Dr. Ling?
Yes.
Okay.
Let's go.
Thank you, Sis Li.
You're welcome.
I told you he's married.
That's his wife.
Where do you want to sit?
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Is that his sister?
She's quite pretty.
I heard that Dr. Ling
has been long married.
Really?
-Let's eat.
-Okay.
You're married, Ling Rui?
She's your wife?
Yes.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Tastes good.
Taste the dessert.
-Morning, Director Ling.
-Morning.
Good morning, Mrs. Ling.
Mrs. Ling is so beautiful.
Thank you.
Here.
No one knows who I am.
I should
introduce you to them.
No, no. I was kidding.
You are better than me in the hospital.
No one will address you as
Lu Fangning's husband.
Now,
I'm Dr. Ling's wife.
Mrs. Ling.
I like this.
I do matter more
than you at the hospital.
Fangning.
I don't quite like being noticed
by many people.
So,
I didn't tell my colleagues
about my marriage.
I didn't know you would...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I didn't mind.
And,
theoretically, the surgeons
must not wear any accessories,
because we may be required
to do an operation
at any time.
But, I don't have any today.
I'll wear it
as often as possible from now on.
I'm not pushing you
to wear it all the time.
Of course, you can
take it off in the hospital.
When you come back home,
just put it on.
Okay.
After breakfast,
I don't have anything else to do.
You can walk me around the hospital.
Okay.
-Go ahead.
[General Surgery Ward Area]
Will I
disturb your work?
Just a while. It's okay.
Um,
how about this?
It's fine.
This must be Mrs. Ling.
So you're going to
make your marriage known?
This is how a honeymoon
should look like.
I got tied up during my wedding.
I didn't have time to ask you.
How should I address you?
Curly.
Look, how curly his hair is.
Call him Curly.
Easy to remember.
You can call me Curly, sounds better.
We all call him that.
I'm Yang Jin, Mrs. Ling.
Just call me Yang.
I'm Mengmeng.
Call me Xun, Mrs. Ling.
You're so cute. Wait a second.
What are you finding?
I think I should give them
some red packets.
You're so generous, Mrs. Ling.
So generous of you.
"Mrs. Ling", I can call that
a few more times.
You know what?
I can call that, too.
Sister-in-law, right?
Wait.
I didn't bring red packets today.
I'll bring it to you next time.
-Alright.
-Thank you in advance.
We're not in a rush.
You don't have work to do?
Alright, we've greeted her.
We didn't get the red packets.
We saw how sweet they are. Let's go.
-Bye, Mrs. Ling.
-Bye.
Alright, go back to work.
Our mission today
has been accomplished.
What about you?
I have something
to deal with later.
Okay, I'll go to work.
Go.
[Always at your service]
So you should
do a regular check-up.
Dad, look...
Why are you here?
Pingping.
I'm sick,
so Fangning came to visit me.
How considerate she is, you see?
Uncle Tang, you don't have to worry.
Ling Rui
is the chief surgeon here.
You can tell him if you need anything.
Um.
Fangning,
about Dr. Ling,
do you mind?
Of course, I don't.
Ling Rui and I
are already married.
If you want something,
you can ask Tang Ping to contact Ling Rui.
But if you think Tang Ping
is unreliable and
immature,
I can help you.
Alright, thank you.
I'm leaving.
You can take a good rest.
Bye, Uncle Tang.
I came to visit Uncle Tang.
Mind your behavior.
As his daughter,
shouldn't you
express your gratitude?
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Didn't you see that
my visit
put Uncle Tang at ease?
Tang Pingping,
can you please
grow up
and be more considerate?
Your father is sick now.
Yet, you let him worry about you.
How could you be a...
Don't say that word!
The grudge is between
the two of us.
Don't get others involved.
Okay?
Grudge?
I don't think there is bad blood
between us.
If there is, it's about winning or losing.
Will you win?
If anyone asks who you are,
you can just say
you're a friend of Mrs. Ling.
That'll be good.
I feel so pleased.
You!
Does the apple taste good, Mr. Lu?
Sister, good afternoon.
Okay.
Sister, how did it go?
Did anything happen?
-I'll peel it for you.
-It was okay.
Okay?
Sister.
About what I did last night,
did I do a good job?
Shouldn't you thank me?
I was going to thank you.
I've told Gao Erfan
about that.
You'll be transferred back to
LM Deer Sing Group HQ,
effective today.
Transfer back to HQ?
Yes.
Sister, I don't want that.
Working in the mall,
I'm content
and I am learning a lot.
It's like wasting your talent
on a petty job if you stay there.
-Are you done?
-In a minute.
Here is my plan.
You can work at the front desk
after you come back.
It's not a hard job.
The front desk?
Are you kidding me?
Sister, do I have to
stand there
all day long?
Also, I cannot learn anything there.
How can you say that?
Why can't you
learn something there?
Besides,
to some extent,
I got you promoted.
Sister.
Good luck.
From now on,
I can see
your cute face
all day long.
My dear brother.
Sister.
All the best.
The front desk?
How can I possibly
go dancing then?
[LM Deer Sing Group]
[Planning Scheme]
Leader, is this color scheme okay?
I think it's good.
It suits Gavin's design style
very well, right?
It's so attractive.
Your proposal
comes with a voice-over system?
I am afraid that you can't appreciate it.
It's passed.
All of a sudden? Are you so surprised?
You have to
go to the western restaurant downstairs
immediately
on behalf of our team.
-Now, go.
-Okay.
Or there won't be any seats left.
Water!
Director Lu, watch out!
There's water here.
You must watch out.
Please enjoy your meal.
Hello.
I'm done.
I want this, without the onions.
Okay.
Hello, Director Lu.
Hello.
Have you adapted well?
Let's order first.
Okay, you go ahead.
Cheers.
Let's welcome Ms. Cai Siyu.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
Please take care of me in the future.
-Sure.
-You're too humble.
Okay. So, let's eat.
Let's eat.
Complicated and mysterious.
Handsome and rich.
Cool and lonely.
He is just a perfect male lead.
He gets bad luck
whenever he runs into me.
This plot sounds familiar.
Will I be
the destined female lead?
Don't just eat this.
Have some meat too.
Here.
I know.
You're too slim.
Eat more.
[Shenzhen Huiren Hospital]
[Emergency]
Dr. Ling.
-Hello.
-Ms. Tang, aren't you finished with
the discharge procedures?
Why are you back?
We don't
welcome returning customers here.
What returning customer?
Touchwood.
Dr. Ling.
I'm here to
say goodbye to you.
I'm so sad.
I owe you an apology
for the wedding.
I'm sorry.
And about my father's illness,
I wanna thank you.
So I want to...
I told you
we can't accept red packets.
What red packets? Go away.
I want to send you a banner.
That's okay.
He's received a lot of these.
Then,
can I take a picture with you?
Don't take a selfie.
Let me be your cameraman.
Isn't it good?
Okay.
-The font...
-What's wrong?
It suits you.
Hold it.
Come on!
Ready.
-How do I look?
-Perfect.
Well,
what are you doing here?
Isn't there's a patient waiting for you?
Go, now.
Yes.
Ms. Tang, I'm sorry.
There are patients waiting for me.
I've got to go.
Bye.
Dr. Ling.
Your phone, here you are.
I'll take a look at the photo.
Why am I the only one
in the photo?
You told me to take pictures of you.
You didn't tell me
to fit Ling Rui into the frame too.
What did you do?
You should take pictures of us.
-Who told you to shoot only me?
-Well...
You didn't make it clear.
-How can you blame me?
-You!
Trash!
The red banner
suits her anyway.
To Dr. Ling Rui,
you're
the star that never falls by day or night,
the light scattered in the world.
You're benevolent,
caring for everything.
You treat patients
like your own families.
You bring patients back to life
and bring comfort to everyone.
The most beautiful
patient's family, Tang Ping.
My God.
Unusual content,
but unexpectedly good.
The fifth guideline of a happy marriage,
cooking skill makes up for charm.
Didn't you want to
keep a distance from me?
Drinking my soup doesn't count
as breaking the contract, right?
I am so virtuous and generous.
How can you not fall for me
after you see me?
I'm back.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
I just thought of
something funny.
Right.
Last time,
I sent you the night snack,
but you didn't eat it.
Try the soup.
Did you make this?
Try it.
I'll go take a shower.
Thank you.
Smells good.
It's pretty good.
Darling.
What?
I'm so careless.
Um...
I forgot to bring the towel in.
Can you get it for me?
Darling.
Be quick.
-I can't reach it.
-Then, I'm leaving.
Ling Rui, Ling Rui!
I'm coming out.
Why is my heart beating so fast?
What's wrong?
Why did you drink so much water?
I don't know why.
I just feel thirsty.
Are you wearing too many layers?
Take off your clothes.
It's okay.
I might have caught a cold.
A cold?
I changed
my shampoo today.
Smell it.
See if you can smell it.
I'm sorry.
I've been in the shower for too long.
I feel dizzy.
No, no.
Ling Rui.
What?
What are you doing?
I don't know why
I feel so hot too.
You're sweating a lot.
Darling.
Flu
is contagious.