[English subtitles are available]
[Begin Again]
[Episode 15]
Is he handsome?
I know he's not as handsome as me.
Who's he?
You're being weird today.
I have a question.
Help me analyze the situation calmly
as an outsider.
Okay.
A friend of mine
has a female friend
who was very interested
in him.
But after he turned her down
a couple of times,
this female friend
became ice-cold.
What caused her to change?
Your friend?
My friend.
Could it be that
my friend said something harsh?
She's hurt?
She's angry?
It's really a friend of yours?
Really, he's my friend.
You really care about him.
Is she going to give up
and find someone else?
I don't think so.
According to
my observation on
all the women in love,
they are usually doing this
to send a signal
to the men.
It means that
"I might be leaving you."
"Be careful."
Do you understand?
Be careful.
What do you mean?
It means that
do something now
before I leave you.
What to do then?
The same, old tricks.
Go on a date.
Give presents.
Beg for her mercy.
Confess to her.
One more thing,
look pitiful.
You know what?
When you went on that business trip,
Mr. Yu and I thought
you and Fangning had a fight.
So, we told her
everything
about your past.
Oh, gosh.
You weren't there to see it.
Her feelings
are shown all over her face.
It's empathy.
I'm telling you, it works on her.
You know what?
Just stand up.
I'll give you a kick.
When you are injured,
I assure you that you will get along well
with your wife.
Both of you will be lovey-dovey.
It's my friend.
Right, right.
It's your friend.
I didn't say it was both of you.
I just used you as an example.
Just a friend.
We're not even that close.
Sure, sure.
You mentioned that
she cried after hearing about
my past?
Her eyes were teary.
But
I don't quite know
if she cried after she left.
You know, women are creatures
that need to be spoiled.
Tell her
what you have in mind.
After that,
do something romantic
and you can surely win her heart.
It's my friend.
Sure, sure.
Your friend.
Eat your noodles.
Stop thinking about it.
Isn't this about your friend?
What are you worrying about,
right?
Sense of ceremony.
Tell her my true thoughts.
[Marriage Certificate]
Her birthday is coming soon.
Put that down.
Blow up more balloons, come on.
Stop playing around.
Blow up more balloons.
Okay.
Ling Rui.
Dr. Ling.
You are decorating for a birthday party?
Sure.
Mengmeng and Xiaoxuan
are celebrating their birthdays.
We are going to throw a party for both of them.
Join us if you're free, Dr. Ling.
Sure.
So that's how you decorate
for a birthday party.
It's pretty.
What about it?
Are you going to throw someone a birthday party?
I happened
to have some extra
colored stripes and balloons here.
Yang Jin and Yang.
Where are the balloons?
Here.
These balloons are sponsored by the hospital.
When you got home,
tie these stripes
on the balloons
like what we did.
Just make the room
look more lively.
Don't make it look gloomy.
Sure.
What else?
Well, they've asked
someone from the security department
to deliver the cake in a mascot costume.
But that mascot costume
doesn't quite agree with your style.
How do you know
it won't agree with his style?
It's not for me.
It's for my friend.
Then can I borrow the costume for him
when you're done?
Of course.
Anything else?
Also, pick a present
that she will absolutely love.
A present that she loves?
Hi.
Happy birthday!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
How do you decorate?
Let me help.
Dr. Ling, you should get some rest.
I'll do it.
Sure. Ling,
blow up some of the balloons.
Just let me
order you around for once.
I can't even tell you what to do?
Welcome, sir.
Hello, I'd like to order a cake.
Sure.
What kind of cake
do you want then?
You could have a look
at this brochure.
There's no need.
Just follow this design.
Excuse me?
I mean,
put this on the cake.
Sure. I see, sir.
Please send me the picture then.
Okay.
What on earth should I write?
If I tell you everything,
will you remember it?
[Deer Sing Group]
[TO: Ms. Lu Fangning]
Hello?
I received it again.
There's still no clue?
Keep on looking.
The money will be transferred to your account.
You're back.
Get well soon.
They prepared these.
They got it wrong.
It's okay.
Ling Rui,
what are you doing?
Come here.
♫ Happy birthday to you. ♫
Do you want to blow out the candles?
Make a wish.
Ling Rui.
Did you prepare all of these by yourself?
I wanted to give you a surprise.
But I don't think it's very successful.
At least the cake is okay.
This is my gift for you.
I hope you like it.
Ling Rui, it just occurred to me
that I have to deal with
an emergency in the office,
I have to... I have to go now.
Thank you.
Fangning!
He's celebrating your birthday.
Lu Fangning, you're so stupid.
A coin?
Amusement park?
Why did he give me a coin
from the amusement park?
Oh, no.
No, no.
Hey, Ling Rui. What's up?
Fangyu,
do you know that
today is Fangning's birthday?
Of course, I do.
Ling Rui.
You didn't celebrate my sister's birthday,
did you?
Did she hit you?
We can't celebrate
her birthday?
Our eldest sister died
on the day of her birthday.
I was still too young at that time,
I don't quite know
what happened exactly.
Ling Rui,
are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Since our eldest sister passed away,
none of us
has celebrated her birthday.
Even though
she looks fine,
nobody dares to
mess with her on her birthday.
Why are you still...
I'm fine.
I think
she even thanked me.
What did you say?
She thanked you?
You really are her husband.
She's very tolerant of you.
I have to go now, Fangyu.
Where is it?
It's so cold.
Fangning, what happened?
What are you looking for?
Well,
the coin.
You dropped the coin?
Stop looking.
No.
You gave it to me, so it's mine now.
I have to find it. Just leave me be.
Stop looking.
Let's go home.
If you insist,
I will carry you home.
Let's go.
It's okay.
Here.
Take the medicine before you go to bed.
Are you going to stay here
and watch me sleep?
I can't sleep when you're watching me.
Why did you
thank me?
Because I know
you did everything
to make me happy.
Do you think
I like acting like a fool
to watch you
ride on the merry-go-round
and play bumper cars with you?
I did all of these
just to make you happy!
Excuse me.
In my eye,
Ling Rui is this amazing.
What can I do
to make you believe me?
Should I sponsor more patients
for your sake?
The vegetables that you like,
fish, Mapo tofu.
And the soup that I made.
Lu Fangning,
I should thank you, too.
I want…
What do I want?
Get married?
No, wait.
Fall in love, get married…
I think we've messed up the order.
Then let me sort it out from the beginning.
Figure it out step by step.
Ling Rui.
Ling Rui?
Where did he go this early morning?
Ling Rui has been investing?
The profits seem great.
He's quite good at it.
At this rate,
he will be able to
pay off his debt soon, won't he?
You woke up.
Where were you?
We were out of milk.
So, I went out and bought some.
Are you feeling better now?
I'm fine now.
By the way,
are there any restaurants that you like?
Restaurants that I like?
I mean,
which restaurant
do you usually go to?
[What does he mean?]
[Doesn't he like]
[homemade meals?]
[He doesn't even want to]
[cook for me anymore now?]
Never mind. Let's talk about it another time.
Ling Rui, I need to use the bathroom.
[What does he want to say now?]
I think it would be better for us
to call off the engagement.
I'm willing to bear
all of the consequences.
Right now,
he's trying to refuse me
before I make any moves?
It's over.
Yesterday, I...
Well done.
You even lost the coin
that he gave you.
Lu Fangning,
why don't you
know anything about love?
No.
I can't sit on the problem.
I found it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you for helping.
I've finally found you.
I had been looking for you.
I will never
lose you again.
I will...
carry you
with me
all the time.
You're in a good mood.
Fangning and you...
Wait, no. How are things going
for your friend
and his female friend?
They sorted it out.
Everything will start again from the beginning.
Hello, Ms. Lu?
Start again from the beginning?
What does he mean?
Going back
to that time
where we didn't know each other?
Not married.
Not in a relationship.
So he's trying
to get a divorce?
Ling Rui.
I won't let you carry out your plan.
Fangning,
let's have dinner together tonight.
I can't go tonight.
I have to work overtime.
Why is the water drained?
I have no idea either.
Why are you following me?
I have a busy day today.
I can't drive you to work.
See you.
You're not going to drive to work?
I am.
The parking lot is that way.
I left something at home.
I have to go now. See you.
I can wait for you.
There's no need.
You can go ahead. Bye.
I'm starving.
Fangning.
It's almost lunchtime.
Let's have lunch together.
No, thank you.
What about dinner then?
I don't want to have dinner. I'm on a diet.
Diet?
I'm not hungry.
Fangning!
I'm not hungry!
[Deer Sing Group]
Please give me the list.
Okay.
Director Lu, here is the list.
Thank you.
Morning, Siyu.
Don't blame me.
I didn't mean to
ignore you just now.
Actually, I meant it.
But it's not that
I didn't want to talk to you.
I just…
I know.
We should keep our relationship
a secret in the office.
It's better for you.
What about after work?
Sorry?
Are we still
going on a date after work?
Where do you want to go?
Anywhere you like...
Director Lu.
Hey.
You don't have to act like this.
I'm your director.
It's normal for you to talk to me.
Right, I can talk to you.
Hi.
Hi, Andy.
Hi, Siyu.
Hi, Liu.
Come in.
Director Lu, I need you to sign these files.
Sure.
Remember to have lunch.
Remember to drink water.
See you in the parking lot after work.
Love you.
Please sign here.
I've signed it.
Thank you.
Director.
What should we do? Lock it!
Do you have a safe?
Trash bin?
Wait, wait.
Calm down.
Just act normal.
Stand up straight.
Come in.
I'm here for Director Lu's signature.
I saw that.
Why did you have to tell me?
What's the matter?
It's about
the condition brought up
by Bai Jing.
What are you doing?
Did you twist your ankle?
No, my shoe got dirty.
Your sticker fell off.
It's just a sticker.
You acted like
it was a love letter.
I should go now.
Sorry for interrupting.
Are you all right, Siyu?
See you, Siyu.
Ling Rui,
why... why are you here?
I'm waiting for you to finish your work
so we can have dinner together.
I already got an appointment tonight.
But...
your secretary told me
you don't have
any other appointments today.
She knows nothing…
I have an appointment with my job.
I have a date with my work.
I have a lot to do.
Why don't you...
You can just go…
It's all right. Take your time.
I'll wait for you.
Why are you still acting sneaky?
I told you it's fine now.
I got used to it.
Besides, if our colleagues
found out about our relationship,
wouldn't it be bad for you?
Siyu,
you really are a good girl.
I think so, too.
Director Lu, did you just like me
a little more just now?
Where are we going next?
Have dinner and watch a movie.
That's boring.
Let me take you to a place.
You'll definitely like it.
Sure.
Buckle up.
♫ The rose petals have a potent fragrance ♫
♫ I don't mind walking on the streets alone ♫
Pet shops? Why did you bring me here?
To commemorate the moment
when you made my heart skipped.
♫ But who will watch them with me ♫
♫ Slowly, we get closer ♫
♫ I like you ♫
♫ Only you ♫
♫ You're my one and only ♫
♫ Tonight, I'll let my mind wander ♫
He's not going to wait here forever, is he?
Is he not leaving
until he achieves his goal?
You're done?
Let's go.
I...
I haven't.
I need to use the bathroom.
Okay.