♪Wind blows through the hair♪
♪Time flows through
the scent of flowers♪
♪Promise is made under the sun,
the moon, and stars♪
♪Love and hate are entangled in cloud♪
♪Over thousands of years♪
♪We brushed past each other♪
♪Music flies into sky♪
♪None is worth my strife♪
♪But for you,
I'm willing to go to the stake♪
♪Moonlight flows in the night♪
♪Between poems and songs♪
♪It's my obsession♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪I took a ladle only♪
♪Of all the flowers♪
♪I plucked one only♪
♪Of all the waters♪
♪You are the only one♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Till old and gray♪
=My Queen=
=Episode 12=
Oh no!
You just
left me one coin?
Do you really want to take her with us?
I have to,
or she has nowhere to go on her own.
What if she wants to die again?
You seem like a bit of
a swordswoman now.
Do I?
But today is full of accidents.
I thought I could have been a bully,
and you'll come here to save the beauty.
But a little accident occurred.
If you want to see me,
why didn't you send out
the Tian Ji Token?
But I want to see you all the time.
(Oh no.)
(I said a little too much.)
What were they whispering about?
Why is it so weird?
No!
You are a bad woman.
Why did I say it out?
Well,
how are you recently?
Did the cold poison relapse?
No.
Great.
You have to take care of yourself.
Don't get sick.
Don't get hurt.
And wait for me
to bring you the blood night-blooming
cereus to cure your cold poison.
Why are you so sure
that you can get the
blood night-blooming cereus?
Because I am Jiang Mengmeng.
Is there anything that
I cannot get?
Alright.
I have to go now.
There's a long way ahead.
You have to be careful.
Just left like this?
Always come and go in haste.
Next time, don't wear a mask.
Forget it.
He has his justice to maintain,
and I have my mission to complete.
What about her?
She'll go with us.
How's the investigation going?
As the investigation shows,
she did come from Nan Cang
two and a half years ago.
But a few years ago, Nan Cang
was constantly at war.
All of our members in Nan Cang have
evacuated already.
Most of the data was destroyed
in the evacuation.
Therefore, it is difficult to verify
the history of Zhe Xiang in Nan Cang.
Are you worrying that
Zhe Xiang harbors malicious intentions
to get close to the 9th princess?
Keep investigating.
Jiang Mengmeng is simple,
and does not have mind of vigilance
to those who are with good looking.
If Zhe Xiang
harbors malicious intentions,
I won't let her get away.
Got it.
Oh,
Master,
these are what you want.
Let's go.
(Jin Ding Manor)
Xiao Ai.
Your Highness.
Don't cry. Don't cry.
I'm here.
Your Highness, where did you go?
I have been looking for you
for a long while.
It's a long story.
I'll tell you later.
Who is she?
(Teammate +1)
She is a bad woman.
Don't listen to him.
I'll tell you later.
Oh,
where are Murong Chen and Chang Kong?
He went to look for you.
Didn't you meet?
Oh no.
Two more lost.
It's raining.
What about Murong Chen and Chang Kong?
Your Highness, look.
What's this?
From which page in Shan Hai Scriptures?
[*An ancient Chinese book on monsters]
Is that you, Your Highness?
Me?
(Missing Person Notice)
Look!
Jiang Mengmeng.
What?
Murong Chen.
This is a behavior of anti-fans,
rather than a Missing Person Notice.
I...
There are more?
I'll find him and kill him!
Murong Chen.
- Who is it?
- What is this?
Your Highness,
please take a break.
You have been doing this
the whole night.
Mengmeng is missing now.
I don't know whether she is
in danger.
I have to find her as soon as possible.
(Every time I meet Yun Ya,
is he just missing me
like this alone?)
(Strange!)
(Why do I feel sorry to him?)
Where is my Mengmeng?
- Stop.
- No way!
Mengmeng!
You are back!
Are you alright? Let me check.
Let me check.
Why did you get hurt?
Not a serious one.
It's OK.
And you,
you have no sense of direction.
If you get lost in the night,
what are you going to do?
I have Chang Kong.
He will find the way.
And I will find you.
It is impossible to get lost.
You said you have to look exquisite
when not at home, didn't you?
Look at what you did to yourself.
Are you worrying about me?
No, I am not.
You think too much.
- You are worrying about me.
- Your Highness.
You are false to your heart.
Who's that girl?
There's a long way ahead
in the depopulated zone.
We can stay over when
we see mountain villa.
How much further to go?
If you get tired,
you can take a rest on the horse.
- I'd better walk.
- Go.
I kill...
Da Huang.
Da Huang, Da Huang!
Don't run, Da Huang.
Da Huang.
The weather was fine all the way.
Why is the fog occurring so suddenly?
Brother!
Where are you?
(Miasmatic Forest)
Brother!
Murong Chen, what's wrong?
The fog seems to be denser.
Why don't we wait
until the fog disperses?
Just fog.
There is nothing to be afraid of.
Coward.
The fog takes at least four hours to
become dense enough to obscure vision.
If we walk faster,
we can walk out of the forest
in two hours.
If we wait here until the fog
disperses completely,
we might have to stay till
tomorrow morning.
It is more dangerous to
stay overnight in the wildness.
Zhe Xiang, you are amazing.
You can tell this.
You are not a woman of the world.
Why do you know that?
I think she just made that up.
Does it have to be a woman
of the world to know about fog?
Nan Cang is located in
a hot and humid place,
always foggy.
I know well about such environment.
And General Song,
you have years of experience
being at war against Nan Cang.
Don't you know this environment?
You make sense.
(If Xiao Ai is for search,)
(Song Che is for attack,)
(Chang Kong is for defense,)
(and Murong Chen has super power,)
(then our new member, Zhe Xiang, is)
(for)
(wisdom.)
(Moreover, if Mr. System wants
to set me up,)
(it's the same whenever we go.)
Let's go!
Welcome to the Lost Phantom Formation.
Da Huang.
Da Huang, Da Huang!
Song Che.
Leave it.
(Phantom Forest)
I guess we might get lost, right?
The fog is coming
quicker than I thought.
Didn't you think it wrong
from the very beginning?
You...
Did you know this is a trap,
and lure us to here?
Stop it!
What we need to do now is
to figure out a way
to get out of here, right?
I have an idea.
We should separate into
groups of two persons,
so we have three groups in total.
We count the numbers every five steps.
It'll work.
This not only guarantees that
we won't get lost in groups,
but also speeds up the progress.
Then how should we separate?
(Chang Kong, Song Che and Zhe Xiang)
(all have power of attack.)
(As for Murong Chen,)
(I'd better avoid being alone with him.)
(I cannot give him the chance
to be alone with Mengmeng.)
(Is he trying to test me
with this chance?)
I'll team up with Zhe Xiang.
I think it's safer to be with her.
(You really are a good actor.)
(I think you just want to
be with the beauty.)
(I regret that I...)
(So typical!)
Then I'll team up with Song Che.
(As expected,)
(Mengmeng still cares about me,
the love one,)
(in the important moment.)
Let's go.
Go!
Your Highness.
Murong Chen,
you're smarter than I thought.
what's wrong?
Nothing. Let's go.
Silly boy!
You are in the formation,
and I am out of it.
Only I can see you.
You are impossible to see me.
One.
Two.
Three.
(Walking Phantom Formation)
This fog is so dense.
Everyone counts and stays
wherever you are.
One.
Two.
Three.
One.
Two.
Three.
Murong Chen.
Zhe Xiang.
I heard that your voice is so close.
But I cannot see you.
As expected.
Stop counting.
What's going on?
If my guess is correct,
we are in the same forest,
but not in the same time and space.
Not in the same time and space?
Is this...
- Parallel time and space.
This is so chuunibyo.
[*Excessive self-awareness of teenagers]
Chuunibyo?
It seems that I cannot get away from
the traps of this game.
I have to figure it out by myself.
(Chuunibyo.)
(Loyalty!)
[*Sounds like Chuunibyo in Chinese.]
We've been separated.
We'll meet when
we get out of the forest.
Mengmeng, you can be assured.
I'm definitely Chuunibyo.
What?
You don't believe me?
I...
I do. I do.
Why is it so difficult to understand
this straightforward guy's mind?
Chuunibyo.
Let's get out of here first!
OK?
Mengmeng,
don't worry.
I've been out for war for years.
I have experience in dealing with
getting lost.
Then do you know which direction
we should go next?
Just stick to one direction,
and keep going.
Keep going.
The worst situation is that
we might go around in circles.
Makes sense.
I have an idea.
Follow me.
Follow...
Whatever.
(It seems that it is the Walking Phantom
Formation of the Sec Master.)
You don't have to do anything.
All you have to do is
to stand the same side as
Jiang Mengmeng does,
stick with them,
and share life and death with them.
You have to protect yourself.
Don't get lost.
There are only me and you here.
Don't pretend it anymore.
I didn't get it.
What did I pretend?
As for Kung Fu,
Chang Kong and Song Che can protect you.
But you chose to team up with me.
You're afraid I'm going to hurt
Jiang Mengmeng, right?
I chose you
for my own safety.
If I'm with Song Che,
I would be killed.
Don't you know Chang Kong likes Xiao Ai?
Didn't you suspect that I
would hurt you?
If you want to hurt us,
you won't get involved in this.
(Such a good move by Sec Master.)
(She knows people well.)
If you harbor any malicious intentions,
you won't take any action now,
especially in here.
(Looks like he's not that simple.)
Mengmeng,
if you're afraid,
you can hold my hand.
No, thanks.
If there's some kind of trap,
I can protect you.
You fool!
If there's a trap
and you are holding my hand,
we'll fall in together.
Or you can hold me by the clothes.
Screw you!
Xiao Ai,
don't worry.
As long as we stay together,
I can get you out of here.
Oh no!
The sun is setting.
We cannot tell where we are then.
Do we have to get out of here by luck?
Da Huang.
It's my horse!
It found us!
Horse?
Mengmeng,
stay here and do not go anywhere.
I'll go after it.
It could bring us out of here.
Da Huang!
Where's the horse?
No!
(Southern Border Battlefield
in Phantom Land)
Uncle Qi, Happy Mid-Autumn Day!
Where did the money come from?
Did you steal from others?
Tell me.
(Ruined Temple of Liang City in Phantom Land)
Who did it?
Me.
Don't look.
It's the falcon of my brother.
(Senior,)
(I'm so scared.)
(I don't want to lose.)
Senior,
I am scared.
I don't want to die.
(Who will be my close disciple?)
(This trial will end if)
(one of you four dies.)
(In the Phantom Formation,)
(you would see the most terrifying)
(or solicitous thing in your life.)
(Let me see what are)
(in the most hidden corner)
(of your mind.)
Steal! Steal!
Uncle Qi, stop.
I picked that money up on the street.
This is not picking.
It's called stealing.
I didn't.
(This girl...)
Where did the money come from?
She is the girl in my dream.
Who is she?
You still think that you are right?
OK.
I'll show you
who you stole the money from.
Remember,
the world is full of difficult people.
Don't ruin other's life
just to keep yourself alive.
These are all my...
No!
These might be the memories of
young 9th princess.
When you were eight,
you sneaked out of the palace alone
and accidentally fell into the river.
You were wandering in the streets
for one year before they found you.
So these are my experiences
at the age of eight?
No wonder as the 9th princess
of Ruo Shui Kingdom,
I'm so money-hungry
and wild about ganghood.
(You have a butterfly
birthmark on your arm.)
(Zhuang Zhou fascinated about
the butterfly in his dream before dawn.)
(Then I'll call you Xiaomeng.)
[*Xiaomeng means a dream before dawn.]
Butterfly.
Xiaomeng.
So Xiaomeng is Jiang Mengmeng.
That is me.
Then A Mu and Uncle Qi are...
My hidden hero?
It can only be triggered
by this instance?
Brother.
It is above the forest.
(Young Murong Yi)
It can tell the direction for us.
Let's go.
Brother,
this time, I won't let it hurt you.
you'll be fine.
You will be able to stand up.
What is happening?
(Imperial Palace of Cang Yun Kingdom
in Phantom Land)
(Cang Yun Palace)
I am handicapped.
Why?
I thought I had changed everything.
Why is my brother still handicapped?
(Murong Chen.)
Who are you?
Who?
What do you want to do?
I want to watch you lose
every important person around you,
dying one by one.
Show yourself!
Who are you?
What happened?
Uncle Qi, where are we going?
Xiaomeng,
it's all my fault.
I got you into trouble.
Senior,
it is so urgent that
I can only find two helpers for help.
Junior,
sorry to bother you.
You have retreated
from the world with great effort.
And now you have to come back for us.
Retreat from the world?
Who is this Uncle Qi?
Please make sure to
protect both of them.
Got it.
Go, go!
I am tired.
(Do you think you could
get away with us?)
Go!
I want to know
how far you can run?
That's her.
The woman in my dream.
Uncle Qi, A Mu.
I'm so scared.
Don't be scared.
I will protect you.
Be careful!
A Mu!
So it was all real.
It can't be.
A Mu!
Being anger for a man and
crying for him,
is the worst thing you should
have ever done in your life.
However,
you won't have the future.
- A Mu.
- Senior.
- Junior.
None of us are going to
get away if it goes like this.
What about this?
Let's separate into two groups.
You'll take Xiaomeng with you.
I'll take A Mu.
OK.
Xiaomeng, let's go.
Let's go. Go!
A Mu.
I don't want to separate with you.
Xiaomeng,
I said I will protect you.
- Go! Go!
- No.
No!
A Mu!
Wait for me.
I'll go find you when I grow up.
I am...
I am A Mu.
Then I'll call you A Mu.
Cry!
I am sorry.
How could I forget all these?
Uncle Qi.
A Mu.
I am sorry!
Sorry!
No!
Those things just now...
are the past that I have forgotten.
No.
I am Jiang Mengmeng.
I am the leading lady of the game,
Jiang Mengmeng.
Those are memories of Xiaomeng.
Xiaomeng's.
But...
Why?
Those are the memories in the game,
not mine.
But...
A Mu!
Who am I?
I am Jiang Mengmeng.
And I am Xiaomeng.
Who am I?
(Xiaomeng.)
(Uncle Qi,)
(why did you name me Xiaomeng?)
(Because Zhuang Zhou fascinated about
the butterfly in his dream before dawn.)
(Zhuang Zhou dreamt
about the butterfly,)
(and the butterfly dreamt
about Zhuang Zhou.)
(Just like your situation now.)
(You forgot your name)
(and your past life.)
(But maybe one day,)
(you'll go back to where you come from.)
(And all the things here)
(will be like a dream to you.)
(But can you tell what is)
(the reality?)
Zhuang Zhou dreamt about the butterfly,
and the butterfly dreamt
about Zhuang Zhou.
Jiang Mengmeng and Xiaomeng
are in the same person.
Right.
I can be Jiang Mengmeng,
and I can be Xiaomeng.
Sweet love and heavy life,
I, Jiang Mengmeng, can handle them both.
Oh, Murong Chen and Song Che.
Uncle Qi!
Where are you?
Uncle Qi, where are you?
Uncle Qi!
It's all my fault.
My fault.
Uncle Qi!
A Mu, this blood night-blooming cereus
strike by Yu Qingzhu
has implanted the
cold poison to your body.
The medicine of Uncle Yun Zong
can only suppress the poisonousness
in your body temporarily.
Her Blood Moon Power
has not been practiced
to the highest level.
So there is no immediate
danger of death.
But you're not allowed to
use internal force in your whole life.
Hide inside.
Hide inside!
Uncle Qi,
what about you?
Uncle Qi will distract them.
Yun Qi died for you,
and you live just for
the sake of remaining alive,
not avenge him.
Do you deserve his sacrifice?
Right.
Avenge...
I have to avenge Uncle Qi.
But I...
But you can't!
You are a loser!
You cannot save your brother,
and you canot kill your enemy, either.
What is the meaning of your life?
You could kill yourself,
and then you can apologize to
Uncle Qi in the hell.
Do it.
Then you can be free.
This represents the lives of
all the brothers of Uncle Qi.
You must take good care of it.
Stay alive.
Don't avenge.
I remember...
Uncle Qi gave me Tian Ji Pavilion,
not for revenge.
Once, I thought about
leading members of Tian Ji Pavilion
to Jing Yue Sect for revenge.
But there is never
an end of taking revenge.
This is not what Uncle Qi wanted.
He wanted the same as I.
That is to try every effort
to protect who we want to protect.
♪With the singing of girls,
I passed the South♪
♪The scenery has come into my painting♪
♪Who would understand
my unrestrained affection♪
♪But as time goes by♪
♪I know she is my only one♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Traveling around and
talking about the world♪
♪With the sand underfoot, I laughed♪
♪Giving up all the fame and power♪
♪I just want to travel
all over the world♪
♪Brace the mountains and
ride with the wind♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪To watch life in the dream and
wake up in reality♪
♪Be cold-blooded
with no fear of the hatred♪
♪Having justice in your heart
makes you a hero already♪
♪Heroes should ride around the world♪
♪Where the heaven and earth become home♪
♪After riding through mountains,
the affection will fade away♪
♪Take the pain easy and drink to forget♪