[eerie music playing]
[eerie music intensifies]
[narrator in Sanskrit] 2,500 years ago,
a monster started opening the door
that bridges the human realm to hell
in order to make humans suffer.
But the Buddha appeared before the monster
and pulled out
the Red Eye and the Black Eye,
which were the source of his power.
However, both eyes
escaped the Buddha's hands
and started to run away from the Buddha.
The Black Eye was caught
by the Buddha soon enough
and was locked inside a sarira casket.
But the Red Eye,
on the other hand, managed to get away
by hiding inside people's bodies
and running away for seven nights.
Then, on the eighth night,
the Red Eye stopped and turned around,
thinking it had come far enough.
But upon realizing that the path
it had been on was actually a bridge
consisting of seven stepping stones
over a narrow, shallow stream,
the Red Eye learned that
it could never escape from the Buddha.
So it faked surrender
and voluntarily got into a sarira casket.
After sealing them
inside the caskets and locking them up
in the vast deserts of the West
and the steep cliffs of the East,
the Buddha said to his nameless disciples,
"You must make sure
they never meet again."
"That is your fate."
OCTOBER 2005- INDIA-PAKISTAN BORDER
[man in English] This is it.
I think I've figured out
the location of the sarira casket.
If it is here in the desert,
I can finally prove
the legend of the Diamond Sutra is true.
[eerie music playing]
[man] Okay. Bring that ladder in.
[indistinct chatter]
[breath trembling]
[chuckles]
[breathing heavily]
[laughs]
[laughing]
[dramatic music playing]
[reporter 1] The ancient relic is said
to prove the legend of the Diamond Sutra.
[reporter 2] To confirm authenticity,
scientists will test both relics.
[reporter 3] Results of the carbon dating
have come back negative.
[reporter 4] Authorities now suspect
Professor Kim Jun-cheol
deliberately forged the relic.
[reporter 5] Professor Kim
denies all the allegations
and vows to fight the charges,
saying people
will know the truth eventually.
[reporter 6] ...shunned by even
his closest friends in academia.
[reporter 7] Due to
Professor Kim's bizarre actions...
AFTER THE RELIC FORGERY CASE
...it looks like the case
will remain a mystery.
1ST SUPER BLUE BLOOD MOON IN 35 YRS
14 YEARS LATER
RED MOON TO BE SEEN TONIGHT
[grim music playing]
TOTAL LUNAR ECLIPSE
FROM 1 A.M. FOR 2 HOURS
[Jun-cheol] The sarira casket is fake?
The legend is a lie?
How stupid can you people be?
I tried...
I tried to tell you...
I didn't lie about any of it.
You people are the liars. You idiots!
The legend was true and I can prove it.
[clock bell tolling]
[clock ticking]
[in Sanskrit] "Do not awaken
what lies asleep here."
"On the night of the Red Moon,
the Red One will be roused from sleep
and return to the Black One."
"When they are reunited,
the world will turn into hell,
where only pain and darkness exist."
[eerie music playing]
[groans softly]
[in English] They'll know
I was telling the truth
when I open the door to hell.
[whimpering]
[chuckles]
I wasn't wrong.
I couldn't have been wrong.
[whimpering]
[screams]
[gasps]
[eerie music playing]
[grunting]
[man] Seonhwa,
it is time.
[coughing]
[grunting]
THE FIRST DAY
[drill instructor blowing whistle]
[workers grunting and grumbling]
[foreman] Hey, get this stuff outta here.
Let's move a little faster, huh?
[grunts]
- [worker 1] What did he use to do?
- [worker 2] I heard he was a monk.
- [worker 1] Come on.
- I'm telling you, seriously.
[worker 1 scoffs] A Buddhist monk? No way.
BUK-SAN, GWANGJU
[wind chimes ringing]
VOW OF SILENCE: SILENT MEDITATION
[man] Cheongseok.
[coughing]
[panting]
[clears throat]
Cheongseok, do you know that you have
been here almost two years now?
[chuckling]
But it is difficult not to talk?
I'm sure.
When we are forced to be quiet,
only then can we truly hear.
WHEN CAN I STOP?
[chuckling]
You can talk again
when I say you can talk again.
- [chuckling]
- [sighs]
Follow me.
[door opens]
Cheongseok.
Do you remember
the story about the monster?
WHY DIDN'T THE BUDDHA
GET RID OF THE MONSTER THEN?
No one can get rid of it,
not even the great Buddha himself.
But he found another way
to stop the monster
by taking its eyes and separating them,
Locking one away in the Far West,
and the other in the Far East.
For the Red One he created a desert,
far away from all life,
hidden deep in the ground.
The Black One, he locked away in the East,
behind rocky mountains and steep cliffs.
And then the Buddha sent two disciples,
a virgin and a nameless monk,
so they could stand guard
by the mountains and cliffs,
and make sure the monster
would never come back again.
But there will come a time.
The Red Eye in the West
will meet a helper.
On the night of the Red Moon,
the Eye will be freed.
And then it will come, one by one,
through seven stepping stones
for seven nights
to find its other half.
But if the Eyes are reunited
on the eighth night...
Then the monster will be unstoppable.
So it falls upon us
to make sure that doesn't happen.
We will have to remove
one of the stepping stones,
should it come to that.
Take any one stone out of the path,
and the Red Eye won't be able
to reunite with the Black One.
Cheongseok.
Did you forget to clean?
I can see dirt on the Urna.
Please wipe it off right away.
[door creaks open]
CHILGOK, NORTH GYEONGSANG PROVINCE
[hunter] Damn, too small.
[grunts]
Huh?
[eerie music playing]
What the...
[breathing heavily]
[creature laughing menacingly]
THE SECOND DAY
- [man] What does he do?
- [woman] Not sure.
He said he's a professor.
- [man] How did you meet him?
- [woman] Through this meditation group.
Well, they call it a meditation group,
but it's more like a cult.
I don't know.
I thought it'd be helpful.
- Did you do it, then? Was it helpful?
- Sure.
At least a little bit.
Got a free checkup out of it.
- What kind of checkup?
- It was no big deal.
They just ran a few tests on me,
took some blood.
So you went for the checkup?
[scoffs] No, of course not.
They actually paid me to keep coming back.
Would you say no to that?
- They paid you?
- Mmm-hmm.
- [chuckles]
- [thunder rumbling]
[bell chiming]
FOUR SEASONS
[sniffing]
[clicking tongue]
- [hunter sniffing]
- [woman continues clicking tongue]
[door opens]
[eerie music playing]
[gasps softly]
[man] Did you have a nightmare?
Cheongseok.
Good or bad,
the dreams don't stay with us forever.
We must try to hold on to them.
We must not let them sway us.
The time has come.
Find Seonhwa.
SEONHWA
Tell him...
the monster is here.
[wind chime ringing]
[sighs]
THE THIRD DAY
[sniffling]
FOUR SEASONS - WELCOME
[officer 1 on radio] He just arrived.
[officer 2] Okay, copy that.
Let me know when he's up.
- I'll bring in a coroner and cleanup crew.
- [detective sighs]
[officer 1 on radio] Perimeter secured...
Hey, did we get a photo
of this shoeprint over here?
- [forensic officer] No, I don't think so.
- Well, why not?
Did you see it? What is this shit?
Hey, this should go
all the way around, don't you see?
- Oh.
- Such morons.
[bell chiming]
[sighs]
- [detective 1] Who called it in?
- [detective 2] Hotel owner.
- Any witnesses?
- No other guests at the hotel.
On weekdays,
it's like a ghost town around here.
- Hey, hey, over your shoes.
- Oh, please.
The owner of the motel was asleep
at the time of the incident.
Did the camera get anything?
Oh, yeah, right. About 11:45 last night,
the victim or, uh, suspect...
What should I call 'em?
What do you mean
what should you call 'em? You stupid?
See for yourself.
The body in the shower is the male.
But the female was gone.
- [camera shutter clicking]
- [groans] Female?
Yeah, this guy checked in together
with a woman named Seo Gyeong-suk.
CCTV has her leaving the hotel
right after the incident.
Where'd you get her name from?
She left all her stuff behind,
including her purse.
[detective 1] Have you
put out an APB out on her?
[detective 2] Yes, sir.
[camera shutter clicking]
[suspenseful music playing]
What about him, there?
[detective 2] That's the one
I was talking about before.
Cameras show he was fine
when he walked into the room, but...
So I guess he's both
the suspect and the victim.
SEONHWA
[monk 1] Shouldn't we let Seonhwa know?
- [monk 2] Do you know where he is?
- [monk 1] Yes.
- [monk 2] Don't.
- [monk 1] But Master Hajeong is...
[monk 2] Let's not bother him.
[monk 1] But then
what do we do about the funeral?
[monk 2] We'll keep it simple.
He would have wanted it that way.
Vow of silence?
For how long?
You know you could stop
now that he's gone.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE MONK SEONHWA IS?
Mmm.
I WILL BE BACK BEFORE THE FUNERAL
- CHEONGSEOK
[eerie music playing]
[voice 1] Bhante Seonhwa.
[voice 2 crying] He's no monk.
[voice 3] He's not?
[voice 2] No, he's nothing.
[voice 4] If he's not a monk,
he can't help us.
[voice 3] How much longer
do we have to wait?
[voices clamoring]
[voice 4] You have to help us!
[voices whispering and clamoring]
[clamoring intensifies]
[voices stop]
THE FOURTH DAY
DAEJEON STATION
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct announcement on PA]
4-91 EUNHAENG-DONG, JUNG-GU DAEJEON
[gasping]
[camera shutter clicking]
[detective 2] We found
Seo Gyeong-suk inside the stall,
dead, just like the other one.
[detective 1] Let's think about this.
These two check in together.
This guy comes in later.
Now, if we had found these two dead,
we'd have a much simpler case,
wouldn't we?
But we find him.
And she leaves the hotel in one piece.
Doesn't call anyone, leaves her stuff.
Then today, we find her dead
in a park restroom.
Grotesque and deformed,
just like the body at the motel.
[officer yawns]
So what happened here?
I want theories.
You, what's yours?
Mmm...
- Me?
- What do you think?
Uh, well...
It... It's a weird one
and we have no clue
why the corpses look like that.
Yeah?
But I have a friend who,
when they had a case they couldn't solve,
he, uh...
[smacks lips]
- I don't know. Never mind.
- Just spit it out.
- Come on, what did your friend do?
- Well...
that one was a tough case.
They spent some time
trying to catch a rapist,
so eventually he ended up
going to a psychic.
Psychic?
He told me she was very good.
I'm sure she is. At stealing.
[cell phone ringing]
CHIEF
[sighs]
PERFORMANCE EVALUATION FOR PROMOTION
[chief] What are you going
to do about Dong-jin?
You need to pull the trigger.
Don't you think?
Uh-huh.
It's hard enough with the ones
that don't have his issues.
- [groans]
- [chief] He's got the limp.
He can barely see anything.
When are you gonna do it?
I got so mad at him yesterday,
I told him to quit.
But he said
he'd have to talk to you first.
It's not your fault he's like that.
You have to stop
blaming yourself for the accident.
Keeping him around
only makes it worse for the others.
It's time to let him go, okay?
[indistinct chatter]
[waitress 1] Why does
he always take this with him?
[waitress 2] Maybe he gives it to his dog?
[reporter on radio] Coming up next,
a man in his sixties who was arrested
after assaulting his neighbor...
[panting]
[exclaims softly]
MONK SEONHWA?
MONK HAJEONG HAS PASSED AWAY.
HE SAID TO TELL YOU
THAT THE MONSTER IS HERE.
[suspenseful music playing]
- [stomach growls]
- [Seonhwa sighs]
[pen scratching]
I'M SORRY.
I LOST THE THING MONK HAJEONG LEFT BEHIND.
[sighs deeply]
[suspenseful music playing]
Miss, is everything okay?
Hey, we met
in that meditation group, right?
[gasps softly]
But what's wrong?
What happened to you?
[bone cracks]
[eerie music playing]
[bones cracking]
[sniffs]
VIRGIN SHAMAN
[eerie music playing]
[wind chimes ringing]
[eerie music intensifies]
[man sniffing]
[sniffing stops]
[snoring softly]
[Hajeong] Your eyes
are still filled with anger.
I thought I should see you,
so I came with the boy.
You know what I've told you before.
You know what you must do,
help the souls cross over.
It is your fate
until the day you die, Seonhwa.
There are thousands
of souls counting on you.
Waiting on you to ascend.
[souls murmuring]
Now he's here,
using the stepping stones, one by one.
You must find the one we know.
The last stepping stone.
- The woman. The virgin.
- [wind chimes ringing]
You must find her before he does.
And then...
kill her.
[door creaks open]
[snoring softly]
[solemn music playing]
[Hajeong] It is the fate
of those who stand guard.
When the time comes, do it.
VIRGIN SHAMAN
45-12 SINPUNG-DONG, PALDAL-GU, SUWON
[somber piano music playing]
TO MR. PARK JIN-SU
[gasps]
THE FIFTH DAY
[dramatic music playing]
[blacksmith hammering]
[indistinct chatter]
[laughs]
[Cheongseok slurping loudly]
[spoon clatters]
Wait up!
Thank you so much.
VOW OF SILENCE
[gasps]
[whimpering]
[woman] Where are you headed?
[indistinct announcement on PA]
[Cheongseok] What is that?
[woman] What's your destination, sir?
[reporter on TV] A woman in her forties,
and the lead suspect
in the Daegu motel murders,
was found dead
inside a park bathroom in Daegu.
Police are combing through
CCTV footage to retrace her steps
in hopes of finding witnesses.
Sources say the police think
Seo may have had an accomplice.
I can't accept that, but...
can I maybe come with you, instead?
Master told me that we have
to stay together, no matter what.
46-9 SINPUNG-DONG, PALDAL-GU, SUWON
[suspenseful music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[scanner beeping]
By the way, I keep thinking
we've met somewhere before?
I feel very comfortable
around you for some reason.
Like we knew each other before.
And I'm not saying this just
because you bought me brand-new shoes...
and all this great food.
I swear it's not just 'cause of that.
[chuckling] I just mean...
[clears throat]
[man] Your life is full of sin.
[footsteps approaching]
[intense music playing]
Searching for someone?
Well...
The woman back at the store told me
you were looking for a psychic.
I heard she moved to Daegu a year ago.
I don't know the exact address.
But what I do know
is that if you go there,
you die.
How can it be unknown?
[Dong-jin on phone] The NFS just sent back
the autopsy and toxicology reports,
but cause of death
is still listed unknown.
[detective] Well, what does
the report actually say?
Okay, so there are a few things...
Oh, Jesus, come on,
just read me exactly what it says.
"The bodies decomposed overnight
resulting in severe tissue damage..."
Wait, what does this...
[softly] The hell
is this shit about now? [sighs]
[normally] Is that all?
It also says each victim
had a hole in the skull.
But that they need to run
more tests to figure out why.
[police officers speaking indistinctly]
Are you sure this is the official report?
You didn't call in some backwoods
private investigator, right?
No, but get this, I was looking
at the corpses again today,
and it's bizarre, but...
Remember the psychic
I was talking about the other day?
- I went to see her...
- Yeah, I already told you to drop that.
Did you put the suspect
on the lookout list yet?
- Yes, sir.
- And the victim?
Twenty-eight-year-old female,
reported missing two days ago.
Went out to meet a friend
and never came back.
- Apparently she didn't have a job.
- No one has a job after they're dead.
Huh?
- [groans] Jesus, that smell.
- [coughing]
- Some gloves?
- Oh, yeah.
[suspenseful music playing]
[flies buzzing]
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
WHO ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
God, how can you always be this annoying?
It's a bus full of empty seats.
Why do you have to sit by me?
[chuckles]
- Just say it.
- Can I really talk again?
[sighs in relief]
Thank you, Bhante Seonhwa.
- It's a relief to...
- Don't call me that ever again.
What? Why not?
- Then what should I call you?
- [sighs]
[chuckles]
[suspenseful music playing]
[eerie music playing]
[compass rattling]
[thunder rumbling]
DAEGU BUS TERMINAL
[woman] I am going to take
my own life to pay for what I did.
I know it's a lot to ask of you,
but please, look after my son, Jeong-hun.
He has no one else left.
I can never apologize enough
to Mr. Park Jin-su and his family,
but I am sorry.
[voices clamoring angrily]
[soul] Kill him!
[clamoring intensifies]
- [Hajeong] You fool!
- [clamoring stops]
[breathing heavily]
THE SIXTH DAY
[snoring softly]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [indistinct announcement on PA]
Where'd he go?
[sighs]
Bhante.
I thought you'd left.
When I woke up, I couldn't find you and...
I was worried you might...
So Master Hajeong
actually... told you to stay with me?
- [server] Enjoy your meal.
- [kid] Thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
[Seonhwa] The motel, the restroom.
Happy?
You could do this yourself.
Look, it's a double burger now. [laughing]
Listen. See this area?
We need to visit
every single psychic in here.
We'll split.
The park restroom is just over there,
so you could start here
and work your way toward...
That's one banana.
You gotta be kidding me.
[intense music playing]
Stay alert and make sure
to meet me back here at sundown.
You like that?
Yeah, even better than I remember.
I had it once before
when Master Hajeong took me to the...
[dramatic music playing]
GYOBANG GIL 91
GYOBANG 2-GIL 37- 141
GEUMJEONGSA
WOMAN'S DEAD BODY FOUND
IN SEWER BY DAEGU TUNNEL
[reporter on TV] However, due to the state
of decomposition the body was found in,
authorities believe
the incident happened quite some time ago.
VIRGIN SHAMAN
What?
[rain pattering]
- [Dong-jin on phone] Where are you, sir?
- [detective] At the scene, why?
- Chief's looking for you.
- All right, then. Tell him I'll head in.
[suspenseful music playing]
[dispatcher over radio]
Responding to the 10-34 call.
We're on our way.
[eerie music playing]
[eerie breathing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Hang on.
Can you show me some ID?
[backpack unzips]
Hey, real quick.
- [Dong-jin] Yeah?
- Need you to look up someone.
Park Jin-su, 750121-1046899.
[dispatcher over radio] Patrol 7 here.
Yeah, we've got another
dead body over by Daegu High School.
[Dong-jin] Uh, not much. Just a fine
for causing a disturbance in court.
[Ho-tae] Okay, thanks.
One more thing.
I'm gonna need to look in your backpack.
- [thrilling music playing]
- [both panting]
[both grunting]
[both exclaim]
[Ho-tae groans]
[grunts]
[suspenseful music playing]
I'm sorry,
but have we met somewhere before?
[ringing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[eerie music playing]
[growls]
[gasps]
DAEGU JUNGBU POLICE STATION
[Dong-jin] You all right?
What do you got?
Okay, so, first off,
the body found by the high school?
Turns out it's the delivery guy
from the tunnel.
Same thing, found decomposed.
What the hell is happening here?
[groaning]
Okay, look here.
NAME: PARK JIN-SU
Your little sparring partner
used to work construction.
But he ended up leaving the job
two days before the first case.
So I found his office manager
and called him up.
Turns out, back in 1999,
his wife and his five-year-old daughter
were killed in a car accident.
The other woman was driving drunk,
but when she went to the court,
she got her sentence reduced.
[Ho-tae] So that explains
the disturbance in court.
"2005, Assault"? What's that?
After the accident,
this guy goes and becomes a monk.
[Ho-tae] A Buddhist monk?
He ends up joining a temple in Gwangju.
And apparently, it's known for exorcism.
- More psychics, then?
- I didn't... What I meant was more...
He's kinda like an exorcist...
Stop messing around already.
Just get to the point.
But this is the point.
He beat an actual demon out of the person.
That's a poor excuse.
But they did reach a settlement.
What about this fraud charge?
Well, after the Jogye Order of Monks
helped him settle the assault case,
they actually found
Park had never even been a real monk.
Is that so?
Simply put, if he was a real monk,
they would have known about it.
So in reality, we have no idea who he is.
[sighs] So that means
we're back to square one.
DAEGU JUNGBU POLICE PRECINCT MAP
Anyway, this other thing
happened this morning...
- Hey, Dong-jin.
- Huh?
Shut up.
[intense music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[Seonhwa] Come on.
[Dong-jin] Oh, wait.
Before I forget... Here.
What's this?
Some underwear and socks.
My wife bought extra for you.
Oh, wow, that's so nice of her.
I got something else. Take this, too.
[Ho-tae] What's this?
Remember that psychic
I told you about? It's from her.
- Jesus Christ.
- Hey, wait!
Don't destroy it. Do you know
how much I paid for that talisman?
Not just money, I bled for this.
She used my own blood to give it power.
Fuck. How did you ever get hired
to do this job in the first place, huh?
Just keep it on you.
It wards off evil, you know?
And who knows?
Maybe it'll help you catch the killer.
Hey, why don't we get rid
of detectives altogether?
Let the psychics do the job for us.
Bro, what do you always say to me?
"It takes everything we have
to catch these guys."
How do you feel?
You better?
I'd say so.
Legs are better now. Eyes, too.
[automated voice] The light
has turned green. You may now cross.
Hey, you really don't need
to worry about me, you know?
It was an accident. Not your fault.
When I jumped in the water,
desperate to end it all,
who was there to pull me out?
In fact... [chuckles]
If you hadn't saved me from that,
I honestly... I wouldn't...
I wouldn't be a detective now.
That's why I have to keep at it.
I owe you that much.
MAP OF DAEGU
[Seonhwa] You didn't see
a female psychic anywhere in here?
[mouse clicking]
What about this place here?
Or maybe over here?
This is where you were, isn't it?
Click there.
- [mouse clicks]
- To the right.
Zoom in there.
But wait, I haven't told you
about what else I saw.
[flashlight clicks]
[Dong-jin] What is this?
The second he heard
about the body on the radio,
his whole face changed.
- Your pen.
- Oh.
[Ho-tae] This is the tunnel.
The high school.
And the restroom.
[officer 1] No new missing person
reports in the past few days,
but there is one runaway.
Except it's nothing new.
She's a repeat offender.
She usually comes back home
after a week or two.
Her mother always throws a fit, though.
Last time,
she was here bawling, screaming,
saying her daughter
was going to kill herself.
Kill herself?
Yeah. She had just joined
some suicide website and then took off.
But from what I recall,
I think she must have come back
just a few days later. Wasn't it?
[officer 2] But it wasn't
a suicide website.
Remember? It just turned out
to be a meditation group.
But it was for people
who had attempted suicide.
- [Ho-tae groans]
- [Dong-jin] Hmm.
[Ho-tae] Hmm.
[Seonhwa] Are you sure
that's what you saw?
You're positive?
[Cheongseok] What was that thing?
Listen carefully.
You need to leave right now.
If anyone asks, say you don't know me.
We've never met, you've never seen me.
Tell them you don't know me at all.
[Cheongseok gasps]
How could I say that
after everything that's happened?
- I could still go with you...
- [grunts]
- You need to go back now.
- Don't make me.
I came all this way.
Whatever it is you're about to do,
you don't have to leave me behind.
[intense music playing]
You think it's easy...
to murder someone?
Because that's what I have to do.
Do you understand now?
Who... Who do you have to kill?
- The girl I saw in the alley?
- Not her, she can't be killed now.
Who, then?
[gasps]
[somber music playing]
You understand I have to stop it.
And if the monster's back,
she's as good as dead already.
- I don't get it.
- And I don't have time to explain.
I have to...
stop him now, no matter what it takes.
That is my role to play here.
I'm sorry.
- Are you coming or what?
- No, you go ahead.
Okay.
One more thing.
- I received another call earlier today.
- What call?
Apparently, this morning,
another dead body
was found in the Chilgok mountains.
They did tell me it must have been old,
but I'm not so sure.
One of ours?
[Dong-jin] Based on the description,
I think it definitely sounded
like it could be one of ours.
- Did you check it?
- Of course I did.
Phone records, e-mails,
bank statements, the whole deal.
I'm on it, boss.
Come on, you know
you can always count on me, eh?
- Go! [sighs]
- [chuckles]
[car door opens and closes]
[dog barking]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [dramatic music playing]
- [panting]
[breathing heavily]
[creaking]
[Ho-tae panting]
[dramatic music playing]
[Cheongseok] We gotta get out of here.
Come on!
You have to come with me.
Please.
- [cell phone ringing]
- [sighs heavily]
- Yeah.
- [Dong-jin] So about the body in Chilgok.
- It's definitely one of ours.
- What did you find?
Name, Kim Jun-cheol. Anthropologist.
He forged some kind of relic a while back,
which caused a whole scandal.
He left academia and started, get this,
a Buddhist meditation website.
But only for suicidal people.
So that's the one.
All of our dead bodies were members.
They're all in this photo
from an in-person meetup in Daegu.
Except for two of them,
all of these people were found
in the rapidly-decomposed state.
But the other two people
I see in that photo...
- Who are they?
- Well, it's...
It's almost hard to believe.
One's the runaway girl
we heard about back at the station.
And the other
is the psychic I went to see.
The one who made the talisman.
They have to be connected.
- And where are you now?
- At the office.
Okay, check out the psychic.
Send me the address now.
And make sure you
meet me there as soon as you can.
[dramatic music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
- [door rattles]
- [gasps softly]
[suspenseful music playing]
[eerie music playing]
- [both grunting]
- [dramatic music playing]
Gotcha, bastard.
[Seonhwa groaning]
Not gonna lose you again.
[grunts]
[sniffing]
You can run.
But you can't hide.
[sniffing]
[grunting]
[wincing]
[thrilling music playing]
OM
- [soul 1] Coward. He's done for, now.
- [souls whispering]
[whispering intensifies]
[soul 2] Your life is over.
[soul 3] You are nothing.
[whispering stops]
[grunts]
[cell phone ringing]
Fine then. Just ignore my call.
Didn't I come this way last time?
It should be here.
Whoa, what the... That looks like...
[girl whimpering]
- Are you okay?
- It's him, it's him!
[sobbing]
Don't move.
Drop your weapon. Put it down!
[suspenseful music playing]
[sniffing]
[eerie music playing]
[eerie music intensifies]
[dispatcher] Got an emergency call
coming in from the redevelopment district.
[officer] This is Patrol 8.
We're on our way.
We're close by.
Heading over there right now.
- [siren wailing]
- That way.
[tires screech]
[bones crack]
[Seonhwa yelling]
[Seonhwa grunting]
[grunts]
[yells]
[grunting]
[choking]
[sizzling]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[panting]
[in Sanskrit] This is not
where you'll die.
Go to Buk-San.
[siren blares]
[in English] Hey, you two.
What's going on over here?
Cut him off! Go!
Patrol 8 to dispatch,
we need backup now. Are you listening?
[vehicle approaching]
Take them.
Gwangju for two.
THE SEVENTH DAY
Hmm?
Master Hajeong?
[panting]
[footsteps approaching]
GO TO BUK-SAN AND YOU WILL FIND
WHAT YOU ARE LOOKING FOR.
Gwangju, please.
I can't go all the way
out there this late.
- Okay, then just take me to the terminal.
- Sure.
[Seonhwa] Taxi!
Taxi! [grunts]
- Gwangju!
- [man] Last bus already left.
First bus is in three hours.
GO TO BUK-SAN AND YOU WILL FIND
WHAT YOU ARE LOOKING FOR.
[Seonhwa] I need to find
the last stepping stone.
The woman, the virgin.
But...
[solemn music playing]
[Hajeong] You're afraid?
Of course you are. Everyone runs away
when faced with fear.
Pity.
All of your souls have left you.
That only means one thing.
It's already done.
The Black Eye has already
stepped on the last stone.
They must have thought you would die soon.
You're all that's left now.
You cannot run away from this duty.
It is your fate
to see it through to the end.
It transferred to you the second I died.
And it will be the same if you die.
Your fate will pass to a new successor.
[Cheongseok] Bhante Seonhwa!
[Hajeong] So... what will you do now?
[young Cheongseok] Sir?
[Cheongseok's mother] I'm sorry.
[young Cheongseok] Why did my mom die?
[bus horn honks]
[dramatic music playing]
Gwangju.
[Ho-tae] That makes no sense!
He has a wife and a kid.
He would never do something like that.
[officer] Calm down.
We're looking into it.
Maybe someone took his gun and his car.
[telephone ringing]
[Ho-tae] Move.
PLATE NUMBER: 23S 7657
Buk-San, please.
[thunder rumbling]
Because he told us to keep it simple.
Don't you think we should do what he...
[screeching in distance]
[eerie music playing]
Let me call you back.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[objects clattering]
What are you doing?
Stop!
- [gunshots]
- [monk grunts]
[in demonic voice] How does it feel
for you to know, old man,
that you have failed so spectacularly now?
[screeching in distance]
[Ho-tae] Any witnesses?
[officer] A few said
they heard the commotion.
But no one could really see anything.
[sarcastically] That's just great.
We need to prove this wasn't Dong-jin.
Yes, sir.
[sighs]
[flags fluttering]
[screeching in distance]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Cheongseok] Are you getting tired?
[breathing heavily]
My name's Cheongseok, by the way.
May I ask your name?
My name?
Ae-ran.
[suspenseful music playing]
Who's here with you?
[gasps]
[psychic] When I first saw her,
I didn't know she was a ghost.
But no one else there
could even see that she was with us.
[somber music playing]
That night, she followed me home.
And told me what had happened to her.
She had been abused
and only saw life as a curse.
She just wanted it to end.
[footsteps approaching]
Then one day,
a man came, like a savior.
[Jun-cheol] Come with me.
[psychic] But happiness
always seems to be...
short-lived.
Liars! Why would you say that?
I was right.
I know I was right.
The prophecy is clear.
"The red-eyed maid
will bewitch the virgin."
I have to find this maid.
Someone who will give herself
as a sacrificial offering.
Do you think I'm crazy?
I know no one else will believe me,
but you will, won't you?
The virgin who guards the path
is the last stepping stone.
Someone will have to sacrifice.
Someone who can bewitch the virgin.
Someone.
I know no one else will believe me,
but you will, won't you?
[wind chime ringing]
[Ae-ran] When someone you love
tells you something,
you want to believe it's true, even when...
you know it isn't.
[psychic] Maybe that's
why life is such a tragedy.
[gasps]
- It came back.
- Or maybe it never left.
[mysterious music playing]
Gwangju for two.
Buk-San, please.
[psychic] The other detective?
He was here.
He came to me a few days ago.
I made him a talisman with his blood.
How could he have known
that he was already destined to die, too?
The whole meditation group,
no one there realized the awful truth.
That their deaths had been
written in stone a long time ago.
They were only alive
because they didn't die
when they tried to kill themselves before.
But he brought them all together there.
How he found them, I don't know.
He took a blood sample
from each one of them
to create the stepping stones.
So that the Red One
could find them
by the smell of their blood.
And pass through them one by one
to return to the Black One.
And then...
[gasps]
[whimpering]
[choking]
- Stop it!
- [panting]
Don't you see? The other detective,
he's the last stepping stone now.
The girl kept me here
so I couldn't escape.
Ae-ran promised me I could live
if I just let him take my place.
But he already wanted to kill himself.
He already did, he wasn't...
[breath trembling]
You are the one who made this possible.
Don't you see?
He was supposed to die,
but you pulled him out of the water.
[psychic laughing maniacally]
None of this would have
happened if you had just let him die.
Why would you come to me
when this is on you?
Get out.
Buk-San is waiting.
There's only one way this ends.
You have to go to that mountain.
It's either him or us.
[solemn music playing]
Leave me.
And where would I go?
Follow my lead.
Got it?
[dramatic music playing]
We're gonna set a trap.
I'll be its bait.
You will follow my exact instructions,
no matter what he tries.
Your clothes will be your talisman.
They'll protect you.
That should do it.
[psychic] Go to Buk-San.
You'll find what you're looking for.
[Dong-jin] I wouldn't be a detective now.
I owe you that much.
DAEGU
[dramatic music continues]
[Cheongseok] What will happen
when the sarira casket is opened?
[Seonhwa] The Black Eye
and the Red Eye will reunite as one.
[Cheongseok] What do the Eyes symbolize?
[Seonhwa] When you live in fear,
waiting for the unknown,
that's anxiety.
When you live in sadness,
dwelling on the pain of the past,
that's agony.
The eyes of the anxious
are dark and have no life.
The eyes of agony burn hot with anger.
So anxiety is black and agony is red.
One or the other would be enough
to make us suffer forever.
So what do you think will happen
if they are allowed to become one again?
What kind of world will this be
if we're eternally stuck
between anger and despair?
Agony and anxiety?
That is a world of endless night.
That is...
a world...
[in Sanskrit] That is hell.
THE EIGHTH DAY
[Seonhwa grunting]
[grim music playing]
[Seonhwa in English]
No running from this now.
[dramatic music playing]
[chanting in Sanskrit]
[screeching in distance]
[chanting continues]
- [gasps]
- [chanting stops]
[screeching in distance]
[footsteps approaching]
[sinister music playing]
[Seonhwa chanting in Sanskrit]
[in English] I'm his last target.
Once he's inside the trap,
he'll take over my body.
That is when you must strike.
[dramatic music playing]
[in Sanskrit] You are foolish.
[in English] Do you want to know why?
You made a miscalculation.
A big one.
I need the guard to open the sarira.
And you, as Monk Hajeong's successor,
should be the one I need.
And you would be.
[continues chanting]
Except...
you decided to run away
from this place, didn't you?
Which means that you're
no longer the guard here, are you?
[dramatic music playing]
OM
Which means,
you serve no purpose.
[in Sanskrit] You're useless.
[in English] So...
kill yourself.
[in Sanskrit] Ae-ran... find him.
[chains rattling]
Ae-ran!
[exhales slowly]
OM
[somber music playing]
[gunshot in distance]
[in English] Dong-jin! Are you there?
[growls]
[Seonhwa screaming]
[wind chimes ringing]
[deep rhythmic chanting]
[souls screeching]
[grunts]
[sinister music playing]
Run! Save yourself!
You must go!
[breath trembling]
[dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
[souls screeching]
[panting]
[grunting]
[Cheongseok grunts]
[footsteps approaching]
[sinister music playing]
[gasping]
It is you.
You idiot.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
[groaning]
- You have to get out. You have to run.
- Dong-jin.
[groaning]
[whimpering]
Go away! Stop!
[gunshot]
[shudders]
- [bones cracking]
- [gasping]
[gun clicks]
Go!
[snarling]
[Cheongseok] No! Please!
- Leave me!
- [Seonhwa yells]
- [gunshot]
- [Seonhwa exclaims]
[groaning]
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
[Ho-tae grunts]
Dong-jin.
[growls softly]
[breathing shallowly]
[sinister music playing]
[in demonic voice] What a pest you are.
[grunts]
[Dong-jin] Ho-tae.
- Come with me.
- Go...
to...
hell.
Not the kid.
Leave him. You can have me.
Now you care for him, do you?
He's the son of the woman
who killed your family.
That hatred still burns inside you.
[rumbling]
[somber music playing]
Let's go.
I can't...
reach...
the light.
Family is
the most important thing in the world.
You've suffered so much without them.
This is your last chance
to put an end to it now.
[sobs]
It's not too late to make it right again.
An eye for an eye.
Like that night when you left the temple.
Take my life.
- Take it like they took yours.
- [straining]
And then your suffering,
your pain, your hell,
will all disappear.
[sobbing]
[somber music playing]
[solemn music playing]
[in Sanskrit] You gave up your last chance
to put an end to your pent-up
anguish and resentment.
You are still unbelievably foolish.
- [Seonhwa grunts]
- [gasps]
[Seonhwa chanting in Sanskrit]
OM
[heroic music playing]
[straining]
[continues chanting in Sanskrit]
[gasps]
[whimpering]
- [Cheongseok screams]
- [in English] Do it!
Son...
I'm sorry for everything.
[sobbing]
[music intensifies]
[yelling]
- [blow lands]
- [thunder rumbling]
[Hajeong] We wouldn't know light
if not for the darkness.
[peaceful music playing]
The deeper our sorrow,
the greater our appreciation
for nirvana will be.
What is our life...
if not like the leaf on the tree.
Vibrant now,
destined to grow frail and then fall.
Like shadows, dewdrops, and lightning.
It is truly fleeting.
But even the most trivial moments
in our predetermined fate
are meaningful as pieces of the whole.
Seonhwa.
Now that you've found that meaning,
it is time for you to wake up
from your dark dream.
[Seonhwa exhales slowly]
[solemn music playing]
[wind chimes ringing]
[uplifting orchestral music playing]
[dramatic music playing]