[English subtitles are available]
This Li Qian
is so sarcastic when she speaks.
No one knows what she's thinking.
She even caused
such burden to us in work.
That's a different matter.
She donated the books with good intention.
If you ask me,
donating book is secondary.
Her aim is to show off to us.
I remember, today,
you didn't do a lot of work either.
The few remaining big boxes
were carried by me and Mr. Ai,
right?
True.
Oh, right, Mr. Ai.
You're the hero of the day.
Wan Xia,
so,
my husband is here to pick me up.
I'll get going.
You two,
good luck.
Goodbye.
Let's go.
Zeng Li,
today, it seems
you've been avoiding me.
[Why didn't I realize before]
[that his mouth shape is so nice?]
[-They seem soft.]
-Zeng Li,
[It's more than that.]
[They're indeed quite soft.]
Zeng Li!
Must be my imagination.
We had an appointment this afternoon
to clean braces.
You also stood me up at the last minute.
[Zeng Li, what are you trying to do?]
[Don't tell me you're thinking
to force your lips on him?]
[You hooligan.]
Don't you have to work today?
I forgot to tell you
when I made the appointment.
Is there something on my mouth?
No.
I just feel that they're nice.
You can work as a lipstick model.
[I really admire myself.]
[Why am I saying
all these sensible stuff?]
The weather's quite nice.
Why don't we take a walk?
So, what did Aunt say?
My mother said,
lazy people like me
will never amount to anything.
Working as a librarian,
probably few more years later,
I'll be too embarrassed
to attend high school reunion party.
But,
that's how I am
as a person.
I dislike complicated
interpersonal relationships
and reading books is my hobby.
When I have time to spare,
I'll eat and drink with my good friends.
It makes us happy.
Could Mr. Ai look down on me
because I'm lazy?
Liu Yu Cheng once mentioned
you follow your daily routine strictly.
Work, studies, gym,
reading books,
everyday without fail.
He exaggerated.
I also often use my time
to go to gym and study
to take a walk
and chat with you.
I feel guilty.
I seem to have influenced the
respectable Mr. Ai in a negative manner.
Well, I don't think
it's a bad thing.
On the contrary, I think
you're quite amazing.
Are you trying to make me feel better?
Really.
You
aren't influenced by how others view you,
nor
let your family decide what you'll do.
You chose a job that you like
as well as lifestyle,
that in itself is a
terrific achievement.
I'm not as good as you say.
If I really
have no self-doubt,
just now,
I wouldn't be so upset.
It's normal.
I also often
have moments of self-doubt,
but making choices usually represent
your own attitude.
Take me for example,
I seem to have chosen
a path which others regard
of as relatively successful,
but in fact I've given up
what I wanted to do a long time ago.
Mr. Ai, what is it
you wanted to do the most?
Have a guess.
Scientist?
Entrepreneur?
No,
these are
what's defined as really
successful people.
If it has to be an ambition that's unique
and niche...
A rockstar?
More or less.
I wanted to be a manga artist.
Mr. Ai,
that's a stark contrast
with your current profession.
When I was younger, I saw
the male classmates in my class
read manga often.
I also enjoyed reading it.
I wanted to join them,
but they thought
I was strange.
How can the first place in our grade
like to
read manga?
When my grandmother heard of it,
she also prohibited me from doing so,
saying it'll affect my studies.
Since then,
I'd wait until they fell asleep
to read in secret.
Although when I become older,
I'm free to do what I want,
but I've always kept this habit.
Following a strict routine
is also my habit since young.
It's all for the 60 minutes
with most freedom
before sleep.
Seems like Mr. Ai
also grew up
like any other usual male.
If I think of it this way, you seem
much more approachable.
Which is why,
you have to stick to
what you want to do.
You have my support.
Actually,
your mouth shape is also very nice.
[Sweet Teeth]
[Episode 11]
How are things going on between
you and your older girlfriend?
What did you mean?
Don't call her that.
She seems to be quite busy lately.
She hasn't been talking to me often
and didn't respond when
I ask her to play game.
Weren't you really close not long ago?
Since when has it become this way?
It's that night
of our winning streak under my lead.
I suggest you
to download Camps of Kings.
Hurry.
[Wu Ying]
She
came to check my battle result last night.
32 visit counts,
but only 12 headcounts are recorded.
Do you know what it means?
What?
You fool.
She alone at least visited your account
20 times.
That means she cares about me.
So why is she ignoring me?
She's jealous.
She thinks you and Xia Xia
play online game with each other everyday
and fell out of love with her.
Your profile picture is Xia Xia?
You just realized?
I didn't notice.
I thought it's just an
image you found online.
I've been using for a long time.
Ever since I changed my profile picture
and switched the gender to female,
it became so much easier
to find someone to lead.
Where are you going?
I'm going to explain to her.
No.
There's no rush.
Let's play another round.
Come on.
Father will be fine.
The door is open.
They're here.
Father!
Dr. Jiang, how's my father?
The surgery is a success.
Don't worry.
It's just that, your father
had an old injury on his leg.
This time, he fell
on the same spot as well.
When he moves,
it'll affect him more or less.
Doctor,
so from now on, is my husband
going to sit on
a wheelchair?
Aunt, it's not to that extent.
Don't worry.
His movements will be a bit slow.
It's best to have someone look after him.
OK, sure. Thank you, Doctor.
No problem.
Slowly.
Come on.
Mother, you all go ahead.
I'll catch up with you.
OK.
-Careful.
Thank you, Dr. Jiang.
I'm just doing my part.
To me, in each surgery,
I'll do my best,
but this time,
I really hope
I'll perform better than usual.
Don't you remember me?
You're my father's surgeon.
Didn't we already
meet few times before this?
The first time we met,
was at the first meeting
since my transfer to
Donghu University Hospital.
You were sitting right next to me.
At that time, the principal
and vice principal
took turns to speak.
You were holding a tablet
without lifting your head once.
I guess you were writing a thesis.
And I thought
this female's quite bold,
but she looks cool.
The weekly hospital meetings
is the time I'm most efficient
at writing theses.
I understand.
Six shifts a week,
at least nine hours each.
Patients' monthly medical records
have to be compiled into a report as well.
Each year, you also need to
publish at least four theses
on academic journals.
The path to become attending physician
sure isn't easy.
Good luck.
I already passed my tests
and the interview.
As for when a spot
is available,
I can only wait
for instructions from
hospital's management.
You can do it.
Thank you.
The lift is here.
Let's go.
[and Liu Yu Cheng, two players mode]
[This rascal]
[is still playing with Xia Xia.]
Dr. Wu, are you available this weekend?
Dr. Wu.
What were you saying?
I said,
do you want to spend the weekend with me?
We don't know each other that well.
Isn't spending the weekend together
kinda strange?
There's always a start to everything.
We'll get to know each other more.
Who knows,
you might find that I'm a nice guy.
Let me think about it.
Xiao Wang,
what a coincidence.
It sure is.
Come on.
Is Dr. Jiang
courting you lately?
You've seen him
for less than five seconds,
and you've come to
such a nonsensical conclusion?
The nurses from department
told me,
recently, Dr. Jiang
has been asking around about your
hobbies, interests, and so on.
He sure acts quickly.
Are you coming or not?
I'm going to take a look at my father.
Wait, I haven't finished talking.
You should consider him.
Dr. Jiang is mature, handsome
and has a successful career.
You two are a match made in heaven.
Compared to that younger boy,
he's much more suitable for you.
Say what you want.
I'm going to take a look at my father.
Just tell me
a little about it.
What's there to tell?
Just a little.
Hopefully this meal
won't be absorbed by our system.
Please.
It'll be eliminated from our
system right after we finish.
Let's eat.
I don't eat vegetables.
I have
an announcement to make.
I've decided
I'm going to attend the signing event.
Didn't you say you're not going?
But it's indeed a good thing.
Who knows, you might become a sensation.
How did you suddenly come to your senses?
I used to think
I'm just using my own experience
as a prototype
to write a story.
If I'm to keep on
doing this,
in fact, I don't know what
I'm going to do from here.
I can't even be considered
as a writer.
I disagree.
I've been dating so many times,
and I couldn't write a single word.
Zeng Li is different.
She wrote 100,000 words just
from having a crush on someone.
You're really something.
But I can't write about my own stories
my entire life.
After all, it isn't a personal memoir.
Agree?
So, do you have a new source
of inspiration?
Not really.
It's just, yesterday,
Mr. Ai said to me,
to do the things
I like to do,
and choosing the lifestyle I want,
is something really admirable
and lucky.
That's why,
I gave it some thought.
In fact, I enjoy writing.
Aside from
whether I'll become successful,
or if I could accomplish
this task,
or if I'll successfully become
a professional writer,
as long as I can do
what I like to do,
with no other motives
or regrets,
it'll be OK.
I understand now.
Mr. Ai is the source of your inspiration.
You wrote 100,000 words for Yu Yi.
For Mr. Ai, at least,
you'll need to write an
entire collection of books.
Right?
You two. Everything
I've said just now,
seems like you just don't get it.
Eat your food.
Of course not.
Zeng Li,
what you're doing is called entrapment.
Do you know how far I have to jog
for this small dollop of sauce?
I'm going to eat your food
and take it from you.
The grass is always greener on
the other side, didn't you know?
Who did you learn it from?
Feeding my girlfriend french fries
is nothing to be embarrassed about.
Come on, let me feed you.
Dip it in two types of sauces.
Come on.
It's so tasty.
Stinky.
I'm telling you,
even though she's wearing pink,
but you can still tell her age.
He's younger than she is.
I thought you want to eat my french fries?
Here, eat it.
Eat more. Eat.
What are you two doing?
Who's dating someone younger?
Who?
Not me.
Don't cue me.
Actually, there's nothing wrong with it.
It's very popular nowadays,
agree?
Dating someone younger isn't the issue.
Wu Ying,
love is about
whether the two persons are
suitable for each other.
I think you and Liu Yu Cheng
are really compatible.
Why mention him all of a sudden?
We're just friends.
Friends?
The truth is,
even if you fooled us,
you can't fool your own heart.
There's no way I like him.
Only you yourself would believe that.
So what if I like him?
You finally admitted?
It seems Liu Yu Cheng's
female online game partner
showed up at the right moment.
It makes Dr. Wu realize
her own feelings deeply.
Since you already
admit that you like Liu Yu Cheng,
so why did you ignore him?
I just don't want to,
because of someone I like,
I can only buy those
colourful clothes to wear
and don't even dare to wear make-up,
worrying about when we go out,
others will say I'm
pretending to be young.
Also, I'll be concerned about
each wrinkle on my face,
and on my birthday,
I wouldn't dare to tell my family
that we're dating.
Or one day, when we broke up,
he's only in his 20s,
as for me,
I'll be in my 30s.
Forget it.
If he's really
going out with the female in the picture,
it's a good thing.
They're about the same age
and compatible in terms of looks.
Attending university together, gaming,
have breakfast and supper with each other,
at least it's better
than being with me, an older woman.
Goodness.
Is this the Wu Ying we know?
In the past, if Wu Ying likes someone,
she's always so fearless.
What's wrong?
I was young then.
What are you talking about?
You're only 27 this year.
It's true that Liu Yu Cheng is young,
but you're quite young yourself.
I'm not young anymore.
Think about it.
In the past,
we could eat three burgers in one go
and it'll be digested the next day.
Now, if I eat one of these burgers,
I'll gain a kilogram.
No amount of exercise
or diet can change it.
I also had excellent sleep quality.
Really.
Not even three or four
alarms will wake me.
And now?
I couldn't fall asleep at night.
This morning when I woke up,
I looked at my watch,
and it's only 5.30am.
It's too early.
Also, when we go clubbing in the past.
In three hours,
we've never
sat once on the bench.
And now?
Don't even bother asking me to club.
I feel tired at the mention of it.
I don't want to go.
Did you know?
I'm beginning to experience hair loss.
Each hair of mine
has its own name.
There're so many.
I know each and everyone of them.
I'm old.
Me too.
See this patch?
-Me too.
-This entire patch is gone.
Why is it happening to us?
Look at my nasolabial folds.
I have those too.
My nasolabial folds are so obvious.
It won't go away when I smile.
-There's none.
-I don't even know what to do.
There's none.
Friends,
let's not forget
our theme today.
Zeng Li, congratulations
for taking one more step towards
being a writer.
Cheers to you.
Let's wish Zeng Li luck
to become San Mao of our era earlier.
One single love story
is written into a dozen of books.
Good luck!
-Good luck!
Can we drink this coke?
Do we have to anti-sugar?
We have to.
Ma Xiao Bing
can go through hospital
admission procedures next week.
If the pre-surgery
examination turns out fine,
probably next,
he can undergo his surgery.
Great.
This is Xiao Bing's grandfather.
This is Dr. Ai.
Hi.
Dr. Ai, thank you so much.
-The effects of the braces are showing.
-If not because of you
helping to strive for the surgery costs,
You finally visit on time.
or it'll be too late.
Didn't I visit on time before this?
-What do you think?
-You're welcome.
It's nothing.
Don't worry.
As long as Xiao Bing
undergoes the surgery,
his illness can be cured
before he turns 18 years old.
Thank you so much.
Normally speaking,
-Did you know?
-Before he turns 18,
-This time, the subsidy
-basically he can
-is just 30 percent.
-fully recover.
The remaining 70 percent
was paid out of Mr. Ai's own pocket.
So, for some time after
the surgery is done,
it might be a little tough for you.
-How much does it cost?
-You all need to take care of him.
RMB50,000 to RMB60,000 in total.
In the beginning, Mr. Ai
didn't want us to tell others,
but it should be fine to tell you.
So?
Does it deepen the feelings you have
towards Mr. Ai?
Thank you.
No.
I don't know what to say.
Mr. Ai,
is cleft lip surgery so complicated?
It's considered to be
a relatively complicated
facial plastic surgery.
First, we need to confirm
the basic anatomy of the lips,
next, perform separation
and incision.
The skin, muscle, and mucous membrane,
all of which needs to
be handled in layers.
After that, for the split part,
restoration
and continuous reconstruction is done.
The entire restoration process
might need to be done in few surgeries.
Sounds like Mr. Ai,
you know what you're doing.
Not exactly.
I'm just doing
what I ought to do.
In fact, treatment of cleft lip
tests the patient
more than it does the doctor.
Think about it.
For example, now
you're only wearing braces.
And you already hope to
have it removed sooner.
But towards
patients with cleft lip,
it could possibly be a decade
they have to undergo continuous surgeries
and rehabilitation care.
It requires strong willpower.
If that's the case, let's go
to the orphanage next time
to visit Ma Xiao Bing,
and cheer him on as well.
Sure.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just admiring
this doctor who paid out of his own pocket
and do his best to perform surgery
for the patient.
You... You heard about it?
Zhou Wen told me.
She also asked me if, towards you,
my feeling of admiration increased.
The way you all put it
is too exaggerated.
I just feel, whether someone
will become a good or
bad person in future,
it mainly depends
on his growth process.
Children who lost their
parents since a young age
in fact, will harbor
negative emotions easily.
Together with congenital disease,
he's even more vulnerable
to trauma psychologically.
I understand.
Mr. Ai,
you want to do your best
to cure Ma Xiao Bing,
both physically
and psychologically.
I'm the same as him.
We're both orphans.
But I was lucky,
since I had my grandparents
by my side
and guide me so I don't go astray.
In comparison,
Ma Xiao Bing
isn't so lucky.
Therefore, I'm thinking,
I'll do what I can
to bring him some
positive influence,
or
create a better environment
so in future, he could become
a better person.
Your braces are ready.
I'll bring them to you.
OK.
[In fact, liking someone]
[isn't particularly difficult.]
[In the beginning,]
[we'll unknowingly]
[attracted by the person's
appearance, strength,]
[or even naivety,]
[it's just a feeling in general.]
[But if we can]
[slowly discover through
spending time together]
[that everything about him]
[is worth my having feelings for him,]
[it's such a great feeling.]
Sorry. I'm really sorry.
I was stuck in a traffic jam.
I'm late again.
No need to apologize to me.
I'll give you a special privilege.
You aren't considered as being
late if you arrive within an hour.
Really?
Let's go.
Thank you
for giving up on your action film
to watch romance movies with me.
That's my plan.
I'll keep you company today,
and you'll keep me company the next time.
That way, in a week,
we'll be going to the movies twice.
Oh, right.
Let me show you something scary.
[Sheng Ming is my boyfriend.]
[Michelle]
[Being lovey-dovey with
someone else's boyfriend.]
[Have you got no shame?]
Fess up.
How many girlfriends do you really have?
You're the only person I like.
You know that.
Why are you so anxious?
Don't worry. I know.
It must a prank pulled by netizens.
Let me tell you,
it really isn't easy for me nowadays.
If I post a selfie,
they'd say it's edited.
If I post lovey-dovey
pictures with my boyfriend,
they'd say my boyfriend
was snatched from someone else.
But I don't care.
Why should I, right?
Go in first.
I need to use the washroom.
But the movie's going to start soon.
Hurry up.
[Xiao Tao]
What exactly do you want?
We've broken up.
[It's not a breakup if
I didn't agree to it.]
Forcing me to be with you.
What good will it do?
[There is.]
[Sheng Ming, I'm warning you.]
[Make things clear with her right now,]
[or I'll bring this to Weibo.]
[I'll tell everyone]
[she got between our relationship]
[and she stole my boyfriend.]
[I'm going to turn all her followers]
[into anti-fans.]
You...
Sheng Ming!
I...
What's wrong?
Do you feel unwell somewhere?
Is it because you were exhausted lately?
What about this?
Let's not watch the movie.
Let's get something to eat
and after that,
we'll go home and rest, OK?
Yi Yi,
you're so good to me.
It's my fault.
What's wrong?
Why are you saying this all of a sudden?
The person who messaged you,
I know her.
We've been dating for 10 years.
When we first knew each other,
I haven't broken up with her yet.
Do you remember asking me
for help to edit your photo?
On that night,
I broke up with her.
So, did you break up
because of me?
I don't want to find excuses for myself
and say you're not the reason.
But I indeed developed feelings for you.
I really like you,
so I decided to break up with her.
She texted me on WeChat later
and called me,
but I didn't reply.
I really couldn't bear to part with you.
Yi Yi.
I didn't handle
this matter properly.
I got you involved in this.
So, what do you plan to do?
I don't know.
Yi Yi.
Hello.
[Hello, your car number plate
is 683, right?]
Yes.
[Come and move your vehicle, quickly.]
[I couldn't move my vehicle because
your vehicle is in the way.]
[I need to go now.]
Vehicle?
I drove here.
[How else did you come here?]
[I'm speechless.]
[The carpark slot
is narrow to begin with,]
[and you went and
park in a slanted manner.]
[You did it on purpose, right?]
Sorry.
I'll go back right away.
[Where are you now?]
But I don't know
where I am currently.
Let... Let me have a look.
I'm now
7 kilometres away.
It'll take half an hour
for me to be there.
[Half an hour?]
[I have an appointment later.]
[How will you make up
for it if it's delayed?]
[What an unlucky day.]
[It started raining after I left,]
[and a female driver's
blocking my carpark slot.]
[I don't care.]
[10 minutes.]
[I'm going to barge my way out
if you're still not here.]
I'm sorry.
It's an unlucky day for me too.
I'm... I'm going...
I'm going back now.
I'm... I'm going back now.
[CAROL'S]
After everything that I've told you,
yet you won't listen.
You deserve it.
How can you blame it on Yi Yi?
It isn't her fault.
Agreed.
Sheng Ming, this unworthy man.
Come on, give me his WeChat.
I'm going to scold him badly.
Give me your phone.
What's the use of scolding him?
That's the way things are.
At least I'll feel better
after scolding him.
Beating people is illegal
in a lawful society.
Or else, I'm going to give him a beating.
Why not?
Cover his head with a gunny bag,
no one will ever find out.
Do you want to be jailed?
That's enough.
If you beat him up,
how am I going to meet up
with him in future?
You still want to meet up?
Aren't you going to breakup with him?
I haven't made up my mind yet.
Ma Yi Yi,
you're going to tolerate this?
In all seriousness,
I'll pay for you to
fix your brain.
In all seriousness,
he really is the person I like the most
this year.
You're too truthful.
Wait.
It's only been 20 days since new year.
If that's the case...
If that's the case, last year also counts.
Why don't we close the shop
for tonight?
Tell us.
Where do you want to go?
We'll accompany you.
Tell you what,
I have morning shift tomorrow,
but it's OK because of you.
I'll stay up overnight with you.
Good girl.
[I'm done. Come pick me up.]
[I feel like having steamboat.]
[Li Li]
[Today is a bit tricky.]
[I have something to do.]
[Deng Hao Ran]
[We'll eat steamboat tomorrow.]
[You have something on everyday.]
[Why is it I don't have the feeling]
[of having a boyfriend?]
[Li Li]
The usual rule.
We'll listen to the person
who's going through a breakup.
Tell us, where do you want to go?
My treat.
I couldn't.
I'm not interested.
Are you sure?
I have a good idea, you know.
Come on.
Stop.
I'm not going.
Are you sure?
Hurry up.
Shake it!
Coming up next, the greatest
electronic music video!
I want to know,
are you ready?
Everybody, let's move it!
Why must we
make things difficult for ourselves?
Let our brother dance with her.
Let's leave an hour later.
Does that make us
bad friends?
30 minutes.
Anyway, look at
our Aunt Ma.
She said she didn't want to come just now.
Look, now,
she's more hyped than anyone else.
Come on.
Let's video her
and keep as evidence.
[Are you asleep?]
[She hasn't checked her phone
once in the past three hours.]
[Impossible.]
[Usually, her mobile phone]
[never leave her side.]
[Why have I only read two pages so far?]
[Aunt Ma has been]
[Wu Ying]
[partying for three hours.]
[Someone come and bring her away.]
[Partying?]
What do you mean?
Come on, let's go.
I don't understand.
No, wait.
Nowadays, deaf-mute
people also go clubbing?
That's a clubbing hand signal.
He wants to have a drink with you.
You chased away your sister's suitor.
I can at least decide that.
After all,
dating someone younger doesn't suit her.
You're right.
Mr. Ai suits her more.
Come back here. Come on.
Sit down.
You two talk too much.
Are we going to drink or not? Come on.
Come on.
Cheers.
Anyway, youngsters nowadays.
That DJ,
what's he playing?
It's a mess.
He has no taste at all.
I miss
our songs back then.
Those tunes were so easy to dance along.
I remember when we used to
go clubbing in the past,
there's this song.
I remember it's got a good beat, called...
What's it called again?
That... That song, that song.
Pokemon.
Boss Deng,
we have a song request,
"Pokemon".
Play it yourself.
I'm not going.
Me neither.
Please.
I'm not going.
I broke up with my boyfriend.
You go.
Fine, I'll go.
Thank you.
Bring the glowstick.
And my maraca.
I need my own stage.
Thank you.
Brother, switch to another song.
To what song?
Play "Pokemon".
This is lame.
Are you serious?
Not only am I serious,
it's also with sincerity.
Come on.
Bring out your QR code.
Sure, no problem.
Hi.
Excuse me, are you queuing?
Yes, it's quite crowded.
You might have to wait a while longer.
Thank you.
[Ai Jing Chu]
[Reply if you saw my message.]
Mr. Ai,
what are you doing here?
I'm
just here to look for a friend.
You sure like to play this
game for someone unskilful.
I'm talking about you.
It's none of your business.
I'm joking.
Don't be angry.
What are you two doing here?
I saw you replying to
Sister Zeng Li's moment,
and I knew you'd be here.
And so I came over.
Mr. Ai...
I came with Liu Yu Cheng.
That's right.
Where's Zeng Li?
They're inside.
OK.
Do you visit the nightclub often?
I can't hear you.
I said, do you visit the nightclub often?
I can't hear what you're saying.
Type into a message.
[Do you visit the nightclub often?]
There's no signal here.
Why do you need signal?
Just show it to me
will do.
Why are you laughing?
You finally hit me again.
However, your father
has an old injury on his leg.
This time, he fell
on the same spot.
It's best to have someone look after him.
Dr. Jiang
is mature, good-looking,
and has a successful career.
Compared to that young lad,
he's much more suitable.
Here, I'll show you.
Just now, I sent to you...
Wu Ying, where are you going?
I'll see you home.
Are you still angry
that I'm gaming with Xia Xia?
But that isn't Xia Xia.
It's my roommate, Mike.
He said to let you be jealous,
and you'll care about me more.
But I didn't expect it makes you
want to talk to me even less.
I'm not.
I just no longer feel like gaming.
So, you like clubbing now?
Although I'm not good at it,
I'll learn.
You don't have to do all this for me.
I volunteered to do so.
Did you know?
You're really charming.
You're the type that, amidst the crowd,
you'd stand out the most,
you're that type of girl.
We have a six years' age difference.
There's no way
we'll end up together.
Age, personality, occupation,
all kinds of practical issues,
we couldn't avoid any of it.
Have you been feeling down recently?
You keep saying things that
sound as if you're discouraged.
No.
No matter what happened,
if you're unhappy,
you can tell me.
If you did,
I'll share the burden with you.
There really isn't.
I'm going home.
You should go back earlier too.
Don't you have lecture tomorrow morning?
At least let me see you home.
It's late.
No need. It's in a different direction.
Be safe.
Your hand.
Up next, tonight
is your favorite Electro Night!
I want to know,
are you guys ready?
Pump it up!
The quiet snow
Suddenly cascaded
My sight frozen at your appearance
I could not believe it,
holding my breath
A feeling strikes at my heart
Heart beating wildly,
crossed the boundary