[Raise vigilance, defend the motherland, be strict with requirements, and make solid preparations.]
Stand up.
[United and tense, serious and lively.]
Sit down.
Now I’d like to make an announcement.
According to the research decision of company party branch,
and the consent of Regimental Communist Party Committee,
comrades Song Xiaoluo and Jiang Nanzheng were selected as
the reserve members of our company
to participate in this telecommunication contest of
the military district.
[United and tense, serious and lively.]
It is hoped that the two comrades will live up to the high expectations of the organization,
actively prepare for the competition,
win the flag and gold medal in the military district,
and win honor for the signal corps of our division.
Let’s applaud and
[United and tense, serious and lively.]
cheer for them.
Chief, have a foot bath.
I thought I was in the wrong place.
Nice job.
This place hasn’t been this clean in years.
Let me help you.
I’ll do it, thanks.
You’re not my son,
and I’m not a landlord, either.
What do you want to ask? Go ahead.
Did you take out the notebook?
Chief,
how did you know I had something to ask?
It’s rhythm.
Everyone has his own rhythm
when talking and doing things.
The untrained person’s rhythm
is messed up
when there is something on his mind,
or when he is emotionally shocked.
You’re new here,
but I can feel 60 to 70 percent
of your virtue.
[Notes]
That’s enough to detect
anomalies when you’re working.
[Rhythm]
Ask any questions.
I’ll give you three minutes.
Chief,
I want to ask,
why didn’t you
put a family photo
or something
at home?
I cleaned it all,
but I didn’t see anything
related to your wife and children.
In this battle,
[Report on Heroic Deeds in Battle]
we took credit.
In the future, we will certainly continue to work hard
to live up to the expectations of the Party,
the country and the people.
Chief,
just tell me.
In fact,
I also want to provide you
with better service in the future.
Put away the notebook.
Sometimes the answer is not important.
It’s the right question that matters.
You just asked a good question.
It’s like a fishing hook.
This hook
reminds me of a lot of old memories.
It seems that three minutes is not enough.
Chief,
then tell me.
Why should I tell you?
Chief, if people always keep things to themselves,
it is easy to feel uncomfortable.
And feeling uncomfortable will affect the work.
Tell me about it.
You can think of me as
a tree hole.
After you tell me,
I promise not to tell anyone.
Really?
Of course, I’d stake my life on it.
That makes sense.
Here, put them on.
Put them on.
I think it’s safer this way.
In 1966,
the army conducted its first scout training.
I was ordered to Heyuan
for closed training.
I hadn’t contacted my family for half a year.
At that time, Yihui was in poor health
and fragile mood.
There’s nothing I can do for her.
We had problems before.
She wanted me to move back to Jiangsu,
stay closer to home
or change my job.
I hesitated at the time,
but the army was
in the midst of intense combat training.
And finally, I did not agree.
There had been
no news for half a year.
She felt that I was avoiding her,
and things got worse.
She clamored to break up with me.
I rushed back to Suzhou
and she refused to see me.
For the whole twelve days of vacation,
she was somewhere else.
She was originally a pianist
with a great future.
She changed her career to become a music teacher
because she married me and wanted to settle down.
I thought
I couldn’t let her suffer,
so, I agreed.
Is it exciting for you to eavesdrop on others?
Well, don’t get me wrong.
You’ve played so many tricks with me,
what on earth do you want?
Wait, chief.
Chief.
You told me this
and it’s guaranteed to be worth.
What guarantee do you have?
Chief,
I’ll send you a daughter.
Chief, after verification, Jiang Nanzheng was a soldier from Jiangsu Province.
She was born in 1966
and has no dad.
Her mom’s name is Jiang Yihui.
She teaches in the music department
of Suzhou Railway Normal University
and is an associate professor.
This is their information.
You go ahead. Thanks.
The operator’s hands
need four skills.
Mental skills, listening skills, mouth skills and hand skills.
Mental skills test memory.
Listening skills test the ability to hear.
Mouth skills test the ability to express.
Then the hand skills
test the transfer speed and accuracy.
For you,
there is a very unfavorable factor.
That is time.
Other contestants
have worked hard for several years,
so, you must
make 120% efforts
[Political firmness and technical shrewdness. Be quick and accurate and keep it unobstructed.]
to catch up.
Only in this way
can you qualify for the competition.
[Political firmness and technical shrewdness. Be quick and accurate and keep it unobstructed.]
You are always wandering around with nothing to do.
How can the division commander not discipline you?
Listen,
don’t come to visit Nanzheng recently.
I don’t know
what you told her yesterday.
She’s in a particularly bad mood
and she’s still preparing for the competition.
I’m wronged, Sergeant Han.
I'm not here for her,
[Communication Station]
I'm here for you.
For me?
I need your help with something,
but you must keep it a secret
and never tell Nanzheng.
What’s it?
There you are.
The sergeant talked to me.
I came to apologize to you.
Do you know what you did wrong?
Not yet,
but I want to apologize to you first.
I shouldn’t have done that to you.
Well, forget it.
I’m not gonna be mad at you anyway.
It’s over.
By the way, the sergeant asked me to get the documents.
It hasn’t arrived yet. I’m waiting for it.
Anyway, there is nothing to do.
Practice with me for a while.
You guys are only interested in
these swords and guns all day long.
I also need to practice, okay?
I want to practice this.
I know,
this is not the same as the one you practiced.
I’m telling you,
you’ll get something out of practicing with me.
Here’s the thing. After coming to the training ground
to practice for half a day,
you sweat
and your spirit is relaxed.
As soon as your spirit is relaxed,
your body will be relaxed,
then your fingers will be more flexible,
and it will be faster to practice inserting wires.
Come on.
That makes sense.
All right.
I’ll practice with you.
- Otherwise, you think I’m afraid of you.
- Come on.
[Strict]
Take the gun.
I’ll teach you how to fight.
Do you want me to practice with a scarecrow?
I don’t want it.
I’m gonna fight with you directly.
Do you want to fight with me?
[Strict]
You’re making a big deal out of this.
I weigh dozens of jin more than you,
and I can knock you out.
You can fight with little Wangcheng. He’s light in weight.
You underestimate me.
Okay, I’ll fight with him first,
and then I'll fight with you afterwards.
Put on the protective gear first.
It’s my first fight with a female soldier.
I’m a little nervous,
so, I gotta go to the bathroom.
How can you go to the bathroom?
Come back.
You stand there.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
No way.
You…
- Idle folks lack no excuses.
- You see?
He’s afraid of me.
Jiang Nanzheng.
Listen,
you’ll never
forget today.
It’s just a protective gear.
How can it be unforgettable?
What a fuss!
Hold still.
Gloves.
Take them on.
Put on the helmet.
I’ll hold it for you.
Head down.
You’re back.
Get started.
How about it? Ready to start.
Okay, ready.
Stab him.
Be gentle, okay.
Again.
That was a hell of a hit.
One more round.
Little Wangcheng, are you okay?
All right, that’s enough.
You’re gonna get hurt.
No way.
It’s the last round.
That’s enough. No more fighting.
Division commander, our division commander.
This is our division commander!
This, our division commander!
This!
She’s just too excited!
Your plan has a flaw!
No…
I thought this would not work at first!
He is the division commander.
Doing this kind of child’s crap
is so not serious.
Which commander did this kind of things?
Listen to yourself!
Other commanders
didn’t lose their kid
for over a decade!
If I had senses in me,
I wouldn’t have listened to your nonsense!
But division commander,
I just felt that
in this way she’ll accept it.
I had no idea
Jiang is this kind of person.
You know I haven’t gotten in relationships or married.
Division commander, in this field,
I really have no experience.
Division commander was married,
but…
Stop talking, you!
If you keep poking division commander’s sour point…
Division commander,
don’t get mad…
I thought it would work.
Division commander.
It’s over.
Now you’re done.
Go for wool and come home shorn, right?
They were both mad.
Everything is doomed now.
[Raise vigilance, defend the motherland, be strict with requirements, and make solid preparations.]
Company commander, I have some family problem.
I apply for a call on the local line.
Approved, say hi to your mom.
Jiang Nanzheng, No.3 machine is waiting for you.
I’ll be right there.
Hello?
Mom, it’s me.
Nanzheng,
why are you calling all of a sudden?
Something happened?
Mom,
I met my dad.
Mom, are you listening?
Did he find you?
I don’t know.
Nanzheng…
Mom,
I thought I was so strong
that I didn’t need a father,
but I couldn’t…
Dear,
I’m sorry.
I’ll call your father,
and tell him everything.
Mom,
what happened between you?
Why did you leave?
You must love each other very much, right?
I’ll go to the troop,
tell your father everything in front of you.
Mom, don’t come.
I just missed you so much suddenly,
and wanted to call you.
You’ve been wronged for all these years...
Mom, rest assure, I’m fine.
I need to work now. I can’t talk to you anymore.
Connect me to
Suzhou Railway Normal University’s music department,
professor Jiang Yihui’s house.
Hello?
This is Zheng Yuan.
I knew
that you’ll call someday.
Why did you keep the child from me?
It’s not too late
to tell you about it now.
This is not fair to the child.
Were you fair to me?
No matter what, you got a father,
and the division commander got a daughter.
How nice is that!
[Defend the motherland]
If it were me,
I would be so happy that I would run wild.
You should be happy too.
Go away. Stop following me.
[Raise vigilance]
[Defend the motherland]
Your training today did not meet the standard again.
You haven’t improved all week,
so I wanted to hear from you.
And know if something happened to you.
Commander, please switch someone else.
I can’t do it anymore.
Do you know how you got the place
as the backup team member?
I asked for it to the company.
No.
This
was given to Han Chunyu.
She came to me voluntarily,
and wanted to give it to you.
She gave it to me, didn’t she?
Why?
Because she said
you are the most talented soldier in our company,
and you have potential worth being inspired.
I hope
you won’t waste her kindness,
and accomplish something despite the obstacles.
Try to go on the battle field
and win a champion.
Nanzheng,
tell me the truth.
Did you come across some problems?
Commander,
don’t worry.
From now on,
I’ll work hard in practices,
and won’t let any emotion get to me.
Great.
[Secure communication with responsibility, arm brain with knowledge. ]
Gu Yiye,
I really want to meet you, at this moment,
and talk to you about what I’m thinking.
In my whole life,
I have never felt such great panic.
I feel like
I’m a lost lamb
stumbled into a strange wood.
The wood is so broad, and I don’t have any companion.
I don’t know which way to go.
Why?
I’m feeling the fear I’ve never felt before.
I’m so afraid.
Nanzheng,
I don’t know what you came across,
but I understand your state of mind.
Just like you,
in my whole life,
I’m feeling
so helpless and afraid for the first time.
Walking from books
to the jungles,
this road
is far more rugged than I expected.
I investigate functions
for the death,
and use cannons
to write them down.
Gu,
under your great bait,
there must be dead fish coming, awesome.
Five at once!
Who is Gu!
Hot blood spreads the battle field, no one braver.
Polite and decent, no one more eloquent.
That’s exactly like me!
Pen and sword!
Right, bro?
I’m telling you, Gu Yiye
used himself as bait, and got 5 at once.
The award from the company is definitely in the pocket.
I’m telling you bro,
if we work harder and get more
so that we can have one each, the
advanced squad is definitely us.
- Alright!
- Keep in line!
Sergeant,
the first company’s scout is caught,
and they are practically blind,
so they must be more desperate than us.
They’ll definitely
advance on a big scale.
What we need to do
is to insert ourselves in their back
and catch the ones left out alone.
Back?
Where is the back?
It’s two mountain peaks away.
By the time we get there,
it will be all bright.
I watched it while training,
going through the small wood,
there’s a creek. Going up along,
there’s a cliff.
We can go up there.
It’s a straight line so it’ll be fast.
Cliff.
I know the training place.
You think about it.
That was in broad daylight,
and we circled around during training.
Now it’s night time.
It’s too dangerous.
I won’t approve.
If we want to
get more trophies,
I stick to my opinion.
A field commander must decide even against king's orders.
Now it's a special situation.
I propose
we should take Gu’s advice.
I agree.
Agree.
I think we should
listen to the sergeant.
Sergeant.
It’s an emergency.
Please give the order.
Ok.
[Raise vigilance, defend the motherland, be strict with requirements, and make solid preparations.]
Nanzheng.
Gu Yiye’s in trouble.
[Unit 53052 of People’s Liberation Army Hospital]
[Oncology Surgery]
The whole company was affected by the First Company.
Gu Yiye is...
[Operating room]
Division commander.
Why are you two here?
We heard that Gu Yiye is having the surgery,
so we rushed over to see him.
Nurse,
how is he?
He is not good.
The doctor is treating
his bones inside.
His left arm suffers a comminuted fracture.
More than a dozen pieces have been treated and are still being treated.
What will happen to him?
Hard to say.
He also has a concussion.
We also have to deal with this after the surgery.
You can ask the doctor about the details later.
Will he fall into a fool?
Cut it out.
[Be quiet Operating room]
Sergeant,
how did Gu Yiye fall?
We had a battle with
the First Company to capture the prisoner.
For expending the result,
someone has proposed that
we could go around behind them.
We need to go through a cliff.
There was a large tree leaning against the cliff.
Gu Yiye and Lin Beihai were elite soldiers at the time.
And Lin Beihai went up,
his foot slipped and almost fell.
For saving him,
Yiye fell.
The idea of going behind them
came from Gu Yiye.
Yes.
It’s Gu Yiye’s idea.
But it’s me who gave the order.
I’ll take all the responsibility.
Doctor, how is he?
He's out of danger,
and now in the ward.
He is tough, huh?
[Be quiet Operating room]
You two wait here.
You're here to keep an eye on.
You go back and get the supplies for Gu Yiye.
I go to the doctor to ask for details.
Yes.
Who is responsible for taking care of him?
Me.
Who exactly?
Me, I’m his sergeant.
No food for eight hours.
No water either.
Every now and then,
moisten his lips
with a wet cotton swab.
Yes.
And, it’s hot,
the hospital facilities are aging,
we have no fan.
Remember to
wipe the patient’s sweat
to prevent it from seeping into the wound.
Okay, call me if you need anything. I'm going out.
Thank you.
[Unit 53052 of People’s Liberation Army Hospital]
Jiang.
Let me do this.
It’s okay, I’ll do it.
I’m going to wipe his body.
I’ll go out then.
[Dormitory]
Nanzheng.
Here.
I’ll help you if you need more.
Thanks.
Go then.
[Dormitory]
Did Jiang Nanzheng ask for a leave?
Hail, Commander! Yes.
How is it going?
[Ice]
So many popsicles.
Where did you get?
Jiang
has collected a lot of Communication Company’s
popsicle tickets.
Commander Zhao
sent over their popsicle
tickets here in person.
Popsicle cooling, physical cooling.
Very effective.
Jiang is smart.
Jiang, thanks.
Company commander.
What do doctors say?
He has severe optic nerve papillary hemorrhage,
increased intracranial pressure,
and brain damage.
More examinations are needed
after waking up,
depending on the actual condition
and development of the injury.
The crushed bones in the arm
have been taken out.
But it will not recover
until the second surgery.
What do you mean?
He can’t be physically handicapped, can he?
Why are you still here?
Hurry back!
What about chief?
I asked for a leave from the chief.
Commander Qin, Sergeant Zhang.
I’m going back. There’s a training this afternoon.
Hurry and go.
We’ll be here. Don’t worry.
Thank you, Jiang.
Company commander.
Company commander, I’ll walk her out.
It’s so obvious
what happened between Jiang and Gu Yiye.
Company commander.
Qin.
Don’t play dumb with me.
Their situation has been revealed in new recruit company.
You knew everything,
but did not say a word to me.
It now appears that
Song Jianshe is more experienced
in this kind of situation.
Gu Yiye had told me everything.
I’m such a fool
for believing him.
Did he lie to you?
No, he didn’t.
I’m telling you.
Both Gu Yiye
and Jiang Nanzheng
have the potential of being an excellent soldier.
But they may also fall on their way
of being an excellent soldier.
The stumbling block is nothing
but a wrong relationship
in a wrong time.
Qin,
I was wrong.
I admit that
I had kept it a secret
for what happened on Gu Yiye.
After all,
it didn’t affect his training, did it?
And,
no influences on his daily life.
And Guy Yiye
did not make it conspicuous.
What’s conspicuous?
A seed falls into the ground
and then it sprouts.
What comes next is growing
into a tall and leafy tree.
This kind of conspicuousness,
isn’t it too late?
I’ll talk to him
after he wake up.
I’ll cut the tree,
and dig out the seed.
What’s the use of all the talking?
[Inpatient ward]
I’m telling you, Zhang Fei.
You’re responsible for the injury of Gu Yiye.
But he has more responsibilities.
Mess around with few military theories.
Listen,
after he’s restored to health,
transfer him to cooking corps.
He can only come back
after getting rid of
his fickleness.
He can go nowhere except for digging up the vegetable plot.
I must end his fantasy
with the female soldier.
What?
You go first. What are you going to do with it?
What are you going to do with it?
Turn a blind eye,
just let it be?
I...
do you think I’m like that?
How can you think of me that way?
I think you’re just like that.
Don’t compare soldiers with officers.
Can anyone learn the skills
and win the battles
being in two minds
and focusing on other things all day?
Qin Hanyong,
how dare you say that!
It’s true that Jiang Nanzheng involves in it,
but she’s not the only one involving.
Gu Yiye from your company
should assume main responsibility.
He should be the first to be blamed.
Thank you very much.
He’s being blamed.
You are the boss.
It’s your call as to how to deal with it.
First of all,
they must not continue
this relationship.
Let alone the principles,
Jiang Nanzheng
is participating the competition on behalf of our company.
Besides Gu Yiye from your company
is also a model.
How can these two talents
be destroyed just like that?
Agree.
Secondly,
secondly, this should not be disclosed.
Are you saying that we don’t report it?
Functionally speaking,
the company is capable of dealing with this kind of stuff.
I mean,
no more punishment.
No way.
I must teach him a lesson.
How is that possible?
Come on, don’t put on airs.
You can see that.
It’s up to you.
If you punish him,
the matter will be made public.
That’s right.
The company is full of young soldiers,
so it is inevitable that there will be some ideas.
Yeah.
After publicity with great fanfare,
there was nothing originally, but everyone would think about it.
That would backfire.
I agree.
I support it with all my hands.
I admire you.
What's the use of admiration?
Think twice next time.
You are majestic
when you train.
Not a night tiger,
when something happens,
but a stupid roe deer.
Am I that stupid?
Commander,
she’s provoking you.
How dare you eavesdrop on others?
Absolutely not, I happened to pass by and couldn’t avoid it.
Come here.
What’s this?
Have some fruit.
Where did you get it? So many.
I picked the fruit in the reconnaissance camp directly under the division headquarters.
There were several dogs chasing me for a long time.
Commander，
you’d better wash it before eating.
It’s delicious.
Well,
the reconnaissance camp uses human waste as fertilizer.
Why didn’t you say earlier?
Commander Zhao was right.
Stupid roe deer.
[Unit 53052 of People’s Liberation Army Hospital]
How dare you run!
You brat.
Did the wounded make any reaction?
No reaction at all.
That’s weird. It’s been almost ten hours.
Try pinching his renzhong.
Pinch his renzhong.
It’s not working.
A little harder.
It hurts.
He’s awake.
You wake up!
Gao Liang.
Do I have a problem with you? You have to pinch that hard.
I’m worried you won’t wake up.
What happened to me?
What happened to you?
You are quite well.
When you lie down here,
there is someone to fan the wind, someone to take care of you.
All the brothers in the company were envious.
Tell me the truth.
Well, to be honest with you, according to your current situation,
you need another operation later.
Then, your brain needs to be cut open
and stirred up inside.
You’re a psychopath.
It’s just an exercise. Why were you climbing so high?
Can you fly?
Or will it not hurt when you fall?
I’m telling you, if I were the company commander,
I would punish you.
What you’re doing is reckless opportunism.
Understand?
Don’t move, can you take a break?
Gao Liang,
have you ever been to the zoo?
Have you ever seen a breeder
feed a tiger or a lion?
How to feed? Just feed it normally.
Otherwise, set a table and eat on the table?
These tigers and lions
are all beasts.
In the wild,
they tear preys to pieces
with their own claws and teeth.
There are rules about
what to eat
and what not to eat.
What does that mean?
But when they arrive at the zoo,
the breeder will
cut all the meat for them.
It’s convenient.
But after a long time,
these beasts
will not be able to hunt.
Give me a hand.
Can you stay quiet?
Come on, give me a hand.
[Wish you good health.]
You’re really a pain in the ass.
I’m telling you,
the army
is such a beast,
if you do not sharpen its claws for a long time,
the fighting ability will disappear.
We can tell ourselves
what is real and what is not.
But over time,
the real will become the fake,
and the fake
will become the real.
Okay,
I get it.
No wonder I feel a little disadvantaged
every time I fight with you.
It turns out that I treat you as my comrade
and show mercy everywhere,
but you treat me as a class enemy
and beat me to death, don’t you?
Okay.
Gu Yiye, I officially inform you.
From now on,
I will show no mercy on the
battlefield fighting for the
revolutionary friendship of Comrade Jiang Nanzheng.
Did you hear that?
Let the gale blow you to death.
You’ve been lecturing me all day.
Nurse.
Yeah, I do like him.
I didn't ask you that.
What are you going to do next?
Continue to like him.
Even if he is disabled,
I will not give up.
[National interests are above all else.]
Well, that’s very touching.
I don’t like him for touching people.
Stop it from now on.
I want you to end your relationship
with Gu Yiye from today,
even if it is an
ordinary comrade friendship.
Why?
No reason.
I am not consulting with you.
This is the decision of the organization, and you must obey it.
I can’t.
There are three stages to the command:
understanding,
execution,
and completion.
I allow you to give a discount in the first stage,
and the next two stages must be completed.
Get out of here.
[Wish you good health.]
I said I’ll do my best today.
Come on.
Do my best.
Okay, we have the attention of all departments.
Makeup, costumes, and props are ready.
Noodles with gravy.
The location of the camera.
What’s the sound?
You wake up.
Give me a hand.
You can’t get up yourself, right?
Let me help you.
Sit.
Lean over here.
This is where the actors are.
So, it’s where the light is.
I’m telling you,
I had a dream that
I ate noodles.
You wish.
That’s Chen Peisi eating noodles.
You woke up just in time,
hurry up and help me eat.
Come on.
I’ve eaten half a bucket this afternoon,
and now it makes my headache.
I’m a patient.
A patient?
Did you just have a baby and can’t you have ice cream?
I’m telling you,
as long as you’re not dead, get up and train.
It’s scary all day.
Jiang Nanzheng brought all the ice cream
from the service center,
to cool you down.
What a pity that it melted.
What a stupid girl.
If she is with me in the future,
she will slow me down.
Well, never mind.
I like her.
Why are you so shameless?
Who says she wants to be with you?
Also,
don’t call her stupid.
You always say things that
don’t make sense.
You stuffed the free military stamp
into the envelope,
and your concern was sent away.
Now, you’ve scraped your head,
and broken your arm,
leaving her on tenterhooks and crying.
Now the company knows about it.
Isn’t she stupid to do so?
What’s going on?
Is she in trouble?
Oops, my teeth!
I’m telling you,
Qin Dapao and Commander Zhao
are plotting.