font-size: 1em; font-weight: bold; color: #ffffff; }
Concubine thought
Let's make her a concubine
keep her forever
Accompanying Zhanji
help him well
free at kisskh.me
father emperor
Since you admire her
She should be kept at the Shang Food Bureau
Let her concentrate on cooking for you
Concubine pleads guilty to His Majesty
His Majesty said before
look at this kid
In fact, she is the emperor
Taisun concubines set for Zhanji
How can you not be kind?
It was her
mother
you promised me
Your Majesty finally remembered
actually
It should have been reported to His Majesty earlier
It's just that this kid is stubborn
Concubine thinking
let her in the food bureau
practice more
Who knows what is wrong
almost missed her
His Majesty
Don't be rude in front of the royal family
I have never been short of people to serve
even if you choose
I want to choose myself
not to mention her
i don't like
Junji
The emperor has always loved you
whatever the king's will
you didn't disobey
This is the person who the first emperor has slapped his eyes
Could it still be wrong?
Okay
well said
This is a blessing from God
no wonder i see her
It feels so familiar
Since it is a good fate chosen by the first emperor
That
Choose an auspicious date
Yes
Father is not allowed
Too much talking, but my heart is still blocked
back off
father emperor
His Majesty
Your dragon body is out of harmony
Concubine even if I go back now
Don't worry too
you let me go to the hospital
congrats sister
you all go down
mother
free at kisskh.me
You clearly promised me
This matter is no longer mentioned
Why repeat the old story
do you really dislike her
like a flower
Are you going to pick it up by hand?
leave it in the garden
Isn't free bloom bad?
you procrastinate for her
out of love
But in the royal family
you and I know
Her name is set early
But sooner or later
you just saw it with your own eyes
Your father's body is not as good as before
also worry about you
Do you have the heart to brush his good intentions?
Erchen resigns
He wanted to
No need for him to speak
Just look at him
there will be someone
Kneeling and holding it to his feet
All things in this world
Nothing is not
Don't say it's a flower
even the whole garden
how can
when did you hear
He said that
What happened in the palace today
Messaging to inform Le'anzhou
Yes
you go down first
what you told me to do
I've done it
Now His Majesty's old illness has relapsed
This is the big sin of the Nine Clan
If Your Majesty is seriously ill
The news of the prince's centrifugation
Spread to Le'an
you say
Ambitious Han Wang
what will be the move
you're going to rebel
wrong
It was the King of Han who wanted to rebel.
Han king rebels
what does it have to do with you
how
Scared
in the Forbidden City
The only person who cared about me
are gone
Even if this subverts
what does it have to do with me
I just don't understand
You are in a high position for your age
Your Majesty
so trusting
what more do you want
you mean
Eagle dog for a lifetime as an emperor
Live at will?
I'm afraid of him Zhu Zhanji
can't stand
Give
flour
Yin Ziping
I've only heard
Shangjiao dumplings, Xiajiao noodles
never heard of
Send your relatives to eat noodles
You are reluctant
little regret
Zijin
my mother used to say
Qin, chess, calligraphy and painting
Women's red cooking is all utensils
Everything in the world can be discarded
What's wrong with that
There is a saying in the Huayan Sutra
All three worlds come and go
Indulge in thoughts
mother once said
Only the beginning of the heart can not give up
I do not understand
I know you don't understand
Ziping
Xiang Shi once said
I'm the one who wants to be a grandson
It's providence
Later, they said that Concubine Taisun belonged to someone else
I don't have such a deep blessing
I do not care
But I don't agree
Even if you are repeatedly tricked by fate
I also wondered if I could fight for my life
not to mention
China's great talents
I am not alone when it comes to food
The chef's hand needs to turn the pot
I can't do it with my right hand
Then I'll go where I can go
do what only i can do
Are you still thinking about Concubine Zhuang?
don't think about it, don't touch it
That's ancestry
Who says ancestry can't be changed?
you are just one
little prince
Who said my life
Just be a prince
you
Ziping
Someone won't let me hide
let me avoid
okay then
I will not hide
Family of exiled rebels
can be released
this world
What else can't be done
hold it by yourself
Your Highness
Your Highness, rest assured
this wound
Rest for another seven or eight days
it will be great
Sheng Yin
The emperor's old illness relapses
menacing
tomorrow
you follow me to the Qianqing Palace
see him
This
back off
Yes
Your Highness
It's no use if you go
The emperor hates his ministers
will never let the minister
treated for it
for the previous
You are treating your mother's illness
The emperor will not hold grudges so much
not for this
minister
I got drunk once
joke with colleagues
I don't know how
spread to
It was in the ear of the emperor of the East Palace
The father has always been lenient
He is rarely angry with his servants
what did you say
Let the father hate so far
For the doctor
look and hear
lead by inspection
Depends on the patient's external response
know its internal organs
know that you are sick
don't worry
But it doesn't matter
the emperor
free at kisskh.me
It's not a sign of longevity
you are presumptuous
empress
It's time to stop
go out
go down first
Your Majesty refuses to see me
I do not know
what did i do wrong
you are not always
Are you all good at planning?
Why don't you talk now
empress
not now
When troubled by grace
real disaster
it's near
you mean
impossible
The emperor flourished in spring and autumn
Fukuzawa is deep
He'll be back to normal soon
empress
Look at His Majesty's look and gait today
How is it better than before
Safe and Dangerous, Good and Bad
how smart you are
Do you still need a slave reminder?
I wish your majesty a speedy recovery
To comfort the concubine's heart
if not
empress
Need to take precautions early
kneel
a prayer
rise
goodbye
samsara
rise
four worship
prosper
Prince Concubine
It's not etiquette
The prince personally sent his sister back
I just don't want to hurt you
The queen mother is afraid that the people in my palace are clumsy
specially given to these people
to take care of your diet
As for these damask hairpin rings
some of my thoughts
I hope you don't refuse
Thanks Princess Grace
Since entering the East Palace
is a sister
Don't need so much courtesy
The greeting ceremony is very tired
go back to rest early
you
Take good care of the prince
Yes
Your Highness
I'm not deaf
this hour
The prince and concubine are waiting for you in the palace
Your Highness
What's up
Your Highness, where are you going?
The prince is still waiting
hurt
lying down too long
I can't use my arms
Do this again and lie down
I'm afraid I can't even open the bow
how come your majesty
This is good wine
You adults drink alone under the moon
It's a pity that Long Yue doesn't know how to drink
why not
let me be your drinking buddy
Your Highness, you can't drink
are you still hurt
People say shochu is strong
Best to drink less
It is best to drink Shaoxing wine alone
but
Rarely meet like-minded people
I like
Your Highness
You can't get drunk tonight
My word is Yunzhou
Okay
Unfune
Shangyuan banquet
I see that your martial arts are extraordinary
Chat with me
Your Highness
Wei Chen dare not
Your Highness be careful
come again
I have read your memorial
bold
Your Highness
Your old wound is broken again
what to do
Weichen Wushu
Your Highness, please forgive me
just learning
sword without eyes
how can i blame you
get up
Your Highness is magnanimous
Thank you so much
But you just said
I say your memorial
I've seen it all
Since taking office
you to the grandfather and the emperor
have done a lot of
whether it is salt administration
water transport
tax law
Coast Defence Military
all involved
And every word is pearly
hit the mark
Unfortunately
these memorials
were thrown aside
No one is looking at it seriously
you see our two patients
It's not even fun to fight
Until your injury heals
we compare
Yes
adult
you are also injured
are you alright
adult
this late
where else to go
go for a walk
Eunuch Chen
Why is your Highness so late?
Please inform the prince concubine
Your Highness is practicing sword tonight
Accidentally recurring old injuries
I'm afraid it won't come
Please place the prince and concubine earlier
Prince Concubine
This makes it impossible
don't worry
Your Highness will be back soon
The holy dragon is not in good health
The prince has always been sincere and filial
I'm so anxious
now this time
free at kisskh.me
Where is the mood Nafei?
The prince will not come
You go back to rest
I said don't let you play
you are not playing
Imperial Physician Sheng has warned
You can't dance with knives and guns
you also drink
Sheng imperial doctor
are you alright
This is just great
Gotta rest for a while.
This tour is in trouble.
I tell you Your Highness
he knew
you are seriously injured
He also wrestled with you
Waiting for the queen to return to the palace
I must report to the queen
punish him for a big sin
eventful
Subordinates retire
Your Highness
Otherwise you should rest
get the book
it's so late
Your Highness' servants have gone to report
she is angry
no no
what did you say
nor
didn't say a word
Your Highness
The ceremony of the crown prince's concubine is cumbersome
Tossed people for days
Good people have lost weight
I've been waiting for you tonight
I'm afraid I can't stand it anymore
This stopped
what do you know
don't talk nonsense
His Royal Highness has not returned
Even if you wait until tomorrow
That's a wait
Your Highness
your madam
go down
I thought I'd be cold-hearted by you
did not expect
you didn't even look
Why do you keep looking at me and laughing?
I don't know the prince's concubine
slept well last night
last night
Now the East Palace except the Crown Princess
your highest score
Others should come to meet
The slave has already instructed the Shang Food Bureau
Ready for a small dinner
Akin
Once upon a time you were Concubine Zhuang
old people around
Now the queen asks you to serve me
Don't you feel aggrieved?
Back to the words of the prince's concubine
Back then, my master had nowhere to ask for help.
if you didn't lend a hand
I'm afraid she won't be able to go on the road in peace
This kindness will be remembered forever
This time the queen concubine
To send someone to the East Palace
It's a messenger sent by the slaves on their own initiative.
If you have any assignments
Slaves must do their best
it's getting late
Slave, let's get ready
I'm afraid it may not be what you want
nothing you go
Yes
Prince Concubine
it's ready
Akin
Yes
go down
sit here
Being a master is different
Much better than in the Shangshi Bureau
But I'm too rude to sit here
In case His Royal Highness
find out what to do
he never came
never been
how come
he didn't come to you
you didn't go to him
You haven't reconciled yet
I know
know what
You blame the queen for forcing you to enter the palace
Even the prince hated it
That's why you promised to marry him
Prepare for a lifetime
come and torture him
right
i can't sit here
For a while, the concubine of the East Palace
come to greet you
I'm so disrespectful to sit here
sit there
Prince Concubine
today
no need to wait
you accompany me to dinner
How dare they neglect you so much
It's so deceiving
The smoked worm you fried today
Oil is too hot
how come
Delicious and crispy
I cooked it myself
stop being rude
Yashiki Zen
Puffer Dolphins at Guanglu Temple
you must handle it yourself
Don't fake your hand
queen concubine
I don't like reed bud soup
Use cauliflower soup instead
And sauerkraut
Also prepare more fenugreek
On weekdays, you stay with the little maids
be kind
can't be called
easy to hate
in my absence
Be careful Yuehua
I don't have to worry about you
it's you
must find a way
Hold the prince
If you want to stay in the East Palace for a long time
The concubines beside Your Highness
Neither one can be ignored
But
princess
how many of them
did not greet the prince's concubine
Miao Xian
you haven't gone today
Do you want to meet the prince's concubine?
princess
It was to follow the rules
Greetings to the new prince concubine
only
This year's buds
It doesn't look very tender
Miao Xian
tomorrow morning
went to ask the prince's concubine
did you hear
princess sister
I didn't mean to be rude
People can't hear it
The smoke on her
what fireworks
Cooking food in the dining room all day long
fishy with lard
free at kisskh.me
Who dares to approach her
Xu is His Royal Highness
also very dissatisfied
On the day of the canonization
Haven't stayed at all?
the palm
The prince did not stay at the prince's concubine
It's true
Your Majesty and the Empress
give her grace
I thought something was coming
amazing person
Who would have guessed that just entered the East Palace
into the cold cellar
I saw the slaves just now
To open the cellared peonies for ventilation
I don't know our prince
when can I remember
This prince concubine
also call her a breath
Don't be sore.
His Royal Highness is a recurrence of an old injury
So it has been
Haven't gone to Xinuan Pavilion
You can't because of this
rude to the prince
can't go
Disturbing His Royal Highness's recovery
especially you
no fooling around
Otherwise I will never forgive
Yes
I was a while ago
made new incense
sleep aid
There's such a thing
Come play with me another day
Who said princes and concubines have no favors?
We should go to the meeting
accepted
What did you say
What can I say then?
That must be a huge thank you
The maid didn't watch
you didn't see
That
The prince rewarded the prince's concubine
That is to openly protect her
If the prince concubine knew
Thank you so much for sure
But it was unfortunate when the slaves went
I am afraid that Your Highness will be in a hurry.
So I came back and got back to life.
But if the prince and concubine knew
will definitely come
from Shane
Prince Concubine
you never went out to thank you
it's illegal
If His Royal Highness knew
to blame
This
wait for me to reapply
An hour has passed
Let the palace envoys have been waiting outside
Once spread
It's disrespectful too
can only blame
This reward came at a bad time
I didn't come at the right time.
His Royal Highness
Ah Jin clothes
Yes
go out
do not touch
Yes
Akin
Your Highness
Please wait in the outer hall
I'll be here soon
i have something to ask
I'll leave after asking
what do you want to ask
Your Highness
I don't want to ask anything now
I'm staying tonight
you go get ready
Akin
Your Highness is not healed
Physicians urged
give you a good rest
if
free at kisskh.me
I'm letting His Highness stay overnight
I'm afraid that tomorrow will be the queen's concubine
called to censure
Do not worry
Mother won't blame you