[English subtitles are available]
[Oh My Lord]
[Episode 5]
[Bai's Mansion]
Miss, miss!
Apple.
If I help you,
Lord Xian won't let my dad live in peace.
If I don't help you,
you won't let me live in peace.
I don't know
if I should
infiltrate into the enemy base.
What's wrong?
[Calming Hall]
My lord.
The accomplices of Eunuch Li's corruption case
have been arrested
and sent to the imperial prison.
Take your time to interrogate them.
Don't let any of them off the hook.
Yes.
What time is it?
It's 5:45 PM.
Chen Youyou is not back yet?
She came back for awhile and
went out again.
I'm not sure if she's with His Royal Highness.
Well,
shall I bring her back?
No need!
She can go wherever she wants!
Wherever she wants!
My lord.
Tiao.
My lord,
my lady invites you to the Lake Pavilion.
It's late now,
you can talk to her once she is back.
My lord!
Chen Youyou.
Why are you being so mysterious?
My lord.
I was wrong.
I shouldn’t have touched the spirit tablets without permission.
To show my sincerity,
I prepared something for you.
Come.
Follow me.
This is...
I disturbed the ancestors.
I prepared these
river lanterns to pray for them.
Pray?
My mother died at an early age.
Since I was young,
I've been wandering around.
I always thought myself as
a kid without a home.
I didn't even know where to commemorate her.
Later on, I heard from an old man
that as long as I light a river lantern,
I can pray for her.
So,
I hope these river lanterns
can also bring happiness and peace
to your family.
Thank you.
Then, my lord,
this means we've made up.
If I
knew more about you,
I would not only avoid making you angry,
but I'd also avoid misunderstandings.
Understand me more?
Yes.
I also want to know...
what is your favorite food.
What you dislike...
Other than dust, what else are you allergic to?
What spices do you use? How do you stay young?
When do you go to bed?
Also,
do you
like Miss Jiang?
Miss Jiang’s father helped the Su...
the Bai family before.
I took her in
to repay the favor.
Are you really just repaying the favor?
It's my turn to ask you.
Recently,
who have you been with?
Recently, I have been with...
with...
with His Royal Highness.
But, please don't overthink!
He has been obsessed with cooking,
so I helped him.
Bai's Mansion is your home.
Don't always run out when you're free.
Home?
My lord, I wasn't done whith my questions.
One question per day.
No way.
What if I
don't ask all the questions and make you angry again?
My lord, wait for me!
Bai's Mansion is your home.
Don't always run out when you're free.
I hope these river lanterns
can also bring happiness and peace
to your family.
What am I imagining?
My lord!
My lord, why are you still up?
I'm not sleepy.
My lord, I made noodles. They smell good!
Do you want to eat with me?
I'm not hungry.
My lord!
Why are you blushing?
Forget it!
I'll eat them myself.
[Wind Booth]
My lord,
it's mid-summer today.
The kitchen specially prepared soup noodles
to cool down the heat.
I don't want them!
From now on, no more eating noodles in the mansion.
Well...
Why are we suddenly not allowed to eat noodles?
Tiao, what are you doing? My noodles!
Miss,
Lord Bai just stated
no more eating noodles in the mansion.
Those who violate this command will be expelled.
Did noodles offend you?
He didn't look well
when I cooked noodles last night,
and now he's doing this.
You really can't mess with him.
That's weird.
He always finished his vegetable soup noodles
every mid-summer.
Why did he suddenly...
Miss,
this must have something to do with Chen Youyou.
Ever since she's here,
everything has changed in Bai's Mansion.
This construction work has been delayed for months!
What's the use of all of you?
Madam De.
The emphasis on beauty
is the tradition of Fuxian City.
I think
the imperial palace for the memorial of the late castellan
must be magnificent,
elegant,
and beautiful.
[Aunt Qi Shengwen, former castellan's concubine]
Ordinary,
aleatoric,
and spiritless!
Bai,
you're late.
Do you not respect Madam De?
Madam's palace
is not suitable to be decorated with gold and silver.
First, it's too ordinary.
Second, the style is different from the palace.
I'm afraid it may be seen as a threat to the throne.
I came late
because I went to find a spiritual item, the twin lotus flowers.
Twin lotus flowers?
Also known as hibiscuses with the same heart.
It means to be together forever.
This imperial palace renovation is
for the late castellan.
I believe all things have spirits, and
I'm sure he'll get our longings.
It sounds good.
Lotus sharing the same stem, twin lotus flowers
are rare.
Bai,
it seems you just wanted to avoid punishment for being late
and blabbered out nonsense.
Don't worry, Lord Xian.
I'll be sure to satisfy madam.
It's decided then.
Bai will be fully responsible
for the renovation of the imperial palace.
Yes.
But Bai,
if you let me down,
I won't spare you.
Yes.
Youyou,
why are you so hungry?
Did Bai Li torture you again?
Don’t mention it.
But, the texture of this wild ginger cake
is really tender!
Really?
I bought a lot of fresh ingredients today.
Let’s make something new.
Okay!
Youyou! Look at my skills.
My lord,
Madam De has a bad temper,
and she is very hard to serve.
No one in the city dares to take on
the task of renovating the imperial palace.
Why do you want to suffer?
Lord Xian wants to impress Madam De
by renovating the imperial palace.
I won't let him do as he wishes.
My lord,
we've been hiding and playing weak for so many years.
Is it appropriate
if we act rashly now?
Lord Xian has provoked me many times.
I don't want to get involved with him.
However, he made Mrs. Zhao
set such an evil plan.
I must suppress him.
But, you didn't drink that sweet soup.
Why are you so angry?
What do you know!
In the pond of Su family's yard,
there were twin lotus flowers.
I remember they were transplanted from a place
10 miles south from the city.
Go and check it out.
Yes.
Also known as hibiscuses with the same heart.
It means to be together forever.
This imperial palace renovation is
for the late castellan.
I believe all things have spirits, and
I'm sure he¡ll get our longings.
Do all things
have spirits?
[Bai's Mansion]
Tiao.
-Have a taste. -Miss.
I just made these with His Royal Highness.
It's delicious!
What’s wrong?
You're frowning.
You're rushing me again.
Aren't you tired of drawing like that every day?
Your Highness has delicate skin.
I believe this drawing
will lead a new trend.
I’m angry today, so
I need an extra drawing
to compensate myself.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, don't be angry.
I’ll report to you on
Bai Li's latest situation now.
Lord Bai has rhinitis.
He sneezes at home all day.
He washes his face with clean water every day.
Recently, he started using a tea-colored towel.
Also, this morning, he suddenly ordered
the prohibition of noodles in Bai's Mansion.
I don't know why!
He is...
Chen Youyou.
Do something for me.
[Imperial Palace Renovation Print]
My lord.
These are snacks made by the imperial chef.
Castellan specially sent them over
as a reward for your proposal.
Leave them.
Wait a minute.
Go and ask Chen Youyou to come here.
Miss Chen is not back yet.
Why is she not back yet?
Maybe something happened?
But, don't worry, my lord!
Miss Chen
is not with His Royal Highness.
Get lost.
Come back!
Heat these up.
Yes.
Twin lotus flowers?
Well...
Where can I go and break them for you, Your Highness?
Anyway, I can’t let Bai Li get what he wants.
If you can’t do it,
the thing that is going to break
is not the lotus,
but your father’s head.
Yes.
Have you arranged
the matter regarding to her father?
Yes.
Are you hungry?
Come and have supper.
Why must you force me?
I'm not forcing you.
If you don't want to eat,
then forget it.
My lord...
you can meddle in anyone's business,
but you choose to go against Lord Xian.
Initially, I only had to say simple things.
But now,
I need to break something...
some... twin lotus flowers?
If I really break that lotus,
all your efforts will be in vain.
Castellan will definitely blame you.
But...
there is only half an apple left.
If I don't do as Lord Xian asked,
my father will die.
God,
What should I do?
Why is everything so hard?
[Qinghe Home]
My lord!
Lord Qiansui!
[Qinghe Home]
Lord Qiansui,
there is trouble at the imperial palace.
Let's go and have a look.
My lord, what about the twin lotus flowers?
It's fine, we'll come back and get them.
I need to find a way to sneak in.
My leg!
Are you alright?
Are you okay?
If you're fine, get up and work.
I have to stand up first.
I'm alone, old, and ugly.
Now, I even broke my leg.
How can I survive in the future?
Lord Qiansui risked our lives to
rush for the construction.
I want to see Madam De.
Justice will be served!
Come on,
stop dreaming!
Why are you so harsh?
Now, my arm hurts.
We'll take you to the doctor.
No.
I'll lie down wherever I fall.
I'll wait for Madam De.
Go do your own work!
How can we work
if you are lying down here?
It’s none of my business.
You'll have to wait with me then.
Lord Qiansui is here!
Don't offend him.
The last person who disobeyed orders
was beaten to death in prison.
For Youyou, I'll do it!
Lord Qiansui.
My leg!
Well...
You broke this one?
Yeah?
Since it's broken,
it's useless.
I'll chop it off for you.
No!
No.
Not this leg?
Then, it's this one.
It's not completely broken.
I can still work.
Guys,
back to work.
Move!
-You should have told me earlier. -Get back to work.
Get back to work.
-Get up. -Let's go!
Your legs and feet are quite agile.
There should be no more mistakes
with the renovation of the imperial palace.
Don't worry, my lord.
I will keep a close eye
on him.
No,
Chen Youyou.
You can't do things that harm others!
I have to think of another way.
Then, my dad...
Forget it!
Just do it!
I'm sorry.
Forget it...
Forget it.
One is my dad,
and one is Bai Li.
What should I do?
What are you doing?
My lord,
if I say...
I picked the flowers to make lotus seed soup for you,
will you believe me?
What do you think?
I...
My lord.
Madam De will inspect
the twin lotus flowers in two hours.
Now the lotus is gone,
what should we do?
You...
It's over.
Now, it's all over!
I'm sorry...
I didn't mean it.