=City of Streamer=
=Episode 35=
Coming.
Shixun.
Shizhen.
What a surprise!
Let's celebrate the New Year
as a family.
Great!
Come in. Come in.
I'll take your suitcase.
Father, Mother, guess who's coming!
Mother.
Shizhen!
- Shizhen!
Father.
Did you have dinner?
I'm hungry.
Shixun,
I'd like to eat your noodle.
Sure.
I'll go make it.
- Let me check. Did you lose weight?
- Sit down.
I've put on weight.
Why is everybody looking at me?
Look at you, daughter,
you come home at the New Year Eve.
You should let us know in advance.
We thought you'd spend the new year
in Peking.
I miss you all.
I miss home.
Welcome home.
Spend more days at here.
Don't hurry to go.
Mother,
I've quitted my job in Peking.
From now on,
I'll stay with you.
I'll stay with the family.
What…?
Did you
have a bad time in Peking?
Anything bad happened to you?
Mother,
Father,
I have something
to talk with you.
Go ahead.
I've found my biological parents.
But my biological father
passed away
like my biological mother
20 years ago.
Shizhen,
it's alright.
If they knew
you've grown up
to such a good girl,
they'd
be very happy.
Yes.
My mother has a sister.
She told me all these.
My aunt is in Shanghai.
She said
she'd come here
to visit you.
- She's welcome.
- Great.
Shizhen, this is good news.
Go tell her,
the family welcomes her.
We're looking forward
to a family reunion.
Yes.
Thank you, Mother.
Get out of here.
Yes.
What do you want?
Who is the dead body in Wenchunli?
I want the truth.
If you have the time,
think about
how to make money for the company
rather than the rubbish.
Are you Qin Shuigen?
Qin Shuigen?
Qin Shuigen.
Do you know?
Bai's daughter is alive.
Can't be!
I saw her fall into water.
She survived.
She's back for revenge.
Father,
tell me everything about Wenchunli.
Tell me what happened there.
What does she want?
She wrote the IOU.
Tell me what she wants.
Father,
don't hide it from me.
Tell me the truth,
or I will ask Uncle Zhao.
He would put all the blames
on you, though,
I can still
make out the truth.
Zhao Hua'an is not a simple man.
Don't trust a single word of him.
He's ambitious.
He wants to take your place.
Father,
he knows too much about you.
It's easy for him to hurt you
and our family.
But I am ignorant of this.
I don't know how to defend.
Know yourself,
know your enemy.
Tell me the truth,
for the family's sake.
My mother died
when I was young.
I lived as a mason.
Zhao Hua'an was no better than me.
We decided
to do some business.
We traded imported goods
to scrap a meager living.
Later,
we met He,
who was the real Rong Dingkun.
It was interesting that
we were neither kith nor kin
but looked very alike.
He was a good man,
kindhearted,
loyal to friends,
and
paid off my debts.
We became sworn brothers.
Men
may be good to you,
but not always.
In three days,
I will have my money,
or I will
have your hand.
Please help me!
Ma Laojiu said
if I can't pay the debt,
he'll take my hand.
300.
I need just 300.
Bro,
I can't help you.
My wife is having a baby.
She's coming to Shanghai.
I have to settle them down.
I don't have extra money.
He won the lottery, 1,000 yuan.
He had the money but didn't help me.
He'd rather watch them chop my hand.
And he blamed me
for breaking the rules.
We all make a living in the dock.
Nobody has clean hands.
I just got something
from Ma Laojiu and I failed
in selling them.
So you killed him?
He forced me to.
Who are you?
Shuigen?
What are you doing?
You're taking my lottery!
I've been so good to you.
How can you do this to me?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Go!
I'll take you to the police.
No!
Go!
To the police! Go!
Bro, are you crazy?
Bro,
don't tell a word of this!
You'll have half of the lottery.
What about him?
We've got too many lodgers here.
They'll see the body.
How do you hide it?
The wall.
So you sealed him up in the wall?
Or what should I do?
I can't afford the risk.
I can't afford the risk
to move his body.
I sealed him up
in the wall.
At the night,
I disguised as him
and told the neighbors
I'd go visit my hometown.
They believed he had gone.
Nobody noticed anything.
Then I disguised as Rong Dingkun
and cashed the lottery.
It was then that I knew
he had written home
about the lottery.
His wife and parents were coming to him.
I talked with Zhao Hua'an that
though we looked very alike,
I wouldn't fool his wife and parents.
I can't do this by half.
So I killed
them all.
So
you're Qin Shuigen.
Yes.
That woman
was so stupid.
She didn't recognize her own husband.
I… I stabbed her twice.
I stabbed her to death.
And her family…
It was so easy.
I found a cloth
of a plague patient.
They all died.
Were you crazy?
You'd have hidden somewhere
for a while.
Why did you do that?
I didn't have the time.
If I didn't do that,
how could I marry your mother?
how could I have you?
But…
I cut the weeds
and didn't dig out the roots.
I saw
that girl fell into water.
Zhao Hua'an said
"she couldn't survive!
she couldn't survive!"
We went to the police
and didn't see her body.
I thought she was eaten by wild dogs.
I forgot her.
Now!
Look at it now!
She comes back
for revenge!
It was Zhao Hua'an!
Zhao Hua'an pushed me into this.
You killed him
and tell me he forced you to.
She comes back for revenge
and you blame Zhao Hua'an
for not having killed them all!
You have blood on your hands
and you stand clear of all these
and blame others.
You are the innocent.
Have you ever thought of the victims?
They were not guilty!
They were innocent!
And the girl who survived,
she did nothing wrong
but has to take the hatred
and live in pain!
Isn't she innocent?
You traitor!
I brought you to this world!
I'd rather I was not born!
For 20 years, you've been
playing Rong Dingkun.
It's time to end all these
and be yourself.
Get out!
A sextant?
Navigators in the past
used the sextant to locate the bearings.
You told me
that you wanted to be a pilot.
I hope one day,
you can bravely chase your dream
and be a free and fearless pilot
high up in the sky.
When I
first saw you in the dancing hall,
I didn't know who you were,
but I knew I'm in love
with you.
I thought
between you and me was the bloodline.
I didn't know it was a blood debt.
How could I face you?
We…
What shall I do?
Are we finished?
Shizhen told us
you'll visit us.
We've been
looking forward to it.
Hope I didn't ruin your new year.
Not at all.
We're family.
You're welcome.
May I
call you Sister Feng?
You're really nice people.
You've taught Shizhen so well.
I…
I will
enshrine you at home,
offer incense,
and pray to Buddha for your family.
Wish you good luck
and fortune.
Ms. Qian,
you flattered us.
Shizhen
is our daughter.
We love her very much.
We're a family.
Yes.
Shizhen,
lead your aunt to the table.
Yes.
Aunt,
Mother,
dinner time.
- Sit down.
Coming.
Dinner is ready.
Tonight
there's a lantern show in Zhaofeng Park.
After the dinner,
let's go have a look,
shall we?
- Great.
Look at this.
It's beautiful!
This one.
How much is it?
This is good, too.
Shixun, look at that lanterns.
We saw them when we were little.
A long row of them.
When they were little,
in the new year,
we brought them to the lantern show.
At that time,
Shixun loves roast chestnuts,
- and Shizhen
- Yes, yes.
was crazy for ice cream.
Yes, yes.
The boy and girl begged me.
They wouldn't go until
they got what they wanted.
Kids are always greedy.
- They got me greedy now.
- This is amazing.
Shixun, I want some roast chestnut.
Go for it.
All yours.
It's good to have a brother.
Flatterer. Go get it.
Keep going with them.
Sure.
Don't waste your holiday at home.
Alcohol is something
that pleases you.
But don't indulge in it.
If you miss her,
go to her.
- Hello, I want a pack of this.
- Yes.
See her or not see her,
what's the difference?
You always tell the opposite
of what you want.
Come to me if you like.
New Metropolis has lots of fun.
Hey.
Shizhen.
Happy New Year.
How are you doing?
Is your father well?
He's fine.
He quit opium.
Now he gets better.
My aunt joined us.
This new year
is not bad.
Will you
go back to Peking?
No, I won't.
I have my job in Shanghai.
The phone call…
I should have known it.
So what?
It makes no difference.
The IOU…
Did he get it?
He did.
So…
he didn't acknowledge?
It doesn't matter.
God
is watching.
Sooner or later
it will be paid off.
He didn't acknowledge,
but I do.
I apologize for my father's sins.
I'll pay my father's debt.
It's a natural thing.
You can't choose your parents.
I don't blame you.
But
we can't be together.
Time to say goodbye.
Shizhen,
I'll make my father acknowledge.
On the 11th of next month,
Fanghua and Yunchi will get married.
They'll live abroad then.
And I'll
send Fanglin to school with them.
Then I'll hold a press conference.
I'll make my father
acknowledge all his debts.
I'm tired of all these.
I used to believe
though Rong's business was a shame,
my father fought for it.
I'm the heir
and I should carry it on.
I didn't know the Rongs…
no,
the Qins…
Every piece of the Qin's brick
has the Rong's blood on it.
And I…
I grew up by sucking their blood.
I'm afraid of going to that house.
I'm afraid that
I'll smell the blood once I get in.
I always think
the wall
has more dead bodies in it.
Jiashang.
Don't pity me.
Every time I go home,
I see my father lying in bed
with opium.
He's like a ghost.
I'm afraid one day
I'll become him.
This is not my life.
Ah,
the sextant you gave to me
is always on my desk.
Every time I see it,
it reminds me of what you said to me,
and reminds me
of the beautiful wishes.
But I always let you down.
Shizhen,
take care of yourself.
I hope one day
I could stand before you,
clear and clean.
Good bye.
Go tell Master.
Yes.
What's it?
The hospital called.
Young master
is gone.
Master!
Master, young master is gone.
Jiakang!
Mother's taking you home.
Let's go home.
I'm sorry, Concubine Sun.
Please give him to me.
Excuse me.
No! No! No!
- He's sleeping!
- Sis.
- Give him to me. He's sleeping!
- It's alright.
It's alright.
This is fate.
Weeping and mourning
won't bring him back.
Don't cry.
Calm down.
Don't cry. Take care of yourself.
He's my son,
not yours!
Of course you don't care about him!
You…!
Ma'am.
So ungrateful!
Let's go!
Go!
He died too young.
There's no grand funeral.
Get some men
and bury him soon.
Yes.
Sister,
you've got to face it.
Don't cry.
Let him go.
You have a long life
ahead of you.
Jiakang is gone.
He was my only son.
Master is in this condition.
He can't give me another son.
Without a son,
I don't have
a future in this house.
Sister,
everyone knows
Master is dying.
Mr. Jiashang takes the wheel
for the family.
Mr. Jiashang is cold,
but he's responsible
for the younger brother and sisters
and the family relatives.
I think
he will be good to you.
I failed
to save your son.
Sorry.
Miss Feng.
Let me.
Miss Feng,
I drove your aunt
to the railway station yesterday.
She'll be in Guangzhou in a few days.
She's fine.
Thank you, Wen.
My pleasure, Miss Feng.
Give it to me.
Thank you.
Do they agree
you live in Baoli's apartment?
I told them Baoli needs an assistant.
Shixun begged them for me.
They approved.
Your brother
is an open-minded man.
Ah, yes,
is he
interested in politics?
Recently he's close to
some progressive youth.
Did he tell you
he joined some society?
He doesn't talk about that.
Is there anything wrong?
Not yet.
How about
I keep an eye on him?
Should anything happen,
I'll let you know soon.
Thank you, Mr. Meng.
Don't worry too much.
Did you read the news today?
Nope.
At 7:00 AM,
Commander Cao and Commander Ma
started a war at Dongpoping.
Good start of the year.
I can't wait to see.
For the commanders,
war is part of their life.
Think about it,
they're good for nothing.
Newspapers always exaggerate.
Are the wars so violent?
The truth is
none of them would
spend on civil war.
The soldiers are reluctant to shoot,
not to mention combat.
Men talk about fighting and killing.
I'm out.
Shizhen,
in fact this has
something to do with the Rongs.
You mean the Rongs
supply arms to Commander Cao?
More than that.
They're closely related to the Mas.
I know it.
Zhao Hua'an plotted this.
But Rong Jiashang
is not clean of this.
Mr. Meng,
I've made a decision.
Rong Jiashang
and Zhao Hua'an
make no difference
to me.
Mr. Yang,
share what you've got.
Apparently,
Rong Jiashang
is at the helm.
Actually most of the businesses
in his hands
are lawful businesses.
Of course,
this is because the Wenchunli incident
has consumed all the cash
available to Rong Jiashang.
The Rong's moneymakers,
arms, opium and antique trafficking,
are controlled by Zhao Hua'an
and some crafty assistant managers.
Rong Jiashang
is seemingly sitting in glory,
which actually tortures him.
Rong's Company's large shareholders
started a war because of
the Wenchunli incident.
Many of them withdrew their shares.
The rest of them are
forcing Rong Jiashang to split the cake
and are fighting for profitable shares.
The information I got this time
is a bit strange.
Why is it?
The information is reliable.
Both Commander Cao and Commander Ma
are using the arms supplied
by Zhao Hua'an.
Technically,
the Rongs are in internal conflicts.
It can't coordinate and supply
a huge amount of arms in a short time,
not even in its heyday,
since the shareholders are
friendly foes.
It doesn't have the efficiency.
It's strange that
how Zhao Hua'an did it.
After Qin Shuigen fell ill,
he's more cautious of Rong Jiashang.
Is it possible that
the one behind Zhao Hua'an,
or
the one who helps him
is Qin Shuigen?
He has but one purpose.
He will retake the rule
as soon as possible
from Rong Jiashang.
He is
always coldblooded.
He shows no mercy
even to Rong Jiashang.
Qin Shuigen
has many old followers.
Zhao Hua'an is not the best,
but the most trusted.
I agree with Mr. Meng.
The one behind
is Qin Shuigen.
It's not about trust.
These two men
know each other's secret.
They share a balance of interests.
They're two-in-one.
In Rong's house today,
Zhao Hua'an
is next only to one man.
If Qin Shuigen does not
try to coordinate the powers,
soon
they'll collapse from inside.
Mr. Meng suggests
we make unrest
and make the Rongs' seniors believe
Zhao Hua'an wants to take power,
and heat up their ambitions.
And then
break up their family.
That's right.
I've considered
Miss Feng's idea.
But the current situation is
Zhao Hua'an
is loyal to the Rong's family.
Zhao Hua'an has a trump card.
What's it?
He has a henchman
at the high level in the south.
That man has the code book
of the transport corps.
That's to say,
only he and his henchman
know where the corps is,
where it is going,
and where it delivers.
Qin Shuigen had a code book.
I suppose Rong Jiashang's taking it.
I know that code book.
Is it the one I decoded?
Yes.
Miss Feng decoded it
and they changed the code.
The most important thing is
Zhao Hua'an
has the code only known to him.
The code for his own corps.
He's not the only one.
All the other gang managers
have their own businesses.
Sometimes they embezzle Rong's goods
for private profits.
It has been Qin Shuigen's long headache.
Well,
can you get the code,
Mr. Yang?
Very possible.
By telegram interception.
But it takes time
to decode it.
That's my job.
The key is
we should get that code book.
Miss Feng is good at this.
I admire that.
Alright,
I'll work on this.
Em.
Any comment, Mr. Meng?
It sounds like a plan.
Just do it.
I have one concern,
or scruple.
The man you love might get hurt.
There is no more a tie between us.
What's more,
he's a man.
Does a man need the shelter of a woman?
♪The aftertaste of love lingers♪
♪Hatred snaps roses in two♪
♪Tear-like drizzle seems fine♪
♪Where's the key to one's heart♪
♪Who knows what lies ahead♪
♪The moon isn't lonelier than us♪
♪Sitting alone to see
begonias in the breeze♪
♪I still remember our dance♪
♪I remember the way you looked at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away thick leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪I remember the way you smiled at me♪
♪The autumn wind can't
whisk away innocent leaves♪
♪However time streams♪
♪Hearts remain tiny cities♪
♪If we could be together in this life♪
♪And trust each other completely♪
♪However time flies♪
♪We're destined to love♪
♪And cherish each other♪