Our Secret
EP09
Didn't you say you wanted to study?
You didn't even open your book.
I was just about to open it.
Mom, you can go back to rest.
I will study.
Take it out.
Whom did you call just now?
My classmate.
What classmate?
It's so late now.
I asked him about the homework today.
Mom
I promise I won't
chat with classmates at night.
I'll keep it for you first.
It's for your own good.
Study hard and don't be distracted.
Remember to eat the fruit.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Happy birthday!
Thank you.
Make a birthday wish.
In one breath.
OK.
No need to thank me.
Just have fun.
Enjoy yourselves.
Kong Shadi, really it's you here.
Haven't seen you for a long time.
It's us.
We were playmates in junior high.
Remember?
You are...
That's unimportant.
The point is that
you're more and more beautiful.
You didn't invite us both
to your birthday party.
What happened?
I only invited my classmates this time.
I'll invite you next time.
Don't wait until next time.
Come to join us. Let's go.
No, no.
Didn't you hear her say no?
Who are you?
It's not up to you to tell me what to do.
You don't know I'm from No.18 Middle School.
Right?
It doesn't matter who I am.
Do you know Jiang Chen?
Of course.
I was with him just now.
He's my childhood friend.
What are your names?
I'll phone and ask him.
Wait a moment.
No no no, forget it.
Don't bother Chen.
It was all a big mistake, bro.
Since you're the friend of Chen
we won't bother you.
We.
We're leaving.
We're just kidding.
-Happy birthday.  -Happy birthday.
Bye.
-Ziqi, you're so cool.  -Cool.
Keep a low profile.
Enjoy yourselves.
I'll find someone to cut the cake.
Why are you looking at me?
You don't have enough friends?
lt is none of your business.
How can you be friends with them?
You don't learn from good examples.
Is it not enough for you to have me?
Studying hard with me is the most important.
Do you hear me?
Yes.
Let's play games.
Any advice?
Word chain.
You're bored.
-So boring.  -Listen to the birthday girl.
Shadi, Shadi, what's your opinion?
What do you want to play?
Word chain.
Look! Look!
Mr. Liu
How's it going? Have you figured it out?
Yes.
The abscissa of point P is one.
You are sure to win the prize.
Let me tell you about the last question.
Many students...
Is that what I asked you?
Will you tell me
where you went last night?
Siyue, if you have something on your mind
you can tell me.
I understand you.
But do not keep them bottled up.
Understand?
Yes.
I'll tell you next time.
What? You.
Thank you, Mr. Liu.
You little brat.
Mr. Liu
I know where Zhou Siyue went last night.
You are everywhere.
Wait.
Tell me. Where did he go last night?
Hello. What's up?
Where is she?
I'll go there first.
You go to get others.
Little Monster
Help.
Please give me your English homework.
Why don't you borrow Childe Zhou's?
He has just finished the competition and is sleeping.
How dare I wake him up?
So I have to settle for second best
and copy yours grudgingly.
Don't take your undeserved gain for granted.
Xianxian
Please give me your math homework.
You two are definitely deskmates.
Thank you.
The monthly quiz results have come.
The class supervisor also said
he would talk with us
one by one.
Be prepared.
How did it happen?
Yes!
What's wrong?
My score of natural science is 270.
A perfect pass.
I said I would stay here.
By the way
my mom confiscated my phone.
So we can't call at night.
Nobody wants to call you.
You called me.
You.
Don't you remember?
Who?
It's you.
You called me.
Who did you mean?
Don't touch my hair.
-Say it again.  -What are you doing?
Concentrate on self-study.
Why are you so happy? A stroke of luck?
Mom, let me show you something.
So
I can stay in science class, right?
You did well enough in this quiz.
It's nothing to me.
In fact, science is not as difficult as you think.
But, Xianxian.
Although you did well this time
-in fact...  -Stop.
Mom, we came to an agreement.
It's dishonest of you to go back on your word.
All right, all right, all right.
Anyway, you choose your own way.
Go by yourself.
Then you know it's hard.
Well.
Mom.
I have finished the exam.
I want...
I know what you're thinking.
Thank you, mom.
Have fun. Pride comes before a fall.
The monthly quiz this time
is relatively simple.
Although your score has improved greatly
your ranking is still relatively low.
Never take it lightly.
OK, Mr. Liu.
Ding Xian
One more thing.
I saw you chat a lot
in class with Zhou Siyue recently.
Did he affect your study?
No, Mr. Liu. He didn't affect me.
But someone did tell me
you two had been so close lately.
And you often go out together after school.
Ding Xian, there's no time to waste.
Focus on your study now.
This is not the case.
Our relationship is not what you think.
Well, change seats with Song Ziqi
after going back.
I'll study hard when I go back.
We won't chat in class.
Don't worry, Mr. Liu.
If I don't make progress
in the next monthly quiz
I'll change seats
on my own.
Who told Auntie?
So gossipy.
Don't ever let me know.
I guess it must be a girl.
She was jealous of your close relationship.
Watch what you say.
We're merely deskmates.
Maybe we won't be deskmates later.
Why?
Auntie asked me to change seats.
He said it would affect my study.
No way.
Why do all teachers like this?
Not only that
he asked me to change seats with Song Ziqi.
You can't.
Don't you dislike him?
I was just speaking casually. I don't mind.
I smell a rat.
When we went to KTV that day
he was angry when he saw
I was singing with other boys.
He just sat there without a word.
Finally, he took me home.
I suddenly felt
he was a little different that day.
Fickle.
You weren't like this the other day.
You were mad to see him
walking with the girl.
That was a mistake.
He told me later
they just discussed
the basketball game.
How did you know that?
I went to her that day to find it out.
Hello.
What's up?
She is actually a national
second level shot-putter.
She almost killed me.
Stop talking about me.
When do you change seats?
Maybe after the monthly quiz.
It depends on my quiz result.
Ding Xian
Can you solve this problem?
I've been stuck for a long time.
Let me have a look.
The function
of ordinate.
Answer.
R is greater than B.
RX proves...
1025.
X equals 1025.
So accurate.
What about this one?
I'll try again.
547.
Nine o'clock.
You can count in your head?
Don't you feel tired of solving problems all the time?
I mean, rack your brain.
No, I don't.
I'll do reading comprehension for relax
when I feel tired.
You're a real brain box.
Let's go on.
I still couldn't understand this question.
Can you teach me with your method?
Superficial knowledge is enough.
OK.
If you can't solve the problem later
you can ask me directly.
OK, OK.
Zhou Siyue
Let's play basketball.
You called me out so early for this?
Haven't you heard
a saying from my idol?
Have ever seen the scene
of Shenhai at 4 a.m.?
It's six o'clock.
They're the same.
Hardship increases status.
I haven't seen you study so hard.
What's the matter with you lately?
It's just a competition.
Why are you so tired?
Competition is not tiring
but explaining problems is.
You're so strange.
Liu Xiaofeng is not much of your friend.
Why are you explaining problems to him every day?
Nobody else here.
I'm leaving.
They will be here soon.
The game is coming.
Everyone will train against the clock.
I won't take part in the game.
Why should I train?
Don't you want to see
pretty girls cheering for you?
Don't you want to
help me teach Class Eight a lesson?
It's none of my business.
But I signed you up.
Nobody can change it.
Come on.
I'll go back to bed.
Practice hard.
Xianxian
Why didn't you go to the basketball game?
Nothing special.
I'm preparing for the monthly quiz.
Zhou Siyue is also the player.
You don't want to go?
Didn't he refuse to take part in it?
Don't you know Song Ziqi?
He must grab Zhou Siyue
no matter what he does.
Class Eight is too arrogant.
They're showing off because they have
posters and banners.
Why not print one?
We're not afraid of them.
But it's too late to print now.
Do you have any cardboards?
I can draw.
How can I forget you?
I'll bring some paper.
Bring it.
Hurry up. Come on.
Here you are.
You guys, come here.
What's the most in science class?
Right.
Boys.
Today is the time for Class Three to distinguish ourselves.
Just do it.
But they have cheerleaders.
And megaphones.
Come on, Class Eight!
So what?
We have Childe Siyue.
Right?
Please do me a favor, bro.
If you don't go, girls won't watch either.
I told you I didn't want to play today.
Suit yourself.
Come here, guys.
Come on.
One two three. Come on.
Ding Xian, you draw very well.
I'm leaving. Thank you.
Thank you. Bye.
OK. Let's go.
Wait a moment.
Xianxian
Can you draw another one for me?
Write "Song Ziqi is handsome" on it.
Something's wrong with you.
Help me.
OK. Song Ziqi is handsome.
What do you mean?
OK. I'll draw it for you.
Come on!
Come on, Class Eight!
Come on, Class Eight! Come on, Class Eight!
How did you pass the ball?
Stop dawdling.
The game has already begun.
Don't rush us.
Don't you see we're busy now?
Done.
So good-looking.
Look. Is it good-looking?
This one is for Zhou Siyue.
I prepared it for you.
It's so kind of you.
Well, you win.
Naive.
No, Class Eight is too aggressive.
I can't hold out.
Hurry to enter the court, Childe.
I'm too tired to play.
You.
You've performed below par?
Yang Chunzi
I'm glad that you bring me water.
But you're in Class Eight now.
I'll feel awkward if you do this.
Siyue, drink water.
Thank you.
Put on airs.
Don't you think she's a hypocrite?
She has the same expression
no matter she's happy or not.
Yes indeed.
They're not in the same class now.
Does she specialize in water delivery?
What are you laughing at?
We're on your side.
Who's tired?
I can't make it. I can't make it.
You can have a rest.
Finally you're awake, bro.
Let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Zhou Siyue. Come on. Come on.
Zhou Siyue, you can do it!
Come on, Zhou Siyue.
Come on, Class Three!
Bravo, Zhou Siyue!
Where is your energy of misbehaving?
We can't lose in momentum.
Shout.
Zhou Siyue, you're the best.
Come on, Class Three!
Zhou is great.
Pretty? Are you blind?
One day has passed.
Why hasn't Siyue come yet?
Did he ask for leave?
We're not
inseparable, right?
I have a piece of good news.
In the math competition of our city
Zhou Siyue
doesn't let us down.
He has won the first place in our city.
Deng Wanwan
Hang the award on the wall.
Zhou Siyue is so brilliant.
Don't be discouraged if you don't
get the ranking this time.
There are many chances in the future.
Look forward.
OK. Stop discussing.
Start your free study class.
Zhou Siyue deserves to be Mr. Liu's son.
What's your meaning?
Let me tell you.
Zhou Siyue was found sneaking out
the night before the competition.
He was still qualified to participate in the competition.
Now he won the first place through the back door.
I can't catch up with him
in this field.
Watch what you say.
He Xingwen, can you be less jealous?
Siyue has won honour in the basketball match
for our class.
He also comes out in front in math.
What? You're jealous, aren't you?
I'm jealous?
Why am I jealous?
I just think it's unfair.
Why is the teacher so partial to him?
I heard Siyue was also punished.
He seemed to have run ten laps in the playground.
Ten laps?
Only ten laps after such a big mistake.
Isn't that obvious favoritism?
If you think it's unfair
you can tell the teacher.
Why do you comment on him behind his back?
That's all what you can do now?
Right.
-Why don't you mention it just now?  -Right.
Why don't you mention it just now?
Zhou Siyue
The light is on.
Who is it?
You have a cold?
I caught cold while playing basketball before.
It's so cold in your house.
You dare to open the window.
Aren't you afraid of getting worse?
It's you?
I didn't mean it.
It can ventilate your room.
It's good.
Where is your mother?
She
went out.
Have you eaten yet?
I just woke up.
I feel lazy.
Is there anything to eat at home?
Instant noodles?
Well.
Is it enough?
Soup?
It's porridge.
I cooked it for the first time.
It looks nice.
How does it taste?
Tasty.
Eat more.
I'll help myself.
I'll repair the window.
No.
It will hurt your hand.
Sit down.
Why did you visit me suddenly?
You have won the first place in the competition.
I want to tell you.
And
Mr. Liu punished you
because you
sneaked out, right?
Who told you?
Sorry.
Not because of you.
Are
you tired?
Yes.
But then what will happen?
I'm afraid you're too tired.
What if
you get depressed one day?
What will
you do if that day comes?
I will help you unconditionally
and stay with you.
Stupid.
I'm not as vulnerable as you think.
And
there must be many more difficulties in the future.
But I won't let you worry.
I'll get you a cup of hot water.
Not bad.
Ding Xian
Where did you put
those dirty clothes?
I'll bring them to you later.
What are you doing?
Your cooking?
It's terrible.
Ding Xian, don't cook anymore.
It's dark cuisine.
You eat my cooking and blame me.
-Ding Xian.  -Come here.
Mom, what are you doing with my diary?
Ding Xian
How old are you?
You didn't put your mind on your study.
What are you thinking about?
You read my diary?
I won't know
what you have done if I don't read it.
I lost to him in the game room.
Mom, stop reading.
Isn't that what you write?
Why are you afraid to hear that?
Give me.
Give me your diary.
This doesn't end if you don't give me.
Give me.
What are you doing? Give me.
Are you satisfied?
I won't keep a diary anymore.
Suit yourself.
I tell you.
You're not allowed to go out from now on.
What are you doing?
I quarreled with my mother.
I threw out my diary.
Are you sure you threw it here?
I just saw a rag man pass by
on the other side.
Excuse me. Did you see a rag man?
He left early.
He left.
Don't cry.
I'm fine.
Let it go.
If you don't want to go home
stay in my house for a while.
Let's go.
Are you hungry?
You didn't have breakfast?
I cooked porridge and
wanted to bring it to you.
But I ran out in a fit of pique and couldn't get it back.
And
the porridge is terrible.
You're kidding me.
Maybe it's because I'm sick
so my taste sense doesn't work.
It seems that there is nothing to eat at home.
Only instant noodles.
Come on.
Seafood or braised beef flavor?
Either.
OK.
I'll boil the kettle.
It's done.
It's my first time to eat instant noodles.
Usually mom doesn't let me eat.
Your mother
treats you well.
Perhaps.
But she doesn't understand
or believe me.
She peeked at
my diary this time.
Your mother
did that because she
cared about you.
Your mother treats you really well.
By the way.
Let me show you something.
What's this?
My awarded work
in the robot competition.
Come on, D2-T3. Dance.
It's cute.
Why does it dance like Chaplin?
You know Chaplin?
Good.
How do you feel?
Feel better now?
Much better.
It's interesting.
A successful test.
Test?
It
is actually a comedian robot.
It specializes in treating
patients with mental diseases.
You're with mental disease.
Well. Hurry up.
I'll take you home after finishing it.
I don't want to go back yet.
Can I stay here for one night?