Yongle twenty-two years in August
Ming prince Zhu Gaochi ascended the throne as emperor
Crown Princess Zhang as Empress
And canonized Guo as a noble concubine
The crown prince Zhu Zhanji was named the crown prince
Hu's Crown Princess
Zijin
Free at kisskh.me
The princess sent someone from the palace
Crying for days before
The princess is weak
Coughing
Hu Shang's index finger asked you to make a medicated meal and send it to you
Yes
The civil and military officials went to the table five times to persuade them to enter
His Majesty has promised to ascend the throne
according to etiquette
Twenty-seven days have passed since mourning
officials who are in a hurry
But the abacus is wrong
Is the father and son concentric
So is the prince
I heard you have a bad cough yesterday
don't hold on
Or ask the pharmacist to come and have a look.
I was too tired a few days ago
stasis heat inside
It was cold again last night
Just rest for a few days
no fuss
it's your body that matters
Slave, this will help you make a cup
Ganfengling developed by Taiyuan Hospital
you drink first
Okay
It's good to use it for the past few days
You are the most considerate
it's hot
I'm feeling chest tightness and thirst
The princess has been coughing for a long time
lotus leaf porridge to clear heat and moisten the lungs
please give it a try
Inside is sweet-scented osmanthus and taro paste
Yes
Cinnamon refreshing fragrance
Taro nourishes the stomach and strengthens the spleen
But the princess is weak and spleen
Taro is easy to bloat
can not be used more
I use this lotus leaf porridge very well
Today's meal is light and delicious
Give it to the Crown Prince as it is.
Yes
princess
Beware of wolves
Free from Yongle's 22-year household registration salt and grain
Everywhere it owes horse grass and charcoal
Before December of the 20th year of Yongle
Do your best to avoid
add one more
flee to every house
all guilty
Return to home country to resume business
two-year exemption
Taxes owed by the household
Do your best to avoid
father emperor
I just go to buy everywhere
did you come for this
The father emperor stopped the horses in the west city and Yunnan
Cochin acquisition
It's all acts of compassion
Sonny has no objection
Only the issue of Nanjing
Also ask the father to think twice
Who said it's all over
You know before I say it
Are you sending someone now too?
Watch my every move
Father's anger
The son just heard that the emperor ordered people to go south
I dare to speculate on the renovation of the Imperial City of Nanjing
After the grandfather's mourning period
The emperor may have intentions to return
Ruo Erchen guessed wrong
Please forgive my father
Free at kisskh.me
Since moving the capital
south-to-north diversion
Labor and wealth
Arutai keeps nuisance
Nanjing
It is the capital of the Taizu
still Nanjing
That is to follow the old system of the ancestors
father emperor
Beijing is the Land of Longxing
dangerous location
The grandfather moved the capital here
It is to honor the Son of Heaven
Guarding the gate of Daming
Control the four levels, level the world, and achieve the foundation of all ages
In a hurry, it is easy to return
Grandpa Huang's painstaking efforts will be destroyed in one fell swoop
father emperor
The person the grandfather wants to kill
Regardless of the severity of the crime
you are always pardoned
his national policy
It's changing one by one
Going backwards everywhere
why exactly
Prince
Don't rely on the emperor's favor for you
You can be so presumptuous to me
grandfather loves me
Only because there are people in this world who can understand him
only me
Grandfather's aspirations, father doesn't understand
never understand
You just want to be a benevolent king
But now the country's biggest troubles remain
rely only on benevolence
Can't rule the world
then you tell me
What is the trouble
Han-o
what i did
you don't need to beak
get me out
get out
Erchen resigns
continue
Yes
At that time, Jinyiwei was ordered by the emperor to test
Oversee the East Palace
where is the volume
Waiting for the grandfather to win
Let's go hunting
adult
I have been instructed to monitor the East Palace
Now the new emperor succeeds
Will it settle accounts after the fall?
kneel down
Hu Shangshi
what does this mean
princess
The slaves came here today to plead guilty
Slaves are not strict
Let Yao Zijin commit the big crime of privately indulging Concubine Zhuang
Private Zhuang Concubine
Before Concubine Zhuang was buried
Yao Zijin took advantage of the meal delivery machine
Concubine Zhuang leaves the palace privately
This is evidenced by Ajin, the maid of Yongning Palace.
Now the harem has been decided
The queen is busy
Slaves dare not disturb
Came here specially to ask the princess to decide
Hu Shangshi
Do you know how sinful a false accusation is
Even if you are my elder sister
I won't be indulgent
Akin
How dare you hide it in front of the princess
Are you dying?
princess
It was Miss Yao who gave her master a jade pendant
Just walked out of Bei'anmen safely
what jade pendant
A phoenix pendant that only a queen can have
The Bei'anmen guard is an old man in the palace
Once you see this
Fright is not enough
How dare you stop
General Chen promises to be tight-lipped
When returning to the palace
But it needs to be left as proof
Yao Zijin
where did you get this
It is said that this phoenix pendant was carved by the emperor himself.
Empress Renxiao carries it with her day and night
Seeing Pei in the palace is like seeing the Lord
Obey the order
Empress Renxiao raised the prince herself
Grandparents are very affectionate
after she passed away
Leave the jade pendant to the late emperor
Indicates that he will leave it to his future granddaughter-in-law
You say
This jade pendant
Why in the hands of a female official
Yao Zijin
who are you
Your Highness
call her
i want to see her
Yes
what's the matter
Your Highness
General Chen Lao, the defender of Bei'an Gate
Knowing that His Royal Highness is waiting for the Zigong day and night
never dared to disturb
I heard that His Highness is back
have something to offer
why don't you answer
Yao Zijin
She was the emperor
Concubine appointed for the prince
Mrs. Peng Chengbo
princess
Sun's Fang is ten years old
He was introduced to the palace by Mrs. Peng Chengbo
Raised by the current Queen Zhang
half a year later
Sun's illness leaves the palace
Stay in Yongcheng to recuperate
You can only get married when you grow up
Who knew that the first emperor obeyed the mandate of heaven
Change you to be the concubine
Sun is narrow-minded
a serious illness
After the emperor found out
displeased
No one has dared to mention her since then.
princess
I said before that you are kind and kind
See it now
You've been blinded by this viper woman
She concealed her identity and entered the palace
lurking around you
what is the purpose
Self-explanatory
Hu Shangshi
You and I have been together for a long time
Have I ever done a bad thing
Did you kill someone?
dare you say
You concealed your identity and entered the palace
not something else
princess
This woman is left behind
can not tolerate
I know you can't be ruthless
I'll do it for you
come
Free at kisskh.me
you really want to kill me
Hu Shangshi
Yao Zijin
Intention to murder the princess
Unacceptable Gong Zhengji interrogation
have committed suicide
princess
Evidence is here
previously
you want to take my identity
Now I'm still making up lies
take my life
I always thought you were kind
But when it involves oneself
you're about to turn things around
Are you reckless?
not possible
elder sister
she must die, the princess
must kill her
elder sister
After entering the palace
i lost a sister
when i see you
The feeling of being lost and found
just before yesterday
i'm still thinking
you are so smart
never fail
future
I should leave the mantle to you
But
You threatened the Hu family
threatened the princess
I have no choice
In the next life I will be a cow and a horse
Pay for my sins today
elder sister
you are confused
Crown Princess, all women in the world can enter the palace
Only Sun can't
I do it all for you
even if you are not for yourself
Consider your loved ones too
what are you doing
Zijin Lai
are you alright
Zijin
Your Highness
take people away
Zijin
If I hadn't sent someone to watch the Qingning Palace
Are you going to lie to me for the rest of your life?
Your Highness, please rest assured
Miss Yao is just too frightened
body is fine
wake up soon
go down
Yes
resign
no explanation
this is going
Yao Zijin
Do not
I forgot your surname is Yao
Is it even a fake name?
Your Highness is really a nobleman and forgets things
when i see you
you're only ten
Yes
Entering the palace for the first time
still young
how many years have passed
don't say your majesty
Who else in this palace remembers who I am?
It was your grandmother who entered the palace for you.
is not it
Does His Highness want to prosecute the slave and maid for the crime of impersonation?
I said
You are not allowed to call yourself a slave
I'm not a slave now
who is that
you immigrated to the palace
approach me on purpose
what do you want to do
Your Highness
that year
I went to worship Buddha with my mother
I accidentally met Mrs. Peng Chengbo
From then onwards
Madam often goes in and out of Sun's house
And my mother taught me
more and more severe
I found out later
In order to consolidate the power of the Zhang family, Mrs.
The girl who has been looking for early wisdom
Teach carefully
In preparation for the choice of the concubine
finally
she picked me
Your Highness doesn't like playing chess with me very much.
listen to me play the piano
In addition to piano, chess, calligraphy and painting
Pipa Orchestra
female red cooking
Even Cuju, riding and shooting are not a problem.
what does your majesty like
I will learn to master
not so
i will be beaten
Serve Your Highness
live for you
Seems like the only meaning in my life
I don't know any of this
Yes
such a small thing
How to tarnish the ear of His Highness
Your Highness will not know
Before I entered the palace to see the emperor
What happened to the Sun family?
Since it is the master who taught you from childhood
You have become the first choice of Taisun Concubine
it was a good thing
why is she
she is not my teacher
she is my biological mother
i pee know
she is my mother
But I never called her once
Because of her humble status
Because she will defile the lintel of the Sun family
So we get along day and night
her hands
teach me to read and write
play the piano
But don't let me call her mother
How many times do I have to blurt out
In the end I dare not
she died
die for me
A person who is a grandson
how to let others know
her mother was born
how proud she is
she never gave up
But she recognized
for my future
In order for me to have a background that is not criticized
She hangs herself
Your Highness
for you
It's just a change of choice
for me
Means my biological mother sacrificed in vain
Means her death is meaningless
I do not want
I don't want to be a grandson
I just hope she survives
I'm wrong
The one thing I regret the most
while she was alive
I didn't call her motherfucker
I am sorry
Zijin
Your Highness didn't ask me
Why enter the palace
Although Xu is not my biological mother
But she pity my mother
treat me like my own
she is seriously ill
still holding a breath
Want to see me marry beautifully
But in the end
Finally got the news
Your Highness
just because of this marriage
I lost the most important person in the world
So I have to enter the palace
I have to see for myself
How good is the woman who replaced me
I would like to ask your Highness in person
where am i going wrong
you're not wrong
it's not your fault
I promise
from now on
No one will dare to hurt you again
I promise
princess
His Royal Highness he
Please don't worry, princess
His Highness was going to punish Hu Shangshi severely.
But Miss Yao said
Acquaintance after all
beg your highness for mercy
His Highness has ordered Hu Shangshi to go back and meditate on his past.
But if you repeat
next time
princess
His Highness ordered the servants to take you back to the palace
go out and guard
Yes
The elder sister is careless
Annoyed His Highness
now you are satisfied
I've never nurtured someone so carefully
Kill her now
for whom
you still don't know how to repent
Even if she really had a marriage contract with His Royal Highness
But now times have changed
Am I so narrow-minded
There are many beauties in the harem
Can't you leave her alone?
why are you laughing
i'm asking you
why not answer
Emperor Taizu to avoid interference in the harem
foreign relatives
ancestral teachings
After Prince Fan
concubines
A woman from a good family in the electorate
These women who were elected to the palace
no family reliance
the only one you can rely on
love with the king
Emperor Taizu's Empress Xiaocima
The late emperor benevolence and filial piety
All of them accompanied their husbands to go to war
made an indelible contribution
in the heart of the king
Even if the world is stunning
Not as good as marrying a wife
Emotions
princess
Now I ask you something
How is your relationship with the prince?
Surrounded by beauty around the prince
but never despised my wife
he's not like that
wife
do not forget
you are in grief
Almost accidentally hurt the prince
What kind of relationship is there between husband and wife?
think about it
Know Sun's misfortune and sacrifice
The prince will surely give birth to infinite guilt and pity
The only thing you should be thankful for is that you took the lead
early name
Otherwise, the Sun will appear
Where is your place to stand?
stop talking
Changes in this harem
Even if there is merit, it may not be safe
Queen Zhang now
Accompanying husband all the way
From the Prince of Yan to the Emperor
Saved him many times in distress
But now in this harem
One more Guo
Founding Heroes
Young and beautiful and won the Sacred Heart
also gave birth to three princes
When His Majesty ascends the throne, he is promoted to the imperial concubine
What kind of person is Queen Zhang
No, it’s not about forbearance and concessions everywhere.
How are you better than Queen Zhang?
The princess should wake up
You were ordered to monitor the East Palace
But only record my daily good deeds
Aren't you afraid that the emperor will blame you?
apprehensive
When His Majesty was in the East Palace
good people say
Your Royal Highness is slanderous
Your Majesty Cloud
I don't know
Know as child
Knowing that there are always people behind the scenes slandering the late emperor
Divorce the royal family's father and son
Your Majesty is gracious
Only read the duty of filial piety for the son of man
minister
Naturally, only do the duty of a courtier
then you are
Is it allegiance to the emperor?
still loyal to me
His Majesty
Emperor Xiandi's Five Northern Expeditions
Entrust the country as much as possible
You sympathize with the Kuan Ren Yu of the Republic of China
Who does not admire the civil and military affairs of the Manchu Dynasty
How can the minister allow the villain to be framed
to the collapse of the country
As a Jinyiwei
perform the duty of supervision
recorded and heard
all heard
If a word is not true
willing to be punished
Almost wronged the loyal minister
get up
Yes
Wang Jie resigned due to illness
I order you
The commander of the collared guard
Don't betray my trust in you
subject to orders
Chen Ding's liver and brain paint the ground
live up to grace
His Majesty
time to eat
go
Yes
Miss Yao refuses to accept it
she says
This phoenix doesn't belong to her at all
from now on
East Palace meal
It's up to you
Hu Shangshi
The Prince and the Prince's Meal
named before
Zijin
Siyi begged me for a long time
I just promised to let you go
you gotta do a good job
don't lose my reputation
Yes
Si Yi Si usually manages some
Little things
Why tune in the past
Who is going to transfer to Siji?
Holy oracle
from now on
Meng Shangshi returns to Shangshi Bureau
still in office
I adult
so
Food Bureau
There are two master chefs
Food Bureau under the jurisdiction of the Secretary
Si Yun Si Pharmacy Si Si Si
heavy responsibility
Since the time of Emperor Taizu
Convenience and food for two
now
It's just following the old example
what's wrong
Congratulations to Meng Shangshi
Hershey Mengshang Food
I adult
I admire Yao Zijin's cooking skills
I want to keep her in the restaurant
what do you think
Meng Shang food is both
Head of the Food Bureau
All staff are under your control
All right
You are all busy
Yes
Great
Zijin
There is Meng Shangshi in charge
We will be more at ease
I adult
you were
promised me
let me run the food bureau
Mengshi domineering
Su Ri doesn't even care about me
how can i help her
This time the holy edict
I'm just doing my job
The person who even the empress hates
how to meet your majesty
Is it Concubine Guo
This officer doesn't know
I adult
you want to stay out
I'm afraid it's not that easy
Since I took charge of the Food Bureau
Lots of current accounts
If Meng clan regained power
Once checked
Inevitably adults will also be involved
you threaten me
dare not
Do it yourself
I already told you
Jingquan is insatiable
You shouldn't get too close to him
At first, I was just in charge of the food bureau.
If you don't give him some benefits
how can
Promoted to Shangshi so quickly
meals to enter the population
Not to be missed
as a cook
for selfishness
indulge others
What qualifications do you have to make meals?
A Wai
you weren't like this
I remember you said
contestable
but you will not forget
The bottom line of being a man
the you now
remember you before
did you say
bottom line
One only needs to take the first step
cross the line
that's sooner or later
But don't worry
If something happened
I'm the only one responsible
won't involve you
This is the period of filial piety
poor meal
Your Highness, please forgive me
Grandpa has always been
against red tape
snort
but
if he knew
The father is now serving vegetables and tofu all day long
I'm afraid it's fun too.
don't speak
it seems
you really hate me
If there is anyone in the world
rule my destiny
cause me a lifetime of pain
i will kill
Your Highness is serious
slaves dare not
do not dare
still don't hate
Even with the ability to reach the sky
there's no way your mother
come back to life
So
can i do anything for you
Your Highness
over time
I have no regrets
I think
woman hired by the royal family
impossible to remarry
become a monk
or die
I have no complaints
I tell you
impossible
i won't let you go
I don't care if you are Yao Zijin
Whatever the Sun family
I will never let you go again
Yuan Qi
Your Highness
take the inkstone away
Yes
stop it
I will not eat
You keep saying that you don't dare
do not complain
all excuses
how
you're getting so timid now
I can't even say the truth
Yes
what
all lies
I hate His Royal Highness hate the palace
I hate what brings me bad luck
everyone
Your Highness
I hate you
If His Highness does not kill the head
The slaves left
Inkstone
I am sorry
i scared you
eat more
so angry
alright, alright
What a coincidence, Miss Yao
meet again
Still in the period of filial piety
Your Majesty is vegetarian
You beast must be punished
This is the prince's inkstone
How can adults be punished at will
The emperor is keeping filial piety
How can the prince be an exception
Give me
You adult
Birds fly long sky fish swim shallow bottom
These are common sense
Why don't you go to Shanglin Garden?
Forcing tigers and leopards to eat fast too
Help Concubine Zhuang achieve her wish
By the hands of the crown prince
Go through the difficulties smoothly
what a good way
just thinking about it
Conquering the Heart of the East Palace
But when the victory
admit everything
self-destructing the Great Wall
Did you know that you do this
equal to the prince
Pushed back to Hu's side
Sir, even the East Palace is under surveillance
Who gave the courage
emperor
I'm not surveillance
I want to be promoted
Of course to please the prince
I don't know how he does it
The old man's secret
more than me
So two people full of secrets
Can we cooperate?
adult kidding
Jin Yiwei's life
I can't do it
Your enemy is not easy to deal with
I'm afraid you haven't stood firm yet
lost his life
think carefully
I am waiting for your reply
I only laugh when I want to cry
so stupid