Previously,
on "Superman & Lois"...
Your mom wanted us
to move to Smallville.
- This family needs Smallville.
- I think I did this to him.
The bonfire... I think my heat
vision caused an explosion
and infected him somehow.
Where's Tag now?
He's with the doctors
at the DOD.
So what exactly brings
a Reuters tech reporter
- to Smallville, Kansas?
- Just want to be on Team Lois.
I think I may have found a way
to get a look inside the mines.
I don't think it was Derek.
His powers were erratic,
like Tag Harris.
Well, whatever Edge
and Leslie are doing
with that machine,
it has something
to do
with the mines.
We now own the rights
to this land,
which holds enough X-Kryptonite
to resurrect an army.
[dramatic music]
- Tag.
- What did you do to me?
Try and outrun me?
Not anymore.
Tag, I don't know what...
[high-pitched ringing]
[groans]
[echoing]
I want the truth, Kent.
At the bonfire party,
when you broke my arm,
what did you do to me?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Liar!
Ever since that night,
I have been different.
I can move so fast.
And I saw Teague's video.
Something caused
that explosion.
You were right there.
And I know
you're different, too.
You better tell me
how to fix it.
- Superman.
- I'm not gonna hurt you.
Wait!
- Are you okay? Are you okay?
- Yeah.
[train horn blows]
Tag, don't!
He got you pretty good, kid.
[groans] It's all right.
Yeah, I thought you had,
like, super durability
or whatever.
I don't know what I have.
I tried to fight back,
but he was stronger and faster.
My head is pounding.
Your abilities are evolving.
You can heal faster,
but you can still get hurt.
What did... what did Tag
want, anyways?
Answers.
He wanted to know
how he got powers,
why he's at the DOD...
He thinks I did this to him.
- Why would he think that?
- Because he saw the video
of the explosion
I caused at the mines.
I know. Look, he doesn't know
everything,
but he know something's up.
What if he says something? I mean...
Guys, can you just give me
and your mom a second
to talk about this, please?
[dramatic music]
[♪]
- I hate the Internet.
- [chuckles]
Your dad called.
Assured me that he's on this.
Apparently Tag escaped the DOD
by some fluke.
His abilities accelerated.
They didn't know
what he was capable of.
And now they're putting
together some plan to track him
and get him back in custody.
And if he gets
to Jordan first?
I'll keep an eye out.
This wouldn't be happening
if it wasn't for Morgan Edge.
Whatever gave Tag those powers
came from those mines,
and now he wants
to extract more of it
and make more Derek Powells.
- What if you went there?
- I flew over the mines.
I scanned the tunnels.
I can't see inside.
They've lined them
with lead fiber.
So I need to investigate.
Find proof of wrongdoing,
hand it over
to the authorities,
and get a proper warrant.
Slow down, okay?
I can find out...
No, I want you focused
on the boys
until Tag is back in custody.
In the meantime, I got to break
this case open.
Think about it... Edge is giving
people Kryptonian powers.
And all of this
at the same time
some armored lunatic arrives
who knows Superman's real name?
You think Morgan Edge
is the Stranger?
Maybe. I don't know.
I'm gonna find out.
Dude, Jimmy Cutter's
literally been talking
smack about the game all week.
That guy's such a dick.
Hey. Hey. Language.
[high-pitched ringing]
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. It's just a headache.
- Hmm.
Jordan, how would you feel
about sitting out
tomorrow's game?
Why?
Well, for one,
you might still be affected
by what happened with Tag.
Well, what does that have
to do with football?
Yeah, Dad, I mean, look,
it's Metropolis, okay?
This is literally
the biggest game of the season.
It's our old school.
I mean...
Yeah, I know. I get that,
but until we have this
under control,
we've got to be careful.
Dad, I have to play
in this game.
It's really important to me.
Please?
You promise
you're 100% healthy?
- Yeah.
- Totally good to go?
- Totally good to go.
- Okay. All right.
Then after school,
you're gonna prove it.
This is proof my suspicions
were correct.
Smallville is the community
that's going to help me
change the world.
So, without further ado,
I'll hand over
to my wonderful staff,
who can assist in getting you
all back to work.
- Yeah.
- Thank you very much.
Yeah.
[chuckles]
Oh, Mr. Edge,
this is gonna put a lot
of people back on their feet.
I cannot thank you enough.
No, no, I'm the one
who should be thanking you.
All this is possible
because of your advocacy,
persuading people
to give me a shot.
In fact, I'd like
to capitalize on our momentum.
Hey, whatever you need,
you say the word.
Well, the Smallville team
needs a strong leader.
And I'd like to fill
that role with you, Lana.
- With me?
- The work you did at the bank
with reverse mortgages
shows me you're not
just highly competent.
You also have
the people's trust.
And I want to use that trust
to revitalize Smallville,
starting with
the community center.
- Yeah.
- I'm grateful.
[chuckles]
I-I don't know what to say.
Well, when you see
your new starting salary,
- you'll say yes.
- [chuckles]
[dramatic music]
[♪]
- Should I deal with her?
- Why bother?
What can she do?
[indistinct chatter]
Figured out how to get
in there yet?
Doing about as well
as you, Marcus.
May the best reporter in.
Uh, he's just worried
about you man.
You need to cut Dad
a little slack.
I know he's just
looking out for me,
but he thinks I'm made
of glass.
This is my shot to finally show
those Metropolis d-bags
who's boss.
Come on.
I'm not gonna sit that out.
I get that.
But I'm just saying... what?
You don't have to
slam it every time.
Dude, I didn't even
slam it at all.
Oh, hey, guys.
Oh, my God,
what happened to your face?
Um...
Did you get beat up
on your way home or something?
We were running plays this
morning in the front yard,
and then I juked him,
and he tripped and fell.
Well, I hope you do better
tomorrow at the game,
'cause I'd hate to go
all the way to Metropolis
just to see you eat it.
- You're coming?
- Uh, yeah.
Friends can root
for friends, right?
I think I'm starting to see
why you're so hyped
for this game, huh?
- [school bell ringing]
- [groans]
What?
Hey, hey, hey, Jordan, Jordan.
[echoing] What's going on?
Hey. Hey.
[continues indistinctly]
Jordan. Jordan.
Look at me, look at me.
Just breathe. Just breathe.
Please, just breathe.
[breathing heavily]
Hey. Hey.
What the hell was that?
Okay, that is not...
That is not a panic attack.
It's my head.
Since Tag jumped me,
I've been hearing this
really loud high-pitched noise.
Jordan, if this has to do
with your superpowers,
then you need to tell Dad.
You might need to go
to the fortress
to figure out what's wrong.
- We can't tell Dad, all right?
- Jordan, you need to tell him.
Look, if we tell Dad,
he won't let me play football
tomorrow.
- Jordan.
- Jon, let me have this.
Those Metropolis guys... Woodrum,
Cutter, Campana...
They've made my life hell.
Just let me shut them up,
just this once.
All right, bye.
It's Bill Hastings.
He starts work next week.
Hadn't heard him this excited
since Junior was born.
You're changing lives, babe.
Yeah.
Hey. You okay?
It's silly, but I don't know,
I just... I thought
that Edge might have
had something for me, you know?
Some managerial work
or something like that.
But do you really want that?
I mean,
you love being a fireman,
and if I'm getting
this promotion,
isn't
that a win for both of us?
[doorbell rings]
I'll be right back, baby.
[door opens]
Lois. Let me go grab Lana.
Actually, Kyle, I was hoping
that I could talk to you, too.
Come on in.
This may sound bizarre,
but I have reason to believe
that Morgan Edge is engaged
in both illegal
and dangerous activity,
and I'm asking for your help
to get into the mines
so that I can prove it.
So let me get this straight.
Even though Edge just gave Lana
this massive promotion,
you want us
to go behind his back
and help you with a news story.
- I know it's a big ask.
- It's pretty big, yeah.
Listen, I'm not alone
in my suspicions.
You both know
that I know Superman.
He's looking into Edge, too.
- Superman? What for?
- I can't tell you that yet.
Of course you can't.
But does Clark know
about this?
He doesn't know I'm here, no.
I'm just trying to explain...
Explain what?
You've got no proof.
You got no evidence.
Kyle, I would tell you
if I could.
I am asking you to trust me.
Oh, okay, you want me
to trust you?
You know what I should do
is, I should call Edge
and we should get
a restraining order.
Okay, Kyle, please.
Listen, I just got off
the phone with a buddy of mine
who hadn't worked
in eight months.
He's got mouths to feed, Lois.
And right now
Edge is the only person
that's giving his family
a chance to survive.
I know it seems like
he's helping,
- but he has...
- No, he is helping...
a lot more than you are.
I came to you guys
because you're my friends
and I need help.
I know I maybe be biased,
but you don't know
what it's like
to see this town dry up.
The things I've see...
Foreclosing on people...
This is our chance to help.
I'm sorry, Lois.
Lana, you know
that I respect you.
So I am telling you, something
sinister is going on here.
And you might not find out
what it is until it's too late.
So just be careful.
[dramatic music]
[♪]
[sighs]
- So why are we down here?
- Training.
This is stuff your grandfather
used to teach me
how to control my strength.
Now it's my turn
to give you a few pointers.
Why, so he can, like, protect
himself from Tag or something?
Well, there's that,
and given your raw power,
we want to make sure
you can control it.
Yeah, I mean, a random super
freak-out would really suck.
- Yeah.
- Anyway...
let's start with this.
Am I somehow supposed
to crack this in half?
Nope. Just punch it.
Don't I need gloves
or something?
You trust me?
[mutters]
Ouch.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Yep. Yep. Okay.
No, I thought we'd try
going on instinct,
but obviously that was
the wrong approach.
Um, right foot back.
Put your hand up like a fist.
Curl your thumb. Bring it back.
Transfer the weight.
Follow through.
Okay.
Jordan...
imagine... imagine this big log
is Cutter's face.
He's just laughing at you.
Pop him. You got it.
Come on, believe you can do
this, and you will.
You're stronger than
you think you are.
- You got it.
- Now.
Yes! Yes!
Yo, that's what
I'm talking about!
- Yes, sir. Oh, my God.
- See? Line it up again.
- Line it up again.
- Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
- [cell phone rings]
- Hold on. Hold on. Wait. Wait.
- Hang on, hang on.
- Okay.
Hey, Sam.
Harris was spotted
in Metropolis.
In Metropolis?
Are you sure?
He's fast, hard to track.
Why?
Something I need to know about?
Uh, that's where the boys'
football game is tomorrow.
You stay with the boys.
I'll have my guys on site.
We have a plan to put this
monster back in his cage.
He's not a monster, Sam.
He's a kid.
Nobody's helping him.
He's scared.
Helping?
He attacked my grandson.
No, I underestimated him once.
He broke out
of a state-of-the-art facility.
His speed rivals yours.
No telling what damage
he can do.
I don't have time to worry
about feelings.
I need to incapacitate
a threat.
That's what I'm gonna do.
[line clicks]
Getting a sitter?
I'm trying.
But nobody we know
is available for tomorrow.
What's tomorrow?
Your dad's
taking me to dinner.
We're celebrating
my new promotion.
[scoffs]
Wow.
Dad finally got over
himself long enough to think,
"Maybe I should
congratulate my wife."
Were you listening
to our conversation?
It's not that big of a house.
Sarah...
your dad... he's trying.
[sighs]
I can watch Sophie.
- But what about the game?
- There's other games.
- Sarah.
- Mom.
Your new job, it's kind of,
like, a really big deal,
and you absolutely deserve
to go and celebrate.
I guess.
I guess it's a big deal.
Yeah. You work really hard.
And you give back
to the community.
So you do deserve
all the karma you're getting.
Mm.
Who knows? Maybe... maybe this
is just the start.
[sinister music]
[♪]
Come on, now!
We are now
in the second quarter
of a surprisingly close game.
There's no show in showtime
if we don't show up!
- Hey. You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, short stack, you see
that linebacker, 55. out there?
He's been killing us all day.
Now, look,
I want you to go in there
and you knock him
on his backside, you got that?
Let's go. Let's go!
[crowd cheering]
Gonna stick your ass, Jo-Jo.
Just like grade school.
[whistle blows]
- [groans]
- [high-pitched ringing]
Here we go.
Keep them out!
Come on, now! Jeez!
Oh! Looks like the Crows'
quarterback is hurt.
Timmy's got
a sprained elbow.
Tried telling Jordan
it's not really his fault.
- [chuckles]
- Yeah, I'm sure that helped.
What about our other problem?
Any sign of our friend Tag?
No. There's a pretty big
DOD presence.
Guess I should thank
your dad for that.
Well, the sooner
we find that kid,
the sooner this
will all be over.
Yeah.
It's the how that worries me.
Clark, with everything
that's going on,
are you sure Jordan's okay?
I don't know.
Something's going on,
but he won't talk to me.
Keep an eye on him,
on both of them.
This can't be easy for them,
playing their old school
and seeing
all the kids they knew.
Yeah.
- [whistle blows]
- Hut!
Come on!
We got to do our job!
Pick it up now!
Let's go!
Focus!
Coach.
We need to throw that ball.
I don't got
a quarterback, Kent.
You do, Coach.
You got me.
I mean, I know our plays.
I know their defense.
I got this, okay?
All right, Kent.
Strong right slot,
Z panther, on three.
- Got it.
- Let's go!
Go get them, 12.
What a game
this has been so far.
There is no love lost
between these two teams.
Whoo-hoo. Big boy Kent.
Hey, you know I'm with your
girl Eliza now, right?
She wanted you to know.
Blue 72. Hike!
Ball, ball, ball!
- Touchdown, Smallville.
- Yeah! Attaboy!
You like that, Cutter?
Hey. Jordan.
Get over here.
- Rein it in, or you're done.
- Just making a block.
That's not what I'm talking
about, and you know it.
You understand me?
- Yeah.
- Good. Go sit down.
Hell, use me
as your unnamed source.
All I need is a press pass
from the "Post."
[knock at door]
I'll call you back.
No, I'm not mad.
Just find me a pass.
[dramatic music]
[♪]
[knock at door]
Who is it?
Your new best friend.
What are you
doing here, Marcus?
Still open to sharing
a byline?
Friend of mine got hands
on a couple inspector badges.
One's for you, if you want it.
You somehow get not one
but two inspector badges
and you're just gonna give me
one of them to be nice?
They're working around the
clock to get those mines ready.
Right now the tunnels
are packed with inspectors.
Security is stretched thin.
A lone Black guy
might look suspicious,
but the two of us together,
it'll seem more legit.
So...
are you in...
or out?
Are you kidding me?
This is your idea
of a disguise?
- It's kind of a clown show.
- Let me do the talking, okay?
You just try
to look inspector-y.
- Inspector-y.
- Mine Safety.
That team checked
in hours ago.
Had to grab more equipment.
Dude, between you and me,
Sullivan is an idiot.
[both laugh]
He can't plan a survey.
- All right, go ahead.
- All right, cool. Thanks, man.
[chuckles]
You want to watch a classic?
There's "Wizard of Oz."
But I like animation.
We can get a new one
on streaming.
No, I'm not gonna buy...
Look, Soph,
I'm fine with the whole, like,
Saturday sister bonding time.
Kind of embrace it.
But, dude, seriously,
we're gonna have to find
something
we both want to watch.
Please?
- [doorbell rings]
- Okay, that's the pizza guy.
Get up.
Okay, go get your stuffies
and your blankets,
and then you can pick
whatever movie you want.
Just...
I'll be back after I'm done
emotionally preparing.
Love you, too.
- Love you.
- Little brat.
[sighs]
- Tag.
- Hey, Sarah.
Thought you went to go live
with your dad.
Are you back in town?
The truth is complicated.
And you've always been
my friend.
You stick up for people when
you know something isn't fair.
No!
Sarah. Sarah.
The Crows lead 35-13
in the fourth quarter,
with only seconds left
on the clock.
Nobody saw this coming, least
of all the Metropolis players.
They look absolutely stunned.
Blue, 72. Hut. Hut. Hike!
- Go! Go!
- Whoo!
Touchdown, Crows!
Yeah! Attaboy!
The Crows win.
What an upset!
[groaning]
Looks like a fight
has broken out midfield.
I don't think
I've ever seen
- anything like this!
- Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa.
Get off him!
Hey. Hey. Jordan, you okay?
I can't hold it in.
- Let it out.
- Let it out right now.
[screaming]
I had a really
good time tonight.
Well, good,
'cause that dinner
wasn't cheap.
[both chuckle]
Listen, um...
we didn't talk about logistics,
with my new hours,
how that might affect the kids
or how you feel about it.
Whatever we got to do,
we're gonna do, okay?
- I know. But...
- No. There's no buts.
Yeah, maybe I'm a little
disappointed, but it's fine.
You saw Morgan Edge
as an opportunity
before anybody.
Of course you should be
rewarded for that.
He's an idiot
if he can't see that.
Whoa, whoa, he is not
an idiot, okay?
He promoted you,
after all, right?
[chuckles]
Listen, babe, you got to know
I'm real proud of you.
I mean, you are the brains
of this family, after all.
We all know that.
[chuckles]
You deserve to be happy.
- I'm happy.
- Well, good.
Then whatever comes next,
I think we will handle it...
- Mm-hmm.
- Together.
Did you get me desert?
Oh, sweets,
it's way past your bedtime.
- Where is your sister?
- I think she's in her room.
Yeah. Go check.
Come here.
[suspenseful music]
[♪]
No.
It's not like Sarah
to just leave.
I'm gonna check
the security cam footage.
For the hundredth time,
I'm fine.
No, you're not.
You just detonated like a bomb
in the middle of a high-school
football game
in front of a crowd
full of people.
I could have controlled it,
all right?
I just let it go
'cause you were there.
Yeah, but what if I wasn't?
Jordan, sit up and look at me.
Do you understand
how dangerous this could be?
Tell me exactly what happened.
Were there... were there
any symptoms, any signs,
something that would have made
you think that this was coming?
Look, Dad, you're thinking
about this too much.
I just... I had a moment,
all right?
- Jordan...
- that's not 100% true.
- Jon.
- What?
Jordan, he needs to know.
Look, the first time that he
had one of these episodes
or whatever,
I mean, it stopped.
It seemed fine.
- The first time?
- I had a migraine at school.
- It wasn't a big deal.
- And you didn't tell me?
I didn't tell you
'cause I knew you'd overreact.
I knew you'd stop me
from playing the game.
- Yeah!
- And I would have been right!
So I'm just supposed
to be punished
for something
that isn't my fault?
This was my shot, Dad.
This was my chance to show the
d-bags at Metropolis who I am.
You remember
how they treated me, right?
Jordan, I know. I know.
And I get it, okay?
I know what it's like
to be picked on.
Yeah, but you get to grow up,
and you get to be Superman.
Who am I?
I'm a weird kid with headaches.
I just... I wanted to be good
at something... that was all.
That's not what
your powers are for. Jordan...
Dad, I'm not you, okay?
[sighs]
[cell phone ringing]
Hey, Lana, sorry.
Can I... can I call you back?
Clark, real quick...
Did Sarah come to the game?
- Uh... no, I didn't see her.
- Why? Is everything okay?
Well, she was supposed
to be here with Sophie,
and she's not.
I knew she'd canceled plans
about coming to the game.
I just thought...
- Is that that Harris kid?
- Oh, my God, yeah it is.
Clark, I got to go.
[line clicks]
- What was that?
- Stay here.
- Everything okay?
You sure about this?
No point playing it cautious
now, right?
And you know
what to look for?
Yeah. Got my hands
on some schematics.
What we want is just up ahead.
And how, may I ask, did you
manage to just take a peak
at Edge EnerCorp's
top secret schematics?
Uh, friend of mine helped out
with some surgically
precise hacking.
Well, points to you
and your friend.
And the grand prize is...
- Should be right here.
- Yeah.
You came prepared.
[distant siren wailing]
Tag, what the hell?
Where are we?
It's okay.
We're in Metropolis.
How are we in Metropolis?
That's the thing, Sarah.
I can move pretty fast now.
[mysterious music]
[♪]
So a high-tech gadget guy
works for LuthorCorps,
the top tech company
in the world,
only to quit and pursue
a career in journalism.
Did I get that right?
Feels like I should be focusing
my story on you.
No, the, uh...
story...
is on what's in these walls.
What is that?
X-K, otherwise known
as X-Kryptonite.
X-Kryptonite?
Rarest form of Kryptonite.
And if my hunch is right,
these mines have the largest
supply of it anywhere.
There's your story, Miss Lane.
Too bad no one's
gonna read it.
[suspenseful music]
Still scanning Metropolis,
General.
Find this kid now.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
Nothing about Dad
on the news.
Can't find anything
on the Internet either.
Jordan you're n... you're not,
like, mad at me, are you?
Nah.
I'm just a little tired
of being told what to do.
That's all.
- [scoffs] Yeah.
- [person cheering]
[pounding on door]
- Come on, man, open up.
- Oh, it's the boys.
Ha! What's good, Mike?
What's good? What's good?
How you feeling, rock star?
Better?
I'm all right.
Yeah. Yeah.
- Good. Let's go.
- Going where?
To pay some millennial
to get us a few sixers
so we can celebrate properly.
That'd be... that'd be
tight, guys.
But, honestly, my pops said
we got to stay here, so...
- Oh, come on!
- He did.
All right.
It's not like
we're going clubbing.
Liquor store's
just up the street.
You know what?
We won a big game.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on.
All: Yeah!
- Whoo!
- You coming?
Yeah. All right.
What are you doing?
Get ready to run.
[suspenseful music]
[♪]
Come on.
[indistinct chatter]
Narrowing in
on his power signature.
Be ready to move.
I'm sorry about your head.
It's because of my power.
- It's hard to control.
- Tag, slow down.
I think it was caught
on camera.
All I want is to just show you.
See that flare?
It's coming from Jordan.
I think he did...
something.
That's what made me this way.
It's crazy, Sarah,
but it's true.
I had to tell someone I trust,
you know?
Plus, you know him...
and I wondered
if he told you something.
Maybe you can help me.
I don't know anything.
Don't run.
I'm here to help you.
Out there, boy. You got it.
You got. You got it.
- Oh! Hands like feet.
- There they are...
the Crows.
Hey, you look pretty good,
Jo-Jo,
for a guy
who was dragged off the field.
Yo, Cutter.
Seriously, man, come on.
Step off.
[scoffs] Oh, are you sore
about Eliza, Kent?
Look, I know we used
to be friends,
but I guess that's
over now, huh?
So what?
You came here to talk
about how it feels to lose?
Wow.
Look who found his voice.
Dorky kid since forever.
Cried if he was breathed on.
[exhales sharply]
What, now you're, like, the
best guy on the football team?
You, uh, juicing
or something there, Jo-Jo?
Is that what's going on?
You juicing Jo-Jo, huh?
Approaching
loading dock, sir.
Suspect is dangerous.
Use whatever means necessary.
I need you both
to come with me.
No. No way.
You took me to that place.
- I was only trying to help.
- They didn't help me.
Tag!
I give you my word...
I will make sure
that you are safe
and that you get
the answers that you want.
But right now
we need to leave.
The DOD is coming for you.
I need you to trust me.
On the ground now.
Do not move!
Bishop Six, stand down.
Oh, look at those eyes, man.
- Tell me the truth, Jo-Jo.
- Cutter.
- Let him shut me up.
- Right here, baby.
Cutter.
Jordan, Jordan, Jordan.
Breathe. Relax. Relax.
- On the ground now!
- We will fire!
No! Don't!
- Tag, stop.
- Engage.
You can't do this.
Oh!
- Stop!
- Take him out!
[dramatic music]
[♪]
[groans]
[grunting]
[suspenseful music]
[♪]
Aah!
Stand down.
No. No.
He didn't try to hurt me.
[indistinct chatter
over radio]
Those won't be necessary.
You're not gonna be alone
anymore, okay?
I promise.
I don't know what
you're upset about.
The girl's safe
and on her way home.
The subject's back in custody.
Let's take this as a win.
His name is Tag.
I wish I had your trust
in people, I really do.
So do I.
You put me
in a bad position tonight.
You know, I thought
about all the ways
you might try
to stop that boy.
Never occurred to me you would
actually use live rounds,
let alone ones fitted
with Kryptonite.
My job is to protect
the American people
by any means necessary.
And now I know.
Dad, Jon's hurt.
Superman.
Hey. Hey!
Are we gonna talk about
what happened back there?
What's to talk about?
You saw what I saw.
That's your story.
You are armed to the teeth
with the kind of weapons
that would put you high
on the FBI's Most Wanted List.
And this security badge... I sent
a photo to a friend of mine,
and she said it's one
of the best forgeries
she has ever seen.
So why don't you tell me
who you really are
and why you are in Smallville,
'cause I don't buy
that you came to write a story.
I can't tell you why
I'm really here.
But I can promise you,
like you,
I am trying to prevent
something bad from happening.
[cell phone ringing]
Hey, babe, can I call...
- How bad?
- I'm on my way.
- Are you okay?
- To be continued.
[engine turning over]
Doctor said the cast comes
off in six to eight weeks.
- Could have been worse.
- Yeah.
And he also said that "maybe"
I get full range
of motion back, so...
- Jon, I'm so sorry.
- Just... just shut up, please.
- I... You know I never meant...
- Okay, but you did.
You... you did, Jordan.
You... you got emotional,
and then I tried to step
in the middle of it
like an idiot,
and now I have a broke-ass arm,
and I'm probably never gonna
play quarterback again.
So, thanks.
Thanks a lot.
[sighs]
I'm going to bed.
You guys know
that I would never mean to
actually hurt him.
- Jordan. Jordan.
- Right?
That has nothing
to do with it.
[door closes]
He's upset.
And he has a right to be.
I told you, your powers
come with responsibility,
and I need you to get that.
Honey, we know
it was an accident.
We know you're sorry.
Jon knows, too.
He just needs a second.
But your dad is right.
Things are different now.
Yeah, I know.
I know they're different.
Do you?
Because you made a big point
at the hotel
of saying you're different
from me.
But you're not.
That anger you felt that made
you want to use your powers
the way you did tonight,
I have those feelings, too.
- You do?
- Yes.
But I keep them in check.
Otherwise, I risk losing
the trust of the very people
I've sworn to protect.
When I first showed up
in Metropolis as Superman,
there was a lot of talk
about what the world should do
with someone
who had powers like mine.
And it took me a minute
to realize that other people
were more afraid
of what I could do than I was.
So what I had to do,
more than anything,
was earn their trust,
prove to them that,
no matter what,
I would never use my powers
to hurt them.
20 years later,
every time I use my powers,
that trust is tested,
every time.
Just today, in fact.
The thing about trust,
Jordan...
Once you break it,
it's take a lot longer
to heal than a wrist.
It's late.
Go get some sleep.
We can talk about
this more tomorrow.
[dramatic music]
[♪]
He's just confused.
He's so young.
He's not ready for this.
I know.
Neither was I, but...
Probably not the best time
to tell you
I almost got killed tonight.
- What?
- I got into the mine,
with the help of this supposed
journalist, Marcus Bridgewater,
and he led me to something
called X-Kryptonite.
- Have you ever heard of that?
- X-Kry... No. No. Wait. Back up.
What do you mean
you almost got killed?
- Leslie Larr came after us.
- Turns out she has powers, too.
She tried to heat vision us,
and then Marcus zapped her
with this,
like, high-tech ray gun.
Why? Why does a journalist
have a ray gun?
- That makes no sense.
- He's no journalist.
I need to figure out who he is
and what he has on Morgan Edge.
Sarah, are you okay?
It's just crazy.
I've known Tag my entire life,
and now he has powers
or whatever.
I was really scared.
But I knew
that he would never hurt me.
He was just
really confused, and...
he was really
focused on you.
He showed me this video
from the night of the bonfire.
He had this whole theory
that whatever happened,
whatever gave him his powers...
had something to do with you.
[zapping on phone]
I don't know
why he said that.
You know, even if...
Even if there was something,
you could tell me, right?
Yeah, of course.
Okay.
- How are you doing?
- [sighs]
I just keep thinking
about what could have happened.
Sarah told me that Tag...
has these special abilities.
He's not sure how he got them,
but clearly this has something
to do with those mines.
Lois, what aren't
you telling me?
I haven't put it
all together yet.
But, yes, it does involve Tag
and two other people,
both of whom have been linkedto Edge.
He's up to something.
I just don't know exactly what.
I could help you figure out
if, in fact,
he was up to something
dangerous or illegal.
Are you sure
you want to do that?
He is very dangerous.
Look, if it's gonna keep him
from hurting other people, yes,
I'm in.
- And Kyle's okay with this?
- No. No.
It's just best to keep this
between us for now.
Okay.
I happen to know that we have
a ton of rocky road
in the freezer,
and I can't handle it
all by myself.
You think I'm six?
No.
But I will say that I have,
as recently as this morning,
kind of wished that you were.
I don't know how to fix this.
I don't know what to do.
I hurt Jon...
bad.
I can still hear
his bones snapping.
He's my brother,
and I did that to him.
- It was an accident.
- And Tag?
That was
an accident, too, right?
It's not your fault.
Mom, I just had to look Sarah
in the eye,
and all she wanted
was the truth,
and I just had to lie
to her...
to the one friend
I even have.
You know, I-I think...
I think some stupid part of me
actually thought
that the powers would bring me
closer to people,
but all they really do
is bring me farther away.
Come here, kid.
[crying]
I just want it to end.
- I know.
- [continues crying]
[high-pitched ringing]
Jordan. Jordan.
Clark! Clark!
[Jordan grunting]
Jordan. Jordan.
[grunting]
I have to get him
to the fortress.
[dramatic music]
[♪]
Greg, move your head.