Previously on "Superman & Lois"...
Let's just focus on what
we came here for... family.
You and Jordan basically are weapons.
I'm the only one in this house
that is completely unarmed.
You don't go snooping around
some guy from another
world's murder van.
We are the extraordinary humans
in a family of super people.
- Have you seen my dad?
- _
- I can't do the performance without him.
- I can do it.
I can't keep getting my hopes up
and then just get disappointed.
Were you able to find enough Subjekts?
Yes, but there's no guarantee
they'll be receptive hosts.
That was a nasty sight.
The gas was an experimental
synthetic Kryptonite
designed to invade
your respiratory system,
weaken you from the inside.
Why is Edge here?
I mean, why Smallville?
Definitely not for the biryani.
He was in and out of Hazel
Green and Granville in weeks,
he shut down operations in
New Carthage in a few months,
and now he's here.
Gotta be for the same reason
as the other towns, right?
Mine for X-Kryptonite,
use that machine I saw
that gives people powers.
Yeah, I know that's part of it,
but Smallville's the only town
where he's sticking around,
so there has to be a reason
why Smallville is different.
He needs this place.
This is your specialty.
How do you suggest we figure out why?
We dig deeper.
We need to use every resource
at our disposal.
So as we know, he was only
in Hazel Green...
Clark's a great reporter.
Now that he's not coaching, he can help.
We get all the information
we can from Lana,
files on everyone Edge has recruited,
who they are, where they come from.
Thank you.
Pore over every single detail.
There's Emily.
And then we start back at the beginning.
All right, so we know
Emily is the newest recruit.
Connect every dot,
piece it all together,
and if we've done our job right,
the answer will present itself.
My goal has always been the same.
I want to change this world,
and I finally found the place
where I can start doing so...
here in Smallville with people like you.
Me?
Why?
I know your life hasn't been
easy the past few years.
I know the pain you're in.
The fear,
knowing you can't provide
for your family,
that burden, that stress.
With my assistance,
all those fears can go away.
I can improve your life
in every way imaginable.
I can improve you, Emily.
Will this hurt?
Not a bit.
If you'd like me to,
I can activate a new life.
A new life?
Process you'd go through
will make you feel
like a new person,
clear-minded, stronger,
capable of things
you never dreamt possible.
But I can only do that
if you're willing,
if you acknowledge
that the life you have now
is not what you want anymore.
Complete host acceptance.
_
Process isn't complete.
It'll take a few days
before you're fully in control,
but once that happens...
Life will be yours again.
Do you want to become
your best self, Emily?
I do.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Lana said Edge asked her
to find more candidates,
so until we can figure out
how to stop him,
we need to convince people to stay away.
Lois, he's offering people
jobs and money,
things they need to feel in
control of their lives again.
Boys, bus'll be here in a minute!
Clark, we have to do something,
and nobody's gonna listen to me.
They haven't since that first town hall,
but they will to you.
- Hey, which one's mine?
- Here.
Thanks.
All right, guys,
we're probably gonna have
another late night working
on this Edge case.
All right, we were gonna see
Sarah's revue tonight anyway.
You guys sure are spending
quite a bit of time together
for just being "friends".
Just trying to support her, Dad.
- Uh-huh.
- Right.
What?
She said she just wanted to be friends.
Might be more than that,
but I will leave it up to her
to tell you.
Bus is pulling up.
All right, there's leftovers
in the fridge, okay?
All right, love you guys. Bye.
All right, I gotta go meet
Lana at the Gazette.
Clark, you are Martha Kent's son.
She was helping people here
way before Edge showed up.
They will listen to you.
All right.
- Bye.
And none of these people are
acting differently at all?
I mean, the only change I see
is how happy they are.
Like, they're truly excited to be there,
to be a part of something,
to change their lives.
What is he doing with them?
Personal development, self-improvement,
trust exercises.
I really don't know the specifics.
Well, it sounds like a cult,
only Edge is power-brainwashing
free of charge.
The only other thing I can tell you
is they started these morning
"togethers" at Victoria May's.
- Togethers?
- Mm-hmm.
Camaraderie-building breakfasts.
Oh, I'm gonna be late.
Wait... Lana, maybe
you should take a break.
This is kinda starting
to get really dangerous,
and I don't want anything
to happen to you.
It's okay, Lois, really.
I mean, if I can keep Edge
from hurting just one person,
it's worth it.
Think I should head over to the diner,
go full intervention on this breakfast.
No, you stay focused
on getting what you can
on Edge's minions.
I know someone who might have
a better shot at getting through.
Okay.
Hey, boys!
Hey, come on over.
- Hey, Mr. Cushing.
- Hi.
Jordan, listen, I...
I just want to say thank you
for stepping up
and helping Sarah with
her audition the other day.
That really saved the day, man.
Yeah, uh, thanks.
Okay, you don't want to be late.
Yeah.
Hey, we'll see you later, okay?
Can't wait to see you up there tonight!
Don't ask.
He's having some kind
of personality crisis.
Really?
Yeah, he keeps telling me
how he's changed for good
and how he feels better.
Things improve for a little bit,
it's the same crap as always,
and then he crashes like
your brother's about to.
What?
I told you, stay away
from Tegan Wickhem.
Just trust me, okay?
Clark?
Emily, hi.
I heard you were back in town.
Yeah, I'm sorry I haven't seen you.
It's been crazy since we moved here.
I bet... me, too, actually,
- but for the better.
- Oh, yeah?
I heard you were working
at Edge EnerCorp.
It has changed my life.
I feel great.
I can think better, focus, you know,
problems that seemed impossible
before are like nothing now.
Really? Wow, you know what?
Actually, I would love to talk
to you about that.
Like, you're looking for work?
- Uh, well...
- Oh, it's okay.
Just talk to Lana.
She hooked me up,
got me into the program.
I'm sure she'd be happy
to help her old boyfriend.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I gotta go.
Let me know if I can be of help.
It was so good to see you, Clark.
- You, too.
- Take care.
_
Thank God you're back.
Edge just sent someone over
with a massive ad buy
for tomorrow's paper.
- For more recruits?
- Twice as many.
Whatever crazy voodoo
Edge is doing to those people,
he's kicking it into high gear.
Where are you going?
Oh, to make a scene.
- Lois.
- Where's Edge?
He's in a group meeting.
I just found out about
the ad this morning.
You don't want anything
to do with what he's offering.
Ms. Lane...
You all need to walk away right now.
Walk away.
Don't touch me.
I'm sorry, if everyone could
give Ms. Lane and I a moment.
I promise this won't take long.
I know this sounds insane because it is,
but he wants to erase everything you are
and replace it with something else.
Well, that was desperate.
I know what you're doing.
Providing good jobs
to a community in need.
You are putting
Kryptonian consciousnesses
into people's bodies.
You are taking them over
and giving them powers.
And your evidence for this is...
Derek Powell, Reno Rosetti, Leslie.
Oh, so two dead men
and my personal assistant.
I have to say, this story has
holes even by your standards.
We both know it's the truth.
In my experience,
truth is rather subjective.
Who do you think people are
more likely to believe?
A has-been slumming it
at the local paper
or the man who's giving this town
the best economy it's ever known?
These people are not puppets
to be controlled by you.
They have dreams. They have families.
No one's being forced to do
anything against their will.
Everyone's made the same offer:
the chance for a better life.
- Says so right there.
- We're not publishing this.
Then I guess word of mouth
will have to suffice.
You can't stop this, Lois.
Perhaps it's time you use
that device you have
to call in your super friend.
Perhaps it is.
Risky, though.
Need I remind you where he's from?
He may take comfort knowing
there are others here
just like him,
as John Irons prophesied.
Superman is nothing like them.
I'm excited to find out.
Hey, looks like you finally
figured out that locker.
Yeah, no, yeah, I took your advice.
You know, nothing good
ever comes from anger, so...
Hey, Tegan.
Hey, um, I was just wondering
if, like, maybe you wanted
to, like, hang out
after school sometime?
Hang out?
- Like, just the two of us?
- Yeah, I mean,
it doesn't have to be, like,
that formal or anything, just,
I don't know, grab a bite
at the diner, or...
Um...
Look, I'm sure you're
a really sweet guy and all...
Look, I just... I thought...
I don't know, I just thought,
like, we were trading looks.
Well, yeah, I mean,
you had that broken arm,
and you looked so lonely.
I was just trying to be nice.
Yeah, right.
Look, I wasn't trying to hurt
your feelings or anything...
No, no, no, no, no, no, it's, uh...
it's all good.
It's my bad.
- Cool.
- See ya later.
Whew, looks like you need
a new playbook, QB number two.
You gotta work on closing that deal
like you close your locker.
- Clark, are you here?
- In the kitchen.
We got a problem.
Morgan Edge is ramping up
that program of his.
Oh, my God, what happened?
I went to stop this bank
robbery, and I got hit.
- Did they use Kryptonite?
- No, regular bullets.
This isn't normal.
Superman doesn't bruise,
especially not from bullets.
Do you think it has something
to do with that gas
Rosetti used?
I don't know.
We're gonna have to call my dad.
Sorry about messing up the intro.
I didn't even notice. You sounded great.
Thanks.
How are you so awesome at piano?
Do you have any other little
secret talents you're
not telling me about?
Um...
nah, this is pretty much it.
Well, thank you for everything,
all the time you've put into this.
It really means a lot
having you here, so...
I want to be here.
Bless you.
I, um... I must have allergies
or something.
Jordan, I...
Jordan!
Jordan.
Something's wrong with me.
You're infected, too.
Come on.
- Here, honey.
- So what's happening?
The Kryptonite gas that
Rosetti used on me at the DOD,
it was a bio-weapon, and I think
it might be communicable.
Like, a virus?
So I'm getting Kryptonite
sickness from you?
Yeah.
Clark, it's not your fault.
You didn't even know anything
was happening until today.
You have super-healing,
so how long are you sick for?
Your dad has never been sick
a day in his life.
Well, I'm not that bad.
Ow.
This wasn't supposed to happen.
Really?
Because it sure seems like a weapon
designed to hurt Superman
would hurt Superman.
It was only meant as a last resort,
just to weaken him temporarily.
Then why is my son sick?
Explain that to me.
You put your own grandson in harm's way.
Sam, how do we fix this?
My guys are working on it.
- Yo, Sarah.
- Hi.
Hey, are there gonna
be, like, refreshments
at this thing, or what?
Have you seen Jordan?
No, he's probably
just, like, putting on
his best black tee for the show.
- You know how it goes.
- No, I don't,
because he left about an hour ago,
and he hasn't come back.
Did he tell you where he was going?
No, he just ran out of rehearsal
like a frightened little rabbit, I...
We were really having
a nice time together,
or at least I thought we were
until he completely ghosted me.
Sarah, I don't think it's about you.
I'll find him.
Okay, well, hurry up because
I think I'm the first one up.
All right.
Emily.
Emily, hey.
I've been meaning to ask you,
how's it going with the program?
Mr. Edge is a genius.
You know, that he somehow
figured out a process
to completely transform people's lives,
it's amazing.
What process?
I'm sorry, I assumed you'd
already gone through it.
No, I haven't.
What did he do to you exactly?
Mr. Edge was very clear
we not tell anyone.
Emily, we've known each other
since the fifth grade.
You can trust me.
Lana, do you have a moment?
I'll see you later.
It seems
you've been looking into things
that don't concern you.
You put me in charge of the
Young Executive Program.
I should at least know
what it's really about.
And is this to satisfy
your own curiosity
or so that you can run
and tell Lois Lane?
- I never told her anything.
- It's okay.
As evidenced by today's spectacle,
Miss Lane is desperate.
In fact, I'd have been more surprised
if she hadn't tried
to scare you into helping.
Emily told me about a process
she went under.
What is she talking about?
An offer I made her,
the same one I'm about
to make right now to you,
and make no mistake.
The answer you give will
impact the rest of your life.
- Jordan, where are you?
- Upstairs.
Wow, it's like Iditarod-level
cold in here.
Your brother's sick.
Does that have something to
do with you flaking on Sarah?
- I gotta get back there, I...
- You're not going anywhere.
Sarah's going on any minute,
and I can't just abandon her.
- She'll be okay.
- No, she won't.
This is exactly what her dad did.
I can't let that happen again.
I know you want to be there for her,
but you cannot go anywhere
until we know exactly what is going on.
Wait, w... wait, we don't even
know what's going on with him?
The Kryptonite that
infected your brother
is affecting him differently than me.
Your grandfather's working
with the doctors
to figure out a way to help him.
Jonathan, he's gonna be fine.
Dad, that does not seem fine.
It's getting harder to breathe.
- What is happening to him?
- We can't wait for your dad.
Let me call you back.
Why's Clark leaving?
To do what you can't.
Lois, that gas Rosetti used
on Clark was synthetic,
experimental, hadn't been tested.
We didn't know what
his reaction would be.
All my life, your job was
your number one priority.
Accepting that wasn't easy,
but I learned to live with it,
and somehow even grew
to respect it because I
believed that you were trying
to do the right thing,
and I honestly naively thought
that once I had a family,
you might change,
start putting us first,
but I was wrong.
Knowingly and willingly
endangering the lives
of the people I love...
I can't forgive that.
So when this is over,
I want you to leave
and never come back.
You're not welcome here anymore.
Jordan's been infected with Kryptonite.
It's affecting his breathing.
He's in respiratory distress.
Why?
The Kryptonite is causing
his lungs to fill with fluid.
As he can condense
large quantities of air...
He's cooling it, like I do.
Can you get the Kryptonite out of him?
Likely, but only the same way we have
with you in the past.
- What?
- Come here.
Come here.
We're gonna have to burn the
Kryptonite out of your system.
Burn it how?
With heat, with some immense heat.
- No, no...
- Listen to me, listen to me.
Listen to me. This is
the only way, okay?
We have to do this,
otherwise your lungs
could completely freeze.
- Dad, I'm scared.
- I'm gonna be right here.
You're gonna take my hand, okay?
You're gonna squeeze as hard
as you need to, okay?
You can do this.
Mom.
Mom, you okay?
I should've protected him.
Mom, this isn't... this isn't on you.
I'm your mom.
My one job is to keep you guys safe,
and I keep failing at it.
No, no, you don't.
You were almost gunned down
in John Henry's RV...
- That was my fault.
- Got into a car accident.
That was also my fault.
I feel like I can't turn around
without one of you
being in mortal danger.
Why is it so hard to keep you safe?
I don't know.
Just...
Just part of being
a super family, I guess.
Hey, come here.
Dad'll figure something out.
He always does.
- Hey, Lana.
- Hey.
- I saved you both seats.
- Oh, thank you.
- Hi, how are you doing?
- Hey.
Good to see you.
Hello, everyone,
and thank you for coming.
Our students tonight...
How did everything go with Edge?
Oh, amazing. He explained
everything to me.
It all makes perfect sense.
- All right.
- Yeah, thank you.
- And for our first performance,
- _
we have the very talented Sarah Cushing
singing "Little Light" by Amos Lee.
Whoo!
Um...
I'm sorry, I can't do this.
Yes, you can.
It's just like being at home, okay?
♪ Some days I can't get
myself out of the box ♪
♪ And some days I can't
find keys to any locks ♪
♪ Some days I feel like
it's all overblown ♪
♪ And then I look at you,
and I don't feel so alone ♪
♪ And I say, hey ♪
♪ Let your little light shine ♪
♪ For the world to see ♪
Just waiting to hear back from my team.
Then we'll get everything
straightened out
with Jordan and your dad.
Little late for that, isn't it?
Why'd you do it?
Why'd you build those weapons
to hurt my dad?
Your father's the most powerful being
this world's ever known.
My job is to keep us safe,
which means being prepared
for any scenario,
no matter how unlikely.
You and I, we're not like your dad,
or even Jordan.
He's my twin brother.
Yes, but the minute his powers surfaced,
you and him began walking
two very different paths.
That scares you, doesn't it?
It does.
You know, I think you're wrong.
I think you're wrong about
you and I being alike.
How so?
I could never be scared of my family,
no matter what powers they might have.
Jonathan, you haven't
seen the things I have.
Yeah, you're right.
But in the end,
I don't think that would matter
'cause I'd still trust them,
and you'd still be a coward.
♪ There's a fight to be won ♪
♪ For the love you find at home ♪
- Mom.
- ♪ Words to be done for... ♪
- You were wonderful up there.
- Thank you.
It felt really good once I got going.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, told you you'd kill it.
Thank you, Dad, for helping me.
♪ Well, I know I have... ♪
♪ Please forgive if I don't walk... ♪
Emily, where are you going?
Avery's not done yet.
I'll be right back.
- That was weird.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna go see what's wrong.
Wait, Kyle...
Have you seen this?
He's still weak.
The exact reason why I just
activated some of our Subjekts.
To take down Superman?
Not him,
the one he protects.
The Kryptonite is nearly gone.
Doing great, you're almost there.
You're almost there.
That's it, that's it! It's over.
That's it, it's over. You're done.
Hey, you did it, okay? Hey.
Hey, I'm proud of you.
You all right? Come here.
I'm proud of you. Come on, stand up.
Stand up.
What do you mean, you don't
know how long it'll affect him?
No, I haven't tested the prototype.
He wasn't exactly in the mood.
Just get me an answer.
Can we just, like... like,
call them or something?
It's named the Fortress
of Solitude for a reason.
I know it sucks.
We just have to be patient, okay?
Hey, Lana.
Lois, you know how you kept asking me
if anyone over at Edge EnerCorp
was acting differently?
I just saw it for the first
time with Emily Phan.
- Emily?
- Yeah.
She left in the middle of
her daughter's performance.
She would never do that.
Avery is everything to her.
I mean, it's like she was...
She was someone else.
I'll get it.
I guess this is what Edge meant.
What do you mean?
Tonight before I left the office,
he made me an offer
to do what he's doing to everyone else.
- What?
- I turned him down.
Lana, why wouldn't you
mention this before?
'Cause I was nervous.
He knew I was feeding you information.
Hey, Mom, I think it's for you.
Lois, I'm worried.
What if he does something?
- Mom?
- Lois?
- She shouldn't have called.
- Lois.
Not this time.
Ahh!
This isn't you.
Not anymore.
Get out of here!
Keep hitting this till he comes.
- It's all we can do.
- No, no, no, no.
- We need to go to the barn.
- I'll keep 'em busy.
You took his weapons?
Kyle?
I just came from the performance.
Lana was scared. What's going on?
- Edge sent people to kill me.
- It's not gonna happen.
Stay down.
Targets first.
So that's what Kryptonite
feels like, huh?
Yeah.
Dad?
I'm sorry, Jordan.
Your life right now
is completely changed
because of who I am.
Everything that's happening to you,
you didn't ask for any of this.
I didn't,
but you didn't ask for what
happened to you either.
Here, give me the gun!
Pretty good with that thing.
We're not just gonna kill you, Lois.
He wanted you to suffer first.
They're gone.
Better than ice,
unless that was a lie
you told me when I was a kid.
Only way I could get you to do it.
We sure went through
our fair share of frozen peas,
didn't we?
God, even as a kid,
you were always coming home bruised up.
I was never there to keep you
from getting them though,
was I?
- Dad.
- It's true.
Everything you said is true.
I wasn't the best father.
I was gone a lot,
and I wasn't there to protect
you the way a parent should.
You were tonight.
Couldn't let them hurt my grandson.
Or my little girl.
Lois, we're gonna stay here
till this is over.
As of now,
you, the boys, Clark, Smallville,
that's my priority.
Good.
'Cause that war John Henry Irons
was talking about,
I think it's about to happen.
Think Mom's gonna let you
keep those solar weapons now?
I don't know.
I mean, they're pretty much the
only reason we're alive, so...
It'd suck to come home and
find out I was an only child.
Yeah.
So...
so you're just, like, fine now?
Yeah, other than ice breath.
So you have that now for good, or what?
- Think so.
- What's that feel like?
Like having a piece of wintergreen gum
in your mouth at all times.
Nice.
I can't believe what happened.
Avery Phan's mom and Mr. Cushing?
Right, but it wasn't them, you know?
They were super, super brainwashed.
I think Grandpa's sending a few people
to go look for 'em both.
What are they gonna tell Sarah?
I don't know.
_
- My God, what happened?
- Are you drunk?
- No.
- Honey, could you excuse us?
- Mom...
- Please?
I need to speak to your father alone.
Sure.
- Are you?
- No.
No, look, I told you
I am done with all that.
I'm trying to improve myself, Lana.
I really am,
but something happened to me tonight.
I was at the performance,
and we were talking to Sarah,
and then I blacked out.
Next thing you know, I'm
out in the middle of a field
somewhere outside of town,
and my ribs...
my ribs are hurting, and I
don't know how I got there.
I don't know what's going on... what?
The steps you're taking
to improve yourself...
did Morgan Edge make you an offer?
How can I help you?
I want to be my best self.
I wanted to be better
for you and for our girls, babe.
Hey, Chrissy.
You said if we kept digging,
the answer would present
itself, and honestly,
for a while I thought you were nuts
'cause nothing new was coming to light,
but then I got back all the research
on the powered people we know,
and I found this little nugget
that means something.
I just don't know what yet
but thought your big brain
might be able to connect the dots.
Chrissy, what are you talking about?
Irma Sayres and David Fuglestad.
Who?
Leslie Larr and motel attacker guy.
Leslie Larr's real name is Irma Sayres?
Mm-hmm, and the guy is David Fuglestad,
and guess what?
I found out they're both
originally from Smallville.
Derek Powell's from New Carthage.
Reno Rosetti's from Metropolis.
David Fuglestad and
Leslie Larr are from Smallville.
When Derek Powell killed himself,
what did he say to you?
- That he was already dead.
- And his powers were fritzing.
Yeah, just like Rosetti's.
That didn't happen when I fought David.
And it didn't happen with Leslie.
When I landed here,
there were meteor showers
all over the world
for an entire week.
Right, remnants of Krypton.
That's why there's Kryptonite.
Right, every form of Kryptonite,
and the kind that landed here
is buried in the mines.
Was X-Kryptonite.
So the only place in the world
that has X-Kryptonite
is also the only place that has people
who've been exposed to it long
enough to accept its effects.
Like Tag Harris.
It's not Smallville Edge needs
to build his army.
It's the people.
What?
It's your ELT.
Edge.
I'm glad you came.
Everything you're doing is gonna stop.
That's exactly what
your friend Lois Lane
keeps saying to me.
You can't make that happen
any more than she can.
Did you really think I'd
be giving people powers
without having them myself?
You see, I got mine the
same time you did, Kal-El,
when I arrived on this planet.
When you arrived?
I think it's time you learned
the truth about who I am
and where I'm really from,
brother.
Greg, move your head!
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -