- Previously on
"Superman and Lois"...
- Let's just focus on what
we came here for, family.
- I came here
with one purpose--
to further
our Kryptonian heritage.
Krypton will finally
be resurrected,
and we'll have
our mother with us.
Help me do that, brother.
- Not like this.
I have to bring back
everyone Edges implanted
with Kryptonian consciousness.
I'll release all my energy
at once.
It'll be enough.
- And you'll be out
of commission for days.
- Dad?
- Sarah.
- No, no, no!
What am I supposed to do now?
- The day has finally come.
It gives me such joy
to see you here.
- Who are you?
- I am Jor-El.
And you...
you are my son.
- What is all this?
- This--this is a place
where you can learn
away from the prying eyes
of the world
lessons about
who you really are
and why you were sent here.
- Sent here from where?
- You were born
on the planet Krypton.
Your true name is Kal,
the last son
from the house of El.
- Why am I so different?
- The Earth's sun.
Your cells
absorb its radiation
in ways humans cannot
creating
nearly endless energy.
Your skin, bones, muscles
all capable
of unimaginable power.
Over time, I will teach you
how to use that power,
that speed,
that strength.
You will learn to do things
you never thought possible
on this Earth.
♪
- Whoo!
[chuckles]
I'm ready, Father.
I can feel it.
- In body and spirit, yes,
but there is something else
you need to learn,
something which I cannot
teach you here.
- What is it?
- Why you wish to help them.
Go.
Reconnect with the world.
Open your heart to them.
Find out why you wish
to be their champion.
- Did you find
what you were looking for?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
I found out who I really am.
I met my Kryptonian father.
- Kryptonian?
- Krypton is my home planet,
Where I'm really from.
I know why I can do
the things I can do, Mom.
I know why
I was sent to Earth--
to be its champion.
- Is that why
you came back home?
To be a hero?
- Yeah, but not yet.
There's someone
I need to see first.
- Kyle's supposed to be here
any moment.
- Lana!
- Hi.
- Hey, I got some good news.
- What?
- There's an opening
at the fire station.
- [gasps]
- Yeah.
- Oh, that's amazing.
- [laughs]
- Oh, I'm so happy.
Oh, that's awesome.
- It's gonna be huge.
- Yeah.
- [chuckles]
- Let's go in.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry, Clark.
But you were gone a long time.
People move on
with their lives.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I guess so.
- Come with me.
There's something
I want to show you.
- What is this?
- After you left,
I had a dream of you flying,
only it wasn't the boy
that I knew.
It was you now, so I made this.
- Mom...
leaving you after dad died...
- Oh, honey,
it's what you needed
to do then,
and this is what
you need to do now.
It's time for you
to go save the world, Clark.
Still needs something
on the chest, I think.
- Uh, pardon me, ma'am?
Ma'am?
Do you know
where Milledge Avenue is?
Milledge Avenue.
Oh, excuse me, sir.
Excuse me.
Do you know
where Milledge Avenue is?
- The brakes are out!
I can't stop!
- It's a red light.
Swerve around!
- There are people!
- Watch out!
- Whoa!
- Did you see that?
- There you go, friend.
- Thanks.
Cool costume.
My mom made it for me.
- Oh, my God.
- Whoa!
- Did you see that?
- Yeah, right here. You'll see.
- See what?
- Some guy just saved a kid
from getting killed by a car,
and then he flew up
into the sky.
- He flew?
- Flew, you know?
Like a bird
or a plane or whatever.
It was crazy.
- Did you see
what he looked like?
- He looked like a guy
in a cape that was flying.
Someone at the "Planet"
has gotta hear about this.
♪
- This isn't a résumé.
It's a cry for help.
- Oh, well--oh, oh.
Sorry.
See, actually I did
some pretty top-notch reporting
for my school paper.
- Look, this is Metropolis.
I need cub reporters,
not lost puppies.
You come find me when you got
some real world experience.
- Oh, no, no, Mr. White,
Mr. White, please, look.
I'm a really quick learner,
and I'll do whatever you ask.
I just--I just need a chance.
- Okay,
there's no health insurance
or overtime.
- Not a problem.
- And you have to pick up
my dry cleaning every Thursday.
- Yeah, absolutely.
Yes, sir.
- Okay, kid, you're hired.
Now, try to keep up.
- Oh, okay.
Do you want--should I--okay.
Yeah, it's--
- Everyone in here, we're
the most dependable friends
the people of Metropolis have.
You remember that.
- Yes, sir.
- Stick with Lane.
She'll show you the ropes.
- Lane, sir?
- Who told you to wear a tie?
Let me guess, Lombard?
Ignore him.
Though he can get box seats
to the Meteors.
You like baseball?
- Uh, of course.
I mean, who doesn't like
America's pastime, Ms. Lane?
- It's Lois.
What'd you say
your name was again?
- Kent. Clark. Clark Kent.
Oh, oh, sorry.
- Hm, never met a Clark before.
- Oh, I've never met
a Lois before.
Actually, there was
my first-grade teacher,
Lois Hannigan,
so I guess technically--
oh, technically
you'd be the second.
You know, Miss Hannigan was
actually my favorite teacher.
She--she taught me
about fractions and cursive.
- Mystery man strikes again.
Third time this month.
- Where was he?
- Saved a boat
sinking off Hob's River.
Jimmy even got a photo.
This is my Pulitzer, Lane.
I can feel it.
- Seems like
a pretty big story.
- Yeah,
which every reporter here
is tripping over themselves
to cover.
Boys and their heroes.
- [chuckles]
Aren't heroes a good thing?
- Yeah, of course, and I know
that we need this guy.
It's just that
ever since he showed up,
he's been dominating
the conversation.
Metropolis has so many problems
that aren't just
rescue operations.
They're systemic.
Here, look at this.
- These lightning bolts.
- Nazi symbols.
They've been popping up
all over lower Metropolis
along with a rash
of arson attacks
against
minority-owned businesses.
- Do you have any idea
who's responsible?
- By all accounts, some psycho
in a metal mask
and a trench coat.
- I didn't know about this.
- That's my point exactly.
I have been covering this
for months,
only my reporting
keeps getting drowned out
by everyone's favorite
miracle man.
- How can I help?
- Psycho in a metal mask
and a trench coat?
That sounds--
sir, I'm listening to you.
- Whoo!
Yes!
- Clark, Clark,
I gotta show you something.
- Well, I gotta get these
to Perry before he goes home.
- Guess who was just arrested?
- Oh.
- You don't need that.
- Wait--oh, no, I gotta--
okay.
- One of these dirt bags
is our guy.
I can feel it.
- You're really good at this.
- Thanks.
- I, um...I should get going.
- What's the hurry.
You got a big date?
- [chuckles]
No, no, nothing like that.
Just, you know,
some "Seinfeld" reruns.
Heat up some
frozen chicken nuggets.
- You've been
a really big help, Clark.
If you want,
I can probably talk to Perry
about you getting
a beat of your own,
local politics or something.
- Oh. Um...no.
That's--it's okay.
I'd rather be here.
- For the story or the company?
- Uh...
[laughs]
I feel like
that's a trick question.
- Good night, Clark.
- Good night, Lois.
You seen Lois?
- Her contact at the library
called back
about some guy who works
at a hardware store.
- Henry Miller?
- Hmm.
- You can't do this, Henry.
They've done nothing wrong.
- They don't belong here.
- This isn't
track and field, Kent!
- These people
have stolen my neighborhood,
and you're spinning it
like I'm the bad guy?
I'm the damn hero!
- Even you can't save
all of them.
- Who's the hero now?
How'd you know about this?
- I've been reading
your reports in the "Planet,"
but also my hearing.
- Your hearing?
- Oh.
[chuckles]
My super-hearing.
- We haven't formally met.
I'm Lois Lane.
- It's nice to meet you,
Ms. Lane.
- And you are who exactly?
Mister Metropolis?
Red and Blue Man?
I'm sure
you'll come up with something.
- Who was that?
- Superman.
- Welcome
to the "Daily Planet Today."
I'm Lois Lane,
and with me for his first
on-camera interview
is Superman.
I appreciate you
agreeing to be here.
- Thanks for having me.
- Now, as you know, the world
has been captivated by you
ever since your first
appearance in Metropolis
over a year ago,
and one of the big questions
that always gets asked
regarding Superman
is how long you were
on Earth before that.
- Well,
essentially my whole life.
After my planet was destroyed--
- Krypton.
- Right,
when Krypton was destroyed,
the pod that allowed me
to escape
crashed here on Earth.
- Where exactly on Earth?
- That's not something
I'm ready to reveal yet.
- The assumption is that
it was somewhere in the U.S.
- Well, don't assume that just
because I'm speaking English.
- You speak multiple languages.
Is that also a superpower?
- [laughs]
No.
Just curiosity about the world.
I wanted to know more
about different people,
different regions,
so I studied their languages.
- How many languages?
- All of them.
- What would you say
to the people of the world
when asked what you stand for?
- I'd like to think
everything good and decent.
Truth, justice.
- The American way?
- [chuckles]
I think someone's just trying
to get me to admit
I was raised here.
- Cut!
Can someone please
take a look at Lois' mic?
- All right, everybody,
let's stand by
for sound check.
Stand by please.
- I feel like
we're not getting anywhere.
- I can't believe it.
- No, I know, he's, like,
giving me the runaround.
- No, not that.
I think Superman is into you.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- The way
he keeps smiling at you?
I dream of having someone
look at me like that.
It's basically how
all my favorite movies end.
- Janet, he's Superman.
It's part of his whole shtick.
He looks at people
in a nice way.
- Okay, listen, I'm not talking
to you as your producer.
I'm talking to you
as one of your best friends.
And I am telling you...
- Janet.
- There is some
serious chemistry happening...
- Listen to me.
- And you need
to bring your A game
if you wanna go out
with the world's
most eligible bachelor.
- I am not interested, okay?
I'm in love with someone else.
Clark from the paper.
We've been dating
for a couple months.
I know he's dorky,
but I love him.
- Right,
the guy with the glasses.
- Yeah.
- He's so sweet.
- Well, that's great, Lois.
I--I had no idea
you were in love.
- That's because I haven't
told anyone yet, not even him.
- Hey, random
Superman question.
He wouldn't happen
to have super-hearing?
- [whispers]
Can we just go?
Yeah, yeah.
- [clears throat]
I apologize.
That was unprofessional.
- That's okay.
He's a--he's a lucky man.
- Don't think this means
I'm gonna take it easy on you.
- I'd be offended if you did.
- Okay.
Ready?
I'm nervous.
- I didn't think
you got nervous.
- Well, it's your mom, Clark.
What if she doesn't like me?
- [laughs]
That's not possible.
- Maybe you haven't seen
the reader mail section
of the newspaper, but trust me,
it's very possible.
Hi.
- Oh, I'm so glad
you could make it.
Oh, look at you.
[laughs]
Ever since Clark told me
about the two of you,
I couldn't wait
to have you out to the farm.
- Told you.
- Well, I'm happy
to finally make it.
- Oh, thank you.
Lots of folks in Smallville
are dying to meet you too.
- Mom, Mom, Mom, you promised.
- Oh, Clark.
It's just the neighbors
and Edelsteins
and, you know,
girls from bridge club, so...
- Well, I'm very excited
to meet everyone.
- Well, come on inside.
I've got lunch waiting.
She's wonderful.
- Yeah, I know.
- So what took you so long
to bring her here?
- Because I needed to be ready.
- To meet me?
- That's not what I meant.
I brought her here to tell her
who I really am.
- Oh, are you sure?
Once you tell her,
there's no going back.
- Yeah, well...
there was no going back
after the first time I saw her.
- I'm so happy for you, honey.
- Everything okay?
- Everything's perfect, dear.
Just perfect.
- You follow me.
I wanna show you something.
[crowd cheering]
- Love you, Lois!
Love you, Clark!
- I can't believe
I married Lois Lane.
- I'm all yours, babe.
For better or for worse.
- You know, I...
I kept my secret
from everyone for so long,
and now I know why.
It's for you.
So we could have
this life together.
- There's no one
I'd rather share it with.
- This might be
a weird time to say it,
but I can't wait to tell my dad
about the wedding.
He's gonna be so excited.
I mean, as excited
as a hologram can get, I guess.
- Well, he's gonna have to wait
till after the honeymoon.
♪
- How was
your marriage ceremony, son?
- It was the perfect day.
Lois looked beautiful.
I wish
you could have been there.
- I need you
to get out of here now, Son.
- Father, what's happening?
- Go!
Get out of here now!
- Hey, babe, there's something
I need to tell you.
- Lois, what day is it?
- I'm pregnant.
- You're pregnant?
- Yes.
I know, we weren't even trying.
We didn't even know
this was possible,
but there are
three pregnancy tests
in the bathroom, and they all
say the same thing.
We're gonna be parents.
- Okay, Lois, something
really strange happened
right before you came out.
- I can't believe it either.
It's like you said
on our honeymoon.
This is why
you kept your secret.
- So we can share
our life together.
- And now we can have a family.
I didn't even realize
I wanted one
this badly until now.
- Yeah. Yeah, me too.
- Okay, be honest,
you want a boy or a girl?
- I--I just want the baby
to be healthy.
- Come on, Clark.
That's so predictable.
- What?
It's true.
- All right,
well, I'm just gonna say it.
I want a girl.
- Okay.
- Oh, my.
- Is everything okay?
- Yes, it's just more okay.
Looks like you two
are going to have twins.
- What?
Are you sure?
- Ooh, is that a--you know?
- Very,
and I can't say for certain,
but, yes,
they do appear to be boys.
- This is what I get
for wanting a girl.
- I can't believe I'm gonna
be a dad twice all at once.
- Can you get me
some water, please?
- Babe.
- Do you think
this is because of Superman?
- My father assured me
everything's gonna be fine.
- He also didn't know
we were having twins,
and that is
a pretty big curve ball.
- Hey, it's gonna be okay.
I promise.
- Yeah, says the guy
who doesn't have to give birth
to two babies at the same time.
Clark, I'm not delivering
the babies at the fortress.
- This isn't real.
- In a lifetime
full of memories,
there is none more special
than becoming a father.
- What have you done?
- Easy, Kal-El.
I'd hate for you
to miss the big moment.
- [screams]
- You're doing great.
We're almost there.
- Yeah, 27 hours later.
- Edge is here somehow.
- I love you too.
[screams]
- Just one more push, Lois,
and baby Jonathan
can meet Jordan.
- He knows everything.
- [screams]
[baby crying]
- You did it!
- We have a family, Clark.
- Yes, you do.
Jordan and Jonathan Kent,
the twin sons
of Lois and Superman.
- No. No, please. Please.
They're just babies.
- How little
you know me, brother.
I would never harm a newborn.
Teenage boys,
on the other hand...
That's a different
matter entirely.
It's good you're awake, Kal-El.
Now you and I can discuss
the terms of your surrender.
- My sons
are not bargaining chips.
- This device
was created by Ter-Loc,
one of Krypton's
greatest scientists.
It allows the user to navigate
the resting mind of another.
- You knew I'd be weak
from my solar flare.
- So I followed you here
where I could sift through
your most precious memories.
- To extort me?
- No, Kal, to understand you.
To understand
what possible reason
you could have
to betray your heritage.
And to think it was all
for a human family.
- You know nothing about them.
- I know enough.
A human wife and twin boys.
How woefully pedestrian.
And you, stumbling
through your daily life
like some village idiot
instead of a true son
of Krypton.
- I'm not the only one who kept
my Kryptonian side hidden.
- I did so out of strategy,
not shame.
To be a man of greatness
and choose to be less...
It speaks to the mediocrity
of this world.
- Whatever it is you want,
threatening my family
is not how you'll get it.
- It's not a threat, Kal.
I will destroy their lives
by taking that thing
you hold so dear, your secret,
and shouting it
for all the world to hear.
Superman has a family.
- No!
- Then tell me another way.
I appealed to you as a brother,
and you attacked me,
a Kryptonian,
and you stole from me,
a friend, and you destroyed
everything I had built.
- He is none of those things.
Do not listen to him!
- It is this man
who has corrupted you,
just as he
corrupted our mother.
- I spoke with her. Lara.
She believes
there is still good in you.
- Was this
as she helped you plot
to destroy Kryptonian lives?
- The same lives that occupied
innocent human beings?
- Enough!
I will not debate morality
with this whisper.
Here I stand, brother.
Flesh and bone
and beating heart.
Your true family.
Join me of your own free will.
- I can't let you do this.
- Then I will make you suffer.
- I love you, son.
- You are my life's greatest
disappointment, Kal-El.
All my life, I dreamt
of having a brother, a family,
only to have you reject me!
It didn't have to be this way.
- This head is pounding worse
than after ten whiskey chasers.
- From everything we can tell,
it should go away
in a day or two.
- How's Emily doing?
- Confused. Overwhelmed.
- What's she know, exactly?
- Just the broad strokes,
same as everyone else.
Edge was giving people powers,
messing with their minds
to control them.
- Nothing about
alien consciousness?
- DOD felt that would be
better kept off the record.
- Still a lot to process.
And people in this town
are gonna want answers.
- Yeah, at which point
they're gonna be looking
for someone to blame,
and pretty sure
I'm gonna be
at the top of that list.
- Your heart was
in the right place, babe.
- Heart's not the problems.
It's this stubborn head of mine
refusing to listen.
I should've never gone
to see Edge behind your back.
- Speaking of Edge,
any idea where he went?
- Superman and the DOD
are looking for him.
I'm sure he'll turn up soon.
- It's like a war zone downtown
with all
of the military patrolling.
It's very end of days.
- I think Grandpa said
they're gonna be leaving soon.
They just have to check in
on everybody that was
mind-swapped or whatever.
- My dad has his good side
and his not-so-good side,
but seeing him become
a whole different person is--
- Must've been strange.
- Super weird.
- I just instantly assumed
the worst about him,
even though my mom told me
that it wasn't all his fault.
- Well, sometimes
it's hard to tell
when parents are
telling you the truth.
- It's probably the same
for them, you know, with us.
It seems like families
are always lying to each other,
which is pretty messed up.
So thank you for being honest
with me about everything.
- Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Just--I'm sorry it was a--
sorry it was such
a traumatic experience.
- At least it was the truth.
Is it cool if I have
a moment alone with Jordan?
- Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
- Sarah, I--I'm so sorry
I didn't tell you everything
that was happening.
John even wanted me
to tell you,
and I--I said no.
I was really scared.
I--
- I don't want to be
just friends anymore.
- Me neither.
- Uh, Lois,
hold--hold up
just a--just a second.
Um...
Listen, I just--
I wanted to apologize to you,
you know, for the way
I've treated you
this whole time.
- It's okay, Kyle.
- No. No, it's not.
Look, I was wrong about--
about damn near everything,
but...mostly,
I was wrong about you.
You're good people, Lois,
and I'm real happy
you're part of this town.
- Thank you.
- So it's, like,
really official official now
or what?
- Yeah, I guess so.
- Yeah?
- Well, I'm happy
for you, sweetie,
but now that you
have a girlfriend,
your dad and I
are gonna have to have
a little chitchat
with you about what we expect.
- Guess Dad's home.
- Your father won't be
returning any time soon,
which is why Uncle Morgan
decided to come pay a visit.
- So this is the life
Kal-El chose.
It's even more
disappointing up close.
- You're not welcome here.
- That's no way
to speak to family, Lois,
especially
with young boys around.
- Where's our dad?
- When I left him,
he was a crumpled heap
in his little ice castle.
Peculiar place
to build a fortress.
I chose the desert.
Like to feel the sun
on my face.
- Leave, now.
- Jordan, stop.
- Oh, I see your son's
inherited your false bravado.
- Jordan!
- Stay away from my sons!
- This is all your doing.
It was your influence
that made him
turn his back
on his own people.
- Let them go.
This is between you and me.
- I'm afraid we've passed
that point, Ms. Lane,
but I will let them live
long enough to watch you die.
Impressive, Kal-El.
But this changes nothing.
- I'll do whatever you ask.
Just leave my family alone.
- Pledge to me
that you will submit,
and I promise
to let them live unharmed.
- Clark, please don't do this.
- I submit.
- Take a good look
at the man you knew,
'cause it will be your last.
- I'm sorry.
We needed more time.
He was right.
- This is--
- My home.
I'm ready, Father.
- Finally.
My son.
What year is it on this Earth?
- By their measurements, 1987.
- And the Eradicator,
you possess it?
- Not yet.
- Did I birth a fool
for a son?
Your mission was simple!
- I've spent years searching,
but it is still yet to arrive.
- I see.
Well, we must prepare
in the interim.
I will train you myself.
- Thank you, Father.
- We must root out
all weakness
so that you can gain power
in this world.
- Were there any other
Kryptonians sent to join me?
There's that weakness.
You need no one, son.
Only me. Is that understood?
- Yes, sir.
- The first lesson
is the measure of pain.
Its application being a tool
of great strategic value.
Although, in your case,
it is necessary that you
be able to withstand it.
Here he is, Father.
- Son of Jor-El.
The worst of Krypton.
- You don't have to do this.
- See how he begs?
His own weakness
never stamped out.
- He has vowed
his submission, Father.
- And the Eradicator?
- Taken from his possession.
- Then let us begin.
- John, it's happening.
Just like you said it would.
I think
Superman's been turned.
- Greg, move your head.