Previously on "Superman & Lois"...
Let's just focus on what
we came here for: family.
- Miss?
- Sharon Powell.
My son was a miner at the Edge Facility.
Morgan Edge offered him
"the opportunity of a lifetime".
Turns out, Miss Powell's son
isn't the only worker
who's gone missing.
How's Eliza doing?
She's okay, she's okay.
Maybe... maybe too okay.
Tag, Tag?
I think my heat vision,
it affected him somehow.
Don't try to tell me it wasn't my fault.
Captain Luthor?
We need to stop Kal-El
before he does to this world
what he did to mine.
I've always loved Smallville
during the fall.
The changing of seasons...
The turning of time.
The last warm moments
before the cold.
_
But what I loved most of all...
was the one weekend every year
when everyone came together
and sacrificed to help those in need.
Harvest Fest?
So, is that why you've been
"Supermanning" all week?
So you free up some time to go to this?
It's a tradition! Goes
all the way back to 1949
when Smallville was established.
It's one of the best things
about being here.
I have been hearing
about this from your dad
since we first started dating.
Bedtime stories to help you
sleep, or what?
Either way, it doesn't sound
like much of a festival.
Just sounds like a whole bunch
of people selling stuff.
Not just sell. Share!
You know, whatever they can,
with anyone who needs it.
Think of it as Smallville's
version of Burning Man.
Minus the fires and BO,
- I hope.
- Ha, ha.
Your grandmother loved it, okay?
She used to spend weeks planning
what we were gonna donate.
She made lists and spreadsheets.
Your dad learned a lot about giving
and helping people in need from this.
Your dad's not Superman just
'cause he has powers, you know.
Aw, thanks, baby.
I know you guys aren't sold,
but when you see everyone
come together like this,
the... the sense of community,
it's... it's the best
of what Smallville is.
It just doesn't sound
like much of a festival.
Well, they have all that stuff too.
The food stands alone.
Funnel cakes, fried cheese curds...
Ooh! The Fishers!
Every year, they have this
"Sugar Bowl" stand.
They make chocolate bacon.
- So good!
- Uh, Eliza's vegetarian, so.
- Oh.
- Hey, I'm glad
she's finally able to come visit.
Look, the Harvest Fest is special, okay?
Eliza's gonna love it,
you're gonna love it...
all of you are gonna love it.
- Let's go! Corn, let's go!
- We're gonna love it.
What?
Two essays in one night.
It's ridiculous. It's,
like, he can't even
- write himself.
- Hey, Sarah.
- Hey.
Wow, um, they really go all-out
with this Harvest Fest stuff, huh?
I know it's kinda hokey, but...
it has its own kind of specialness.
You sound like my dad.
Shut up.
Um, you guys going tonight?
Yeah. Actually, Eliza's coming too.
- Ooh, Metropolis girl?
- Yeah.
What about you?
Do you maybe wanna go together?
L... like from beginning to end?
That is how I understand
the concept of "together".
Um, Sarah,
let me just speak for my brother here.
He would love to go with you.
Right?
Yeah, no, no, no, yeah.
I would love to go.
Great. Um...
we'll meet up beforehand?
For sure, yeah. I'll text you
when Eliza's coming.
Cool, okay. Um...
Awesome, well.
Oh.
Okay.
Hey, babe, what's up?
What? What are you...
what are you talking about?
Eliza! Hey, hey.
Eliza, can we... can we please
just talk about this?
Okay. Whatever.
Yeah, bye.
That didn't sound good.
It's great. Great...
If you consider getting dumped
by your girlfriend of over a year
the night you're supposed
to see her "great".
Look, man, that sucks.
All good. Welcome to Smallville,
the place where you get
dumped over the phone, right?
Hey.
What are you up to?
I was thinking we'd
make this the home office
of the world's most famous journalist.
But these are all your mom's things.
Yeah, I know, but
it's what she would've wanted.
And the Harvest Fest is the perfect time
to give this stuff away.
Okay.
If this is really what you want.
No, no, no!
Not that. Sorry.
Hey, Chrissy.
Lois, are you coming in soon?
Why, what's going on?
Uh, Sharon Powell's here.
She okay?
Yeah, she's okay, actually.
And so is her son.
You don't remember what happened?
Uh, no, ma'am.
I was coming through the tunnel
and I was reading my paycheck.
Hadn't seen a number
that big in a long time.
Just wasn't paying attention,
I guess, and...
hit it real good.
Next thing I know, I wake up
in Stanton County.
They found him outside a church.
St. Anthony's.
They helped me remember
who I was.
I saw the flyer that you made.
That was the best call of my life.
What about the phone messages
you left your mom?
I don't know anything about that.
You said the job wasn't
what you expected.
You sounded scared.
Well, the doctors said
that with a hit to the head like that,
it might take some time
for his memories...
return.
Look, Miss Lane, we are so grateful
for your help, but I'm just...
so happy that he's back.
All this other stuff, it just
doesn't matter anymore.
Sharon, someone tried to kill you.
I have my son back.
T... there's just no more
story to tell anymore.
W... we just came to say thank you.
- It's up to you.
- What?
You were almost murdered
by someone with superhuman strength,
and you're just gonna let that go?
You wanna write something?
Write about how my
missing son has returned.
That's a nice story.
Thank you for your time.
Okay, that phony story
- was all sorts of rehearsed.
- I know.
Sharon almost got killed
by someone who works
- for Morgan Edge.
- Yep.
I'm acting like you right now?
That's because we both know
this is a big story.
And we will figure it out, but for now,
let's just be happy
she got her son back.
It appears we've successfully located
Lois Lane, Captain Luthor.
Are you certain this is
the best course of action?
I am.
One thing I know for
sure about this world...
wherever Lois Lane goes,
Superman follows.
_
Great, housewares.
All we could give this year, Lana.
Oh, don't you apologize, Aidy.
Not after everything
you've been through.
Thank you.
- Hi, there.
- Hi.
Couple bags of men's clothes.
Oh, great. We always get so much
women's clothes but not enough men's.
Can I get a name for recognition?
Sure, it's Sharon and Derek Powell.
Derek Powell?
From New Carthage?
Glad you're back.
Yep, got a happy ending.
I-I'll go get the rest of the bags.
Ah.
Ms. Larr, there's something wrong.
I... I don't know. I... I feel off.
Ah.
I need to see you.
Now.
Hello?
Are you there?
Ah!
Well, it's a different look for you.
I feel like it really pops.
Ah.
Yeah, it's definitely assertive.
You sure you want to wear that
to the Harvest Fest, honey?
You know, Lana's gonna be there.
You're right.
I should probably stick with flannel.
I know you don't like
talking about it, but...
is Lana still seeing that Cushing boy?
Mm.
See? No alarms.
Let's get out of here as fast as we can.
Easy, now!
This is some real high-end equipment.
Which you need to put back.
I think you got the wrong idea, here,
Ski Mask Guy.
Pretty sure you used that crowbar
to break into this shop,
where you stole 12 TVs,
10 VCRs, and more than
a few salad shooters.
Put the stuff back.
Sorry, kid.
Put it back.
Our bad.
We'll put it all back.
Like we were never here.
I need more hoses on the roof now!
Tamara's gonna get you looked at, okay?
- Where's Mitch?
- Thought he was with you.
Mitch!
Mitch, you in here?
Mayday, Mayday, Mayday.
This is Chief Cushing.
I got eyes on Mitch.
Bravo, Charlie, corner.
Heavy smoke and fire.
You're gonna be all right, okay?
Right, now, get your arm
around my shoulder.
- Ah!
- There we go.
Ah.
You're gonna be all right. There you go.
Okay. Just come on.
Let's pick up that pace
just a little bit, okay, bud?
Ah!
Ah, ah.
Close one, boss.
Come on.
We got 'em, Chief.
- Come on, Mitch.
- Come on.
- Here we go.
- Come on, let's just go.
Come on!
Is that...
is that frost?
I should've been there sooner.
By the time I got there,
all the donations
were already destroyed.
That's awful. What are they gonna do?
I don't know.
Most people already gave
everything they have to offer.
Sharon Powell was hanging
around outside the Center.
At the fire?
- Yeah.
- Was Derek there?
No. It seemed like she was
looking for someone, though.
- It could've been him.
- That doesn't sound right.
I'm gonna go down
and start asking questions.
Guys, got your favorite pizza.
I'm not hungry.
Eliza dumped him this morning.
I'll go talk to him.
First breakups are rough.
Pretty much crawled into
an REO Speedwagon rabbit hole.
Speedwagon?
- Never mind.
- All right.
Jonathan?
Jordan just had to go
and announce it to the world, huh?
He's just worried about you.
So am I. Do you wanna talk about it?
What is there to talk about?
I mean, clearly,
she knows that she can do
better than dating some kid
from some middle-of-nowhere town.
I'm sure it's complicated
for her, too, sweetie.
Our move here was really sudden.
Are you seriously
taking her side right now?
No. I'm just saying,
as a former teenage girl myself,
you gotta give it some time.
She might wake up and remember
how incredible you are.
And if she doesn't, then it's her loss.
Well, thanks for
your Cosmo Girl opinion,
but, honestly, I just want
to be left alone right now.
Trigger warning, Lane.
Don't want you having any flashbacks
to what happened to your car.
Any idea what caused this?
Not sure.
You know, I don't know
what's more confusing,
how the damn thing started
or how it ended.
Was anybody hurt?
Tom Mitchell.
I met him at your barbecue. Nice guy.
He was the best man at my wedding.
You know, probably the bravest person
we got on this crew.
Is gonna be okay?
You know, it's not looking good.
So unless you got any more questions...
I do have one, sorry.
Have you seen this guy
anywhere near the Center?
Derek Powell?
I might've seen him
come around the back.
W... why are you asking?
I need to talk to him about a story.
Thanks for your time.
I'm sorry about your friend.
Chrissy, Kyle saw Derek Powell
at the Center
as the fire trucks arrived.
Well, that's 50 shades of suspicious.
We don't know anything for sure yet.
My big reporter energy knows something
crazy weird's going on
with Derek Powell.
I need you to get his mom
and get her to The Gazette right now.
- On it.
- Miss Lane?
I've been looking for you.
So you're a reporter?
That's right.
Marcus Bridgewater.
Sounds vaguely familiar.
- "Politico"?
- "Reuters".
Mainly do business coverage,
focusing on big tech.
I have a background in engineering.
I used to work at LutherCorps.
Lex Luthor, the only human
being worse than Morgan Edge.
Guy, uh...
Definitely has his secrets.
So what exactly brings
a "Reuters" tech reporter
to Smallville, Kansas?
You.
I'm a huge fan. And
after reading your piece
- on Morgan Edge...
- My heavily redacted piece.
I thought there might be
a bigger story here,
so I did a little digging.
- You trying to poach my story?
- That's not my intent.
Just wanna be on team Lois.
Not sure I have much
of a roster these days.
Still have Superman.
Unless someone else is covering him
now that you've left Metropolis?
He's a public figure.
Anyone can cover him.
Yeah, but, you're the one
who seems to always have
the inside track.
He's just someone I report on.
Sure, but, without you,
I think we all know
there'd be a lot more
questions about the guy.
So, what is it you have on Morgan Edge?
Nothing yet. But I think I may
have found a way to get
a look inside the mines.
Thanks.
Doesn't exactly sound legal.
The less you know, the better.
Well, if you manage to dig something up,
give me a call.
Maybe we'll split the byline?
Let's see what you come up with first.
He really said that to you?
Didn't even have the nerve.
He sent me a text, I mean...
I just got him back,
and... and out of nowhere,
he needs "space"?
He say anything about where he's going?
Any chance I can see that text?
Sure.
You and Derek wouldn't be sharing
a phone plan, by any chance?
- It's the only way anyone can afford it
- _
these days.
- Why do you ask?
- _
Um...
I just wanted to vent.
God, those phone companies
are such crooks, right?
Hey, Dad, um,
mind if I leave early
to meet up with Sarah
at Harvest Fest?
Uh...
any chance this meetup is, like, a...
like a date?
I don't know. Maybe.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
Yeah!
- All right, all right.
- Okay, yes!
- Yes, of course you can!
- All right, Dad. Dad.
What, what? This is what I was talking
- about, Harvest Festival.
- Be cool.
If I have to hear anything else
about this stupid Harvest Fest.
- Jon.
- Farming or community or
basically anything else
about this backwards-ass town.
Hey.
I'm sorry about Eliza.
It's not about that, Dad.
I wanna move back.
I lost all my friends.
I'm probably never gonna
play football again,
and... and now, what? You just expect me
to drop my life for everyone else's?
Look, I know, I know. A lot has changed.
But I promise you,
it's all gonna work out.
You don't know that!
I get it. There was a time in my life
when I felt just like you.
Yeah, well, I'm sure. When was that?
When you were, I don't know,
lifting an oil tanker
or maybe flying laps around Saturn?
- Jonathan...
- No, Dad!
I'm not like you, and
I'm not like Superboy
over there, okay?
And this town?
It is my kryptonite. I hate it.
Look, Dad, um...
Bryan Kelso's older brother
has a place, okay?
He just graduated from Met U,
there's a spare bedroom.
It's just outside of downtown.
I... I was thinking,
maybe I could just stay with them.
Uh, no, no.
You are not going to stay
with the Kelsos.
You know what? Maybe I'll just do it
anyways, then, because
that's what Jordan did
with football, and you let him
get away with it.
Whatever. Jordan, come on.
If this Harvest Fest is so awesome,
let's go have some real fun.
Go.
Thanks.
Will you listen to me?
We've talked about this, Clark.
You can't be running around
playing masked vigilante.
- They were stealing!
- I understand that,
but we've got rules in this family.
Those were Dad's rules,
and he's not here anymore.
That doesn't mean you get to ignore
everything he taught you.
It's been a year. You know?
We can't keep pretending
everything's the same.
We have to move on with our lives.
Moving on can be a distraction.
Sometimes to heal, you've gotta...
you've gotta sit with
the feeling, you know?
- Let it run its course.
- Dad understood.
He knew I was sent here for a reason.
Your father and I both knew
you were sent here for a reason.
Well, I'm pretty sure that reason
wasn't to be Martha Kent's son.
Thank you for all your hard work.
Clark is gonna be so surprised.
Okay, I'll see you soon.
I'm sorry I'm late, babe.
It's okay. How's Mitch?
Well, he... he took in a lot of smoke.
Doc's a little worried
that the lung damage
- might be permanent.
- Oh, God.
Yeah, it's... it's a lot questions
as to whether or not
he's gonna be able
to come back to the station.
I'm sorry.
Aww.
Have you been drinking?
Y... yeah, you know, me
and Tamara and the boys,
I mean, we went out and
had a drink in his honor.
Smells like you had
a little more than one.
L... let me just get a quick bite,
- get showered up...
- I have people waiting on me.
We're trying to figure out what to do
- about the donations we lost.
- Come on, babe.
It's been a long, hard day.
Okay? Just...
it'll only take a minute.
Mom?
Just take Soph.
- Let me just...
- No, I got it.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
_
I really hope she's not
having second thoughts.
Jordan, she's the one
who asked you, man.
Just have a... have a shred
of confidence, okay?
Hey, look. It's the Kent sisters.
Yo.
- What's up, boys?
- Got your text, QB2.
We are locked and loaded.
- Hell, yeah.
- Better drink up
before the big game.
Are you sure that's a good idea tonight?
Uh...
Thanks for looking out, Mom.
Mm.
- Why don't you go find Sarah?
- Fine.
You do you, party guy.
We'll see how that goes.
We'll see.
Okay, we will.
Yeah.
Dad?
Hey. Thanks.
Hey, you, sit... sit down
for just a minute.
Hey, you remember that song
I used to sing you
when you were a little girl?
♪ De la Sierra Morena ♪
♪ Cielito lindo, vienen bajando ♪
♪ Un par De ojitos negros ♪
♪ Cielito lindo, De contrabando ♪
Dad, stop!
That was a long time ago.
Yeah, time really does fly, doesn't it?
I should get going.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll be... I'll be right
behind you, mi hijita.
Yeah.
I started that fire.
If he finds out it was me...
Nothing is going to happen to you.
This was an accident.
But if I can't control it...
We can fix this.
Follow me.
Gotcha.
I'm sorry about earlier, Clark.
It's okay, Mom. I shouldn't have gotten
so upset, and you were right...
No, no, just listen to me.
I didn't want to admit that
this home isn't the best place
for you anymore.
You are special,
and I know you're meant
for... for bigger things.
And that time might have come.
What is this?
Your father found it
in the pod when you arrived.
I don't know what it does
or what it's for, I just...
I just know it belongs to you.
And it might be the key to figuring out
what your future is.
Hey, hey, Lana. How are you?
- Hey, Cobb.
- How are you?
I'm good.
I, uh...
I heard about Mitch.
- It's a damn shame.
- Yeah.
Listen, um...
is Kyle gonna be here tonight, or...
Oh, he... he wanted
to stay at the hospital.
He's a good man, that Kyle.
He is.
- Hey.
- Hey!
I'm really sorry I'm late.
It's all right. You okay?
No, not really.
Um, but, I don't really wanna do
sad stories tonight, so.
All right.
My dad can't shut up about these.
You probably shouldn't eat
anything here that's on a stick.
Come on, let me buy you
some elephant ears.
All right.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, that sounds great.
- Okay.
What makes you think this
time, it'll be any different?
Trust me.
You know, I think I'm
starting to see what my dad
saw in this place.
From this? Really?
It's pretty great.
Look,
about earlier...
everything's not okay.
It's just...
I don't know, the sheer weight
of all of the really bad things
that are going on in my life,
and I'm pretty sure that
my therapist is tired of
hearing me talk about the same stuff.
So, try me.
Well...
okay. My dad, he...
Yo, yo, guys, look!
It's everybody's favorite
Kent brother. It's Mr. Charming, baby!
- Look at this guy.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Not now, all right? Not now, please.
Whoa, whoa, relax, relax, relax, relax.
Chill, chill, chill, chill. Look.
Guys, guys, guys. Get this.
It's this guy's first date ever.
It's his first date!
What?
First-timer.
Wow. You can't go one weekend
without partying like idiots?
It's kind of pathetic.
- Sarah, hey, look, you need...
- Don't touch me!
- Hey, we're just kidding.
- Don't talk to me like that!
Look, uh, he's... he's having
a really rough day,
that's all this is, okay?
Oh, you're having a rough day?
You have no idea what
real problems are like.
For people who don't come
from a picture-perfect family
like you,
you all can just get drunk
and act like total idiots
and think that there's never
any consequences?
Yo, Sarah,
we were just... we were just kidding.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Save it. Have fun.
Talk to you later. Move!
- Wait, Sarah...
- Jordan.
- Hey, Jordan!
- What, what, what?
Jordan.
Look, I'm... I'm sorry, man. I didn't...
I didn't mean to ruin
your night like that.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Let's just...
let's just get you some water.
- Okay?
- Okay.
I'm sorry.
You're right. These are
severely underrated.
- Right?
- Yes.
- You talk to Jonathan?
- Whoa!
Um, yeah.
He wants to move back to Metropolis.
He said that?
Yeah, among other things.
Here he comes.
Oh, and he's been drinking.
What?
You've been drinking?
- What?
- Your dad can smell it.
I can smell it. The whole
town can smell it.
It's... it's not that big a deal.
- Excuse me?
- Okay, both of you,
call a rideshare and go home right now.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Fine, we were going anyway.
Go faster!
Chrissy, now is not a good time.
Okay, so, Sharon Powell
came into the office
and I, like, totally sleuthed
my way onto her phone
to get Derek's location.
So then I thought, "WWLLD",
"what would Lois Lane do",
which is easy,
dig deeper and follow the lead,
only I never would've thought
it would lead me to him
making out with Leslie Larr.
Leslie Larr is there with Derek Powell?
Yeah, she took him to this building
where there's this crazy
Bride of Frankenstein machine.
Did it work?
What is this?
Protect the asset.
Projectile in motion, sir.
Speed and flight pattern unique
to Kryptonian air mobiles.
Kal-El's here?
- They're two of them?
- It appears so,
though I have still yet
to identify the other.
- Where'd they go?
- Flight algorithm suggests
a five-mile circumference.
Continue on this road,
and we'll intersect
in 23 seconds.
Take over.
Auto-drive engaged.
What did she do to you?
She resurrected me, Kal-El.
You're not alone anymore.
45 degrees southeast,
in three, two, one.
Fire.
I can help you.
No, you can't.
I'm already dead.
Ah!
No! Wait, wait, wait!
I guess Harvest Fest
was kind of a bust, huh?
Hey.
I just wanted to say that...
I'm... I'm really sorry
- and I promise that...
- Stop.
It's okay.
This is your one
"get out of jail free" card.
It is?
Wait, seriously?
Jonathan, I told you,
I know how you feel, and I do.
When I was just a couple
years older than you,
I did leave home.
- Why?
- Lots of reasons.
The main one was that I needed
to become someone else.
Someone I thought was more
important than Clark Kent.
And to do that,
I had to leave Smallville.
And he never came back.
I still think about that decision.
That time that I gave up
with my mom, I never got it back.
She only had so much time to give,
and she sacrificed it for me.
Jonathan, you have your own path.
And it might not feel like it right now,
but I know it's gonna
lead to great things.
All I'm asking is that you give
Smallville a little more time.
If, after that, things
still aren't working out,
then we can discuss other options.
- Okay.
Right, I wanna give you something.
Something from that time in my life.
Dad, there's nothing in here.
The box is the gift.
Your granddad gave that
to my mom when he proposed.
And she gave it to me
when it was my time to leave.
Wow.
All right, it's getting late,
you better go upstairs
before we change our minds
about that punishment.
Thanks, Dad.
See ya.
Softy.
I know.
I'm still trying to process
what happened to Derek Powell.
I feel so bad for his mom.
Can't believe he just
killed himself like that.
I don't think it was Derek.
- It was his body.
- Yeah, but his powers
were erratic, like Tag Harris.
And he said he'd been resurrected...
whatever that means.
Well, whatever Edge and Leslie are doing
with that machine, it has
something to do with the mines.
Hey.
Hi.
I know it isn't much,
but every little bit helps, right?
Aw, thank you. That's so thoughtful.
Just wish that we could
replace everything
that was lost in the fire.
Oh, you're never gonna believe this.
- We already have.
- What?
- How?
- Morgan Edge.
He heard about what happened
and wrote a check to replace everything,
and then some.
Very generous.
I... I guess he just wanted to help.
Okay, come with me.
One last donation you need to see.
Okay?
As you know,
the Harvest Festival was your mom's
favorite time of the year,
and we really feel her absence.
Martha Kent was everything
this town aspires to be.
She was kind,
she was generous,
and she was always there
when you needed her.
Everyone in Smallville
can remember her sitting right here,
talking with and laughing with
whoever was right there beside her.
And though she is no longer
physically with us,
her spirit remains, and she will be
right here for whoever needs her.
_
Did you know about this?
Are you gonna sit down?
The train will be here any minute.
Clark?
It's time, Clark.
I was so selfish.
Everybody is at that age.
It's part of growing up.
Yeah, but Mom knew that.
And she let me go anyway.
Because she loved you and
she wanted you to be happy.
And now we're at the point where
our own kids are talking
about leaving home.
It feels like they were just born.
It's easy for you to say,
you didn't have to go
through 27 hours of labor.
That's true.
Love you.
Love you too.
Biometric readings
suggests your pulse is abnormally high.
This must be
- about Lois Lane.
- Hmm.
It is worth reminding
you that this is not
the Lois Lane from your world.
Everything about her is the same.
Everything, except she
marries someone else.
Come back to me.
I always do.
There are other variables
that you have not t...
I'm glad that Jon
didn't get into trouble.
Yeah.
Uh, my dad was pretty cool
about it, it was nice.
Can you tell Jon that I'm sorry?
I didn't... I didn't mean
to get so mad at him.
It's no big deal.
It kind of is, though.
I know that I asked you out on the date,
only to completely
and totally ruin it, but,
I think I could really just use a friend
more than anything else.
Yeah.
Yeah, um...
well, as long as we still get
to spend some time together.
Yeah, I do believe that
that's what friends do.
So...
You know, you were the one
that ruined the date.
Hey! So now you don't
- want to be friends?
- Eh, you know...
I'll think about it.
Mm-kay.
Tag?
- What did you do to me?
- What?
- Tell me!
- Hey, man.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Greg, move your head!
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -