[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
Si Tu Mo
[Preview]
For you
[Episode 11]
Come in
Professor, you looking for me?
Xiao Gu
Have a seat
Taste my new tea
Thanks
Well...
Is the book useful?
I tried the most logical
and the most illogical chapters
It's not effective so far
Impossible
Professor Jiang, I knew that
you gave him tips
I was wondering what made
Gu Wei Yi so excellent
in experiments and calculations
He beats me in everything
Zhou Lei, you got it wrong
Professor Jiang, I caught you red-handed
No excuse
Listen to me
Listen
Come sit down
and listen to me
Okay
Have a seat
Say it
Actually,
I gave him a book
about tackling a girl
I didn't tell you
as I didn't want you to think too much
Professor Jiang
You should've told me
that you guys were merely chatting here
That's more like it then
Show it to him
Show him the book
I didn't bring it
See
This is a typical story line
How can I
convince you then?
Well...
Give me the same book
This is impossible
The book is out of print
That's why I gave it to him secretly
He's now in a very moment
Wait...
I recalled it
My wife has a copy with her
It's in the same series
I'll ask her to bring it here
Really?
Really
Exactly the same
[How to tackle a handsome guy?]
That's crap!
You made me come all the way for the book
Stop standing here, have a seat
Sit down
Xiao Gu, you're mature enough
Shouldn't have a love sick
You're asking lousy ideas
from the professor, huh?
What lousy ideas?
I have even passed him
the book of my collection
You guys are only good at
scientific research,
but no way out
in dating
Why?
How did I marry you then?
That's right, I used to have
a girlfriend too
What's wrong?
It's true
We used to do homework together everyday
I helped her complete all her work
Alright
Even if you had a girlfriend before
Let me ask you,
what should you do
when you see a girl you like?
I know
Say it
Go after her
Smart!
How?
That's the question
Know yourself as well as the enemy,
you'll win every war
First, you must understand the girl
what's in her mind
Only so you can cater to her pleasure
Dear Scientists, think about it
How should you let her know
your feeling?
Confess
What a smart boy!
You're quite talented
How to confess?
Say
I love you
The youngsters of today
are too rushing
Do you know how Professor Jiang
confessed to me?
Stick to them
Don't mention us
Professor Jiang
used to write me a love poem everyday
Wind of Autumn
Blooming of flowers
As if we meet each other again
When I read it,
my heart
was melted
It was long long ago,
don't mention it
I think the girls of today
will not like it
You know nothing
Are you married?
Have a girlfriend?
Are you a girl?
So, I'm the expert
I got it
Alright, I have to go now
Well...
Digest the points
which I have taught you
Next time,
I'll give you another lesson
Xiao Zhou
Keep the book
Otherwise, you always
blame Professor Jiang
to play favorites
Mrs. Jiang
I don't need it
Please take it back
Take it
-I...
-Take it
Just keep it
[How to write a love poem...]
[You are like Schrodinger's Cat...]
[How to draw a cat...]
Very good
Sincere and straightforward
Take a look
Although I don't want to admit it
but I have to say
your literature level is above me
And you even drew a picture here
I think girls will like it very much
Gu Wei Yi
Are you ready?
Sure
Good luck in your confession
Bro
Go for it!
Notice of power cut
Thanks for your understanding
I don't understand
I hate climbing stairs in my period
Still no power supply
It's damn cold
Hello
Can you buy me
a pack of warming patches
when you're back?
There's a power cut
in the house, I'm so cold
I'm downstairs
Come down now
Although it's colder in the house,
I don't want to go out
It's snowing
Snowing?
It's snowing!
Si Tu Mo
For you
Why are you giving it to me?
Why are you giving me your notes?
Don't you get it?
Are you bloating
that your lesson is complicated?
No, think about it
Schrodinger Equation is a law
about the motion of micro particles
What micro particles?
I don't understand
It's so cold
We should have some roasted chestnuts
I'm craving for it
Let's go buy some
Let's go
Boss, how long will it take?
It will be ready in 3 minutes
I have never expected
to see the snow again
in South City in my life time
I saw it for the first time
when I was in the kindergarten
What a pity
it melts when it falls onto the ground
I wish to make a snowman
Gu Wei Yi, you came from the North
Have you made a snowman before?
Yeah
I have never seen a real snowman
If only I had a chance
to see a snowman in real
Boss, it seems you make a big
money during the snowy days
Yeah
My hot chestnuts
are made for such cold weather
Alright, I'll pack for you
Don't take so much, I can't finish it
Sure you can
Your are wearing too little
Take more and
hold it in your hands to make you warm
Thank you
You're welcome
It's okay, I'm not cold
RMB 20
Take it
Here
Okay
Thank you
Take it
Wait a moment
Thank you
So cold
It's damn cold
What is that?
When did you buy them?
So smart
I saw the notice
on my way out this morning
Forgot to tell you
Warming patch with Doraemon
I have never seen it
I don't know
I simply bought it
You like Doraemon too?
I saw you draw one
on your note
Light up the candles
Have you successfully confessed?
No
Why?
Why
She doesn't get it
[Professor Jiang]
Gu Wei Yi, how come she doesn't get it?
It's so simple
That's right
Schrodinger Equation is about the particles
Particles stand for the
structure of everything
You are telling her
she is the structure of your everything
And you said when multiplying it by time,
it will be a complete wave function
It means
she makes
your life more complete
It's so simple and romantic
How can she not get it?
Did she pretend it purposely?
Why are you two staying together?
We're doing an experiment
I'm not like you
Xiao Gu
What field is she studying?
Accounting
What about you write it in Math?
Well...
She will understand then
Si Tu Mo
Have you learned Further Math?
Yes
What is this?
Solve it
Did I annoy you today?
What's wrong?
Why did you keep
insulting my IQ?
Don't trouble me with
science again
Did she solve it?
I never expect you're so romantic
I would say yes if I were a girl
She didn't solve it but got mad
I think she doesn't like you
Better forget it
Don't listen to Zhou Lei
I guess this is indirect for her
Learn it from me
Lower your level to match up with her
Use the poem I wrote to my wife
Wind of Autumn, blooming of flowers
As if we meet each other again
Straight to the point
Si Tu Mo
What?
Wind of Autumn, blooming of flowers
As if we meet each other again
How's that?
Wind of Autumn, blooming of flowers
As if we meet each other again
I've only heard of this
Wind of Autumn
Yummy crabs
It is nicer when you add chillies
Forget it, I go to bed now
I'm the one who should be angry
Rascal!
I think she doesn't like you
Better forget it
"The difficulties in the books"
"are not a problem"
"All the puzzles come with axiom"
"I thought I have the perfect logic"
"Now I find no solution"
"That's how"
"you came into my heart"
"Sweet and childish"
"Nothing can describe your smile"
"You bring me courage"
"Put your head on my shoulder"
"Pass over the seasons hand-in-hand"
"The youth marks my
heartbeat and feeling"
"Our love is passionate"
"Never fade"
"Put your head on my shoulder"
"Pass over the seasons hand-in-hand"
"The youth marks my
heartbeat and feeling"
"Our love is passionate"
"Never fade"
Gu Wei Yi
How was it?
You didn't reply our message
You made it?
How was it?
Wait
Did you use the direct way
which I have told you?
Yes, I did
Wind of Autumn
She said, yummy crabs
Yummy crabs?
Impossible
Was she playing dumb?
Professor Jiang
The girl doesn't like him
Impossible
Professor
Here you are
Feeling better?
I'm alright
That's good
You're not fully recovered
You'd better
stay away from me,
I don't want to be infected
I don't want to be near you
It's too bad
You shouldn't come as you're sick
Do you want everybody to get infected?
Never care about other's feeling
Don't worry
Human flu
can't infect you
Xie Yu Yin
Why are you fighting
in the early morning?
Do your work
What's wrong with you?
You are responsible to check
the mailbox this week
I have checked it out
and forwarded it to Miss Sha Sha
It's not like I can make her read it
Why didn't you send
a cc copy to Miss Li Na?
I thought Miss Sha Sha
would read it
Forget it, we've taken the blame already
No point to argue anymore
I'll check the mailbox from today on
Come on. I'll be more careful in the future
I'm hungry, let's eat something
I haven't done it
I knew
Let's go for a meal first
Alright
I want to go for a hot pot
We don't have time
Where did you learn
the unfriendly tone?
From my room-mate
Which room-mate?
It's almost lunch time now
Take a rest
and continue after lunch
Okay
Which canteen? 1st or 2nd?
2nd, they are selling claypot rice there
I like it the most
Gu Wei Yi?
I'll pass, enjoy yourselves
What's wrong with you??
Nothing
Are you having a fever?
So hot
He's burning
He's burning!
Oh, my god!
Let's go to the hospital
I'm okay
No, you must go to the hospital
I'm leaving first
Or else the claypot rice
will be out of stock
I just need to take a rest
Gu Wei Yi
Gu Wei Yi, get up
Finish the food
You'll get hypoglycemia
if you eat nothing
Take it
No food allowed in the lab
I don't care
I bought it for you
Quickly dig in
Don't move
I've applied for leave for you
Quickly go home after lunch
I said I have applied for leave for you
I'm not that serious
I want to chase senior out too
You two are mobile virus
I...
Don't move
Stay away from me
Getting better?
Much better
I bring some medicine for you
Thank you
I just met Zhou Lei
Radiation protection suit?
He has
a sharp tongue, but kind
He even let you have the last
claypot rice
and applied for leave for me
He urged me to go home quickly
For me too
Go! Go!
Hurry up!
How did you play?
Sorry, bro
He's in a bad mood
Forget it
Calm down
Wang Shan is watching
Don't scare her
Didn't you see he hit my hand?
This is normal in games, right?
You used to be pushed when
you tried to score a goal
But you didn't get mad
I was timid before
Okay?
So you have the nerve now, huh?
What's wrong?
Something's wrong with him recently
I don't know who's eating him
He refused to tell
Please comfort him
Go for a date!
Let's go
Okay
Come on
Forget it
Let's go
Miss Li Na
Why are we buying so much juice?
This is my personal habit
I'll compare the product of our project
to the other of the same kind
It doesn't help much,
but it could inspire your mind
Shall we bring it back to the office
and taste together with the others?
You live nearby?
Yes
Bring the info and juice to your home
Make a report after analysis
Can save you some time
I drink it all alone?
Any problem?
No
Pay then
Okay
My god!
I...
Did I leave the key in the office?
Hello
What's wrong with your voice?
Fever
How come?
Taken any medicine?
Seen a doctor?
Where are you?
I didn't see any doctor
or take any medicine
At home
Do you have medicine at home?
No
Wait a moment, I'll be right there
Okay
Why are you here?
Zhou Lei chased me out of the lab
I saw your unfinished report
So I bring it to you
and see your condition
How did you know my address?
Zhou Lei told me
What's wrong? You don't want to see me?
Come in
Shall I change my shoes?
It's alright
Have a seat, I'll bring you water
Let me do it
You're sick
Have a seat
Let me open the door
It's heavy
I...
Have some water
Thank you
Take the medicine
Have some water first
I gave you the medicine in the morning
Will it harm you if you take it again?
I forgot to bring it back
Hurry up take the medicine
Later
Gu Wei Yi
Take the medicine
So, are you staying together
because of your parents?
My mother and his mother were classmates
What a coincidence!
Done
So fast
I shall go back
I'll walk you out
Gu Wei Yi
Are you sick
because you get infected by me?
If so,
you'd better go to the hospital
as my condition was quite serious
It's alright
I'm leaving first
Bye
Take care
See you
Why did you buy so much juice?
Testing
Leave it to me
You want to take a rest, don't you?
Where to put it?
In the fridge
Do it yourself
So strange
Open it for me
Open it yourself
What's wrong?
Put it in the freezer
How do I drink if it's frozen?
No more space in the cooler
What's this?
Branch?
I don't know, I go to bed first
Branch, wolfberries and a leaf
What's this?
I bought it?
Can't remember
Hello, Mo Mo
Hello, Shan Shan
What should I cook
for a person who has a fever?
Porridge
Who has a fever?
Gu Wei Yi
My mom used to cook in this way
First, wash the rice
Put little oil
and salt into the rice
Then, boil the water
Put dried tangerine peel
in cold water and boil it
Put the rice in after it's boiled
When the water bubbled up again,
turn it to medium or low heat
Make sure it doesn't stick to the pot
When it's almost done,
take out the peel
Forget it, let him starve to death
He doesn't need the porridge anyway
It sounds complicated
In fact, it's simple
Come and help me
Okay
See you in a bit
Don't pretend sleeping. Gu Wei Yi is sick
Not my concern
Don't you want to visit him?
Don't you want to go to his house?
Mo Mo doesn't want to see me
I went to see her a few days ago
She told me not to turn up again
That's why you're
getting mad in the court?
Have you guys made it clear?
She didn't give me a chance
Alright, I'll bring you there
[Here comes the Easter egg...]
In girl's view, what should
a sexy boy look like?
The answer might surprise you
First, hair
Among the girls whom I've interviewed,
hair style is their main concern
Mind your hair style
Hair style is not only
important for actors
You hair look like a toilet lid
Handsome!
Which hair style do you like?
This one?
This is not suitable for you
I want it exactly the same
You need to have a perm then
A perm?
Yes
Direct Current or Alternating Current?
Of course Alternating Current
Otherwise, I can't do it
Right?
It's really not suitable for you
I'm okay
Okay
Thank you
Let me make you another hair style
It's alright
Get another one
You'll spoil my reputation
if you go out like this
You'll break my name
It's alright
No way
Let me make you another one
Come on
Very fast
I'll make a new hair style for you