[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
[Preview]
I'll miss you
[Episode 23]
Did you tell your parents?
I did
No
You
I won't tell if it's not confirmed
Moreover, I always
make my own decisions
I'll make the decision and tell them
What about your girlfriend?
You didn't tell her too?
I didn't tell her
Alright then
You'd better
watch out
Is there something you want to ask me?
If you were Si Tu Mo,
will you get mad if I didn't
tell you about the trip?
You should ask her
Okay, I remember
I'll see you in a minute
Bye
I left something
in Professor Jiang's office
I'll go back and get it
Come on, I'll take you to the lab
Let's go
Where are the others?
I don't know, they're here just now
You used to do experiments
in the new lab
Why did you suddenly
go back to the old lab?
The new project needs to be done here
And the old lab
is more in line with the
experimental environment
Take it off
Take off your white coat
I want to wear it for a long time
Nice looking?
Xiao Gu
Get the nitroglycerin for me
The nitroglycerin is explosive
But I can only
think of "Nitroglycerin",
which seems
a very professional word
What are these?
I have something to tell you
What's the matter?
In the last exam,
I did better than Zhou Lei
Congratulation!
So,
I'm qualified to join the
Heidelberg University exchange
in Germany with
Professor Jiang and my seniors
Congratulation!
What?
Germany?
How long?
More than 6 months
When?
The school is now
speeding up the visa for us
It may take two weeks if it's fast
The university
sent the invitation
at the end of last year
So a lot of the process is done
You knew it last year
and you're just telling me now
As I was not sure
that I'll be qualified
Maybe Zhou Lei can do
better than me in the exam
After all, he's been serious
And I'm busy falling in love with you
Do you mean
I disturb your studies?
I didn't mean it
Who else is going with you?
Professor Jiang,
Lu Jian Shi and Xie Yu Yin
Don't follow me
It takes so long
It's normal,
girls always slow
Must be Meng Lu busy with make up
She makes them late
Meng Lu is pretty by nature
She doesn't need to make up
Only Meng Lu likes to make up
Must be Wang Shan makes up for so long
Wang Shan is simple
Here they are
-Come on!
-Hurry up!
What makes you late?
We need to make up
Get up, why did you take my seat?
Go away
Fatty, why are you laughing?
You shouldn't laugh
Order my favorite food
Beef
Crayfish
Clean it for me
Alright
You're so beautiful today
Still angry?
All the best for our bright future!
Fatty, I tell you
Stop playing online games again
Battlegrounds, huh?
Stop playing it again
Watch out
I'm better than you
Stop it
I can swim faster than you
Cut it out!
You swim
Swimming
Hurry up!
Fu Pei
I told you not to drink so much
Alright, get up
Honey
Don't be angry
You shouldn't scold me
as I can drink so much
Don't do this again
Let's go, walk properly
Let's go
What are you doing?
I'm drunk and can't stand
Really?
But you were just fine
It just kicked in
It's just beer, not strong alcohol
Gu Wei Yi
Stand up
I don't know if you're really drunk
I'm really drunk
That's crap
Watch out
Sit down
I'll bring you a glass of water
I'm not thirsty
Are you sure you're drunk?
Yeah
I'll ask you for one last time
Are you really sure you're drunk?
No
Say it
What?
Why didn't you tell me
that you're going to Germany
with Xie Yu Yin?
I told you
I know it's my fault
I didn't tell you in the first place
I've never thought
about it before
Because I made
all the decisions myself
since I was small
I just need to inform them
after making the decision
This is the most efficient way
that I communicate with them
Because they didn't have time for you?
Because they didn't understand
what I'm going to do
But,
if you don't like it that way,
I'll change my style for you, okay?
You have such a good attitude
I shouldn't lose my temper with you
Do you want me to go to Germany?
Will you retreat
if I don't let you go?
Just do it as your planned
I'll wait for you
You should take the blood first
I'll get the vaccine number
for you
No rushing
Just do the checkup today
and do the vaccine next time
No way
We must get it done by today
Is it not easy for me to
accompany you to the hospital?
Your turn, let's go
What's wrong?
Why are you wearing sunglasses?
I don't want to see the color of blood
Alright
Let's go
You're going to get two vaccines
Put your left hand out
left hand
Don't be afraid
Alright
Done?
Yeah
Change to right hand
Help me press it
Can I have
my trainee nurse to do it for you?
It's okay
Come on
Push the needle
It's a little deep
Pull the needle, but don't pull it out
It's okay
Don't look, just look at me
How are you?
It's okay
Still feeling pain? Let me see
Not painful
Let's go
It's still bleeding
I'll get the cotton for you
Hello, aunt
Xiao Gu
How is your preparation
for going abroad?
Pretty good
Did Mo Mo mess with you?
No
It's almost there
I'm just calling you
to remind you that
"A little feeling"
"A little strong"
Mo Mo will be a bit different
when she feels reluctant
So you mustn't be angry with her
She will be always picking
about something with you
and make you annoyed
Don't move
Your glass will leave a mark
Your glasses are all over the place
"I want to go further with you"
Then, she'll start to be cold
and pretend that you
do not exist in this world
"I want to go further with you"
"It's all I miss"
"Shoulder to shoulder
with the touching moment"
"I want to go further with you"
"Despite the changing of world"
"Still holding each others hand"
"Let the time of a love song"
"witness our love forever"
In the end, she's going
to stick with you
Like a super glue
You just can't shake it off
Bring me along
Okay
Lie down
You can't go to Germany alone
You can't drink the German beer alone
You can't leave me alone
Something's going to happen
Bring me along
I'll be back soon
"Take up the courage
to make a promise"
It's okay
"I want to go further with you"
"The sky of glowing starlight"
"Melt me into your eyes"
"I want to go further with you"
"It's all I miss"
"Shoulder to shoulder
with the touching moment"
"I want to go further with you"
"Despite the changing of world"
"Still holding each others hand"
"Let the time of a love song"
"witness our love forever"
Wait
I want to go to KFC
Let's go
The Lucky Puppy Candy
Let's see that
Gu Wei Yi, there's ramen
Let's eat ramen
It's about time
I'm leaving
Give me a hug
I'll come back soon
I'll miss you
Si Tu Mo
Can you really live on your own?
I'm going back
Tell me when you get there
[6 months later]
Two of you are
the top staff for this round
Congratulation!
When the executive
gave us the lollipop,
she wanted us to stop making noise
about the name of the artwork
That's what the company means
Two of you have been screwing
with me for 6 months about it
I think,
you'd better make more
good designs
instead of messing around
Make more good designs
and let you put your name on, huh?
We don't need this
We need our own signature
If you guys
keep such attitude,
I think our company
may not be suitable
for your future development
You're going to fire us, huh?
I didn't mean it
You guys seemed
to have a big objection on the
company's arrangement
As your direct leader,
I just give you my advice
Okay
I'll resign
I don't want my position
in the company
to be controlled by people like you
So, I'll quit
I'll quit too
Jie Er, you...
Let's go
[Resignation Letter]
"Reason: The leader
is too ugly, so I'll quit"
Fu Pei
Where's Chen Xiao Xi?
You didn't pay the salary to her
for 2 months continuously
Of course she's not coming
That's right
Salary
Yes, salary
Stop!
How was the dealing with the bank?
Are they willing to offer us a loan?
The bank
is not opened
We can't go on like this
Although you have only one employee
But we can't operate
without money
At least, you must pay
the salary on time to Chen Xiao Xi
I only owed her for two months salary
But you just run
the company for 6 months
And
When are you going
to hire an accountant?
You can't wait for me to come back
and help you during my break
I'll be back to school soon
Why not?
You're my girlfriend
You're the lady boss here, why not?
It will cause a bad debt if
you leave the account behind
It's not conducive to
the company's development
Forget it
I used to rush you every day
I don't feel like your girlfriend
But look like your mom
Now you know, huh?
You're back
What are you taking from the company?
I just resigned
Resign?
It's my belonging in the company
I got it back today
I thought you did a good job
Why did you resign?
You will not understand
even if I tell you
Can't I understand Chinese?
Or you're not talking in Chinese?
Why do you always say
I don't understand?
I got a headache
I'm going to bed for a while
You...
Your mom's here
Yes
Didn't you call her
to take care of me?
She's cleaning in the living room
She wants to sterilize it
She should bring you
to the hospital first
I just have a cold
I just need to take a break
Wear more cloth at home
Si Tu Mo
What's wrong?
Okay
My mom is calling me,
I have to go out for a while
Mom, I don't drink Chinese medicine
It's not Chinese medicine
I cooked the walnut soup for you
Your grandmother said,
it's effective to heal a cold
I couldn't find the mug
you often use just now
So I took a bowl
Drink it while it's still hot
You'll be recovered after this
Finished, I'll go and
clean up my things
Wait
Well
I need to talk to you
Mo Mo
How's your German visa going?
It's passed
They rejected me before
as they suspected
I'm going to migrate
Then, Gu Wei Yi planned
an itinerary of Germany trip for me
And the application is passed
Xiao Gu is really awesome
I've never thought a scientist
could in charge of a visa too
Mom
What are you trying to say?
I just want to ask you
When are you two going to marry?
Why are you asking me again?
Wait
What do you mean by asking again?
It's been more than 6 months
Xiao Gu went to Germany
I can understand that you're not able
to get your visa to Germany
But it's been such a long time
Did he ever think
want to come back and see you?
Don't you feel panic?
We keep in touch every day
Why should I panic for?
Don't pretend
I don't want to talk,
I have a headache
I don't want to talk to you either
You're back
What are you doing?
Finding clothes and going out
Si Tu Mo
What's wrong?
Your mother said anything to you?
Nothing
I just don't know which dress to wear
Alright then
Now
Do you believe that
I have a girlfriend?
I don't care
She's in China
I can be your girlfriend here
I won't tell her
Stop bothering me
Anna
Did you turn her down again?
You're so cool, aren't you?
She's the professor's daughter
You didn't give any face to her
Why are you so anxious?
It's not your daughter
To get a daughter,
I surely need time and space
I don't want to go out today
Why?
My girlfriend's sick
She might contact me at anytime
You may go out
and find a place to sit down
and drink a cup of coffee
while waiting for her
I just bought a flight
ticket to go back
I'm broke
That's why you don't eat
It's up to you
You will be awkward anyway
Who knows?
What are you guys talking about?
I love you
I love you very much
You're so sweet
You're the most beautiful girl
I've ever seen in my life
Really?
Are you kidding me?
No, I'm sure
Please have a seat
Director Sha Sha will
come down in a minute
You sit here for a while
I'm going out to answer a call
Wei Wei
Ye Tian
Did you hear that
Si Tu Mo has resigned?
Of course, it's all spread
But the reason of her
resignation is interesting
If I were Sha Sha,
I'll apply leave too
Shame on her! How could she do that?
She took the winning
design of her staff
and put it under her name
And the resignation letter
directly kept her mouth shut
I really want to upload
the letter to the Internet
Stop talking about her
Let's go to the photocopy room
Come on
What are you doing?
Circle is out of battery
I want to recharge it
I'm bringing you a glass of water
Why are you sitting on the floor?
It's cold
You just caught a cold
Quickly get up
Get up
What is this?
I don't know
Well
Only the people like your father
who always hide private money
could think of that place
I couldn't think of it
Not you?
That's...
-Gu Wei Yi
-Xiao Gu
The scientist's brain is so strange
I'm done
The abnormality of the
scientist influenced you, huh?
You...
What are you doing?
Why are you packing up the thing?
I'll go to Gu Wei Yi
Gu Wei...
He's in Germany
You're still sick
Don't be crazy
You may go there when you're recovered
I'm going to force him to marry me
Go away
Stop packing it
I'm going to Germany instead of outing
You can eat it later
Bring it along
Alright
Let's go
Shall we
give him a call?
You can't suddenly go there
Why do you want to call him?
What if he runs away
from me after that?
It's impossible
He's scientist
He does everything thoroughly
with plans
What about beyond the plan?
Let's go
Attack him
when he's unprepared
Go!
Come on
Fu Pei, I'm Gu Wei Yi
Hey bro
Before you introduce yourself,
can you check out the current time
of Beijing first?
I couldn't
contact Si Tu Mo for almost one day
Have you and Wang Shan been
in touch with her these few days?
Yes, she said she was busy
Her mother is taking
care of her, right?
Her mum didn't pick up my call
Of course
It's 2 am in Beijing right now
I'm tired, bye
Hey scientist, what's going on?
I'm playing games
Your girlfriend is sleeping on my bed
That's your girlfriend
I'm going to play games
Don't disturb me
My girlfriend?
Si Tu Mo
"The difficulties in the
books aren't a problem"
"All the puzzles come with axiom"
"I thought I have the perfect logic"
"Now I find no solution"
"That's how you came into my heart"
"Sweet and childish"
"Nothing can describe your smile"
"You bring me courage"
"Put your head on my shoulder"
"You are my unknown world"
"Untie the knot of silence for you"
"You'll never be timid"
Si Tu Mo
How are you?
Fine, thank you. And you?
"The youth marks my
heartbeat and feeling"
"Our love is passionate"
"Never fade"
Xiao Yi
Well
I'm just asking
if you see Si Tu Mo
She's with me now
She's with you?
Are you guys alright?
I just want to ask
When are you guys
going to settle down?
I'm planning it
Planning it?
Are you saying
that you're getting married soon?
I'll hang up first
"To my daughter: Good luck
and come back with a wedding!"
Si Tu Mo
Are you here for a wedding?
Yeah
really
Mom, let me sleep for a while
But I've already bought my ticket
to marry you there
But I love you
I love someone else, please leave
I want to see your girlfriend
It's none of your business
I'm his girlfriend
[Here comes the Easter egg...]
[Brainstorming]
Gu Wei Yi
We'll be graduated after 2 months
Let's travel to Tibet
As long as you like it,
we can go wherever you want to
It's hard to book
the train ticket
Don't worry
The APP can make it
Advance purchase 63 days
with auto ticket-grabber
I'm willing to go
anywhere with you
Me too
"Advance purchase 63 days by APP"
Gu Wei Yi
Cool man
Why are you wearing sunglasses?
You...