[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
[Preview]
What is your feeling with Si Tu Mo?
It has nothing to do with you
But it's very important to me
[Episode 8]
With the sea in my heart,
everywhere can be Maldives
I had a cat before
It liked to catch cockroaches
One day, after I woke up from a nap,
it put more than 10
cockroaches in front of me
and walked away proudly
Mine too
It gave me dead rats
Look similar?
Exactly
So beautiful
Meng Lu, your boyfriend is so charming
"I wish to give you all my good"
"Do you know?"
"You are very important to me"
"I appreciate every
moment we're together"
"Together we wait for the sunrise"
"Your breath became my heartbeat"
"I want to build a castle"
"with the smell of the ocean"
"Running barefoot at the beach with you"
I want to ask you something
Alright
What is your relationship
with Wang Shan?
Mo Mo wants you to ask me?
No
Why did you ask?
I want to know your feeling with Si Tu Mo
It has nothing to do with you
But it's very important to me
Why?
She is not the type
you nerds like
You're not going to
fall out with me for her, are you?
You should
be thankful with these food
Quickly dig in
Who stole my sausage?
Who?
Don't know
Meng Lu
Mo Mo
Is it you?
I'll give you two back
No way
Three
Fine
Okay, three
Is it worthy you do that for a girl
who stole the sausage?
It's worthy
Are you okay?
I'm okay
I'll wash it with cold water
Go
Take a look at him
"Get myself in trouble"
"The spine at your mouth"
"Know well of your own shadow"
Are you alright?
I'm okay
Apply the medicine
You can't just
leave the wound behind
It's so serious
If there's a blister,
we should see how big it is
If it's big, you should poke it,
squeeze the water before applying the medicine
If it's small, it will recover itself
When we're at Gu Wei Yi's house...
I knew you were drunk
and mistook me for someone else
I'm so sorry
Buy me a meal as an apology
Are you falling in love with...
Are you dreaming?
I heard it from Mo Mo
that you always treat her luxury meals
So I want to steal a meal from you
Forget it
If you really feel sorry to me,
you should pass the CET-4
I don't want to see you anymore
Alright
I will buy you a luxury meal
Promise?
I'll keep my promise
If you're into someone for a long time,
but you didn't tell her because
you're afraid of losing her
Now, you will really lose her
if you keep hiding your feeling
What will you do?
If it were me,
I would let her know
What if you lose her after that?
Then I'll end it smartly
and start a new relationship
I have never thought
you are so experienced
Why should we move the tents?
The tents are too close to the sea
It's windy and the tide will be in
Moreover, we didn't drop any anchor
It's unsafe for lack of grip
What about here?
Okay
I will set it here
Alright
Si Tu Mo
Pull it
Slowly! What if I fall down?
Get up again
Are you finished?
Drop the anchor
How? Do we have a hammer?
Use your internal strength
It's not funny
I know who has it, wait for a while
How did you know I brought the heels?
Didn't you change it
in the car for selfie?
Hit it lightly, it's very expensive
What's wrong?
I couldn't sleep and came out for a walk
What are you holding?
A selfie stick
Just trying it
What's wrong?
Aren't you taking a photo?
Come on
Gu Wei Yi
What?
Are you hungry?
I'm starving
Any left over foods?
I guess no
I'm hungry
Let's go
Where to?
To get you some food
Can you catch it?
Sure
My god, you caught it!
A crab and it's still alive
Let me see
My goodness
Let me try
Can I?
What's that?
Quickly catch it
What was that?
A mantis prawn
You are so annoying
The prawn is alive too
How to grill this with no fire?
I wanted to try drilling wood for fire for a long time
Are you serious?
You tell me
So how to grill it?
As a nerd
what idea can you think of?
What a good smell!
Any salt with you?
It will be delicious with some salt
What's this?
Sea water
Are you crazy? Is that edible?
The salt inside the
sea water was about 3.5%
It means
there's 35g of salt
out of 1000g sea water
Moreover,
the temperature of
an open fire is 700 degrees
So,
nothing can stay alive
Thanks to a scientist like you
You granted whatever I requested
You are my Doraemon
Let's eat
It's hot, be careful
Have some
What a nicely grilled prawn!
Nice smell
But we have only one
Take it
Take it, I don't like it
Why?
Allergy
and it looked like a giant cockroach
It sounds like sour grapes
If you don't want it
I'll throw it away
I want it
Take this
Mo Mo, we'll leave first
Bye
Drive safe
You hand was hurt
We don't want to risk our life with you
It doesn't matter
Gu Wei Yi, you drive the car
You'll be my navigator
Okay
Girls are weak in sense of direction
Let me help you
What did you say?
Say it again
Nothing
I'm weak in sense of direction
Turn left at the junction in front
There is no junction in front
Really?
Did I get it wrong?
Impossible
You are right, we're not there yet
Don't get nervous
Alright
Drink some water?
No, thanks
"Arrived the destination"
Si Tu Mo
Someone is waiting for you
Is my mother here?
It's it
Get back to work
Why don't you give it a name
and take it for a walk everyday?
Giving it a name is a good idea
Then give it one
I got it
What?
Circle
Circle fits its look, doesn't it?
Alright, thank you, bye
Hello
I'm the new intern
I'm here to report for duty
Please follow me
Come in
Director Sha Sha
I'm the new intern, Si Tu Mo
The HR Dept. told me to report to you
Hello, welcome to our department
Thank you
Li Na, come in for a while
Director
Li Na is our Creative Executive Director
Hello, I'm the new intern, Si Tu Mo
Hello, I'm Li Na, come with me
Alright
This is your seat
He is the Art Editor, Ain
New colleague, Mo Mo
Hello
I have done the introduction
You may report to the HR
and help me get a sample
of roll-up banner downstairs
Alright
What a...
So sorry
Be careful
Will you get together with Fu Pei
after graduation?
Xu Jie Er
It's you!
Why are you carrying things here?
I'm an intern here
So am I
Which department are you in?
Creative Department No.4
Me too
Could you lead me the way?
Sure
Let's go
Let me help you
When did you report?
I just arrived
So did I
Is it heavy?
It's okay
Come in
Director,she is the new intern, Xu Jie Er
You are Jie Er?
Welcome
Mo Mo, you may leave now
How has Mr. Xu been?
Haven't seen him for a long time
He is fine
Let's go
Dear all
From today onward,
we're back to the new campus
Are you clear with the duty
I have just given to you?
Yes
Professor, you didn't give me any duty
You should focus
on your thesis of your Master Degree
But I want to join the experiment
The most important thing
is to select the topic of thesis
You will run out of time
It has no conflict between
the thesis and the experiment
Have you done the calculation
that I gave you the other day?
Not yet
Xie Yu Yin
Human has his limited energy
Now
you should focus on the thesis
But I really want to join the experiment
I have been doing it
since undergraduate
I can't accept that
you want me to stop
I don't mean to stop you,
but just afraid that
you may slow down the experiment
Can I join it
once I have done the calculation?
Alright
Pass up the calculation by tomorrow
Tomorrow?
Even the professor can't do it himself
No problem
Listen
I want a calculation without any error
Professor Jiang, I want to ask something
The experiment...
How far have you done the calculation?
Don't you need to pass up by tomorrow?
I just said it in anger
It's impossible to get it done
It can be done if we work together
Do you know how to do it?
Of course
Hello
Hello, we have put your parcel
in the mail box
It's fresh food
Please get it as soon as possible
Okay
Mo Mo
Why are you here?
To pick you up from work
Are you crazy?
Let me buy you dinner
No, thanks, I'm busy
Are you still angry with me?
What I have done to Wang Shan
was just a misunderstanding
It has nothing to do with me
I want to go back now
Mo Mo
Fu Pei
It's been a long time
How are you?
You two still together?
No
You two work together?
Why didn't you tell me?
We didn't know until today
Right?
I leave first
Fu Pei
Which way are you going?
That way
So am I. Let's go together
Alright
Let's go
Dad
I'll go to your place tomorrow
Have lunch with me
I don't have time
The signal is poor here, I'll hang up
Your dad?
I still can remember
what he had done to us
although it's been so many years
He made us so scared
that we broke up the next day
Let's go
Hello
Hello, mom
What did you send to me?
I have made you
some sauced beef
You and Xiao Gu may have it with rice
What rice?
We don't know how to cook
I knew it
That's why I made you the sauced beef
Xiao Gu can have it with beer
So troublesome
No trouble at all
Why should I take care of him?
I'm tired too
Alright
Are you really my mum?
Hello
Why aren't you back yet?
I'll stay at the lab tonight
You should tell me earlier
Okay, I will tell you next time
That's all, bye
It's not my concern
Shall we take a rest and grab a bite?
It's okay, let's hurry up finish it
Circle
Your dad is not coming back,
don't you care?
"Low power"
"Turning off"
Thank you
I take a nap first
She made it
It's impossible
I think so too
Can I take part in the experiment?
Wait
Did you simply make up the data
to fool me?
Professor!
Let me pick a few and
do the calculation myself
Gu Wei Yi, Zhou Lei
Help me do it
Alright
Gu Wei Yi
You're disrespectful recently
Look at your senior
She has done such difficult
calculation in a night
How about you?
You're sleeping here
Professor, Gu Wei Yi...
See, she is trying to protect you
Don't you feel ashamed?
No, he doesn't
Because he did two thirds of these
What?
Yes, I did it, is the result wrong?
Impossible
An undergraduate can't do this
Professor, Xia Yu Yin is telling lies
just to protect him
It might be possible
if it was Gu Wei Yi
Then...
Professor, can you ask him
to do it in front of me?
Zhou Lei
only agrees with it
after he gets stricken down by Gu Wei Yi
The fighting of two geniuses
I feel pity for Zhou Lei
to get hurt every time
Professor
Can I take part in the experiment?
Forget about it
It was done by Gu Wei Yi
Not you
You said you wanted accurate results
You never specify who to calculate it
Can you really carry on?
Yes
Professor, can I stop?
I want to go back to sleep
Ask if Zhou Lei agrees
Why isn't he back yet?
That's all
Alright
Please wait for a while
The food here is delicious
Michelin 3 Stars
A very famous restaurant
Thanks a lot, Director Fu
Not Director Fu
You should call me Boss
You are so funny
Dad
Here you come
Sit down
Why didn't you pick up my call?
I put it in the silent mode
My son, Fu Pei
A student of Management
in Southern University
Southern University?
Must be a top student
Of course
Son, this is my new assistant
You may call her Aunt Ling Ling
Why are you here?
Where is mom?
I came here on business
Why would I bring her?
She can't help me in business
Is that so?
Mind your attitude
What major are you taking?
Are you about to graduate?
This year
An elder is asking you,
answer it properly
How did I teach you?
It doesn't matter
She's not my elder
She is about my age
But you call her my elder
How could you say it?
Director Fu
My schoolmate knew that
I'm here on business
and she wants to meet me
Perhaps, I shall leave first
Enjoy the meal
Come with me
Now you've grown up
Is this what you've learnt
from the university?
Do you think no one can bother you
after you get into the university?
Let me tell you
Don't dream of it
You are to listen to me
as long as you are my son
You're just like your mother
You two are ungrateful
Don't mention my mom
Why not?
Your mother is not a good person
She left you alone
when you're small
It's because you were messing about
So what?
She was the one who left you
Do you think she
came back for your sake?
You are wrong
All she wants is my money
I have plenty of money
If you don't have money,
no one will stay by your side
No one will care about you
I tell you
No one
What's that look?
How dare you?
There will be!
Gu Wei Yi
Is he dead?
What are you doing?
I'm calling you to eat the sauced beef
Come on
Has the ghost come out?
Has it?
Has it come out?
Why did you watch it
since you're scared?
Why did you watch it since
you're not scared?
Finished
I sliced the meat, so you wash the plate
You finished so fast
There is more in the fridge
Go get it
Who is it?
Who will come during mid night?
What are you doing?
Let me open it
Just to open the door
Why do you bring the knife?
A girl shouldn't open
the door at night
Here comes the Easter egg
Si Tu Mo
What's wrong?
I know the pattern
password of your phone
How do you know?
You drew it many times in front of me
I hope you change it to a more complicated one
Alright
By the way
Send me the photos we took at the beach
Alright