[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
[Preview]
Do you think I'm cute?
Cute
So cute
[Episode 13]
We meet again
What a coincidence!
Yes
There's something that I'd like to ask
Do you think...
Do you think there's a pure friendship
between a man and a woman?
You're staying with Gu Wei Yi,
but you two are not a couple
So I'm wondering about it
Or you guys...
No
We're just friends
But when a man stays with a woman,
you might...
Absolutely no
Senior
Why did you ask?
Are you into Gu Wei Yi?
That's right
Oh yeah
He said he'll come for lunch with me
Why didn't he come?
I thought he's busy with the
experiments in the old campus
We moved here long time
ago, didn't he tell you?
No
Maybe he thinks I'm not important...
Maybe he thinks it's not important
and he doesn't need to tell me
Yeah, as you're not
helping in the experiments
Gu Wei Yi
Let me call him
You're so slow, don't eat
You...
I haven't taken my lunch yet
I'll buy you a treat
Where's Si Tu Mo?
Let's dig in
What's happened?
Let's eat outside
Didn't you want to eat outside?
What's happened?
The food at the canteen was suck
You seem like trying to run away
I'll buy you a treat outside
Want to go?
Sure
Let's go
Wait
I need to send the meal box to Ke
Let me call him to get it himself
What?
My mobile phone
I left it at the canteen
As well as my meal card
I'll kill you if my phone goes missing
No need, I'll commit suicide myself
Your phone is with you, huh?
Hello
Your friend's mobile phone and
your meal card are with me
I'll go and see you now
I have something urgent in the lab
See you in the lab
Okay
Gu Wei Yi is keeping it
and he's back to the lab
Let's see him after lunch
I've promised Ke to go for a movie
Help me to keep the phone in the dorm
Okay
Let's go for lunch
I must have something expensive
No way
I have no money
Gu...
How? Is it cute?
It's so cute
How could you let
Professor Jiang to chase it out?
Don't bring me into this
Do you think I'm cute?
I'll come to you if you don't response
Okay
Cute
Are you Gu Wei Yi's friend?
Professor Jiang
Are you looking for him?
I want to get something from him
Where's he?
I don't know
I'm here
What are you doing there?
Thinking of something
Thinking?
Alright
Take your time
Have you been waiting long?
Just arrived
Take it
Thank you, I'm leaving
Where are you going?
Dorm
What time will you go home?
I don't know
I'll wait you, let's go back together
I don't want to disturb you
It's alright
-I...
-I'm not alright
What's wrong again?
Jealous again?
I didn't do anything
Class
Let's call it a day
It's about time
Okay
Professor, I'm leaving first
See you
Zhou Lei
Wait a moment
Stay here
Please clean the lab
thoroughly
Professor Jiang
Why me?
How dare you ask?
Your kitten made
the whole lab dirty
Didn't you see it?
You must clean it up
I...
Let me clean it
Professor Jiang
He offered himself to clean it
Aren't you ashamed?
Look at Gu Wei Yi
and look at yourself
Oh, no!
Are you going to give
him an extra lesson?
Stay here for the extra lesson then
Take your time
Say it
What's your trick?
I'm waiting for someone
Who?
Okay
You may clean it yourself
I'm leaving first
Take your time
Love can make ones do everything
I'm leaving, take your time!
Bye
Xiao Gu
What brings you here?
I'm waiting for someone
Waiting for someone?
Call her and ask her to come down
She didn't pick up the call
Whom are you looking for?
Let me bring her
It's alright
I'll wait for a while here
Now you're here, don't be ashamed
Are you waiting for her?
Is she the girl you
mentioned on that day?
No
It creeps me out
Both of them are a lovely couple
You can't make them apart
They're a couple?
You know them?
The guy waits for her everyday
They used to bring many books along
when they went out
They study even in love
I have set hope on them
Stop!
This is girl's dorm.
What are you doing here?
I left something in the dorm
Call her and let her bring it to you
That's crap!
Remember to miss me
Gu Wei Yi
What brings you here?
Waiting for Si Tu Mo
Sorry for that day
That day?
What's that?
What he meant?
The day we went to Mo Mo's house
and cooked porridge for him
You don't have to be afraid
You helped him, didn't you?
He thought I helped you to get Mo Mo
He's angry with me
You really tried to bring us together
It's all my fault
Sorry
I accept your apology
Fu Pei
We need to talk
We shall go for a fight
because of the previous incident
Did you tell Si Tu Mo
about you and Wang Shan?
We have made it clear
You meant...
Gu Wei Yi
I seldom see you in the look
We've been living together
in the dorm for 4 years
You only look normal today
Answer my question
We have made it clear
She doesn't like me
I don't like her too
We're apart
She could
get into
someone else
I could get into Wang Shan too
We can't stop each other
Really?
Of course
Gu Wei Yi
You should back up me
I was hurt by Mo Mo
and it left a shadow in my heart
Why are you laughing?
You snatched my girlfriend
You're such a bad boy
You know?
Was she your girlfriend at that time?
Almost
I feel like give you a whack
Let's fight
Don't call her Mo Mo again
if I beat you down
Are you getting crazy today?
Are you calling me?
Why didn't you pick up the call?
I was in the bathroom and my
phone was in the living room
You're home?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why should I?
Alright, bye
She off the phone, huh?
Mo Mo is not easy to be handled
Alright
Si Tu Mo
I won't call her Mo Mo again
Insane
Do you think I'm cute?
Cute
So cute
"Not cute at all"
You have the keys, right?
Can't you hear it?
It's a song
No
Listen
"If I had a wand"
"I can be big, small and pretty"
"I want to get a house which full"
"with comics and chocolates"
"If I had a machine cat"
"I'll call it Doraemon"
"A hopter and time tunnel
can bring us to everywhere"
Stop pressing it
Is the juice nice?
Try to drink more
than 10 bottles and see
Do you want to drink it with a mug?
I did use a mug
Si Tu Mo
What's wrong?
Are't you working in
an adverstising company?
Why did you only look into
the flavour?
What are you looking at?
Show you something magic
No, thanks
Take a look
Come on
The orange juice under zoom 2000X
What is this? Why is it moving?
Microorganism?
Let me see
Not microorganism
It's Brownian motion
Your cutie suddenly appears
Do you think I'm cute?
I'll come to you
if you don't response
Get back to your room
You are disturbing me
For you
What's this?
Take a look
I don't want it
This is out of print
Where did he get it?
I love it
Gu Wei Yi
Finally, you bring it back
Let me try it
Let me see
Gu Wei Yi
You're staying outside
So?
You are the one
who stays outside among us
Now we have an honour task
for you
I'm not interested
Professor Jiang doesn't allow me
to bring the kitten into the lab
He's extremely strict these few days
Are you willing to
see the kitten homeless?
Yes, I'm
What an emotionless killer!
We received the message
from the client yesterday
They have changed their spokesman
to a new artist
His name is...
Lin Zhi Cun
Yes, Lin Zhi Cun
Jie Er
Find out his information
and sort it out
Okay
So, we should change
our thinking as well
Don't think he's famous like super star
Zhao Xue Yu
Don't think about
the difficulty of shooting
Focus on the creativity
Li Na
Get several proposals
done in these few days
Okay
One more thing
There's a graphic
design competition recently
We have distributed the message in OA
You may look into it
if you're interested
Gu Wei Yi
What brings you here?
Buying books
The perspective of advertising?
What now?
Are you sitting for advertising?
I just read it for fun
For fun?
I don't think so
Let me think about it
Who works in an advertising company?
I knew
I'm leaving
Don't go
I haven't finished
Take your time, I'll walk around there
Why did you buy the book?
Si Tu Mo always gets mad
without reason recently
I'm wondering if it's related to her job
What's wrong with you?
You said you stop...
I feel happy for you
Finally, you're growing up
and know how to take your initiative
Do you think you can
find the answer from the book?
So?
Only several conditions
will make a girl mad
Can't eat or sleep well
and the menstruation pain
I don't think so
Well...
Tell me what happened recently
Lin Zhi Cun is quite handsome
Really?
Send me the picture
I'll send it to the chat group
Okay
Mo Mo, have a look
Is he good-looking?
Look at it
Not bad
Look at his mouth
Do you want to kiss him?
No
You're loyal to Fu Pei
Fu Pei and I are not...
What?
We're not a couple
Who is your boyfriend then?
Look at your face
Tell me!
Get back to your seat
No way
See ya
Are you in love?
No
Liar
Your face told me that you're in love
Or you met
a flirt?
Cute
So cute
This is what happened recently
That means
Si Tu Mo was angry
because of your senior
it's easy
She gets jealous
Professor Jiang told me the same too
But the most recent,
she was angry outside of the lab
My senior wasn't there at that time
Are you sure?
Think about it again
Was she there?
Gosh!
She was in the room next to the stairs
She's playing with the kitten
I guess she was jealous
with our conversation
What a smart boy!
I know Si Tu Mo very well
Come to me
if you have any problem
I'll be your counselor
So, you'll get Si Tu Mo easily
You can't manage to get her, right?
Are you guys still chatting?
Just finished
Let's go
Let's go for a movie
Don't bother the single man
See you
Senior
Don't set hope on Gu Wei Yi
He refused to help
Cold-blooded
Gu Wei Yi, can't you really...
Senior
Don't beg him
No need
When he finds his conscience back,
he'll be in tears of pain
and regret
Give it to me
I'll take care of it
No way
Cut it out! He just agreed
Give the kitten to him
He refused to take care of it before
Why should I give it to him?
I tell you
Even if the kitten and I are homeless
or starve to death,
we won't beg him
What if I put the kitten
at the animal shelter
and bring it back after 2 days?
Will they allow it?
Call and ask them
Okay
Zhou Lei
Give it to me
I really want it
No way
What do you want me to do?
Beg me
I beg you
Gu Wei Yi
You begged me readily
I don't feel satisfied at all
Put it in my bag
Look
It's funny
Let me chat him first
That's right
The guy is handsome
Really
He's carrying a kitten
He must be a kind man
Try to chat him
-It's not appropriate
-Go!
Go ahead
Okay
Hello
The kitten is cute
I wanted to get a kitten for so long
Mew...
It's not mine
Where did you buy the bag?
I don't know
Could I add you in WeChat?
Look
Where did you get it?
I'll tell you later
Let's go home
All the handsome guys have a girlfriend
Where did you get it?
You want to raise a kitten?
It's Zhou Lei's kitten
He needs my help for several days
Cute?
Not bad
My senior said, this is
the cutest stage of a kitten
Really?
Wait, the kitten will have a faint
Alright
I'll teach you a secret
way from Si Tu Mo
A girl can't stop a sticker
Stick on her
Follow wherever she goes
What's wrong?
I don't know what to do with the kitten
Why did you
bring it back then?
Zhou Lei said, the rules
of the dorm is strict recently
He has nowhere for it
My senior stays in the dorm too
Please take care of it
Why should I?
I don't like kitten
Why did you bring it back then?
Because someone got it wrong
When we're in the
room next to the stairs,
I meant the kitten was cute,
not my senior
Actually...
Why do you want to
come for a movie suddenly?
I bought the tickets
We made a deal before
We wanted to make a date,
have a meal and go for a movie
I wanted to date you out
I won't let you out
I have an allergy to kitten
Stop mewing
I won't fall for that
Come out yourself
What's wrong?
I have an allergy
Really?
Even mantis prawn and kitten
You're really too much
I'm serious
I'll bring it into my room
So cute
"Arrived the destination"
Come on!
I want to kiss you
Good
I like you the most
Si Tu Ding Dang is so cute
Like your name?
Ding Dang
I'm calling you Si Tu Ding Dang, okay?
So good
Hello
Si Tu Mo is staying in the room
and I can't stick on her
What?
Go to her room
She has a cat there
Cat?
Lure her out then
I'm in a movie, bye!
What's wrong?
It's okay
Let's go out and let it stay in the room
You may go out yourself
We don't have to go with you
I want to play with it
Close the door when you go out
Don't let it out
Have some water
Si Tu Mo
Anything?
Come out for a while
I'm playing with Si Tu Ding Dang
It will go out if I open the door
Who?
Si Tu Ding Dang
I gave it the name
Why did you call me?
Let's clean the house
It's night time now
The house full with cat hair
Let Circle clean it
Circle is tired
It needs rest
I'm tired too
I need rest
"A cat likes to bath
will have healthy skin"
"Stay away from the fleas
and so much bubble"
"Si Tu Ding Dang is pretty"
Don't be afraid, Ding Dang
I'll bath you
Don't be afraid of water
Good boy
Did it hurt you?
No
It's afraid of water
So, it screamed when
I put it into the water
What's this?
Mosquito bite, I scratched it myself
Aren't you having an allergy?
Sit down
Step back
Don't be angry
It didn't hurt you purposely
I'll come to you if you're angry
I'm not angry
Don't come near
Ding Dang wants to eat dried fish
I have only cat food
No, dried fish
Okay, I'll buy for you
Ding Dang wants to thank you
It wants to give you a kiss
What are you doing?
Don't be ashamed
Come on
Step back
What if I don't?
What do you want to do?
Huh?
I'll kiss you then
You did it before
When you're drunk...
I'm just kidding
Don't be serious
[Here comes the Easter egg]
[Brainstorming]
Where can we book a reasonable hotel?
Gu Wei Yi, do it
Too many options
It's hard
but reasonable
The peak is affected by
the supply and demand,
pricing will up 20%
Third party promotion
covers the price increase
or gets a lower price
It's done
Apply VIP membership
can get 20% off and above
It's worth
What a science freak!
[Download APP to get 20% off and above]