[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
[Preview]
What are you doing?
[Episode 7]
Fu Pei, you are drunk
Mo Mo
Mo Mo, I'm not...
Shan Shan
Have a safe journey
Mo Mo
We are not...
You should go back
Let's go back
Leave it, I'll take the mop
Every product of glass will have
a caution sticker on the packing
But, not everyone
will take caution on it
They'll think
it won't be broken easily
It's alright
It's all okay in the past
However, when they open the packing,
they will find it
broken
What to do?
We have to throw it away
Si Tu Mo
What's wrong?
You can't leave
Why?
Clean up everything first
I have cleaned it up
Remove the things on the wall
The paint will be ruined if I remove it
Why did you stick it since you knew it?
I will remove it
Fix the wall before you leave
It looks perfect
Alright?
I'm leaving
Wait
What again?
The drain is clogged
So?
It is alright
If the previous drainage volume
can reach 1.2 liter per second
It is at most
0.6 liter per second now
Then?
Why should I clean it?
Alright, I know my hair is long
I'll get the plumber
I'm leaving
Wait
What again?
It's too late now
I can only get the plumber tomorrow
But I won't be around tomorrow
Can you wait for the plumber here?
Okay
I'll cook some noodles, do you want it?
Yes
Where's the instant
noodles in the fridge?
I ate it
I'll go and buy
What brands do you prefer?
Anything
Anything else to buy?
Eggs?
I'll go with you
Thanks
Thank you
We have bought it all, right?
Yes
Young man
Try some
Aunt
I don't like sweet
It's not sweet at all
Let me try, aunt
Delicious
Good taste, right?
Let's buy one
Try some
Buy it?
Give me one
Alright
Where is he?
A graduate is always
courteous and knows how to enjoy life
I'll put
the machine here
Any after-sales issue,
you can look for me
Anything else you need?
This robot is good
It can
manage the 3 machines
Besides, it can manage all
the AI household machines
-in your house
-Gu Wei Yi
Look at this
You took all of these?
What's wrong?
Put it back, it's expensive
I can afford it
No...Young lady
Actually
It can not only manage
all the AI household machines,
but also has a special function
It has a mimic emotional function
It would chat with you
when you are bored
It can chat with me
I can do that as well, let's go
Wait, young man
I know that
you love your girlfriend very much
All our robots
are very useful
They can do the housework for you
You must buy them if you
really love your girlfriend
Young lady
I know
you don't want your boyfriend
to spend the money
We are not a couple
Why did you care so much of him then?
Let's just buy one
Okay
Pay it yourself
Young man
You shall see this AI robot
and the machine for window cleaning
Sir, we're doing a promotion
Every RMB200 spent will get a free bag
Your bill is about RMB190
We bought a sweeping robot
Is it still yet to RMB200?
So sorry
The electronic item won't be counted in
You may buy a box of chewing gum
in order to get the bag
I'll take one
What are you doing?
Continue your research
I'll go to bed
Who is it?
The robot knocked onto it
[Drain clogged; her mom won't
let her move out; closer to company...]
[Horror film; ghost at home;
house on fire; thief breaks in]
When will the plumber come?
Very soon
You said you had things to do
Why are you still here?
I'll go soon
Are you going back to the dorm?
Of course
I suggest you stay here
Why?
First it is near to the company
that you went for interview
You can even walk to work
But I'm not sure if I'm shortlisted
Second, the checking of
the uni is strict recently
The uni
is far away
Once the internship starts,
you have to consider it
Third, your mother has paid
the rental for a year to my mom
Enough until your graduation
My mum will return the money to her
if you are not staying here
But, I don't know
if your mother will give you money
to rent another house
Mr. Gu, right? This is for you
Thanks
[Contract: Si Tu Mo promises not to move out]
I guess your mother
will not pay for your new rental
Why?
I'll stay here until the completion of
the experiment at the old campus
Then I'll move back to the uni
Why do you want me to stay here?
I'm afraid of your mother
I understand you
I got it
Hello, did you call for drain cleaning?
Yes, please come with me
Okay
I'll be here
You can leave now
I go back first
You didn't come back last night
Tell me
You stayed at Gu Wei Yi's house?
I have told you, right?
Don't pretend you don't know.
Go on
Mo Mo
How come Niu Niu's eyebrow
can't fit in any of the colors?
Will it be fine if you draw it thicker?
Thicker?
She will then become Crayon Shinchan
Let me try it
No way
Niu Niu
-Help me!
-No way
Don't run, Niu Niu
Help!
Thicker will be nicer
Believe me
No way
Don't move, I'm coming
I don't...
Niu Niu
Don't run, Niu Niu
Don't run
Help me! Shan Shan
You're back
Yes
Hello
Hello, are you Si Tu Mo?
Yes, I am
I'm calling from Ori Advertising
I'm pleased to inform you that
you have passed the interview and test
Really?
Yes
Thank you very much
Bye
Mo Mo
What happened to you and Shan Shan?
Nothing
Are you sure?
Really nothing
Oh yeah, I'm going to move out again
Why?
I was shortlisted by Ori Advertising
Really?
Mo Mo, you're so awesome
What a smart girl!
I knew it
You do a gathering just because of that?
Don't you feel troublesome?
Girls are always meddlesome
Just a small quarrel
They'll be fine in several days
Who touched my drawer?
Ah Ke
Where are my socks?
He gave all the socks in our room
to his girlfriend to hide the boiler
Hide the boiler?
That was the story
Such a nice boyfriend
His girlfriend has been calling him
to do a club gathering
Are you going?
No
I knew that
Okay
I'll off the phone, bye
Can you help me?
My girl has low marks in co-curricular
She wanted to do a club gathering
I hardly get people to participate
I don't do this stuff
We seniors
have no time for gatherings
The girls who join it are still single
I suddenly have time now
Right?
You must go
No, thanks
Mo Mo
Here
You know each other?
He is my boyfriend
You have a new boyfriend?
How long we didn't
share secrets to each other?
I have broken up with my ex
and I met
a new guy through games
after the campus merged
What?
Haven't I told you before?
I remember I have.
Mo Mo
He's Ah Ke
Si Tu Mo
Hello
For you
Thank you
I'm Meng Lu
Hello
My girlfriend
I knew
How come I don't know anything?
Both of you are...
-Roommates
Felt like I've been fast-forwarded
Eat the prawn
Take off the shell for me
Try this, it's delicious
Give me an egg
Okay
Well
Did Ah Ke tell you
about the gathering?
Yeah
What?
How come I knew nothing?
I'll take you out for fun
For fun?
Don't bother so much
Just come with me
But I'll be on internship
It's before your internship
I have to get more co-curricular marks
You must support me
But I...
No but
Don't you want to Take a rest
before the internship?
Furthermore,
we'll go to the beach
Count me in
Will you go?
He won't
I'll go
Didn't you say you wouldn't go?
You didn't mention the beach
But, we used to go to the sea...park
I got it wrong
It's a sea park
You like the beach too?
Yes
Eat more vegetables
I'll send it to you once
I complete the schedule
Okay
We'll go dating
You may do whatever you like
You free this afternoon?
Yes
Help me move my things,
I'll treat you watermelon
OK
Let's go
Tell me once you've done the calculation
So I can rent the tents
Okay
Okay, no worries
Go and take a bath
You stink
How can it be only 14 person?
Have you included Si Tu Mo?
What's wrong?
What activity?
We...
I'm in
I'm okay, it's not heavy
Help me to hold it then
Give it to me
Take out the key
Where is it?
The first slot
Not here
I got it
The chewing gum we bought?
Don't...
-Not me...
-I knew
Sorry
First floor?
I found it in the bag
when we bought
the sweeping robot
I must have thought it was a chewing gum
and took it
Shall I
put it in your drawer?
Throw it away
Are you sure?
Then you keep it
Throw it
I'll throw it
Actually, I want to ask you
Why did you keep it in your bag?
Any activity tonight?
You want to join?
Do you want watermelon?
Come in
Anything else?
That...
The rectangle paper
Are you listening to me?
Yeah
Give me the contract my mom sent you
I didn't take it
Where is it?
I can't find it
I don't know
Didn't you take it?
Why should I?
It's true
You won't be so bored as to keep it
to help my mum to threaten me
I won't
Alright, I will look for it
A Chance!
Yes!
No! No!
No Chance!
A loan, usurious loan
-Can I?
-No way
You are back
How long will you get here?
I saw you guys
Get into the car
The security won't allow us
to stop for long
Get in
I can smell the sea
Help carry the things
Look at Xiao Pang
Okay, shall we go now?
Is this the sea?
More like a river
A river is much cleaner than it
This is not what I expected
Since we're here
can't just go back
Let's set up the tents
Chop, chop!
"Happiness is ringing beside the ears"
"So happy to be young"
"Love is the sweet transform by rain"
"Dropping one by one"
"The eyes full with sunshine"
"Warm the memories"
"Can't speak out most of the plots"
"Just keep it warm inside my heart"
"Never get tired of missing you"
What are you doing?
Taking a selfie
Come join me
Alright
What are you doing?
What...
You guess it
What do you think?
Help me, Shan Shan
Be careful
"Speak slowly and don't be nervous"
What are you doing?
Slow down
"Like the sunny day we just met"
"The little time of aroma"
"Growing naturally in noise"
"Looking and greeting you in happiness"
"It's worth keeping it forever"
"The little time of aroma"
"Speak slowly and don't be nervous"
"The sky is warm"
"Like the sunny day we just met"
"The little time of aroma"
"Growing naturally in noise"
"Looking and greeting you in happiness"
"It's worth keeping it forever"
Mo Mo
Anyone inside?
No
Get changed
Don't catch a cold
Meng Lu, help me tie my hair
Thank you
Let's have a fair competition
For Fu Pei?
I won't do that
What do you mean?
All of a sudden I feel like
I don't like him anymore
Is it because of me?
You don't need to...
I swear
It's not because of you
Let's go
Why are you standing here?
You walking the kite?
Fly it if you're so smart
Take it
The wind is blowing this way
Let it go when I say so
Alright
Let it go
It's up
It's up to the sky
Higher
Get higher
Slowly
I don't know how
It's simple
Pull it when you feel it loosened
It's flying up
Are you okay?
Some people are just like a kite
Keep flying out once the string
is held in someone's hands
They never think that
the person holding the string
might get tired
They don't let it go
only because they feel hard to do so
It's not hard this way
Gu Wei Yi
It's not easy for me to fly it up
I want to kill you
Calm down
I'll kill you
My footprints are so deep
Mine are deeper
By visual check, mine are deeper
My visual check is different
You should follow my visual
Look, what is this?
A shell
What shell is it?
This...
Is this a gem?
A mosaic tile of the toilet
I heard we can hear
the ocean through a conch
It's true
Listen, it is really the sound of ocean
Have you watched the SpongeBob?
There's a magical conch
It knew all the secrets of the ocean
This one might know
many secrets too
It is really the sound of ocean
You're just hearing
the blood flows in your brain
and the sound of air
In the theory of resonance,
when the vibration frequency of sound equals to
that of the inside of the conch,
both the amplitude and intensity
of the sound wave will be magnified
and form a resonance
So
what you heard was
the sound of air flowing
inside the conch
and your blood flowing
What?
It's the same if you put a thermos
near your ear
Why should I do that?
A glass will do too
No way
Pick it yourself
Anyway, I know nothing
See what can you get?
Here comes the Easter egg
Morning
Wait a moment
Get in later