[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
[Summary]
You or me first?
You first
Wait for me then
Hurry up!
Si Tu Mo
I killed her with poison
When will the ambulance arrive?
[Episode 3]
Fu Pei
Mo Mo, hurry up pick up the call
He has been calling you from the morning
Hello
Hello, are you Si Tu Mo?
Yes, I am, who are you?
I'm calling from Pu Hua Accounting Firm
We have received resume
I think you're suitable
and meet our requirements
Do you want to come to our office
for more details and
let's discuss about it?
Pu Hua? Now?
Yes
Okay, I'll be coming now
Wait for me
Hey
I need a favour from you
What's wrong?
Help me look for someone in 208
I'm from the class of 208,
whom you're looking for?
Si Tu Mo
Are you Fu Pei?
Mo Mo mentioned about me?
Please help me look for her
I couldn't get her by phone
She just awoke
You have been calling from the morning
All the girls in the room
awoke to the ringing
So sorry
Wait a moment, she is coming soon
I have a class now, see you
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for you
Why? I'm rushing out for an interview
Yesterday...
Don't mention it
I couldn't remember it
Did I do anything shameful last night?
Yes
You
hugged me tightly
After that,
you held my face
and wanted to
kiss me
I said no
Behave and be calm
And you touched me
in this way
You touched here,
here
and here
At last, you hold me in this way
Is that Fu Pei?
What's wrong?
Yeah
You kissed me and hugged me
I said no as there're many people around
You said, it's alright
You enjoyed it very much
Come in
Good day, Professor Jiang
You're
Gu Wei Yi
Did you complete the paper alone?
Yes
Well,
you should join our project team
I think
you're quite suitable
This is out of the rules
There's a top scorer
in the last examination
He should join your project team
You didn't sit for
the examination, did you?
I have checked your level
If you sit for the examination,
you may get the highest mark
How can you say this?
Yes, you're absent
Look at this
I have taken the top scorer
to join our project team too
Don't you want to
work and study together
with the top students?
You can even fight with him
Are you recruiting for 2 person?
2 person?
If the experiment needs more people,
I can recruit more candidates
After all, I don't have to pay you guys
Piss off?
Think about it
This is the top team of the college
Don't you want to join us?
Look
If someone gossips behind you,
I'll attack him with this
Thank you, Professor Jiang
Finally, you agreed to join us?
Mr. Xu
told me that you're so fussy
and won't join us easily
So, I have prepared a lot of reason
to convince you
It's alright
I want to join in the best team
I'll brief you about
our company's background
Recently, we'll recruit some trainees
We'll pick the elites among them
and keep them in our company
How many trainees
that you have recruited?
But, you're the only
trainee in my department
If you have no problem,
just do your best
I will try my best to
keep the position for you
Alright, thank you, Sis Qing
Anyway,
the employment
is a two-ways choice
You may think about it after this
Mom, I'm not going back
Your father has talked to Uncle Li
Uncle Li wants you
to work as an accounting
clerk in his factory
I found a trainee job
and I'm not going back
Why don't you back to the hometown?
You don't have to pay for
the rental and eat outside
Then, you can save more money
I found a job in a big company
May people want to work for them
What company is that?
Pu Hua Accounting Firm
What?
Putonghua?
I have never heard it, is it reliable?
You went to several interviews before
and still jobless
Don't decide recklessly
Quickly come back after the graduation
Even if you found a trainee job,
you don't know if they want to
keep you as a permanent staff
It's hard to make a living in a big city
You have to go out
in the early morning
and work until late night
You are a girl
Your father and I are worried about you
Mo Mo
Mo Mo, I'm talking to you
You...
Mo Mo
Mo Mo, are you listening?
I'm talking to you
How is the company?
You don't know about it
Mind your words
Let me try
Where is the location of the company?
Is that far from your college?
It's in Guomao's area,
a bit far from here
I'll look for a room later
My friend has a house
What about...
Mom, let me handle it myself
You?
Since you're so smart,
can't you just give birth to yourself?
Alright
You're really...
Okay, bye
Bye
Attention to everyone
She is our new trainee,
Si Tu Mo
If you need help,
you may look for her
Hello, everybody!
I'm Si Tu Mo
That's your seat
You just sit there
I'll get the
administration department
to set up the computer for you
Thank you
Do your work
Sis Qing
Please record the certificate
Okay
Hello
Don't push
I never push
Hurry up
-Move inside please
-My bag!
Just move inside
Can't board it
Forget it, let's take another bus
Ths bus is full
Hello, mom
Mo Mo, are you back to the dorm?
Have you taken your meal?
No
Why aren't you back at this hour?
Still on duty?
I was unable to board the bus
because it was too crowded
I'll walk to the next two station
You travel so hard everyday
I have talked to Aunt Xu
Her house
is near to your office
No one is staying there now
You just need to clean it up
Aunt Xu
left the keys in the mailbox
I'll send the number to you
Okay
Gu Wei Yi
What's your name?
Xie Yu Yin, I'm from Graduation Class 2
Hello, Senior Xie
You got it wrong here
Here
Thank you
It's okay as long as you correct it
FP
Fart?
It's done
Let's go to have some food
Okay
What are we going to eat?
There's a new beef noodle downstairs
The food is nice
Alright
Si Tu...
Mo
I'm Kang Lin
You can call me Xiao Lin
Hello, Xiao Lin
Are you having lunch in the office?
That's right
The smell of Liuzhou River
Snails Rice Noodle
is too strong
It lasts for the whole noon
You might not smell it
But all of us are going
to be crazy in the chat group
I'm so sorry
I don't know that you hate it
Aren't you invited to the chat group?
You have been here for several days
Let me add you into the group
Be smart
Okay
Scan my ID
Let's eat together
Where should we go for
Liuzhou River Snails Rice Noodle?
Wait, let me look for it
Xiao Lin
The shop was penalized
due to the hygiene problem
You have a strong stomach
Fortune telling?
Please check my fortune
It's not funny
I heard you joined Professor Jiang's lab
You made it, didn't you?
You're right
Si Tu Mo
Do you smell something stinking?
No
It comes from your body
I just took
Liuzhou River Snails Rice Noodle
You'd better take bath in the dorm first
I'm no longer staying in the dorm
I have moved out for a week
If I go back to the dorm,
they will ask me to pay on the bill
I'm quite poor recently
Have you ever rented a house?
No
My landlord is really strange
The decoration of the house
is just like a sample house
Cool and lack of sense of humanity
I feel like sleeping in the mortuary
So, I'll
I want to read a book here
It looks like a mortuary here
Hello, mom
Are you staying in Aunt Xu's house?
Yes
Did you dirty the house?
No it's clean
Alright
Aunt Xu said,
her kid might go back to
the house for several days
When?
Tomorrow
Are you cleaning up the house?
Don't dirty the house
No it's clean
Why are you here?
Are you
Aunt Xu's son?
Hello
So,
you said
that my house is a mortuary?
I'll increase the temperature
It's a bit cold
I can explain for it
Explain it
I wanted to restore it
to original before tomorrow
My mother told me that
you'll be back tomorrow
I had an experiment in the old school
and I couldn't get a cab as it's raining
Will you stay here tonight?
Why did I back here then?
That's right
I don't know Aunt Xu's kid
is a boy
I don't know the child
of my mother's friend is a girl
I'll move out then
I'll back to the dorm now
Can I just
move out tomorrow?
Okay, keep the things
Okay
Throw the Liuzhou River
Snails Rice Noodle first
I haven't finished it
Throw it
Please
Okay
I'll throw it
What are you waiting for?
Put down the bolster
It will be smelly
I won't throw it
You throw it
Help me throw it
It's stink and I don't want to touch it
I'll throw it later
It's stink
Okay, wait a moment
Why?
Can't you just throw it right now?
Wait a moment
Right now
I don't wear my inner
Understand?
Take your time
Why didn't you wear it?
Are you wearing an inner in the house?
Let me clean it
Thank you
Let me help on it
It's done
You or me first?
You first
Wait for me then
Hurry up
So tired
Done?
Almost done?
Not yet
I'm done, go ahead
I'll go to bath now
Si Tu Mo
You have only one toothbrush?
That's right
My toothbrush!
Wait a moment
This is the only toothbrush
that I could find in the house
Thanks
What now?
Can you give me one?
Mom, what's wrong with you?
Why didn't you tell me
that Aunt Xu's kid is a boy?
How?
I heard he's good-looking
Mom
Okay
It's alright
Aunt Xu said, he won't be always there
Moreover,
it's alright for you
two to stay together
Then you can know him better
I heard he has been holding
the scholarship all the time
and he's handsome
He won't fall into you
I'll have to pray in the
temple if he's into you
Si Tu Mo, are you listening to me?
Yes, I'll move back to the dorm tomorrow
You're really pig-headed
You really piss me off!
You piss me off too
Mom
What's wrong?
Why didn't you tell me
the kid of your friend is a girl?
What's the problem?
You don't like a girl, do you?
I mean...
You don't like a girl
and even a boy
Moreover,
you're not staying there now
You pissed off by me?
It's okay, I'll go to bed now
Okay
What's wrong?
I only sleep on my bed, so I'd like
to exchange the room with you
What's wrong with you?
I'm stomach-ache
Wait, I'll get the medicine for you
I used to take this when I was
stomach-ache during my childhood
Hold it
Si Tu Mo
Hello, this is service of 120
I'm in Guan Mei Garden
of Xiu Xin Road, Gu Qian
My house number is 1708
I need an ambulance
Okay, where did the patient hurt?
She is having a stomach-ache
When will the ambulance arrive?
I have arranged it for you
Is she conscious?
No, when will the ambulance arrive?
Is the breathing smooth?
Has she taken any medicine?
When will the ambulance arrive?
Sir, please calm down
and answer my question
Has she taken any food
or medicine before?
I killed her with poison
When will the ambulance arrive?
What happened?
She took the dirty Rice Noodle
and it caused Acute Gastoenteritis
Poison?
She took the expired gastric pill
and her boyfriend was very anxious
Let's go and check it out
Okay
I told you that I can't go back now
My child is sick
That's all
Okay
You look familiar
You checked her limbs when
she was injured that day
The wheelchair
You again, huh?
She is having Acute Gastoenteritis
and the pain makes her fainted
She only needs to finish the drip
and to be observed for one night
Then, she can go home
Doctor
Why isn't she awake?
Are you sure it's Gastoenteritis?
Yes, it's only Gastoenteritis
Don't worry
She's just sleeping
Well
If you love your girlfriend so much,
please take good care of her
Don't give her poison
Doctor
Look at my child
He's painful for a long time
What's his problem?
What happened to him?
He said that he's having a stomach-ache
since the morning
The examination shows everything's fine
But he cried when we got home
Let me check it out
It's okay
It's painful
Boy, you have an
examination tomorrow, right?
How did you know?
It's okay, you can go home now
Doctor
He's crying
How could you say it's fine?
He has an examination tomorrow
So, he's pretending
It's painful
Wait a moment
My boy is painful
How could you say he's pretending?
Are you really a doctor?
Mind your words
I'm a doctor
When I said he's fine, he is just fine
So what?
You must check his body
I tell you
This is a hospital, don't act recklessly
So what?
If you heal my boy, I'll keep quiet
Otherwise,
I'll destroy the hospital
Gu Wei Yi
Happy birthday
Thank you
Why do you look so cool?
Happy birthday
Come on
I have a present for you
Who gave you the
permission to lie on my bed?
Come down
I'm giving myself to you
Come down now
Don't show a fierce look on your face
Come on
I have a present for you
Take off the blanket
Be patient
Fu Pei
The basketball is me
I'm a basketball
I'm giving myself to you
Fu Pei
You're so shameful
We paid for the present together
Why did you only put your name?
I'm the one who bought it
I'm not going to play the basketball
You have to work it out