[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
[Summary]
What are you doing?
Don't look at my girlfriend
Are you in the bad mood?
I thought you want to beat me
[Episode 4]
Gu Wei Yi
You had pressed on the infusion tube
Hello
Hello, what do you want to eat?
Give me one bowl of porridge
One baked roll
Two Youtiao
One sesame ball
and salty Douhua
Lao Wang, is the porridge ready??
Okay
Others are ready
Only the porridge is still cooking
Are you okay with the soy milk?
Our soy milk is rich in taste
No, thanks
You must try it and
you will believe it
My friend has a gastroenteritis and
she needs only the porridge
Okay then
Please take a seat and wait for a while
Why you came so early?
She has vomited yesterday
I'm worrying that she will
get hungry after wake up
You treat your friend so good
My husband has never treated me
like what you did when he ran after me
Am I right?
Never buy me a breakfast
in 6am morning
Why not?
I was always worried
that you'll get hungry
and I always treated you with nice food
Now your body weight can prove it
Pardon?
Okay, I dare not say it anymore
Quickly get his order ready
Okay
Hello
Where are you?
Could you send me
a pair of sport shoes now?
I have a match this afternoon
My shoes were wet last night
although I have tried to dry it up
Hair dryer is prohibited at our dorm
Could you ask Ke to send it to you?
I'm not in the university now
They can't help
Otherwise, I won't trouble you
Take it yourself then
I'm in the training now
Or else I won't stay here overnight
It won't take you so much time
Are you saying that you refuse to help?
Well
I'll pay the fare for you
I'm in the hospital now
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
Si Tu Mo was admitted
What are you looking at?
The body check monitor
Why?
Thinking how to on it
Are you an internet addiction?
Have your breakfast first
Porridge
It's alright for me to eat others
I vomited and my stomach is empty now
You see...
Are you Si Tu Mo?
How do you feel?
It's getting better
You were suffering in gastroenteritis
You can't eat those food
I eat only the porridge
That's good
Dr. Liu will come here in a short while
You will get scolded
if he sees it
You can't eat this
Have a good rest
What are you doing?
Give way
I can't
Why?
Don't look at my girlfriend
Look like she has been fully recovered
My hair is so oily
Do you have rubber band?
Do you think I will have it?
You made the point
Wait for a while, I need to go
through the discharge procedure
Okay
This is for you
Thank you
Don't eat snail noodle anymore
It's so dirty
You'll get stomach-ache again
I got it
I buy you some delicious food
I'm better now
You always made people in worry
Are you okay now?
Okay
So fast you are here?
Yeah
This is a small matter for me
Master, can it be fixed?
I'm rushing
I need more time to fix it
You are out of the range
The power will be cut off,
you'll not able to return the bike
You are out of the range
The power will be cut off,
you'll not able to return the bike
This is really a small matter for me
Let me take it
You really helped me a lot
But how come you sent Mo Mo here?
-She's now living in...
-We met at the roadside
So I asked him to come with me
It's okay, I can walk myself
Are you okay?
Slowly
Dr. Liu
Where is your boyfriend?
Your boyfriend asked him to help?
Boyfriend?
Take a good rest after this
Don't always get admitted
You have made your boyfriend in worry
If you admit again,
he will be crazy
It's not as what you said, Dr. Liu
Not like that
Your boyfriend is coming
I'm leaving first
Waiting for me?
Let's go
Gu Wei Yi
The doctor said you
are Mo Mo's boyfriend
What's wrong?
The doctor must be mistaken
Is that true?
Of course, what are you thinking then?
It's true
Gu Wei Yi doesn't like
the girl like Mo Mo
What type of girl I like?
Maria Curie I guess
Not at all
Take the money
Okay, thank you
My princess Mo Mo
Please
Okay, don't act anymore
Yes
My lady
Okay, good luck in the match
Give me a call in anything
I'll leave first
Let me help you
It's okay
It's so heavy
Don't worry
I will carry it to your dorm
Mo Mo has moved out from here
Why are you
still wandering around here?
What?
You don't know?
I knew it
I just sent her back
Thank you
Good bye
See you
She's not at here
Hey
Enjoy your tea
But, could you please
stop making the sound?
Don't you think
this will make your office
more vitality?
Cut the crap
It's bored
Professor Jiang, the senior
looked  down upon me
What's wrong?
Mr. Wang, Professor Jiang, look at this
This is my experiment report
She marked my report
without my knowledge
Who gave her the authority?
Professor Jiang
I am your student but not her
How can she mark my report?
I have just argued with her about this
She told me that
even Gu Wei Yi could
accept her guidance modestly
Why can't I?
Why did she compare Gu Wei Yi with me?
I'm smarter than him
I get here by my strength
But he get here through
the back door, am I right?
You're wrong
You...
The red color remark
is to keep you reminded
the mistakes you did in the report
As a senior, I'm trying to help you
But you refused to accept it
That's why I can only give you
an example of a successful person
after he accepted my guidance,
Gu Wei Yi
I didn't expect that you'll
in such big response
You...
Professor Jiang, look at here
How could she...
Look at it
Xie Yu Yin
has marked
the mistakes
and she has also written
the correct answers at the bottom
Wang, check it out
It's wrong
All wrong
Where?
How can it be wrong? I have
calculated it for a few times
I can't see any wrong too
It's wrong
Yes
It's because your writing
is too horrible
Gu Wei Yi
Professor Jiang, here is
my experiment report
Don't read it
We won't look at his report
Well, I'll check it later
Zhou Lei
I have checked your experiment report
The calculation part was wrong
I have written the correct
answer by pencil
If you find it wrong,
just erase it and
do your own calculation
Let's discuss it later
It's okay for the others
I'm leaving first
Okay
The writing is so nice
Why? Are you going to leave here?
How long you'll go back for this time?
About a week
I'll come back after the completion
of Professor Jiang's experiment
Why can't you do it at here?
What's the purpose to move in here?
Some equipment is still
at the old campus
I don't really understand
the scientific research
Could you lend me your house key?
My key was left at your house
I need to go back to pack my belonging
Please don't tell anyone that
I stayed at your house before
I really had my bad day
After I failed in interviews,
I noticed that the girl I like
still entangles with her ex-boyfriend
He visited her everytime
when she was sick
It has nothing to do with him, right?
Hello, you there?
Her ex-boyfriend
never wants to be with her again
and why he still disturbs her?
However, she is happy with it
Tell me what is actually
in lady's mind?
Si Tu Mo
Remember to bring back the
report that I have passed to you
Okay
Let's go to Ao Li Advertising
together tomorrow
Okay
What's wrong? Don't scare me
Hello
Gu Wei Yi
Why you never reply my message?
I have set my phone to silence mode
You have forgotten
to bring the key, right?
Let's go back together
Bus or cab?
Anything
Gu Wei Yi
What's wrong again?
The luggage is not in proper zipped
Thank you, let's go
Is that your girlfriend?
No
Let's go
Where do you want to go?
Anywhere
Thank you
Not at all
Young man
I saw many kinds of people
when I was driving around
Don't be sad
I guess you
are not married yet, right?
I'm not cheating you
I used to take a female
passenger in the past
She asked me to wait at the downstairs
because she wanted to beat
her husband and the mistress
She said she will be leaving after that
But unexpectedly,
her husband has rented a room
to put those plastic dolls
What you called it?
Alright
The sex dolls
They have quarrelled
on the way back
She acted without checking
and made a joke
Master
Please u-turn
Why do you look at me?
Nothing
I...
I'm looking at the fridge magnet
It's so cute, how wasted it's with you
Take it
Don't waste it
Are you in a bad mood?
No
I have washed your bed sheet yesterday
But it's not dry yet due to rain
I dry it for you now
You can set it back after it's dry
Wait until it's dry
I don't know how to set it on
I will help you to do it
when I'm free, okay?
No
Are you trying to make me in trouble?
If you don't set it on,
then I can't sleep on it
Alright
Crazy
I should beat him up, he must be crazy
Come on
Take it
Why did you let it go?
I thought you want to beat me
No, I won't do that
Go and get the bed sheet
Try this, see whether can get it or not
Give it to me
Hold it high, can you reach it?
Hold it higher
Pick it up
Why did you jump?
You told me to jump, right?
I told you to pick it up
and swing it out, I'll catch it
Try to pick it up
Why did you jump again?
I'm not tall enough
I'm 1.87m
Is it?
It's true
Alright
Alright, the man of 1.87m,
please pick up the bed
sheet and swing it down
Jump
You almost get it
Jump higher
How come there's no fruits?
This plate looked strange
It's green color
Fu Pei
This is a misunderstanding
I'll bring you some fruits next time
What fruit you like to eat?
Watermelon...
Watermelon is good
Are you okay with the watermelon?
Watermelon is good for summer
Do I look great in this?
Fashion
Not bad
This hat is not bad
It's dirty
Have your time here,
I'm going out for a while
Sit down
Where do you want to go?
This is your house, right?
Understood
I am disturbing you
I'll be leaving here shortly
Is that okay?
It's not like what you think
You got it wrong
What?
How could it be?
Are you saying that
you never live together?
Gu Wei Yi, are you okay?
The green color bed sheet
is not suitable for you
It's fit to me
Look
Is it nice?
Together with the hat
Nice?
Green Light Hero
The house is just nice
for you two to live together
Fu Pei
Gu Wei Yi, are you feeling shamed?
Don't shame on it
Don't keep it from me as you
guys have been living together
Am I right?
Moreover,
look at Mo Mo
She's so good
It is good to settle down now
Mo Mo, you shouldn't do this to me
How can you
keep it from me as we're good friends?
This is not something you
shall do to your friend
What is our relationship?
What shall we do between friends?
As your best friend,
I shall tell you that
Si Tu Mo,
Gu Wei Yi really suits you
Wish you good in happiness
Alright,
I won't disturb you anymore
I nearly forget that I have
a game in this afternoon
I shall leave first
Gu Wei Yi, Mo Mo
I leave first
Si Tu Mo
It's really look strange that
the plate with no fruit
I'll go and buy some
Si Tu Mo
I'm asking you, what fruits you like?
Watermelon
I like watermelon too
I go and wash the bed sheet
Si Tu Mo
It gets dirty again
Let me see
Painful?
Yes
You can cry it out, it's alright
It's painful, but I don't want to cry
I buy you a band-aid
Young man, this is the last station
Fu Pei, why are you here?
Do you want to be a cleaner?
I'm so sorry, coach
I'm speechless to you
Think about it yourself
You're back?
Why you bought the watermelon?
I bought the watermelon
because the plate was really empty
We wanted to buy watermelon, right?
Thank you
Your hand still painful?
No
You and Fu Pei...
What?
Look like yours is sweeter
I'm hungry
Can the Gastroenteritis
patient eat watermelon?
I can
It's up to you
Do you really like to eat watermelon?
Yes
But you don't look really like it
How about like this?
I like watermelon
more than like you do
Hello
Have you done the report?
It's done
Bring it to office now
Okay
Which is nicer?
This one
All are looking good
My baby is so pretty
No matter how I comb,
you still look pretty
This one, okay?
This is too small
The bigger will look nicer
Pink colour just fits to you
This one?
Keep it first
I will comb for you
the most beautiful hairstyle
Hello
What's wrong?
Could you please give me a rubber band?
Sure
This is mine
Sweet heart, you got so many of it
Just give him one, okay?
No
I'm so sorry
She has been spoiled by me
I'll pay RMB10 for one
RMB20
Deal