[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
[Preview]
[Episode 10]
It fell!
Let me see!
Take a selfie
with someone you like
Who?
What?
This is selfie
He took a photo of himself
What now?
I like myself
So lame
Let's change to another game
Ke
Be careful
Can you manage to go back?
What about overnight here?
Forget it
This is far away from our place
We have schedules for tomorrow
Are you alright?
Alright, don't worry
Hurry up!
-The Fatty is heavy
-Bye
You...
Be careful
Let me know once you're home
-Okay
-Bye
Take care of your room-mate
Gu Wei Yi!
Go back to your room
Gosh!
You're so heavy
Take your time, I won't bother you
Gu Wei Yi!
I...
I should just let you freeze
Rascal!
Take your breakfast
Thank you
Last night...
Did I trouble you?
Sorry
I shouldn't do that
without your permission
Actually,
I've liked you
since long time ago
So have I
What the crap!
So have I?
Take your breakfast
Thank you
Last night...
Did I trouble you?
Sorry
I shouldn't
let you clean it up alone
I have cleaned the
balloons in the living room
What's wrong?
You forgot it?
Don't you remember anything else?
Anything else?
What?
What's that?
It's okay
I don't want to eat,
I'm going to be late
You'll be alright
after finishing past year's papers
I have done many papers
You used to tell me the same
You have been in so many relationships
and you're still saying the same words
Wang Shan
Yes
You say it easily because
you never have a boyfriend right?
So what?
Will I get fined?
Only those who have never
loved will say it easily
You have a lot of experiences
Then do me a demo
Sure
I'm worried that you can't hold it
Says who?
Do you really think
you are an expert in love?
3 steps in dating
Go out for a meal, for a walk and a movie
I'll show you one by one
Let's see
Let's go
Please
Lu Lu!
Lu Lu, get up
Lu Lu
Quickly get up, it's urgent!
Help!
What's wrong?
Are you pregnant?
[Sorry, I really don't want to lose you]
[Sorry, I really don't want
to lose a friend like you]
Why are you so quiet?
You make me feel awkward
You look good
You should get a change earlier
Let's go
It's so cold
Cold wave is coming soon
I brought some warming tea
Do you want it?
Only for Gu Wei Yi?
For everyone here
Why did you only ask him?
Cut the crap!
Professor, do you want some tea?
You're young,
but weak
Look at me
Cold waves
don't affect me
I don't need any warming tea
I never drink it
Come on
Take a rest
Drink the ginger tea
I don't want it
What?
I have worked so hard for it
Quickly drink it
No food or drink are allowed in the lab
I'll drink it at home
That's crap!
You're busy with the experiments
and only reach home
in late night every day
You would ave finished it
if you didn't grumble at me
Quickly finish it, cut the crap!
Three of you, come and drink it
The weather is so cold
You drink it
It's enough
I have taken 2 bowls of it
This is ginger tea, not medicine
Don't show me that face
Hurry up
Xiao Gu, take some
Why did you give it to him?
I still have it here
Enough
Hurry up
All your proposals
were rejected by the art director
and the project was
assigned to the 3rd group
We couldn't fight even among ourselves,
let alone
the others companies
You know what the art director said?
Old-fashioned,
boring
He said,
only the idea of Mo Mo
and Jie Er can be accepted
But their proposal
is not professional at all
How could your people
not as competent as the interns?
Sorry
Well,
we have no project now
Just take a rest
Miss Sha Sha, we received an email
We got a project of fruit juice
I'll leave it to you
I don't care
What now?
We're not as good as the interns?
That's right
Took me several days to work it out
Okay, stop grumbling
We'll discuss the juice project later
I don't want to be criticised
as not professional again
Okay
Get back to your work
and prepare the proposal
They received negative
comments from the art director
and only ours was accepted
How dare she scold us?
Do you want to buy anything?
Just look around
Since we want to experience a date,
we should be holding hands
There's a milk tea house
Let's go for it
Besides...
You're the first girl
who paid in a date
Only two cups of milk tea
I still can afford it
Let's go play games
Let's go
Are you ready?
Sure!
Come on!
I'm faster than you
You're left behind now
Wait! I'll overtake you
You can't beat me
I'm a super racer
Gosh...
You're speedy
I got you
No!
You're cheating
What a speed!
Stop!
Let's play this
Can you catch it?
Don't look down on me
I'll catch one for you
I think I could break the record
Don't just stand here
Help me, Mo Mo
You didn't break the record
It's alright, play again
I suddenly recall
that I have an online class tonight
So sorry
We didn't go for a meal or a movie
Have to wait till next time
I'll tell you after I pick a movie
Why are you here?
We...
You guys went to buy
birthday gifts for Mo Mo?
I bought
a humidifier in Doraemon shape
Luckily we didn't buy the same one
No
We got it from the crane machine
Mo Mo's gift is on the way
I go back first
Bye
I actually didn't think so much
I thought all the girls like it
It's okay
It's not a real date anyway
But,
I hope you bear in mind
I don't like spicy food
horror films
or Doraemon
These are all Mo Mo's favourite
Not mine
I'm going to the class
Can we
complete the process
of a date next time?
Sure
See you
The toys...
I'll keep them
Just to make you guilty
You're so mean
Bye
Just go ahead if you want to
text her or even meet her
Don't hesitate
I'll be late for experiments
Won't be back tonight
How could you forget the kiss?
Rascal!
Thank you
Gu Wei Yi, you caught a cold?
Don't come near to me
Mask
I'll find you a mask
Forget it
Xiao Gu
It doesn't matter
The experiment
is not urgent
You may go back and take a rest
"Don't come back then"
"I'll watch the ghost movie myself"
To avoid the infection,
I'll go back now
Alright
You did it very well
I wouldn't be able to do it
Fu Pei
Waiting for Si Tu Mo?
I'm rushing home, see you
Quarrel?
Let's go for hot pot together
Alright
I'll pass, enjoy yourselves
I want to go home
Let's go, the bill is on me
I want to thank you for
helping me on the proposal
I'll pass
Seriously
Let's go
-No, thanks
-Let's go
I'll pass...
This is the entrance to the office
People
might think we're fighting for a man
We did it indeed
Only spicy?
You guys didn't care
about me
Let's dig in and go home
Frankly, I never bless you guys
But I really wonder
what is happening now
Quarrel
or dishonesty?
It's my problem
I...
Sorry
Your problem?
It's most likely dishonesty
No
We're not the kind of relationship
Just normal friends
Alright
As long as you treat me as a friend
It seems I should
use the bathroom
to give you guys some space
Mo Mo
Sorry about that day
I wanted to say "that's alright",
but I can't do it
I'm still angry
Could you please don't turn up again?
And
I hope you don't treat Shan Shan
the way you treated me
I'm leaving now. See you no more
You said you won't be back tonight
Where did you go? Smell like hot pot
I just had a hot pot
With whom?
Fu Pei
You said you rejected him
He suddenly turned up
and he knows my colleague
It has nothing to do with me
Waiting for the bus?
Going back to the new campus?
So cold
What a waste!
We don't have radiators in the house
and it's not snowing
The weather is so cold
I...I wish to see snow
I've never made a snowman
I came from the North
So you're not afraid of cold, right?
We have radiators
Since it's so cold,
let's have a hot pot tonight
You had it last night, didn't you?
We can still have it tonight
It's cold
Hot pots are for cold weather
So lame
Here you are
Gu Wei Yi
What a smart boy!
Just in time when we
have adjusted the equipment
You're so smart
Turn it to the original then
I...
Gu Wei Yi, come on
Your senior is on a sick leave
So, you do it for her
Okay
Professor Jiang, why did you
ask him to do 2 experiments?
You never ask me to do it
This...
Take it
Please do it
Xiao Gu
It seems you're in a bad mood
Are you okay?
I'm okay
Really?
Yes
Gu Wei Yi
I told you I'm fine
I just want to ask about
the experiment record
Are you sure you're alright?
He just said it! Cut the crap!
Do your work
Hurry up!
That's right
I told you before
I really can't live with her anymore
I'm pissed off
She's really bad-tempered recently
It's hard to live with her
Like I owe her money
Always showing me her long face
As she's
not happy,
I wanted to buy her a treat
But she told me to get on diet
Too bad
Who knows?
I guess she's in love
People who are in love are insane
You meant,
the girl you like
met her ex-boyfriend?
The girl who pleaded for you
was not your girlfriend?
No interrupt please
You're worried she may leave you
but don't know what to do
And you are mad now, right?
Yes
It's so easy
The problem came from her ex-boyfriend
Is he also in our university?
Yes
Beat him up
No way
You can't do that
No, you can't bring him down
Well,
you may request his counselor
to have a talk with him
Professor Jiang
Look at his face
What a snobby look!
Did I say it wrong?
How dare he doubt me!
Has he been in love before?
Enough
Carry on your experiment
Don't think too much
Do your work
Stay for a while after this
I'll give you something
It helped me to get my wife before
What are you chatting about?
Nothing
I want him
to clean the lab after this
I'm alright
Are you getting better?
Okay, I'll wait for you to come back
So handsome!
The hair style is extremely nice! So handsome!
Like a pineapple
What?
You hair looks like a toilet lid
So good-looking
Insane
I'll wait for you to come back
To praise a girl
Not only her make-up or outfit,
but others
What's wrong?
I use a warming patch for stomach ache
I take you to the hospital
It's okay
Let's go
I have my menstruation
Is it painful?
It's okay, I can stand it
You are strong
You folded the clothes nicely
Smooth and straight
Thank you
You're welcome
Most of the boys misunderstand that
all the girls feel scared
to talk about sex
When an energetic girl
is with the boy she likes,
talking about sex
in a simple and natural manner
will make her think you're interesting
The Animal's World?
Do you know why are
the Bombus Affinis going extinct?
What's that?
Bombus Affinis
Because they can't get
mating and breeding now
Why?
They're infected by a parasite
called Nosema bombi
The parasite
causes an edema so severe
that they can't breed
The edema swells up between
the soft tissues of its organ
So the drone is overweight
and can't bend to mate with the queen
The queen produces
male offspring by itself
But it needs fertilization
to get female offsprings
Could you explain it
in a straightaway language?
Overweight will cause
a failure in the sexual activity
Why are you laughing?
Nothing
I find it interesting
Overweight will cause extinction, huh?
Exactly
You're right
Where did you get
the strange information?
The Atlantic
What? I've never heard it
A foreign magazine
My senior brought it to the lab
I'll go to the bed,
remember to turn off the TV
In girl's view, what should
a sexy boy look like?
The answer might surprise you
First, hair
Among the girls whom I've interviewed,
hair style is their main concern
Mind your hair style
It is not only
important for actors
You hair looks like a toilet lid
[Here comes the Easter egg...]
Gu Wei Yi
What did Professor Jiang tell you?
To clean the lab
I wasn't born yesterday
I'm not falling for that
Xiao Gu, how?
Have you cleaned it up?
Stop! I bet you swapped the books
Just like in the movie
Swap them back!
Zhou Lei's always full of suspicion
I can't help him
See you
I just bought it
Professor Jiang
What did you tell him?
To clean the lab