[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
[Summary]
Make a contract with me
What contract?
The contract of
"You Will Never Move Out"
[Episode 6]
Two of you are matched
People might think
you've been
living together for years
Mom
Could you please stop
talking nonsense?
What did I say?
You think too much
When are you leaving?
You said you'll stay for a night,
but it's going to second night
Alright
I knew
Xiao Gu never asks me to leave
How can you ask me to leave?
Am I right, Xiao Gu?
Yes
This is nice
Morning
Let's dig in
Take a bun
Take it
Look like you guys are not rushing today
I'm going back to school
to discuss about my thesis
I'm going as well
Are you going together?
What's wrong?
Nothing
You answered it without a hitch
Why are you going back to school?
How is the experiment in the old campus?
Professor Jiang will stay
at the new campus today
I need to see him for something
I see
Are you still listening the cross talk?
I'm too busy recently and forgot
to download the new show
I have downloaded it
Thank you
Surprise!
Mo Mo
It creeps me out
Why do you look guilty?
The staff will check on those
high power consumption today
Put it at the place we used to hide
The small room at the
end of the corridor
was found by her
Then what should we do?
I plan to hide the boiler
inside the dirty clothes basket
She will never touch the basket
Then I'll be safe
How long you didn't wash the socks?
Meng Lu took it from his boyfriend
Her boyfriend then took
a pile of stinking socks from others
What are you doing?
Cleaning up the room
Or hiding your boiler?
No, we're not
We collect those dirty clothes
and plan to wash them together
What is this?
Dirty clothes
Hands off
We didn't wash it for two weeks
The clothes are very dirty
Well
The room hygiene is part of
the spot-check
Are you really hungry?
You cook the socks as well?
Come get it after your graduation
I...
Aunt...
It creeps me out
Hello
I'm not interested in fitness,
nor health care products
No
I'm Si Tu Mo's friend
My name is Fu Pei
Do you still remember me?
Maybe I'm getting older
That's why
I can't remember you
I went to your house before
I sent the report card to Mo Mo
and you treated me with walnuts
It's such a waste
What did you say?
Nothing
I need to prepare the meal,
let's chat next time
Mom
With whom you're chatting with?
You're back
Let's go, I'll make you soup
Hurry up!
Aunt
We have to
go back for dinner
You shall go back too
Hurry up go back
Let's go
Aunt
Fu Pei again?
There's once
during your secondary school,
you locked yourself inside the room
and cried for a whole night
Your diary was full
with the words of "Fui Pei"
Mom, how could you read my diary?
Because you cried for the whole night
Your father and I couldn't
sleep for the whole night
It is too exaggerated
I thought you have broken up with him
I don't want to keep
in touch with him
Mo Mo
Since you're small,
you are
more sensible than your brother and sister
You don't usually cry
and you do everything independently
But at that time,
you were depressed
for quite some time because of him
However, you pretended
like nothing happened
We dare not ask you
Did you know how sad we were?
My little Mo
Actually, your father and I
never put any expectation
or hope on three of you
We never expect you
to make any big achievement
We just want you
to live happily
I knew
about Fu Pei
He wasn't a bad boy,
but only fickle
If you really get together with him,
I bet you will always
keep everything in your heart
and get things settled in tears
Mo Mo
Don't stoop to reach a compromise
You can't do so
That's not the right way
Mom
Alright
Stop talking about him
Let me tell you some good news
What kind of good news?
I'll go home tomorrow
I have packed everything up
You always want me to go back
Like I'm forcing
you and Xiao Gu to do something
Mom
I'm not driving you away
I'm...
Alright
I know you very well
Okay, I won't interfere
your business again
Mind your business
by your own in the future
This boy is so stupid
You must not find a boyfriend like him
Okay
This girl is so stupid too
You must not act like the girl
Understand?
Okay
So stupid
I'm back, aunt
Xiao Gu, you're back
Come and sit here
Have you taken your dinner?
Yeah
I'm thinking
to tell you something
I'll go back to my home tomorrow
I hope
you'll take a good care of Mo Mo
Okay
You are always welcomed
Alright
Take your seat first
I'll go and bring you some oranges
Gu Wei Yi
You very smart, right?
Perhaps, you can help me
write my graduation thesis
Just forget it
You won't understand it as
we are not in the same subject
What is the topic of your thesis?
It will creep you out
I'm ready for it
To informationize the SME Accounting
by cloud computing model research
Is that making you confused?
What is the topic of your thesis?
The law of Viscosity of Polyvinyl
The improvement of viscosity-
average molecular weight
Sorry for disturbing you
Your thesis is not going well?
I was scolded by the lecturer
He said the thesis doesn't show
my own point of view
and the points are unclear
He didn't see any of my view pertaining
to the future of accounting
How should I know it?
Just like I don't know
whether I'll be an accountant or not
What do you want to be?
Advertising designer
It's good to be an accountant
Don't think too much other than that
Am I right? Xiao Gu
It's more important that
we can do a job we love
I'll wash my hand first
Okay
Don't you want me to send you?
It's okay
You need go back to the office, right?
I don't want to trouble you
Be careful then
Okay
You have to make a contract with me
What kind of contract?
The contract of
"You Will Never Move Out"
You said that you won't force me
and let me make my own decision
After thinking twice of it,
I think I can't let you go
[Contract]
When did you prepare this?
You don't need to know
Sign it
No
No?
Really?
I will not sign it
Fine
I won't go back then
I feel hard to leave Xiao Gu too
Mom
I sign it
That's what I want
Take it
and sign it
Alright
I'll take my leave now
Take care of yourself
Come and give me a kiss
Come
Okay
I leave first
Alright
Bye
Don't let me go?
I'll go now
Gu Wei Yi
My mother left
and I'll move back to dorm
Sorry to trouble you
for the past few days
I'll buy you a meal when I'm free
I'm so sorry
I'm craving for Liuzhou
River Snails Rice Noodle
So delicious
Hurry up dig in
Fragrant?
Eat more
What are you doing?
Open the walnuts
You can't do it in this way
Don't press too hard
Let me show you
It will be cooked in paste
So, it's okay to be broken
[Girl's Dorm]
Aunt
Aunt, please open the door
You again, huh?
Thanks, sorry to trouble you again
Then, you shouldn't come back so late
I told you before
I worked overtime
Right
This is the typical excuse for
those who came back late
Come register your name
Thank you
Take it
You have registered 4 times in this week
If you really work overtime,
I shall
call you boss then
That's the truth
Believe it or not
I'm done, thanks
I go back to the room first
If you come back late so often,
you should move out from here
Then I don't need to
open the door for you
You ruined the rules of the dorm
I shall do it as your wish
There's a house waiting for me outside
I have been teaching
you for quite some time
Try to do the mock test
Any award?
You still want to go to Mo Mo's house?
Why can't you just tell her
you want to go out with her?
Why must you bring me together?
There will be no surprise then
If I suddenly show up
when you meet her at her house
This would be a surprise
I don't know what you are thinking about
What?
I said alright
If you manage to pass the test,
I'll make an appointment with Mo Mo
You must keep the promise
Alright
Mo Mo
-Help
-What's wrong?
What's wrong?
The graduation fair is coming soon
My poster has been rejected
and I need to redo it again
Would you help me to do it together?
You should look for your course mates
I'm too busy with
the thesis and practical training
I thought you were very interested
in advertising
So, it's more reliable
to do it together with you
Nevermind, I will look for others
if you can't make it
It's more important that
we do a job we love
I'll do it with you
Really?
That's great
Have some water
Are you serious?
Have you done your thesis?
Have you done the work
of your practical training?
How come you still have time for this?
I must squeeze the time out to do this
Mo Mo
You must know the priority
and importance of it
What should you do with
your practical training?
I'm thinking to resign
I know you're having
a hard time recently
But I think
you will regret if you give up
because of the hardship
I'm giving up because of that
I just think that's
more important to do a job I love
"Love is the sweet transformed by rain"
"Dropping one by one"
"The eyes full with sunshine"
"Warm the memories"
"Can't speak out most of the plots"
"Just keep it warm inside the heart"
"The little time of aromatic"
"Growing naturally in noise"
"Looking and greeting you in happiness"
"It's worth to keeping it forever"
Sis Qing
I have done the report you asked
Thank you
How is your thesis?
When would you be my permanent staff?
I'm thinking to tell you about this
I want to resign
Resign?
You're doing well, aren't you?
I'm thinking to turn you
as a permanent staff
Thank you, Sis Qing
I have thought about it for a long time
I prefer to be an advertising designer
Advertising?
How could Ori Advertising steal my staff?
Oh, no!
I don't get any job yet
I just personally like advertising
and wish to be an ad designer
Means you don't like finance
Many people might feel
bored with finance
Sometimes, it brings lots of fun
You can even use your
professional knowledge
to save a company
Really?
Of course
How?
Why should I tell you
since you don't like the job
Forget about it
If you don't like it,
I won't force you then
I hope you will get a job
that you love
Thank you
I'm going out first
Okay
I wish you a good future
Thank you
Is it clear?
Okay
Good
Morning, Professor Jiang
-Professor
-Busy?
Hi
Carry on your job
Gu Wei Yi, what are you doing?
I'm writing the thesis
Thesis?
How can you do something
not related in the lab?
I have told you before, you must be
serious and respect all the experiment
Don't you remember it?
Writing a thesis?
Have you done the experiment?
I have completed it
Done?
You have done it, then...
you can help them
Are you really writing the thesis?
I'm checking the origin of the surname
You should redo the experiment
and please focus on your duty
Okay
Gu Wei Yi
Why are you here?
I'm lost
I'm unfamiliar with this area
and it has been too long
since I left
Where do you want to go?
Where are you going?
To an interview
Then we can go
together
How did you know I got an
interview at Ori?
I heard it from someone
It spreads so fast?
Let's go
Here it is
Is the place
you want to go far from here?
Not far, just around here
Then I go in first, bye
Bye
How come you are still here?
How's the interview?
Should be okay
They asked me when can I start working
Let's go
I'm going back first
Okay
Go ahead
You wanted to get into the building
to sell your products, huh?
I'm not a salesman
Are you sure?
You are standing here with
the flyer for quite some time
Are you new in sales?
I've been working here
over the years
I know what you are trying to do here
Hurry up, get away
I'm not a salesman
Pei Lan
Wait a moment
I'm catching a salesman
Where?
Here
He is my student
Gu Wei Yi, he is not a salesman
Your student?
Yes
He is holding the...
Draft papers?
Draft papers
Another bookworm
I really don't understand
what is in your mind
Are you trying to tease me?
Hurry up get away from here
You have been standing
at the girl's dorm for so long
That's why I treated you as a salesman
Fine
Let's go, Xiao Gu
Pei Lan
What about we...
There is no "we"
Do you realize your mistake?
Yeah
Say it loudly
I realized my mistake
Will you smoke behind me again?
No, I won't
You're not sincere at all
Hurry up give me the key
I need to take some files from home
I'm leaving
Xiao Gu, go back
Aunt
You and Professor Jiang...
He is my husband
Finally, I have done the thesis
Can I make a curse?
Congratulations!
At this moment,
I want to dedicate the thesis to...
Gu Wei Yi
Hello
Si Tu Mo
Come back home now
Whose home?
My home
Why?
Your mom wanted to come
What?
Did you tell her that I moved out?
No
Okay, hold on a while
I'll be back soon
Hurry up! I'll try my best
Okay, bye
My god
What are you doing?
I told you before
My mom wished to make
me a match with Gu Wei Yi
She forced me to share rent with him
Gu Wei Yi just told me
my mother will come to his house
I need to rush back and
pretend I never move out
How about
I go together with you
I'm just curious
what the house of
the Physics genius look like?
You said it looked
like mortuary, right?
Moreover, your mother will believe
you didn't move out
if you bring a friend home
Perhaps, she will never do
the spot check again
That's right
Hurry up, pack the things up
Hi
I'm Wang Shan, Mo Mo's roommate
She is my friend, Wang Shan
Hi
Where's my mother?
She decided not to come
Why?
She's playing mahjong with someone
Really? She tricked me again
You can call and ask her
Never mind, forget about it
So, we will leave first
Wait a moment
Someone is coming
Who?
You will know later
Open the door
Let's celebrate for Mo Mo
as she has done the thesis
We shall celebrate
for Mo Mo today
Do you mind if we
make your house a mess?
What if I say I mind?
Then you are a niggard
Any drink you want?
We have beer,
juice
and soft drinks
Give me beer
Mo Mo should not drink the beer
What's he doing here?
You have so many films here
Why all horror movies?
Let's
watch a movie
This granny wasn't a human
Have she gone away?
Yes
He will eat the candle later
Please don't say it
Why did you stop talking?
You asked me not to say it
You shall say
Shall I say or not?
I don't know
No tomato flavor?
It has been sold out
-I go and...
-It's alright
I just merely said it
You were forced to stay together
because of your mother, right?
Yes, what's wrong?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why should I?
You are not my boyfriend
Where are you going?
I remember we have
tomato flavour chips in the house
Fu Pei
I'm okay
I'll bring him water
Si Tu Mo
Come and find me the honey
Fu Pei
Are you okay?
Let's go back
Mo Mo
Fu Pei
Fu Pei, you are drunk
[Here comes the Easter egg.]
Hello
Xiao Gu
Is Mo Mo okay there?
She's pretty good
I sent you something
several days ago
Should be arriving today
Please check it
Okay
You must tell me
if Mo Mo bullies you
I'll scold her
Okay
Si Tu Mo, come home for a while