[Put Your Head On My Shoulder]
Where are we going to?
[Preview]
Here it is
Playground?
To have fun here?
I wait for you at the entrance
Must find a place where
Si Tu Mo can't run away
to confess to her
[Episode 14]
Sit down
Step back
Don't be angry
It didn't hurt you purposely
I'll come to you if you're angry
I'm not angry
Don't come near
Ding Dang wants to eat dried fish
I have only cat food
No, dried fish
Okay, I'll buy for you
Ding Dang wants to thank you
It wants to give you a kiss
What are you doing?
Don't be ashamed
Come on
Step back
What if I don't?
What do you want to do?
Huh?
I'll kiss you then
You did it before, when you're drunk...
I'm just kidding
Don't be serious
Did I kiss her?
I was drunk
and fell asleep
Until the next morning
Which cloth you want to keep?
I'll help you
I'll do it myself
It's good if you could record it
Have you zipped the bag shut?
Yes
That's good
I'm worried if you forget it
You're worried if I forget it?
Drink it
It's early morning
I'm going to the lab after this
Cut it out
Drink it
I can't drink it anymore
Can you recall it now?
Now?
I recall...
Now I recall it
It's good then
My goodness!
We change it to chemistry now?
I wanted to make a simple antiseptic
You stir it with the pipette?
Oh yeah
Miss Li Na did ask us to make a proposal
for the orange juice
advertisement that day
Don't you think Miss Li Na
likes to order trainee?
She wanted us to do the proposals,
but never submits it
Are you listening to me?
Jie Er
Well...
Forget it
I hate people stops at half way
I just want to ask you
to submit the proposal
together with me
Are you sick?
You always ahead me
I'll wait for you then
Alright
Take the coffee and do your proposal
Okay
Focus on the internal structure
and jot down the data
Gu Wei Yi, how is my kitten?
Pretty good
Did it miss me?
Stop chatting
Don't waste your time on a kitten
How could you raise a cat in the lab?
Ridiculous
Zhou Lei
You're always
affected by the mess
Look at your result
You always get the lowest mark
You should take care of the cat
Why should I?
Because you don't allow
me to raise it in the lab
Your wife is the dorm keeper
She didn't allow it too
Now your family
hurt our family
Well...
Continue the experiment
"How to judge if a man likes you? "
Pass up the proposals before noon break
Let's meet at 3pm to
discuss about the proposal
Mo Mo, arrange the meeting room
Okay
Pass the ball!
Stop him! Defend!
Defend!
Good!
Well done!
Awesome!
One more!
Have some water
Fu Pei!
Enjoy yourselves
One more!
Who is that?
Did you see I make the 3 point shot?
Yes
Charming?
Charming
Extremely charming
Let's have some food
You have studied for a day
Let's have something nice
Let me enjoy it for a while
Studied with brain
is more tiring than me
We must eat something
Let's go
See you
There he goes
Okay
Let's continue
What do you want to eat?
I just received
the notice from the university
They will have an equipment check
in the labs at 4pm
So, we must finish all the job
before 3pm today
I have something
in the college in the noon
So I can take a leave now
Gu Wei Yi
I have an appointment with the clinic
We can bring the kitten
for vaccination in the noon
I have no time for it
You always have no time
You raise it, you should be responsible
I have an examination in the noon
I applied leave yesterday
Yes, Xiao Gu applied leave yesterday
Senior
Can you bring the kitten
for vaccination in the noon?
I have applied leave for the noon
to correct the thesis
I thought the graduates are free
I'm a postgraduate
Don't look at me, I'm a Professor
Professor is the freest among us
Professor Jiang
I'm full
Enjoy your meal
I have looked into all the proposals
It was suck!
Only Li Na's proposal is accepted
But,
you are the creative director
I hope you share the ideas
and guides to your
members without hiding it
Alright, brief us about it
Okay
Focus on the health
We'll set Lin Zhi Cun to
be a software programmer
who has sub-health problems
Moreover, he's a "budget husband",
who is the most popular man so far
He measures
everything with a perfect form
"Like"                                                "Form"
Focus on your experiment
Otherwise,
I'll chase the cat out
I'm serious
in the experiment
Xiao Gu
Try another connector
"You are passing by or staying here?"
"Crash makes a crush"
"My serene heart ripples"
"Tomorrow will be bright or rain"
"Depends on your tone"
"You hide or encroach"
"Marking Form for Gu Wei Yi"
"Here and faraway"
"Always meet accidentally"
"See your breath, look at your face"
"Can I sense it?"
"Guess if I could"
"conquer your heart"
"Any story line for me?"
"My heart is hiding the
puzzle for your answer"
"Are you willing to..."
It's good then
The feeble-minded?
"The lowest energy spectrum"
What are you dreaming?
Professor
I have something to discuss with you
Okay
Say it
I want to join too
Come on
About relationship
Okay, say it
We are listening
When I was unconscious in a drunk,
I kissed Si Tu Mo
But I forgot it
I wanted to kiss her after I recalled it
But she pushed me away
Does it mean she hates me?
But you said
she was jealous because of me
She should be into me
She must hate you
You're trying to harass her
Cut the crap!
She should have made a police report
But she didn't
I'll go home and ask her
If I were her,
I'll lock the door
and won't listen to you
Xiao Gu
Take it easy
Think about it
This is not the first time
we attemp to conquer Si Tu Mo
Before, we couldn't make it
because we didn't use scientific ways
So,
we must find a better way
from the scientific mind
to conquer her
Let's think about
Scientific ways
I have an idea
I ask you
What is science?
Always come with hypothesis,
infer and find out the truth
So,
we must
find out the truth
with 3 kinds of hypotheses
that we have now
Professor Jiang
What are the hypotheses?
Think about it
Like
Hate
Dislike and harmless
Gu Wei Yi analyzed it thoroughly
First
Of course
is "Like"
Alright?
The inference is so simple
No matter what Gu Wei Yi does,
it has only one outcome
Successful
What about the second hypothesis?
Second
Hate
This is the most likely situation
which I can tell
from the way Si Tu Mo ignored Gu Wei Yi
If you want to make it clear,
it has a drawback there
Like what Zhou Lei said
Si Tu Mo might hide from you and
it will cause two of you
unable to communicate
In short,
Gu Wei Yi must find a place where
Si Tu Mo can't run away
to confess to her
Moreover, the place
must be romantic
How we could get it?
You should think about it
I have no idea
It's about time
Quickly complete the form
and leave the lab
The staff will come here for a check
Professor Jiang
Don't forget to bring
the kitten for vaccination
Why are you here?
I'll bring you to somewhere
Where?
Come with me and you'll know it
Please hold it
Hello, Miss Li Na
Okay
I got it
Where do you want to go with me?
Let's have some food
I have eaten during the
tea break and still full
Let's eat again
I don't want to eat
Let's go
Where are we going?
You'll know it
Are you hungry?
Let's have some food
I'm not hungry
Mew...
How are you?
What are you doing?
Carry the cat
Aren't you having an allergy to cats?
I can overcome it
Overcome, huh?
Let's go
Bye!
Professor Jiang
In the electronic correlation
of topology of flat belt,
the interaction of fermion and boson,
numerical studies of
quantum lattice systems,
an Abel type of
Quantum Hall effect was found
as well as non-Abelian Quantum Hall
What?
The kitten scratches me
Bye
That's right
Exactly
Okay
Are you busy?
No
Let's go
to the place next time
Almost there
Let's go
Gosh! My honey
Pork liver again
She used to cook pork liver everyday
Mew...
This is good for your health
Eat some meat
after the vaccination
Hurry up!
Eat the meat
so that you'll become a big boy
Don't eat my eggs
Don't eat the eggs
Eat the liver
This is good for your health
Come on
Eat more
Eat some meat after the vaccination
Where do you want to bring me to?
Here it is
Playground?
To have fun here?
I wait for you at the entrance
Must find a place where
Si Tu Mo can't run away
to confess to her
You only play this in the playground?
I want to ride the roller-coaster
Too noisy
Why did you come then?
Just want to make you relaxed
To me, the most relaxing way
is lying on the bed after work
I have something to tell you
What's that?
This morning...
Say it
I want to tell you...
What do you want to tell me?
Hit him!
Say what?
Say it
Gu Wei Yi
What do you want to say?
One more time
No way
Si Tu Mo
What do you want to say?
Say it now
I wanted to tell you
This morning...
Professor Jiang
Gu Wei Yi
The kitten suddenly didn't move
after the vaccination
I couldn't get Zhou Lei
I'll be right there
I need to rush to the pet clinic
Why?
Professor
What are you doing?
I used to smoke before
Even stopped smoking,
but I can't get out of it
I want to smoke when I'm anxious
Doctor
How is our baby?
It's okay
It's in a fever and sleepy
Some kittens
have the symptoms after vaccination
No problem
Mew...
Take a rest
Be gentle, let it rest
We must bring it home
No
You guys go home first
I'll bring it home later
It stays in our house all this while
From today onwards,
I'll bring it home
I'll take care of it
But...
It's alright
Professor, this is our kitten
I...
I'll give it to you
But I want to hug it for a while
Be gentle
Be gentle, it just got a vaccination
Give it to me
Don't be afraid, honey
Don't be afraid
"Low power, going to power off"
Why didn't you save Circle?
It needs to grow up itself
"Charging"
When do you want to bath?
I want to clean the sewage
I'll go first
It's done
You can take bath now
You haven't taken your dinner, right?
Want to eat Liuzhou River
Snails Rice Noodle?
You're awake
What smell is this?
Liuzhou River Snails Rice Noodle?
Yes
Wait for a moment
Why do you cook the Snails Rice Noodle?
You didn't take your dinner last night
No one will eat this
in the morning
I'll get some porridge then
No need
Go ahead, I'll eat it
I'll wait there
Wait a minute
Only one? Don't you want to eat?
I have eaten outside
Taste it
I'll finish it then
Gu Wei Yi
I feel awkward when you're looking at me
I want to wash the bowl
Gu Wei Yi
If you don't like the smell,
go back to your room
I'll clean it after this
It's okay
Only Snails Rice Noodle
Okay
Gu Wei Yi
I...
Do you like me?
[Here comes the Easter egg...]
[Brainstorming]
Where can we book a reasonable hotel?
Gu Wei Yi, do it
Too many options
It's hard
but reasonable
The peak is affected by
the supply and demand,
pricing will up 20%
Third party promotion
covers the price increase
or gets a lower price
It's done
Apply VIP membership
to get 20% off and above
It's worth
What a science freak!
[Download APP to get 20% off and above]
So you didn't confess
on the bumper car, huh?
Yes
I knew it
Hey
Why must you confess on the bumper car?
The playground is romantic
and she can't run from the bumper car
Listen to me first
You don't know
There's a ferris wheel in the playground
You can be romantic on the ferris wheel
Well, it's not important now
I found
a marking form
about me
I got -10 marks
So, I think...
Oh, my goodness
I thought 0 is the lowest, you got -10?
What should I do now?
What else?
Get more marks
before the next confession
As a whizz-kid,
you should be well-prepared
You don't know?
But, -10
is extremely low
Bye