♪Waking up in a nightmare♪
♪Facing this cruel world♪
♪Whose heart is flipped♪
♪Missed farewell to lover♪
♪If the ending is tragic♪
♪Fearlessness is born in adversity♪
♪Even if the wings are torn♪
♪And fall back to the abyss♪
♪Hold your hands and move forward♪
♪Never stopping day or night♪
♪Transcending time and distance♪
♪I may be hurt and heartbroken♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops♪
♪Turning behind, you are always there♪
♪Lash out the curse in life♪
♪Let the story be eternal♪
♪Martial Soul surges aggressively♪
♪To embrace your lone wolf braveness♪
♪Even if the future is harsh♪
♪I will never give up♪
♪When there is no way out in reality♪
♪Hope is vexed by desolation♪
♪Yet smiling freely♪
♪Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant♪
♪The power of twin souls illuminates♪
♪Surviving in every plight♪
♪I will never give up♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
How is this a sea star?
This is a sea monster!
Let me finish this joke of a battle.
Ninth Soul Skill,
Tidal Wave Gravity!
Out of all the tentacles,
one hasn't attacked me at all.
Good job, Brother San!
Give him a taste of his own medicine!
[Episode 194]
Are you here to challenge me?
We are here to learn from you, Senior.
Please go easy on us.
Okay!
I'll go easy.
She looks too young
to be a Grand Soul Master.
Don't think this is strange,
I'm not a human.
I'm a mermaid.
Female mermaids never age.
Mind reading?
Wow, you can recognize my innate power?
You're very powerful!
But why can't I read your heart?
That must be why!
You are the human that has the honor
of taking the God of the Ocean's Nine Tests.
With the protection
of the Light of the God of the Ocean,
no wonder I can't read you.
Since she knows how to read minds,
Zhu Qing,
I won't be able to use spirit power
to guide your strategy.
You guys are so bad.
You're going to take turns to fight me?
Do you have the heart to?
This is our test. It doesn't matter
whether or not we have the heart.
Then let's begin!
Sisters, you're so pretty!
This is my first time seeing girls
as pretty as me.
Sister?
Senior, may I ask how old you are?
One, two, three, four,
ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen,
twenty-two, twenty-three,
sixty-eight, sixty-nine...
I can't remember
if I'm ninety-six or ninety-seven.
Sister, why do you look so unhappy?
I'm not saying you look old.
Us mermaids can live
fives times longer than humans.
Based on that ratio,
one times five is five,
one times six is six...
You should be less than twenty years old.
Sister, you're so smart!
Got it!
Wait, let me find it.
Where is it?
I found it!
I've been so bored guarding this place.
I finally waited for you two to come.
Let's not fight and kill, okay?
Let me play a song for you. You'll pass if you
listen to the entire song.
How about that?
Don't let her play! Attack immediately!
Jiubao Boosts! Second, Speed!
Nether True Form!
You're so bad.
You're not gentle with girls at all,
so annoying.
Zhu Qing!
Her black flute has some sort
of invisible shield that deflected me.
Ah, I'm sorry.
My hand slipped. Are you alright?
She knows how to read minds!
She made Zhu Qing grab the flute on purpose!
I play my flute very well.
Just listen to me play.
We won't fall for your trap.
Fifth Soul Skill, Ghost Shadow Connection!
Oh, no!
Sister, you still fell for my trap.
She broke Rong Rong's support!
You are indeed quite fast.
Even though I read your intentions,
I still didn't react in time.
But...
Rong Rong, be careful!
It's too late.
Third Soul Skill,
Seven Stars Demon Music!
Zhu Qing!
Illusory Wisdom Bone Skill,
Space of Illusion!
Why can't I feel your thoughts suddenly?
The Space of Illusion
may only block her out for a moment. After...
You hid a trick up your sleeve.
But it's useless.
Sixth Soul Skill, Tsunami of Fury!
What did you say behind my back?
Rong Rong, Zhu Qing!
Such strong spiritual shock.
Everyone, block your ears!
The Blue Silver Emperor's aura
is suddenly clashing in my body.
I need to fully amplify Zhu Qing's power
so she can escape quickly.
That's a good idea.
But I heard everything.
Phoenix True Form!
How do you know this skill
as a support soul master?
Rong Rong, go in for the final attack!
Sixth Soul Skill...
Don't even think about it!
Ghost Shadow Connection!
Nether Slash!
If you're hit by Zhu Qing herself,
you won't be able to avoid any attacks
form her shadows. It's formidable.
What?
[Soul Land]
You lied to me.
The Space of Illusion
may only block her out for a moment.
After this, let's attack with skills
that are the opposite of our thoughts.
What did you say behind my back?
You're bullying me! I admit defeat.
[Support Branch Tool Soul Master]
Ning Rong Rong has passed the Fifth Test.
[Soul Power: Lv. 78]
All soul rings increased by one thousand years,
soul power increased by one level.
Zhu Zhu Qing showed strong perseverance
and motivation.
You have completed
all five of the Black Level Tests
and are specially awarded
Black Level Authority on Haishen Island.
[Cat of Netherworld, Sensitivity Soul Master,
Soul Power: Lv. 80]
Soul power increased by two levels.
One God-given Soul Ring awarded.
Isn't a God-given Soul Ring
the only reward for Black Level Tests?
You got lucky.
Besides the one level increase in soul power
from the Fifth Test,
your power increases one more level
when you finish all the tests.
Your soul power is now at the next level
and you received an additional
God-given Soul Ring.
Congratulations, Zhu Qing!
You're the next to reach
the highest soul level after Brother San.
Brother Dai, how does it feel
to be surpassed
by Zhu Qing?
Of course, I'm happy
that my wife's power increased.
Based on this,
once we finish the Sixth Test,
we will also receive a God-given Soul Ring.
Xuan Tian Strike's self-protection
is starting to fight against
the Blue Silver Emperor's aura.
Why did these two energies
that were merged
suddenly start splitting apart?
The sister that's dressed in purple,
why don't you absorb it here?
The Sacred Totem's power
will protect you.
You were the one that stopped me
from playing my flute earlier.
That's so bad of you.
Didn't you want to challenge me?
Come on.
I've heard that Senior's Ninth Soul Skill
is extremely powerful,
and even warded off a group
of Demon Tiger Whales that attacked.
How about this?
Attack me only.
I will listen to you play a song.
If you can't defeat me in one song,
then let me pass the test.
Brother San, Bai told us before
that even amongst all
of the Seven Grand Ocean Masters,
this attack has the widest range.
The listener cannot think
about resisting at all.
They can only die.
Even though I lost the battle,
my spirit power wasn't affected.
Even if Tang San has
the Light of the God of the Ocean,
he still won't be immune to my song.
I've never seen any Grand Soul Masters
use sound waves as their attack.
I take this as an eye-opening experience today.
Then I'll fulfill your wishes.
Rong Rong, it's alright.
You go back first.
The Golden Trident Mark
that the God of the Ocean bestowed to me
is showing unusual spirit power fluctuations.
Grand Sea Daughter Master, please begin.
Tang San is quite powerful.
I need to give this my all.
Seventh Soul Skill,
Martial Soul Form.
Ninth Soul Skill, Divine Tune of the Ocean.
Her heart is distracted.
Concentrating for a long period of time
to use her Ninth Soul Skill
already took a huge toll.
Along with the strong emotional hit,
the battle has been decided.
Look! It's Brother San's Fifth Soul Ring!
This is the soul ring created
with Blue Silver Emperor's awakening.
This soul ring comes from yourself.
It will continue to evolve
as your tolerance increases.
The inflow of the power
from the Grand Sea Star Master
and the stimulation
from the Grand Sea Daughter Master's music
fully awakened
Blue Silver Emperor's evolution.
He really is the God of the Ocean's
chosen one.
Tang San has passed
the Sea Daughter Totem's Test.
Wu passes as accompaniment.
Senior,
please continue protecting Zhu Qing
as she absorbs the God-given Soul Ring.
Don't worry.
I hope that you'll be as successful
with the Sea Dragon as well.
[Advertisement]
I'll tell you a secret
that is not even known by Yu Xiao Gang.
Scan this QR code
and follow Soul Land's official Wechat.
Not only will you gain stunning wallpapers,
but you'll also find out the secret
to cultivating Twin Martial Souls.
So
are you willing to join Martial Soul Hall?
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 194 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1739 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2930]
[Total scene: 70043]
[Total CGI: 31135]
[Total plan of action scene: 14172]
[Total scene model: nearly 613]
[Total character model: nearly 1121]
[Total props model: 13483]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪We still have to part from each other♪
♪I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving♪
♪Amidst the grieving woods♪
♪Who is crying out there♪
♪I still relentlessly hold on♪
♪I refuse to accept this destiny♪
♪Desperately searching♪
♪Any signs of you♪
♪The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight♪
♪In your eyes, the world never changes♪
♪Yearning grows and interweaves with the past♪
♪Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you♪
♪You are the memory I refuse to let go♪
♪And the craziness of my desperation♪
♪Can you hear♪
♪My calls♪
♪Breaking through extreme dolours♪
♪Rushing towards your embrace♪
♪You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair♪
♪And the wish I made upon a star♪
♪One day♪
♪You will turn up gorgeously♪
♪And hold my hands♪
♪To envisage our future♪
[Next episode]
I've already fully recovered
to my best state.
Wu, let's go.
You came faster than I expected.
Even though domain skills are an advantage
against other Grand Ocean Masters,
they are useless against
the Grand Sea Dragon Master.
My domain is called Destructive Demon.
I need to pull out
all my skills for this battle.
Interesting.
Looks like I need
to treat this seriously too.