(This drama is set in an imaginary dystopian Korea,)
(and all people, organizations, and incidents are fictitious.)
(Lieutenant Yoon Soo Hyun)
Salute the deceased!
Soo Hyun.
My baby.
My poor Soo Hyun.
Mom.
Did you get hurt?
I love you.
Will you marry me?
No, I was kidding. I don't love you.
I love you just a little.
- Bye. - Bye. Take care.
She might trip again.
I'm on my way.
What weird taste.
- Is that what you say? - It's what you said.
I'll be careful. Don't worry.
Soo Hyun.
I want to like you forever.
I really like you a lot, Soo Hyun.
As a judge...
of the Republic of Korea, I do solemnly swear...
that I will rule independently according to my conscience...
and in conformity with the Constitution and laws.
I swear to abide by the code of judicial ethics...
and to promote the welfare of the people...
executing the duties faithfully...
- to the best of my ability. - to the best of my ability.
(Appointment Ceremony for Judges)
Here we go. One, two, three.
- Oh, no. - Come on.
Okay, please stand in the middle.
- Why don't you two take this one? - Oh, no.
I'll just step out of the picture.
My goodness.
I'll take one more picture.
Everyone, just smile.
One, two, three.
The roses of Sharon have blossomed.
Kim Ga On, stop crying.
You'll be fine.
You'll be okay.
You're okay.
Don't cry.
I love you.
Don't cry, Ga On.
Don't cry.
Ga On.
Ga On, I love you.
(Yoon Soo Hyun)
Soo Hyun.
(Lieutenant Yoon Soo Hyun)
(Episode 14)
Are you okay?
The shooter. Did they find the shooter?
We have to find that scumbag. That son of a gun.
- Kim Ga On, where are you going? - Let go.
- I have to catch that jerk. - Where do you think you're going?
- Let go of me. - Stop it.
Please.
What if something happens to you too?
What good will that do poor Soo Hyun?
Are you planning to die in the street?
Do you think Soo Hyun will be happy to see that?
Just stay here for now.
Just stay here...
and talk to Yo Han. We'll find a way...
We'll find a way no matter what.
Have you calmed down a bit?
Who do you think shot Soo Hyun?
He wasn't trying to shoot her.
They were planning to attack us in the confusion.
Attack us?
Think about what the foundation has done.
They took us off the air and knocked out power in the district.
- Wait. - What's going on?
Turn the lights on!
They had no time to think of the consequences...
and had to do something fast.
But it didn't work.
So they decided to kill us off.
Then did Soo Hyun...
die...
Did she die instead of me?
I know how you feel right now.
You must feel like you're in a fiery pit.
An eternal fiery pit you'll never be able to get out of.
I know how you feel...
because I live in the same place.
But if you have time to cry,
find the people who are responsible for this...
and make them burn in the fiery pit.
That's the only way you can survive in that place.
So have you arrested Juk Chang?
Then we'll have to start with him...
in order to punish the foundation.
Let us begin.
I am ready.
- Here they come! - They're here!
The emergency rescue workers sent by the government...
randomly assaulted innocent citizens...
and brutally murdered an elderly citizen.
Also, an unidentified gunman...
shot an officer to death.
The government still has not given any explanation.
I'm going to take this case of state violence to court...
and hold everyone involved responsible.
But President Heo announced that an emergency court...
will replace the current live court show.
I'd like to make one thing clear.
I'm not planning on joining the so-called emergency court,
which only aims to suppress...
and control the citizens.
The trial has already begun.
(Innocent, Guilty)
More than five million citizens have already voted for "guilty".
Whoever tries to stop...
this trial...
is the culprit.
(Live Court Show to Hold Government Responsible)
Unbelievable.
He's openly threatening us.
"Stop us, and we won't sit back." Is that it?
You and your obsession with viewer ratings.
I knew you'd mess up big time someday.
What are you going to do now?
Who knew Oh Jin Joo would stab us in the back like this?
I thought she was the ambitious type.
What's gotten into her?
She had her eyes on the Chief Justice position.
She probably wants to get there on her own.
I've never seen her glow like this before though.
Twinkle, twinkle.
Twinkle, twinkle, my foot. Doesn't this concern you?
If this gets out, there will be a riot.
We'll all be stoned to death!
I'm not afraid.
They can put us on trial if they want.
What?
That's not okay.
We'll keep the press under control and pressure the Supreme Court...
The entire nation watched it live...
when that old man got beaten to death with a metal pipe.
It's too risky. That's not an option.
For now...
It's time to shift blame.
The recent incident is...
a tragedy caused by the overenthusiasm...
and competition...
among the field workers.
I sincerely apologize to the deceased and their families...
(President of Korea)
on behalf of the government.
(The Blue House)
But it is unacceptable to use this occasion...
to spread groundless conspiracy theories...
and criticize the emergency rescue measures.
If any of that happens...
during the coming trial,
it will be considered...
an evident case of treason.
Good work, sir.
The problem isn't...
that the old man got beaten to death.
It's the virus.
I think we should prepare ourselves.
What do you mean?
Many people are debating whether the virus exists or not.
But we can give it to them.
We'll make sure it's found.
We'll make sure the virus is found...
in some slum areas.
Are you saying...
you'll spread the virus on purpose?
If that's what it takes, I will.
At times,
a leader is meant to face the lonely decision...
to sacrifice the lesser for the greater good.
And that moment...
can come to me as well.
Haven't you seen it in Hollywood movies?
A man crossing himself before pressing the nuclear button?
What's wrong? Is there a problem?
No, sir.
I'm just moved.
I don't like your tone.
You don't seem so happy about what we're doing now.
What is it? You want to back out?
That's not okay. That's cheating.
Hold on a second.
Do you have feelings left for Kang Yo Han?
I'll take care of Kang Yo Han.
Meanwhile, I need you to keep that punk quiet.
Who?
The very person who caused this situation.
The president of your fan club.
Juk Chang.
I trust you don't have feelings left for him.
We've managed to bring them to trial.
We now have to prove them guilty in court.
We'll have to prove the virus never existed.
Will that be possible?
Lawyer Ko contacted a researcher...
at the emergency response headquarters.
I'm meeting with him later.
Do you want to come with me?
Sure, let's do that.
Hold on.
Did you have dinner?
I'm not hungry.
Wait.
Yes?
I'm a little hungry.
So I'm going to make some ramyeon.
Should I make some for you too?
Thanks.
But some other time.
Ga On.
Hey.
What are you listening to?
Just...
some music.
Listen to something cheerful.
Stop looking so depressed.
Did you...
have dinner?
I'm thinking of making some ramyeon.
You're just like him.
What do you mean? Who am I like?
Your uncle.
What?
How can you say I'm like that middle-aged man?
You're both bad at comforting others.
Comfort, my foot.
I just can't stand seeing you like this.
You look like the world has come to an end.
It's boring.
But it actually comforts me...
that you're so bad at it.
Thanks, Elijah.
What are you saying?
(Voice recordings)
Will you marry me?
I love you.
No, I was kidding.
I love you just a little.
Will you marry me?
I love you.
No, I was kidding.
I love you just a little.
Many people are debating whether the virus exists or not.
But we can give it to them.
We'll make sure the virus is found...
in some slum areas.
That crazy clown.
(Board Chairman Jung Sun Ah)
Hey, Sun Ah.
Do you remember the neighborhood I grew up in?
Is that an emergency quarantine area too?
Probably. It's a really poor area.
Right. Makes sense.
What about the youth welfare center I went to as a mentor?
Is that place also...
No. That place is affiliated with the foundation,
so I'm sure it's not included.
Do you want me to check?
What? No. I was just curious.
My mom must've hoped...
that I'd grow up to be an ordinary, good person.
Then why did she do that to me?
If that was her wish, why did she beat me up...
every time she was drunk?
My mom did that too.
She did?
Usually, she was nice like an angel.
But she changed completely when she was drunk.
She'd start crying and...
Gosh. You're acting weird.
Are you going through menopause?
Why are you worrying about other people?
Hey. Don't you know how much I worry about you?
You always make me do such dangerous things.
What do you mean you worry?
We have a business relationship.
Just make sure you pay me for the risks I take.
You're so cold and rude.
Bye.
(Board Chairman Jung Sun Ah)
How did I end up here?
What can I do?
I'm already here.
(Board Chairman Jung Sun Ah)
You made it, Doctor.
Judge Kang.
My name is Kim Ga On.
Nice to meet you, Judge Kim.
Let me get straight to the point.
Is it true that they found a mutated virus?
As for as I know,
I haven't seen any scientific evidence to prove it.
Haven't you been a researcher in the infectious disease control team...
for three years?
But are you telling me that you haven't seen anything?
About a month ago, the Blue House changed the researchers.
They classified all the key documents,
and the emergency response headquarters is in a state of fear.
Armed soldiers are restricting everything.
Are you saying that you haven't seen a sample of the virus?
Right. I barely managed to sneak a peek at some autopsy reports,
but there were no similarities between the cases.
It's impossible for one virus to cause such a variety of symptoms.
The only similarity they have is...
What is it?
Malnourishment.
Malnourishment?
Almost all of the deceased were homeless...
or neglected senior citizens.
The areas where this so-called virus has been found...
are all extremely poor areas,
and the thing that killed these people isn't a virus,
but poverty.
People who suffer from chronic diseases...
due to malnourishment and bad hygiene...
are dying for various reasons.
They're claiming that a fatal virus has been found in certain areas...
to clean people up.
That's the essence of this situation.
Sir. Do you think that you can testify in court...
about everything you just told us?
Yes, I can.
This is dangerous.
Are you aware of that?
I have prepared myself.
To prevent the virus from spreading,
they have forbidden people from entering the Supreme Court.
The attorney has gained interest as an active-duty colonel...
and Deputy Minister for Legal Affairs...
of the emergency response headquarters under the president.
The entire nation is watching and wondering if the truth...
will be revealed.
(Defendant: Kim Choong Sik, 33, Job: Internet broadcaster)
This was an unfortunate accident.
Counsel, did you just call it an accident?
Kang Yo Han! Get down here!
Get down here!
Please answer me again.
Was this an accident?
Yes, it was.
Shouldn't the entire context of the incident be brought to light?
Right. Could you tell us what context permits someone...
from beating an old man in his 70s to death?
Korea is pretty much in a state of war right now.
In order to prevent the spread of a fatal virus,
field agents risk their lives and are sent to the site.
This was just an accidental casualty that occurred...
because residents refuse to follow emergency evacuation orders...
and they resisted.
It is nothing more than an accidental casualty.
Do you believe that this is proper execution of justice?
Let me repeat myself. We are in a state of war.
If the virus ends up spreading throughout the country...
because we are busy considering human rights and processes,
who will take responsibility for it?
Will you take responsibility for it?
Very well.
Then let's first find out if we are truly in a state of war...
like you keep reiterating.
By the authority of the court,
we will call a witness...
to verify the existence of the virus that was said to have been found.
Very well, Your Honor.
Mr. Yoon Myung Jin.
If you are looking for Dr. Yoon Myung Jin,
a member of our emergency response headquarters, unfortunately,
he passed away this morning.
He got infected while treating a patient with the mutated virus,
and within 12 hours...
May he rest in peace.
(Defendant)
The ultimate sacrifice that Dr. Yoon has made...
is evidence that shows exactly...
what kind of state we are in right now.
Your Honor.
(Dr. Yoon Myung Jin Passes Away From the Virus)
As expected. The beauty of courtroom dramas...
is the nerve-racking,
bloody, and unexpected twists that occur.
Don't you agree?
The people who killed Soo Hyun killed Dr. Yoon as well.
Calm down, Judge Kim.
What should we do, Chief Kang?
At this rate, the only option we have left...
is to get Juk Chang to talk.
We have to get him to talk no matter what.
I prepared something.
Just watch. Don't say anything.
Pardon?
Very well.
What does counsel think is an appropriate punishment?
(Counsel, Defendant)
It was an accidental crime that occurred in a tense situation.
Also, the defendant is a young man...
without a job who is living from hand to mouth.
What is most important is that he sincerely regrets his actions.
Please hand down the most lenient sentence.
Prosecution, what do you say?
Considering the circumstances,
I request you sentence him to seven years in prison.
I see.
(Live Court Show)
Thank you for sharing your opinions.
I have a question for the defendant.
Defendant.
Yes?
Put the camera on him.
Show that loser's face.
- Smile while you can. - Okay.
When President Heo was an online political broadcaster,
you were part of his staff.
And also president of his fan club.
Your Honor. What does that have to do with this trial?
You were an unofficial staff member during his presidential campaign.
Is that correct?
No, I know nothing about that.
Oh, it's what you did and you don't know about it?
No.
How interesting.
You wielded steel pipes a lot then too, didn't you?
You and your team interrupted a peaceful protest,
used violence, and stole from nearby stores.
(Live Court Show)
(Facts and Cause for Non-prosecution)
By strengthening the law, you bring order to society.
That was President Heo's idea, and you contributed to that.
Is that not true?
He's trying to expand the issue, isn't he?
The old man's death was an excuse.
He's planning to overturn the government!
The fool is out of his mind!
No. A judge ruled on that case.
- It was a drunken mistake. - Was it?
Then when you wielded a steel pipe while providing urgent assistance,
was that a mistake too?
Or...
did someone give an order?
To drag out as many as you could.
I received no order. I made the decisions myself.
Defendant, you were also a popular online personality.
Yes.
You gathered your fans, poor young men with no jobs...
to help you in Hyungsan-dong. Whose idea was that?
I received no order.
I realized the tough situation they were in...
and wanted to pay them...
My beloved and respected patriots.
Who will make Korea safe?
We can't just depend on the police.
We should take the initiative to...
Right after this broadcast of President Heo's,
you gathered the jobless youth...
and assaulted foreign workers.
The same youth were sent to Hyungsan-dong.
And yet you say you received no instructions?
(Counsel, Defendant)
Yes. I did what I did out of love for my country, Your Honor.
As a member of the public,
I strongly sympathized with the president's philosophy,
and decided to take action!
Is that a crime?
How is that a crime? How?
So you did everything voluntarily?
- Yes. - You take full responsibility?
(Counsel, Defendant)
- Yes. - Very well.
Counsel.
Like your client,
do you also sympathize with the president's philosophy?
Of course, I do.
During a crisis, we must support our leader.
Then we have our answer.
The appropriate punishment.
Our president already has the answer.
To make Korea...
a strong and proper, decent country,
what do we need? In three words?
The death penalty.
Criminals are just insects.
Why should we spend tax money...
to feed and shelter them?
It's all because of hypocrites...
who cry about human rights.
Murderers who took lives.
Judges just give them 10 to 20 years.
Does that make sense?
On Heo Joong Se's show that is so refreshing,
that can never be accepted.
Listen up.
The price of a person's life...
should be paid for with a life.
Do you get that? Do you understand?
Eye, eye, tooth, tooth.
That is the second lesson for today.
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.
Also, useless members of counsel who get sentimental and say...
it's because one was brought up...
in a bad environment and was traumatized by abuse.
They should all be arrested.
A strong law and order,
a more powerful nation!
Take out the enemy with their own blade.
- Korea will become... - What Kang Yo Han's really after...
Get down here!
You made all the decisions...
and were given no orders.
If you wish to take responsibility, then do so.
However...
it must be a life for a life!
[VIU Ver] tvN E14 'The Devil Judge'
"A Life For A Life"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
As the most appropriate penalty for this crime,
I suggest death!
- Your Honor! - That is nonsense.
No one has ever been sentenced to death for killing one man.
Is one death not enough?
Must we wait until the defendant kills 2, 3, 4 more people?
Is the life of a murderer...
more valuable than the life of a victim?
The defendant grew up in a poor...
If you want to get sentimental, just give it a darn rest.
Not everyone who grew up poor commits crimes.
(Counsel, Defendant)
This court will treat every criminal fairly and equally.
Humans are dignified because we take responsibility.
Cheap pity is an insult to our humanity.
Ladies and gentlemen.
What is the correct penalty for a murderer?
How can he pay for the blood of the victim?
(National Vote Status)
(Death Penalty: Against, For)
(Hourly Graph)
(For)
Thank you for showing us your yearning for justice.
Justice must not end in just words.
A penalty that is not carried out...
is fraud, not justice.
I demand that justice be served.
The electric chair?
The death penalty will be carried out in 24 hours.
Right here in this hall.
I'm sorry.
(What's your choice?)
With your own hands, let justice be served.
The more you vote in favor of his death,
the higher the voltage of the electric chair.
We need over one million votes for the defendant to die.
I will see you tomorrow.
Your Honor.
Wait.
Your Honor!
Wait. Your Honor.
(Supreme Court)
Does he want to turn the court into a slaughterhouse?
Oh, my gosh...
What is he up to?
That is what Kang Yo Han really wants.
Fear.
That's also why he gave the public 24 hours.
He wants Juk Chang...
to get so scared he'll tell the truth to the world.
Before the entire nation.
What a heartless jerk.
Is he even human? Gosh.
What are you going to do, Mr. President?
We should keep him quiet, shouldn't we?
We must get rid of him. Send someone to his cell and...
Park Du Man!
Do you want to advertise that we gave him orders?
What do you suggest then?
I'll...
keep him quiet.
How?
I know how to deal with a guy like him.
Don't worry. I'm Heo Joong Se.
Don't you know who I am?
Trust me.
I'll take care of it.
Chief, this is not right.
No matter how I look at it, this just isn't right.
Then what do we do?
Are there any alternatives?
Do we have to go this far to make Juk Chang talk?
Are we going to electrocute him using the public?
I asked a question, and the public gave me an answer.
You saw how the majority voted in favor.
Isn't that what democracy is all about?
Then what makes you any different from Heo Joong Se?
If you're so strongly against it,
leave the bench.
Chief.
Can you talk to him?
(Associate Judge Kim Ga On)
Judge Kim, have you seen the news?
Following Judge Kang Yo Han's announcement of the execution,
Chief Justice Min Jung Ho resigned from his office in protest.
This isn't punishment. It's barbarism.
The Supreme Court has been taken over by a mad rabble-rouser.
(Chief Justice Resigns)
I'm leaving the Supreme Court as of today.
(Chief Justice Min Jung Ho)
Professor.
Ga On.
You must stop him.
This is unacceptable.
Kang Yo Han...
is a devil.
He's turning every citizen into a murderer.
I'm sure he's doing this on purpose...
- to make Juk Chang talk... - So?
He's having the public electrocute him...
in the sacred Supreme Court!
You shouldn't trust him.
That serpent is using people's weaknesses...
to ridicule the world.
But Professor,
people with power are harming innocent citizens.
- They even killed Soo Hyun... - Are you sure?
- Pardon? - Are you sure...
they're the ones who killed Soo Hyun?
Who else would have tried to shoot us judges?
- Think about what happened... - Fine.
That's what I thought at first.
But...
something's been bothering me.
Recently, Soo Hyun came to see me.
She told me...
Is everything okay?
Is this about Ga On?
She was worried you were being fooled by Kang Yo Han.
She never liked him anyway.
There's more to it. She was...
digging into Kang Yo Han's past.
The church fire.
That incident?
You know how persistent she can be.
Whenever she had time, she went to that neighborhood...
and looked for people who were involved with the church.
But there was one man...
named Joseph that she couldn't find anywhere...
as if someone hid him away on purpose.
Who is he?
He lived at the church, taking care of all kinds of chores.
His responsibilities included...
managing the CCTV.
Soo Hyun was searching for him.
What if...
she found him in the end...
and Kang Yo Han found it out?
That's just an assumption.
You think Kang Yo Han killed his own brother?
Do you know how much he suffered after his death?
His suffering was completely real.
What if...
he was suffering from guilt?
What if that's why he was hiding his past so desperately...
and Soo Hyun was closing in on it?
Please stop.
I'll be going.
Answer me one thing.
If Soo Hyun saw you...
electrocute a person...
next to Kang Yo Han,
what would she have said?
That doesn't mean a judge can act out like Kang Yo Han.
What you heard and saw are weird enough.
He broke the rules.
That's also a crime.
- And don't get the wrong idea. - What wrong idea?
Whether Kang Yo Han had a reason or not,
nothing changes.
Everyone has a reason.
But not everyone breaks the law.
If Soo Hyun saw you...
electrocute a person...
next to Kang Yo Han,
what would she have said?
(Ministry of Justice)
Ga On, what's going on?
Why are you here?
- Soo Hyun. - What are you doing here?
Do you know what I had to do for you?
I had to destroy the evidence.
How could you disappoint me like that? How could you?
What do I do?
That poor grandpa.
I really had no idea he would die like that.
No. He's going to save me.
He cares for me a lot.
He's not going to abandon me like this.
He won't.
What is it?
What are you doing? Darn it!
What is this?
Stop it!
Mr. President.
("Beyond Good and Evil")
Are you really going to move forward with it?
Is there a reason to stop?
Bad people were the ones who committed a crime,
so why must innocent citizens be punished?
Punished?
Are you saying...
that making people kill someone in the middle of the day...
isn't a punishment?
Is it okay to let someone else kill them instead?
I don't believe in cheap justice...
that people talk about in the comforts of their own homes.
You want someone else...
to fight evil on your behalf without getting your hands dirty?
That just makes them accomplices.
There is no such thing as an innocent person in this world.
No. I disagree.
Even if they can't stand up to fight,
there are a lot more people who do no harm...
and work hard each day.
And in order to protect that world, some people risk their lives.
Just like Dr. Yoon Myung Jin...
and police officers like Soo Hyun.
A world where everyone has blood on their hands is just pandemonium.
You're trying to make the world like that.
The world I was born into was always like that.
Can you please stop?
I don't want to see you go to a place you can't turn back from.
Please.
I don't...
have another choice.
May I ask you something?
What is it?
When we went to the site of forced removals,
did you know that the conflict between...
the residents and the Jukchang troops...
could end with a casualty?
Your neighbors are dying right now.
Are you just going to sit and watch?
Get hit with a rock!
- Chief Kang. - Judge Kang got hit with a rock!
Did he get hurt badly?
Judge Kang!
You ought to be punished!
Darn it!
Kang Yo Han!
Get down here!
Wasn't that your plan all along?
If you want people to fight,
you needed a victim to shed blood.
Is that really what it was?
If you have time to ask me questions,
act.
(National Participation in Kim Choong Sik's Execution)
The time has finally come.
Please get ready.
Are you going to take full responsibility?
Are you sure nobody ordered you to do this?
I already said so. Why do you keep asking,
you evil jerk?
Very well. Fellow citizens. Please execute his sentence.
(Number of Voters)
Is this fun for you?
I'm not going to die.
Why would I die?
I didn't do anything wrong.
You're a true patriot, so why are you suffering like this?
You've been through so much. I mean it.
Have a seat.
Why is a man like you crying?
Did you think I'd abandon you?
It's me. I'm Heo Joong Se.
No, sir. I had complete faith in you.
That's right. You just need to trust me.
Have a bit more faith in me.
You need to sit...
- in that chair for a bit. - What?
That Kang Yo Han is just putting on a show.
He's just threatening you until you say my name.
But still... Are you telling me to die?
Don't be scared.
Just endure it.
If things seem really precarious,
I'll stop it.
I'll cut off all electricity to the Supreme Court to save you.
So don't worry.
This is all for the sake of our nation.
Your wish.
I told you hundreds of thousands of times.
I'll make it come true. I'm serious.
Will you do that, sir?
The thing you've dreamt of all your life.
An apartment that overlooks the Han River.
A permanent position in a state-owned company.
And on top of that, I'll give you a ton of Bitcoins.
Mr. President!
Thank you.
You fool.
You're so brave.
Yes. It's okay. Cry.
Who are you to kill me?
Give it a go.
(Number of Voters)
Members of the public.
You are sovereign.
That is why you must be responsible.
You are sovereign because you show responsibility.
I need you to exercise your ownership.
"Exercise your ownership"?
What a joke.
Will you let him go?
Even so. It's so dreadful.
I can't kill someone myself.
He killed once. Won't he kill again?
He got up to all sorts of evil.
We have to vote.
Let's all vote.
- Vote. - Shall we?
(What's your choice?)
(Number of Voters)
Oh, nice. Wow, I'm feeling it.
(What's your choice?)
Hey, it really worked.
It worked?
Did it go up when you voted?
Yes. I wasn't sure, but it really worked.
Did it?
Should I give it a go?
You jerk.
Yes. The law is the law.
We should vote.
(What's your choice?)
It actually works.
That's fascinating.
(Number of Voters)
I can endure this.
It's fine.
He told me to endure it.
(Number of Voters)
Click yes.
- For real? - I'm not sure.
I must hang in there.
I'll hang in there.
Not bad.
Yes. Okay.
(Number of Voters)
Zap. I zapped you.
Kids.
Press it.
Oh, gosh, no.
Why not?
My gosh.
He told me to endure it.
(Number of Voters)
(What's your choice?)
Your Honor.
The Ministry of Justice just issued an emergency stay of execution.
On whose orders?
Judge Kim Ga On just held a press conference.
The live court show...
was all...
a fake.
(The Devil Judge)
I am a criminal.
Do you fear me?
Don't you want to be a monster like me?
You are just a clown I put here as a puppet.
Kang Yo Han for president!
What now?
He's so lucky.
It belonged to Soo Hyun.
It's time you found out the truth.
I saw it clearly.
Did you meet Joseph?
This is what the young master did his best to hide.
You will regret this.
Forever.
Now you finally look lonely.