(This drama is set in an imaginary dystopian Korea,)
(and all people, organizations, and incidents are fictitious.)
No, Judge.
Don't come up here. Don't!
No, Judge...
Don't come upstairs, please.
Please, don't come here!
Please don't come up here, Judge.
It's dangerous.
I said, don't!
Put that down.
You know,
I want you to be lonely, Young Master.
Like me.
Then perhaps you'd stay by my side.
If there were no one else by your side.
Professor!
Don't do this!
- Let go. - No way.
Professor.
Help us! No, mister!
Mister!
Stop it! Let go!
Let go of me!
Let go!
I won't go!
No!
Darn them.
Don't do this to me!
Let me go!
Let go.
Are you okay? Get out.
Are you okay?
It's okay. Are you okay?
Yes. Thank you.
- Go that way. - Thank you.
Ga On!
It's been a while.
It's me. Don't you remember me?
It has been a long time.
Darn you. Die!
Get him.
I will...
kill you...
in a lonely, miserable way.
In a way that suits you perfectly.
Does it hurt a lot?
Yes.
Too bad.
You need to go and save Ga On.
Go to the Hyungsan-dong slum.
I told you.
That I want you to be dead lonely.
(Redevelopment kills the people. We are against it.)
Lieutenant Yoon? It's Kang Yo Han.
What do you want?
Ga On's in danger. Find him.
What?
The Hyungsan-dong slum. Right now.
Your life really blows.
Just as much as mine.
It was almost over.
You just had to live your own life.
Me...
and you...
The receiver cannot be reached.
Elijah won't pick up.
Elijah...
Gosh, let go of me.
No!
- Where did he go? - Get him!
(221S 3584)
Kim Ga On!
Hey!
(10S 0846)
(72L 0685)
Excuse me.
(Oh my Judge Kim, Hope everything comes up roses.)
(Pandemic Emergency Assistance Destination: Dream Home Village)
(Social Responsibility Foundation)
(221S 3584)
- Soo Hyun. - I'm good if you're not hurt.
But why were you there?
I got a strange phone call.
He told me to go there if I want to save Professor Min.
What are you talking about?
I talked to the professor this morning.
He's resting fine at the hospital.
Are you sure?
Then that son of a gun Juk Chang lied to get me there.
How did you know I was there?
I just...
I got the message from the police radio.
Ladies and gentlemen. A plague virus...
reemerged in the Hyungsan-dong slum.
We can fight this again.
Whatever difficulty we face,
we can overcome it.
Judge.
Judge, you have to get up.
Judge, you have to wake up now.
Judge.
Judge, get up.
Judge, you should get up.
Judge.
- Judge. - Judge.
How are you feeling?
We stopped the bleeding for now.
Are you okay?
People who assisted you are being attacked.
I was worried about you.
I tracked your location and found you here.
We can't find Han So Yoon.
What?
You two go find Han So Yoon.
Hello.
Why aren't you picking up your phone?
Gosh, you startled me.
Why are you yelling? I couldn't get it because I was asleep.
Listen to me carefully.
Whoever comes to our house, do not open the door.
Just stay in your room. Do you understand?
Okay.
A plague virus reemerged in Hyunsan-dong.
It’s an area where a group of people in poverty reside.
The government and Social Responsibility Foundation are...
supporting relief activities for the resident in...
Elijah...
How did you know I like this?
It's delicious.
Where did you buy it?
You and I have the same taste.
It's good.
You're here.
You're late, Judge.
She saw strange men in front of the house.
I could've been in trouble if it wasn't for her.
I heard you asked her to check on me.
Oh, right. I did.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Let me do that for you.
I want you to be lonely, Young Master.
Like me.
Here.
Thank you.
Elijah, why don't you go back to your room?
I need to talk to Ms. Jung.
She can't go.
We just got close. Isn't that right?
You're an interesting person.
I think you and I will get along well...
because we're similar.
We are, aren't we?
We are so similar.
We're both smart and ruthless.
And we're both a little bit broken.
Master Yo Han, this is only the beginning.
My goodness.
But don't cross the line.
Gosh, what am I doing?
I went over the line. Silly me.
I'm sorry, Elijah.
See you later.
What's wrong with her? She's weird.
Why are you sweating so much?
Did something happen to you?
No.
What is this?
Is this blood?
I'm okay.
I'm okay, Elijah.
I'm okay now.
You said you didn't get hurt.
I'm sorry,
Soo Hyun.
For what?
For putting you through all that.
When Cha Kyung Hee died.
You don't have to apologize.
I've never been a great cop anyway.
I know that Kang Yo Han's ways are not right.
I know that it's illegal for a judge to do that.
But I can't stand it.
If I don't do this, I'll go crazy.
I don't deserve to be next to you.
I've been a nuisance to you since we were little.
I know it's shameless,
but I can't live without you.
I think I'll really die.
You're such a fool.
I've had enough.
I can't stand the stupid things you say anymore.
- Soo Hyun. - Can't you see?
I don't care whether or not you deserve something.
I don't know what's right and wrong or what's happening to the world.
But please...
don't make me see you in danger again.
Don't cry.
Don't become miserable.
Please stop ruining your life.
That's all I need, Ga On.
You're all I need,
Ga On.
I'll get going. I need to make sure everything's okay outside.
You stay put.
There might be another attack. Bye.
Soo Hyun.
- See you. - Wait, Soo Hyun...
What was his name, Juk Chang?
I like the way he handles things.
He's quite bold.
- He works extremely fast. - Yes.
Those who have nothing to lose are often good at their jobs.
Ms. Jung, what about those who were helping Judge Kang?
Have they been taken care of?
Yes, most of them were picked up by the evacuation bus.
Human lives come first, right?
I'm glad that you know that.
Come in.
Come on in.
Are you done filming the emergency broadcast?
You're doing a good job.
Judge Oh, our trusted judge,
has put the citizens at ease.
- Give her a big hand! - Way to go!
By the way, how serious is the situation?
I heard that the mutant virus is quite deadly.
I'm worried about its effect on the working-class residential area.
Don't worry too much.
Emergency measures have been taken...
throughout the area.
Instead of just filming a broadcast,
maybe I should go out there and help...
Hold on a second.
I think it's best...
to leave that to professionals. Don't you agree?
Of course.
Okay, I understand.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Judge Oh, you should start getting ready.
Pardon?
To become the presiding judge.
Let's have a drink together sometime.
Following the breakout of the mutant virus in Hyungsan-dong,
the Dream Home Village project is progressing...
faster than initially planned.
As a result, Social Responsibility Foundation is raising additional...
Stay put...
- and get good rest. - Director Jung will be leading...
- Thank you. - efforts to contain the virus...
and develop medicine.
If you'd like to make a donation,
you can find more information...
on the foundation's official website.
We look forward to your active participation.
Are you okay?
How did you get hurt so badly?
It's no big deal.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
Don't worry. I'll stay healthy...
until you can stand on your own feet and kill me.
What?
What are you talking about?
- Do you think I'll be worried? - Moving on.
President Heo will make an emergency statement shortly.
He will be delivering the government's position...
on the mutant virus situation in Hyungsan-dong.
All citizens are asked to pay attention.
- Hello? - Mr. Ko.
Judge Kang, are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Have you found Ms. Han yet?
What about the others?
I think they got taken away by the foundation.
Using evacuation as an excuse,
they're taking people away as they like.
In this emergency situation, all citizens' lives are at risk.
From now on,
the press must follow the government's instructions.
Also, a 10pm curfew will be introduced.
This morning, the government rounded up...
a group of rebels who disturbed public order...
by spreading false rumors...
and is currently looking into those who are behind them.
We can't find Han So Yoon.
Have you found Ms. Han yet?
I think they got taken away by the foundation.
Despite the terrible events from 10 years ago...
Whenever I see you, Judge Kang, I feel bad for you.
Judge Kang, what happened?
Since I don't have a promising future,
am I supposed to put up with it?
Yo Han.
Is this your method?
You're cutting off the people who are right next to you,
so how do you intend to fight against people who move the world?
That's my method.
That won't change in the future.
You know what kind of people we're up against.
They're going to be more high-spirited now.
You don't know what they will do next.
I never mistook my actions for justice.
I am just making certain choices.
Judge Kang Yo Han...
is stirring up lunacy and violence in our country.
We will consider all interferences to emergency disease prevention...
and emergency rescue attempts as murder,
and they will be charged with the maximum sentence.
What if that blade turns to face you?
They turned a crisis into an opportunity.
This is how the ones who conquer the world work.
I can't stand such people being hypocrites too.
It makes me nauseous.
Monster?
You're not even brave enough to face your pains.
No.
Does this fight seem like a joke to you?
You must stop.
You are ruining the world.
Do not be afraid everyone.
We will win no matter what.
We will overcome this crisis without fail,
and we will show the world that we are...
the best nationality in the world!
So please have faith in...
me and this nation.
Yo Han, can you promise me something?
Can you promise me something?
Don't hurt innocent people.
I'm sorry, Isaac.
I can't keep my promise.
The Social Responsibility Foundation has the tremendous responsibility...
to prevent the mutated virus from spreading in Seoul,
and they are doing everything in their power to move...
the residents of Hyungsan-dong to the Dream Home Village...
to provide them with treatment and relief measures.
The Social Responsibility Foundation is working alongside the government,
and is led by...
Judge Kim.
All of that is a bald-faced lie.
Do you know what's going on outside?
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
Things are chaotic because of the virus.
They're dragging people away like they're a pack of animals.
The news? That's all fake.
The foundation made it all up.
That doesn't make sense.
I saw and experienced it myself.
The Jukchang troops did this to me.
They are beating people up with metal pipes.
You were attacked?
You know what scares me even more?
No matter how much I think about it,
I think that the virus itself...
is a lie.
Hold on.
Judge Kim. You're completely sane, right?
They claim that this mutated virus is fatal with a high death rate,
but they chose Juk Chang, who is nothing more than a thug,
to be at the front lines.
He doesn't wear proper protective gear and only feigns wearing a mask.
Think about it.
Juk Chang was an administrator of Heo Joong Se's private guards.
How could they put a criminal who used to wear an electronic anklet...
on the front lines of disinfection during a national emergency?
Judge Oh.
You're being used.
The streets are filled with videos of you...
I'm sorry.
You seem to be too upset right now.
I don't know what kind of excessive measures are being taken out there,
but you want me to believe in what you're saying?
Don't you think you're going too far?
Judge Oh.
At times like this, we need to take calm and orderly actions.
I'm just helping with that.
I didn't see you in the courthouse.
Is something wrong?
I heard you got hurt.
I'm fine. More than that...
Do you know what's going on right now?
I'm glad that you're fine.
We'll talk about that later.
Hello? Hello?
Come in.
Hello, Judge Kang.
Come have a seat.
I've been told that I have a good figure,
but I don't look good in this.
It's so ugly.
We need to become more developed in this area first.
What are you trying to start?
What am I trying to start?
I'm trying to protect the nation and its people from an epidemic.
By using a private organization...
to drag away the poor?
Is that what you're talking about?
Then what do you want me to do?
Should I leave the ten million who live in Seoul to die...
just to protect the rights of 10,000?
Ten million is significantly more than ten thousand, isn't it?
Don't you know basic arithmetic?
Furthermore, when this situation is over, people will be happier.
Why? Because Seoul will be cleaner...
and the cost of apartments will go up.
That's how humans are.
Is there...
even a virus?
Seeing you now, you're just a lunatic.
Hey. Why would you joke around like that...
during a state of national crisis?
Let me get straight to the point.
Stop doing all of this.
Cease it.
What if I don't want to?
I'm going to put everything you did...
on the live court show and reveal the truth behind everything.
Until angry people...
set this place on fire...
and drag you out like a mutt.
Those who have nothing in their hands...
always try to act tough.
How dare you threaten me when you have nothing?
Do you think it will work?
Don't kid yourself.
The citizens...
are scared out of their minds. Who would they believe?
Me, who tells them strangers are dangerous and to stay at home,
or you, who tells them to go out and save strangers on the street?
Who do you think they will choose?
You seem to be overconfident because you've gained some popularity,
but don't kid yourself. Don't be mistaken.
The people who are obsessed with you...
and the people who made me president...
are no different from each other.
They're all the same, okay?
Listen to me carefully.
I'm going to say something intelligent.
Those who created me...
are the same people who created you, you punk.
Got it?
If you insist on testing your luck...
You look good in yellow.
[VIU Ver] tvN E13 'The Devil Judge'
"To Kill or To Be Killed"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
This is a restricted area. Please step back.
Judge Oh.
Is everything going well in there?
Pardon?
(Police)
Open up for her.
The plague virus reemerged in the Hyungsan-dong slum.
(Police)
Whatever difficulty we face,
we can overcome it.
(Police)
Ladies and gentlemen. A plague virus...
reemerged in the Hyungsan-dong slum.
We can fight this again.
Whatever difficulty we face,
we can overcome it.
(We oppose the redevelopment that kills residents of shantytowns.)
- Is this the police officer? - Yes, ma'am.
Remember how you asked me to call...
if I remembered anything?
About Joseph, who took care of the chapel.
Yes.
Someone told me they saw a person who resembled Joseph...
in a town in Seoul,
but I'm not sure how accurate that is.
It's okay, so tell me everything.
Yes.
- Ga On. - Hey.
I told you to stay inside. What are you doing out here?
I had a feeling you were coming.
Shut your mouth. Let's just go inside.
Soo Hyun.
What?
What happened earlier.
It's not like anything happened.
I won't apologize, but...
I think I got the order wrong.
The order?
Do you know how timid I am?
I trembled in fear all day today.
What if things get awkward between us?
What if I ruined everything?
I thought so my whole life.
What if we...
get together,
then fight over nothing like others,
misunderstand, get jealous, and get upset,
and then...
break up, what then?
You are all I have.
If I lose you too,
I won't have anyone.
If we stay friends,
the best friends in the world,
I thought I'd never feel lonely.
I'm stupid, aren't I?
And selfish.
But I can't do this anymore.
I don't care about anything else.
Even if we fight over nothing like others,
misunderstand, get jealous, and get upset...
I want to like you forever.
I like you a lot, Soo Hyun.
Kang Yo Han.
Do you think he really has something?
Disease Control, the press, the prosecution, the police,
we're in control of them all.
If we say a virus exists, it exists.
How can he prove it doesn't?
It's not like he can go around with a microscope.
Still, I have this bad feeling.
If I could have my way,
I'd love to bury him where no one will find him.
If we were to do that, the country would flip out.
Ms. Jung, share an idea if you have any.
If he is given a warning and he doesn't heed,
we must blow him up.
That is exactly how I feel. But if we were to do that...
First, get rid of the stage.
The stage?
A star only shines when he or she is on a stage.
Without a stage,
a star is just another person.
Ga On. Ga On, wake up.
The government decided to disband the live court show.
To combat the current nationwide emergency we're facing,
we will establish an emergency court.
The emergency court will rule on cases regarding...
the disruption of pandemic assistance or relocation,
the spreading of slander,
and illegal gatherings and protests.
Judge Oh Jin Joo will preside over the emergency court,
and associate judges will be selected from applicants...
with a strong sense of nationalism.
- This is crazy. - That's all.
Soo Hyun. We have to stop this.
They're lying to the public.
Chief Kang's the only one who can stop them.
Not Kang Yo Han.
It's true that what's going on is strange,
but how can we trust Kang Yo Han? He's dangerous.
- Soo Hyun. - Wait.
Give me some time.
I'll find out who he is.
I'm almost there, Ga On.
Soo Hyun, please. Trust me this once.
We have to stop this no matter what.
Whatever Kang Yo Han is, we can find out afterward.
Okay?
Soo Hyun.
Can it be done?
It must be done even if it is impossible.
I'll call those who are left of our people.
We do have someone who can get into the main control room.
Chief.
I'll call you back, Lawyer Ko.
Won't you do anything?
Right now, out there,
innocent people are getting beaten up and dragged off.
Will you just sit and watch?
Say something...
(Old house, blue gate, uphill)
(2-10, Ryangjin-ro, 6-gil)
Hello?
- Hello. - Hello.
I'd like to ask you something. Do you know this man?
No.
Okay, then. Thanks.
Hello?
Congratulations, Judge Oh.
Chief of the Emergency Court.
You must become the chief justice and then head the Supreme Court.
I'll see to that.
Why don't you do it properly, then?
- What? - Judge Kang Yo Han.
You may put him down, but he's still very popular.
If I'm to become the presiding chief,
I must beat him in popularity.
Don't you remember his inauguration speech?
He said, "I am power."
Your beginning should have more of an impact?
Yes.
What you see is what you get. My image.
But a certificate of appointment can't give me that.
I'll only look like a cheater...
who took her superior's place.
What do you want then?
Do you want to give a speech?
Yes, at the very place where Kang Yo Han did,
with Kang Yo Han and Kim Ga On sitting behind me.
(Chairman Park Du Man)
Will Kang Yo Han agree to do that?
I'll persuade him.
(Chairman Park Du Man)
"I can't let you step down like this."
"I'll prepare a short goodbye broadcast."
"Let me honor your achievements that way."
(Chairman Park Du Man)
So basically, you want a coronation.
Kang Yo Han transferring his crown to you himself.
Wouldn't that be beautiful?
I'm sure we'll get high viewer ratings as well.
If it's an exclusive broadcast on such a hot topic,
high viewer ratings are guaranteed, I guess.
This is driving me crazy.
This is the most successful show I've ever made.
Is it really going to end like this?
Are we getting fired?
I heard there will be an emergency court instead.
Come on.
Do you think people will watch it?
It reminds me of an emergency court-martial.
Hello, Judge Oh.
Yes.
I'm so touched that I want to cry, Judge Oh.
Please don't take this the wrong way.
I meant what I said.
Please accept it.
Well... It's only while the emergency situation lasts.
Once things settle down,
I'm sure the live court show will resume.
Tell people that you're letting Judge Oh take over until then.
That way, you'll be able to get back smoothly later.
So you need sidekicks. Is that it,
Judge Oh?
Judge Kim, don't be like that.
Let's do it.
Chief Kang.
But make sure things look good.
Please consider my position.
You don't have to worry about that.
I'll bet my entire career on this.
Hello?
Who is it?
- Hello, I'm from the RIU. - Okay.
Do you know a man named Jung Joseph?
There's no one here by that name.
Have you ever seen a man who looks like this around here?
No, I haven't. Don't you know what kind of situation we're in?
Hello?
Who is it?
Mr. Jung Joseph?
Just a second. I'm Officer Yoon Soo Hyun from the RIU.
(285S 7511)
I have a feeling we'll get amazing viewer ratings.
Everyone will be stuck home, staring at the TV anyway.
- Are we stopping for lunch? - What?
They seem to be taking a detour.
You're right.
They didn't say anything about it.
Are they looking for a bathroom?
Hello, Judge Oh.
We still have some time, right?
Let's stop somewhere for lunch.
Sure, let's do that.
Okay.
We're stopping for lunch.
Check the commercial time.
Yes, sir.
You can't enter here.
What's going on?
What's happening?
Come here.
We're ready to roll.
Are there even any restaurants here?
I'm sorry.
But I'll make sure you get incredible viewer ratings.
- I promise. - All right.
What is this?
What's going on here?
What are they doing?
We need to show the world...
what is happening here.
Count me in.
Judge Oh.
Judge Kim, I've seen what's going on.
I know I can't be forgiven even if I say I didn't know.
I'll do anything.
I'll do everything I can.
Do you mean that?
Yes, Chief Kang.
Great. Then we can make things look more natural.
Yes, we should.
If I see this...
and don't film it, I should just quit my job.
Gather around!
- What's the matter? - Hey!
You go and get the equipment.
Change of plan. I'm sorry.
But please trust me and do as I say.
I'll leave it to you.
It's time for a trial.
A trial?
Put these on first.
It's time to go on stage.
Judge Kang.
You can leave this place to me.
Please.
(We don't want redevelopment!)
(Police, Social Responsibility Foundation)
Are all cameras on the rooftop?
Yes, they are.
Okay. Be careful.
Team A, shoot the judges.
Teams B and C, take close-up shots of the scene.
Teams B and C, shoot the entire scene!
I'll be following Judge Kang around.
When will the generator be here?
- It's too late... - The sun is setting soon.
I'll take full responsibility.
Hold on.
Attention.
Attention!
(We don't want redevelopment!)
Dear fellow citizens.
This is the Hyungsan-dong emergency rescue site.
What? What is that?
As you can see, this is the truth.
(The Live Court Show Reveals the Truth About...)
(the Hyungsan-dong Emergency Rescue Site)
Oh, my. Is this for real?
All of the footage you have seen so far was a lie.
The government is hiding the truth...
- and committing state violence. - What... What...
are you airing right now? What is this?
Are you in your right mind?
Oh, it's not that...
Stop talking nonsense and end this broadcast right now!
Hurry up! Right now!
Darn it.
Call Juk Chang and tell him to get rid of Kang Yo Han.
Got it?
What are you doing? You're getting paid by the government,
so do your jobs!
Yes, sir!
Everyone.
Please open up the DIKE app...
and judge.
(What is your choice?)
Get them!
- Get them! - Go!
- Get them! - Get them!
You little... Get out of the way!
- Get them! - Drag them away!
- Hurry! - Get them out of here!
Kill them all!
- What are you doing? - Grab him!
- Over there! - Stop right there!
Throw things at them!
Go get them!
- Get them! - Throw rocks!
Hey! Go after them!
- Judge Oh. - Oh, my.
Your neighbors are dying right now.
Are you just going to sit and watch?
Get him!
The government is covering your eyes.
It's time for you to open your eyes.
Sir! Open the door!
Stop the broadcast!
Open the door!
- Move! - Nobody is responding.
- Hey! - Open the door!
Open the door!
(Live Court Show Reveals Truth About Hyungsan-dong Rescue Site)
Get them!
You got him!
Are you okay, Ga On?
(We oppose the redevelopment that kills residents of shantytowns.)
- Are you okay? - Yes, I'm fine.
Keep going.
(Judge Kim Ga On Attacked)
Ga On.
Director. Over here.
Okay. Be careful.
- You punk! - Get over here!
Drag them out!
Get them!
- Please let us go! - Stop!
Get down here!
- Come at us! - Come down.
- Get them! - Keep attacking them!
- Get them down here! - Get them!
Hit them!
Chief Kang.
Judge Kang got hit with a rock!
Judge Kang got hit with a rock.
Judge Kang!
You ought to be punished!
Darn it!
No.
- Don't do anything! - Just stay quiet.
Wait... He's...
Stop.
Sir...
Why are you doing this?
- Sir! - Oh, no!
He's going to kill him!
Kang Yo Han!
Get down here!
Kim Choong Sik!
Sir!
- Why did you get involved? - Oh, no.
You should come down now.
Right?
Come down.
How could he do such a thing?
My gosh! Turn off the electricity at the station or that entire area!
Just turn it off!
Just turn off all the electricity.
(Government Indiscriminately Assaults Residents of Hyungsan-dong)
I'm not kidding. Do it.
I ought to break every TV out there.
I'm going to kill the punks at the broadcast station!
(MBN)
(Government Indiscriminately Assaults Residents of Hyungsan-dong)
(We don't want redevelopment!)
What?
- What is this? - What, you punk?
- It's still on the DIKE app. - Really?
I guess the electricity is out there too.
You're right.
Are the lights ready over there?
Okay. Get ready.
Hold on.
- What's he doing? - What the...
Let's take out our cellphones too.
- Let's do that. - Right.
- What is this? - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - Sit back down!
Turn off your flashlights!
- Darn it. - Turn them off!
- Turn it off! - Turn it off!
What? What are you doing?
- Turn it off! - What?
What will turning on your flashlights do?
What will it do?
- Turn it off! - Get ready.
Turn it off!
- No! - We won't!
- Turn it off! - What are you doing?
- Hey! - Turn it off!
- What are you doing? - Turn it on!
- Ready. - Darkness...
Go.
can't beat the light.
Okay. Number two. Get ready.
Darkness...
can't beat the light.
Go.
(DIKE, What is your choice?)
(DIKE)
- What the... - Surround them!
What is this?
- Go! - Go after them!
Let go of me!
He disgusts me so much.
- Good job. - Thanks.
- Well done. - My gosh.
You did well.
(285S 7511)
(221S 3584)
Ga On.
- Ga On. - Soo Hyun.
What are you doing here?
Wait.
No!
Soo Hyun.
Soo... Soo Hyun.
No. No way.
No, Soo Hyun.
No.
You got hurt.
Soo Hyun, no.
I told you not to get hurt. Why did you get hurt?
No.
- Soo Hyun. - Don't cry.
Don't get hurt, Ga On.
No...
No.
I mean it.
Soo Hyun.
Ga On, I love you.
I love you.
No. Soo Hyun.
Soo Hyun.
No, Soo Hyun.
No!
Someone, help her!
(The Devil Judge)
(Special thanks to Park Hyung Soo.)
It feels horrible.
I get it. I live it every day.
If there are people trying to stop this trial,
they are criminals.
We must cut off the loose ends.
You don't have feelings of regret, do you?
To get them to fight each other,
you need the blood of a sacrifice?
That is what Kang Yo Han really wants.
Fear.
Are you sure who killed Soo Hyun?
A life for a life!
I suggest death!
My child wanted to attend this school.
You've received an invitation...
Who did it?
Who brought me and my child here?
Who tortured us until now?
Why me?
(High Class)