[English subtitles are available]
[The Flowers Are Blooming]
[Episode 22]
Master has been standing here for two hours.
Go persuade her to go back to the house.
But the princess told us not to disturb her.
If she stays like this,
she'll catch a cold.
You can go back.
I'll go talk to her.
You don't like the hairpin with mechanism?
I give you a new one.
What do you think?
Under this situation,
you still have the mood to make a hairpin?
Let me put it on for you.
No.
This hairpin
took me a lot of work.
I went to many jewelry shops
and asked many girls in Lin'an.
Also,
I studied the royal jewelry of the previous dynasty and the present dynasty
so as to make this unique hairpin.
You really don't want it?
You went to shops?
You asked girls?
You don't know how anxious I am now.
No wonder you've been feeling listless.
It turns out that you're doing such useless things.
How is that useless?
It's important
to make my love prettier.
But you don't even help me
before I leave.
Langyue.
I have an idea.
What is it?
Fill the depressions with soil.
I have an idea.
Take this hairpin,
then I'll tell you.
Look.
This is the chorography of Lin'an.
Here, here, here.
Three points.
They are the three soil-transporting places closest to the Sanjun Tower.
Isn't this place closer?
What's the purpose of setting these landmarks?
Don't worry.
Let me finish.
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
You are right.
These two points are indeed the closest to the Sanjun Tower.
But even so, we won't have enough time.
But what if
we take the water route?
Water route?
Where is it?
Look.
We can dig out a river bed
in this place
and divert water into it.
Then we can transport the soil with ships.
It can improve efficiency.
I have calculated.
In this way,
it will take half a month at most
to fill bottomland
in low-lying areas near the Sanjun Tower.
What's wrong?
All right. All right.
Problem solved.
You should go back to your room to sleep.
You’ve been
too tired recently.
It's all your fault. You wasted your time making that hairpin.
Indeed.
You are right.
In this case,
I’ll throw it away
so that you won't be annoyed.
How can you do that?
You made this for me.
How could you have it back?
I'm going back to sleep.
Petty.
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
What do you think?
It seems
we still need to go to the Ministry of War.
I've been thinking about it every night,
but I still can't figure it out.
Maybe only the Arrow-making House will find the answer.
Architect Li.
Don't expect too much.
If the Arrow-making House is capable to create a super bow,
the Southern Xiao wouldn't be subject to Northern Zhou.
We can only bet on luck.
[Ministry of War]
[Super Bow Draft]
Go.
[Sanjun Tower]
[Super Bow Draft]
[There was a godlike construction]
[Two pillars, each full length.]
I...
♫The wind stopped in the story of flowers♫
♫Waiting for people to listen♫
♫The moon hidden in the boundless night sky♫
♫Looking for its dreamboat to find♫
♫I'm trapped in an endless universe♫
♫You are the starry night sky♫
♫Every single word♫
♫Is never heard but familiar♫
♫Like we have been in chemistry since we were born♫
♫The wind chased the moon for a thousand miles♫
♫Write the most romantic poem of my life♫
♫You are my unexpected scenery♫
♫It's the first time I feel my heart flip♫
Does your beauty
♫Not knowing why♫
entitle you to disturb my sleep?
♫Just let it pass by♫
♫The moon has seen my hair get lifted by the wind♫
I'm going to ask them to work.
♫It also knows what I hope most for the lengthy life♫
♫I have no courage to guess our ending♫
This scene is quite spectacular.
So pity that
Luo Ye is not here to see how amazing this is.
You think it’s amazing?
Maybe in Boss Luo’s heart,
what he does now
matters more.
I wonder if Boss Luo
can bring sister Han back.
If he can't,
he doesn't deserve to be my boss.
Don't worry. I trust him.
Do you trust me?
What did you say?
Nothing.
I miss you so much.
Why are you so anxious?
Rest assured.
Since Han Niaoniao and I get engaged,
she won't be able to run away,
as well as the Han family’s business.
Won't your children have Han as their surname?
Just for two years.
After the old man dies,
my children will switch their surname to Dong.
Are you going to take my family property
to your family as well?
We're family.
Qi is Dong.
Dong is Qi.
Give me a kiss.
[Han's Mansion]
Let go.
Lord Han.
You can't go in.
This is a good friend of Miss Han.
Let go of me!
-You can't go in. -Lord Han.
You again?
Lord, he...
You brat!
How dare you go after us like this?
Lord Han, don't be angry.
I'm not here for Niaoniao.
Do you think I'll buy that?
Tell me.
How much do you want?
If 1,000 taels are not enough, I'll pay you another 1,000 taels.
[Issued by Wanchang private bank]
Not to mention 1000 taels,
even 10,000 taels or more,
I won't care if it's not mine.
[Issued by Wanchang private bank]
Money can buy all treasures in the world,
but you can't buy my true love for Niaoniao.
What on earth do you want?
If I tell you...
I came here rashly
to do a big business with the Han family...
Young man, what do you want to do?
I took the scissors
from Niaoniao's room.
Why don't you come with me,
and you'll know the real meaning of the scissors?
Please.
Excuse me, another pot of wine.
Got it!
[Han's Banking House]
I am Zhao Yunjie,
the second son of the Zhao family in Lin'an.
I want to talk to Boss Dong.
Mr. Zhao.
I brought the accountant
to do a good account with Boss Dong.
Please.
Boss Dong.
Have you thought about
what we discussed at noon?
It's indeed a good business.
But after thinking about it at noon,
I still have a little doubt.
I often meet the 7th son of the Zhao family
in Yangzhou.
But the second son...
It's understandable.
He does come to Yangzhou often.
Sometimes, Ning also comes with him.
I don't come often
because I'm always at Shouchun.
There's something wrong with his goldfish.
He has no appetite for food every day
and couldn't sleep at night.
My father had no choice
but to ask me to come.
I heard that he treats goldfish as his life.
In that case,
I understand now.
Ning was supposed to come this time,
but she recently invested
a craftsman team called Wood Feather House.
It is helping with the official expansion of the Fengjiang Tower.
So she has no time to come.
I heard that Miss Zhao is a genius in investment.
She is even doing business with the court now.
Recently, Ning fell in love with
an architect.
I'm afraid it's hard
to persuade him to marry into our family.
Men of our state have integrity.
Naturally, it's hard to persuade him.
But I heard that Boss Dong...
I...
Never mind.
Okay.
Let's not talk about these trivial matters.
Anyway,
I'll take you as the successor of the Han family.
Let's get down to business.
Are you going to do
the business of smuggling salt and iron?
The Han family started their business by doing building business,
and then they built the shops on their own,
becoming the largest trader in Yangzhou.
With huge quantities of goods coming in and out every day,
it shouldn't be difficult
to sell salt and iron.
But this is smuggling after all.
Zhao, do you understand what I mean?
Of course I understand your concern.
But you heard it just now.
Our family can
do business with the court.
We have our own ways and connections.
And I will try my best to put the Han family behind the scenes.
I won’t let those big shots
hear anything about the Han family.
Just make your money.
You can also make a lot of profits for the Han family.
Why not do it?
If it can be done successfully,
you can tell Mr. Han with confidence
that you'll marry his daughter
instead of marrying into the Han family.
I didn't expect you
have already seen through my thoughts.
So... You are in?
This is a big deal.
I think...
I think it's better to work with the Qi family.
The Qi family?
Yes.
To be honest,
I can't make decisions in the Han family.
But it's different in the Qi family.
In the Qi family,
I'm not a son-in-law
but a nephew.
Besides, Han Zhongzheng is so stubborn.
He won't work with us.
Long before Han Niaoniao appeared,
I had been with the eldest daughter of the Qi family.
And Mr. Qi helped me a lot.
He hid me and entrusted me with a important task.
He hoped that one day
I can lead the Qi family
to make it the richest family in Yangzhou.
But I heard that you
are going to marry Miss Han.
I can divorce her after we get married.
She can be downgraded as a concubine if we can't divorce.
We are all businessmen.
Zhao, don’t you understand?
You are indeed brilliant.
But I also heard that Mr. Han
also appreciates you, Boss Dong.
Nonsense.
He treats me as a dog of the Han family.
I can’t go west if he tells me to go east.
He's always ordering me.
Even if I have a baby, it'll have to surname Han.
If I hadn't deducted some money,
I would have starved to death in Han's mansion.
Mr. Han? Bullshit!
He's just a hateful old man.
Bastard.
I...
Bastard, you're going to jail!
You...
No, dad.
Listen to me.
My lord, we found Dong Dacheng’s ledger.
It has been sent to the government office.
Are you satisfied?
Isn't this what you want?
No.
What I want is Niaoniao.
Niaoniao.
You told me
Dong Dacheng was up to something.
But I didn’t listen to you.
You must be very sad.
Say something.
Uncle,
please give her some more time.
Yes, I am very sad.
Father, I've always listened to you since I was young.
I have never done anything against you.
But in the end, you would rather believe an outsider,
a villain who humiliated me.
I can’t accept it.
But...
But I did it for your own good.
I know you did it for me.
You asked me to eat
to grow up.
You asked me to play the guqin
to become virtuous.
You asked me to study supervision
to do business.
You asked me to marry Dong Dacheng
so that I won’t be wronged.
But, father,
did you ask me
if I want it or not?
So,
what you want is
to be a maid in Lin'an.
Yes.
I'm willing to live in Lin'an,
and go back to the Wood Feather House
to be with my friends.
I don't want to be controlled by you anymore.
I want to
be with Luo Ye
in this life.
Me... Me too.
I... I really want to.
My daughter,
I was wrong.
Father...
[Han's Mansion]
All right.
Let's go.
Father.
This job
is very meaningful
for everyone in Wood Feather House.
So I must go back
and face it with everyone.
When the work is over,
I will go home and give you an explanation.
Fine.
I’ll wait for you to go home.
Don’t worry, uncle.
This is also my home.
I will bring back Niaoniao.
Don't be too proud.
I haven't accepted you yet.
We will see what will happen
between you two.
I understand.
Uncle, after this work is over,
I will give you and Niaoniao an explanation.
Alright.
Go now.
Dad, I'm leaving.
Go home early.
Go.
We're back.
Qingfeng, Miss Chen.
Officer, Luo.
Why is nobody here?
Maybe they have gone to work?
Mr. Luo, sister Niaoniao.
You’re back. Good for you, bro.
You brought back Niaoniao.
Of course.
What are you doing?
I received your report yesterday,
and learned that you are back today.
So we have prepared some dishes and meat
to welcome you back tonight.
Don't... Don't bother.
It's a great thing
that you brought back Niaoniao.
Of course we have to celebrate.
I mean
Miss Chen is worried about work.
I heard she's in trouble.
So...
It’s settled.
Settled?
Look at you.
Have some confidence in our Wood Feather House, OK?
It was just a small problem
which can be solved easily.
How did you solve it?
It’s not urgent.
Let's talk while eating tonight.
OK. Let's go inside.
Let's go.
Cheers.
Cool!
The wine I bought is so refreshing.
I knew Qingfeng would find a way.
So,
in half a month,
all the depressions will be filled.
Three days later, the river will be open to navigation.
If nothing happens,
we can fill the depressions in 12 days.
Nothing will happen.
I have contacted
all boatmen in Lin'an.
Don't worry about the soil-transportation.
It won't be late.
Great. That's great.
Then drink.
And tell us
how you brought a beauty from Yangzhou.
That's right.
Fill up my glass if you want to hear stories.
Cheers.
Come on.
[Wood Feather House]
The Sanjun Tower is finally ready.
You all worked very hard.
Come on, eat.
Come on. Drink more.
Yes.
Drink more.
Look at him.
Why did you run away from drinking?
♫How many times I miss you at night♫
♫All I say in my sleep is your name♫
Look.
The moon tonight is so beautiful.
♫I feel so safe♫
♫My dreams are all about you♫
The breeze.
Bright moonlight(Langyue).
♫How many times I travel back in time♫
And the flowers are blooming.
♫Just want to meet you again♫
♫I am so lucky♫
Nerd.
♫You did not give up♫
♫You'll step on the colorful clouds♫
After I leave,
♫You'll show me the world♫
you have to take care of yourself.
♫But I can't guess our ending♫
You have to take good care of everyone in the Wood Feather House.
♫I want to be a butterfly♫
Do you hear me?
I don't want to make this promise.
♫Fly round and round♫
♫Fly into your arms♫
♫Ask your heart♫
♫Even if only a drop♫
♫A drop, a drop♫
♫A drop of love is left♫
♫I would love to♫
[Yinglie Hall]
Serve the incense.
I set up the Sanjun Tower
to worship the soldiers who died
for our country.
They also embody the spirit of the army.
From now on,
the spirits of the army will return to the Sanjun Tower.
The Xiao soldiers should constantly strive to become stronger.
The spirits of the army will return to the Sanjun Tower.
Your Majesty.
[Beautiful clothes and dresses of four seasons]
[Li's Sichuan-Chongqing variety shop]
[Hanyuan Hall]
Summon the Crown Prince of the Northern Zhou, Yelv Zhigu, to the court.
I, Yelv Zhigu, a foreign minister,
greet to Your Majesty.
Long live Your Majesty.
It's a good thing that the Sanjun Tower is built.
Why are you all so calm?
How about this?
I'll be the host today.
Let's get drunk.
How about Zuixian Restaurant?
Nonsense.
I really want to kill He Zhigu.
Don't be angry.
I'm angry. I'm too angry.
Calm down, everyone,
and accept this fact.
It’s easy to say.
How?
I can't calm down, so what?
Even His Majesty can do nothing about it.
What can we do?
That's annoying.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
What?
Ask Luo to tell Langyue
that I want to see her.
Yelv Zhigu enters the palace every day.
His Majesty has ordered
not to let the princess see anyone in the Wood Feather House.
She will be grounded for ten days.
Ten days later,
the delegation of the Northern Zhou will take her to their country.
Ten days.
[Big wood as the main body of the bow]
[Plum wood Ladder]
[Super bow draft]
Luo.
Call my dad here tomorrow.
Ten days?
Right?
I heard that
the moon in the Northern Zhou is more round than that in the Southern Xiao.
It can't be true.
Look.
The moon in the Southern Xiao
is so full.
Luo,
you don’t want to go, either.
Right?
Of course I don’t want to go,
and much less I want you to go.
Then don't go.
Really, Your Highness?
We don't need to go to the Northern Zhou?
I mean...
you don't have to go.
I...
No.
I’ll go wherever you goes.
In this life, Luo belongs to you.
If you don’t want me,
I’d rather die.
Even I become a ghost, I will still follow you.
What are you talking about?
What ghost?
You want to scare me?
Besides, I'm just saying.
In the rest of our life,
we will live happily.
OK?
As long as you are happy, I am happy.
Then you should get out of here in a few days
to find Meng Yuanxu.
You want to see Mr. Meng?
You are the one who should see him.
I...
Think about it.
If you go to the Northern Zhou with me,
will Meng Yuanxu be sad?
So seize this few days
to meet him and talk to him more.
Are you going to see Architect Li?
Don't you worry about me.
Ten days is not a long time.
Isn't it good to live happily?
Will you listen to me?
Okay.
Be good.
Don't cry.
Li Qingfeng, listen to me.
I don’t care how hard it is.
Just make the bow.
If you make it,
I, Meng Yuanxu,
will not ask for salary in Wood Feather House.
You'll be my boss.
I'll call you brother forever.
My son will call you godfather forever.
Do you hear me?
I'll kneel down now.
Officer.
Luo.
If you go to the Northern Zhou,
how can you have my baby?
Office, keep your voice down.
Take him back.
He's so noisy.
Li Qingfeng won't be able to focus.
Let's go.
Go back to your room.
Luo.
Officer, stop it.
[Thorough survey of curves and lines]
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
[Big wood as the main body of the bow]
[Plum wood Ladder]
[Wood Feather Pavilion]
Go.
You... Qingfeng.
Where are you going?
Qingfeng, what's wrong with you?
God, Buddha,
Bodhisattva,
I'm going to offer incense to you.
[Imperial Study]
Mr. Situ, come and have a look.
[Super bow draft]
Your Majesty,
this draft will work.
But in my opinion,
it shall be discussed by the Arrow-making House of the Ministry of War
before making.
OK.
Mr. Situ, take this drawing to the Ministry of War.
I'll wait for your news.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I’m guilty.
For what?
I’m just a civilian.
But I fell in love with Princess Zhaohe.
And I even made her sad.
This is the first crime.
I trespassed the Arrow-making House of the Ministry of War
and stole the draft, which is lawless.
This is the second crime.
For my personal feelings,
I made the draft of the super bow,
but I've never thought about my country.
This is the third crime.
I put Your Majesty in dilemma,
making the officials in the court
arguing.
This is the fourth crime.
But I still want to beg Your Majesty
to keep the princess.
Rise.
Do you know that Princess Zhaohe
has to marry
for the sake of the country?
I know.
Do you know
I also want to keep Langyue?
I also tried my best to keep Langyue.
Your Majesty seems to do it for peace,
but in fact, this is weakness.
It can't solve the problem fundamentally.
How dare you!
It's the Northern Zhou who dares to invade.
The weaker Your Majesty is,
the more audacity the Northern Zhou is.
You...
Your Majesty, the foundation of peace is not compromise
but to strengthen our country's power
so that the barbarians dare not invade,
and all other countries will pay tribute to Xiao.
Your Majesty, please believe in our country's fate.
[Zhaohe Palace]
Architect Li, please.
Li...
[Zhaohe Palace]
Your Highness.
Why are you flustered?
It's Architect Li.
What's wrong with him?
Architect Li made a...
He made a super bow day and night.
Lord Wang told me
he would take his men to Kaifeng immediately.
With this super bow,
we won't be afraid of Northern Zhou anymore.
Architect Li has convinced His Majesty.
Your Highness, we really don't need to go to the Northern Zhou now!
This nerd...
Why didn't he tell me?
Lord Wang also said
actually, when we were working on the Sanjun Tower project,
Architect Li studied
this super bow every night.
But he didn't tell anyone.
He was afraid that
everyone will be disappointed if he didn't make it.
So he worked during the day
and drew the draft alone at night.
Speaking of which,
Architect Li hasn't slept well
for two months.
Nerd.
I think Wang Sheng
will arrive in Kaifeng tomorrow.
Li Qingfeng,
you've really impressed me.
Officer.
You said
you would call Qingfeng brother.
I said that?
Yes.
You start to speak for him now?
I just hope everything goes well
and nothing will happen.
What can happen?
His Majesty postponed
the princess's wedding day for a month
on the ground of the queen dowager's birthday.
The emperor of the Northern Zhou wouldn't be so narrow-minded, right?
I always feel a little panic and anxious.
You should believe that God will help you.
Miss Chen is blessed.
She will stay.
That's right.
Don’t jinx me.
Wang Sheng personally sent the draft.
With the most experienced designer
in the Arrow-making House of the Ministry of War,
there will be no problem.
You are panic because you are hungry.
Finally, Miss Chen doesn't have to marry to Northern Zhou.
I think she must be very happy now.
I’ll ask Luo tomorrow.
Li Qingfeng, are you done packing?
Let’s go. I’ll treat you to a drink.
Have some supplements.
Officer, please let Qingfeng go.
He's really tired recently.
Let him have a good sleep.
Then you go with me.
No.
I was just kidding.
[Thorough survey of curves and lines]
After him!
Minister Zheng,
tell me how to calm down.
Wang Sheng.
You left the palace secretly.
How did you expose your whereabouts?
The Northern Zhou secretly inquired about the actions of the Ministry of War.
Therefore they set an ambush.
The Northern Zhou's spies have been hiding in the Xiao for many years.
I've told you this is a big trouble.
You should have investigated it thoroughly that day.
The spies can’t be cleaned up.
Your Majesty, I have another thing to report.
Go ahead.
Last night,
the envoy from Northern Zhou sent a message that
their emperor's birthday is coming.
They hope the princess
can celebrate his birthday on time.
They asked the princess to leave as scheduled.
You may leave.
I shall take my leave.
All of you.
In the history of the Xiao,
every dynasty inspires awe throughout the world.
But now,
our country is subject to other countries.
I
am a sinner.
Your Highness.
You came back alone?
Yes
Then
when will I leave?
As promised.
Two days later.
Two days?