Unforgettable Love
EP02
Here's one for you.
This is mine.
Let's make a pinky promise,
and it'll never change.
Let go of his hands.
Aunt, please excuse me.
Aunt?
Hey, you...
It's you!
What a small world.
What happened last night
was planned by you, right?
It is a
very subtle plan.
From live to offline,
Until Xiaobao disappeared,
you showed up by chance.
Nothing more nor less,
the video is nearly a minute in length,
and spread on the Internet.
From last night to today,
you haven't lost anything.
But my company
has taken on
heavy financial losses
and immense public pressure.
What are you drivelling about?
Come on, how much do you want?
You've suffered a loss?
I've also suffered losses.
I have been unaccountably implicated.
Just name your price.
Two hundred.
I'm right.
Check.
Don't be like in the TV series.
Two hundred yuan.
Two hundred yuan?
Are you taunting me?
For us girls,
you can kill me,
but you can't mess up my haircut.
Look,
what you've done
to this hair!
I'm going to ask the best hairdresser
to cut my hair.
Two hundred yuan.
It's really puzzling.
I don't want more.
Xiaobao,
There are weird aunts everywhere.
You must pay attention to
personal safety in the future.
Do you understand?
Hey...
Let's go home.
You are weird uncle.
He Weifei,
I haven't received those two cards
for so many years,
but you gave them to a weird aunt.
Forget it.
I'll take you to
a more normal hospital.
Go!
How long are you going to
confront me?
Let's talk about it calmly.
You can put forward your needs.
Dr. Qin?
What does Dr. Qin mean?
You want Dr. Qin to come to our home
and be your doctor?
Turn off the light and go sleep.
Mr. He.
This is what I collected and sorted out
all information of Dr. Qin Yiyue.
Did you see the two meetings
between Xiaobao and Dr. Qin
with your own eyes?
It's the first time I saw Xiaobao
can be so close
to a stranger.
It's strange, to be honest.
I'm so surprised.
After all these years,
I've been so nice to Xiaobao,
he didn't even let me
touch his little hand.
Look.
Look at it.
I'm so curious.
Which fairy she is,
can shake the big and small icebergs
in your family?
She was born in a county
next to Qincheng.
Her parents
are all ordinary workers.
From primary school to high school,
she never left that small county.
She has no
background of studying abroad.
She has only worked for three years
and with little clinical experience.
All in all,
She can't compete with
overseas medical experts.
Most importantly,
her temper
is very unstable
and moody.
In terms of both short-term cooperation
and long-term development,
cooperation with her
is more harm than good.
You can do chart analysis for all of this.
I also considered
using value portfolio management model
or 7S model for analysis,
but I found that,
the available data did not support it.
Lao He,
not all people and things
can be explained
by business logic.
You're wrong.
I have an employment relationship with her,
which is an equal exchange
of salary and talents.
So you've seen her twice.
What do you think of her?
and it'll never change...
She's quite special.
Tell me.
That's all right.
So much nonsense.
Very wierd
Xiaobao likes her very much.
Although the child doesn't speak,
he is smart,
just like his father.
He knows how to
judge a person.
Xiaobao is always my most important Party A.
He has the right to appoint partners.
I'll trust him for a while.
Good morning, Mr. He.
Good morning.
Mr. He, Miss Qin politely refused.
She said she doesn't receive patients
during the vacation.
In addition,
About the personal doctor,
She also refused.
Refuse the Prince Charming of Qincheng girls?
This is something new.
I'm more and more curious
about Dr. Qin.
It seems that I need to
send her an e-mail in person.
E-mail?
Oh my God, only you can do this.
Let me see.
For the contract and related matters,
please refer to the attachment.
Please find the attachment.
Bro, you are too rigid.
It's strange that she will accept your request.
You just wait and see.
What are you doing?
Girls in nowadays
don't value money,
they value your character.
It's in vain to
give you such a good appearance.
Don't make trouble for me.
Give it to me.
Wait a moment.
With 100 MB optical fiber,
even if you turn it off,
it can be sent out.
It's disgusting.
He's a psychopath,
and a narcissist.
It's all pictures of himself.
You can send,
I can delete.
Delete.
Don't want to look.
I thought as much.
As for the formal negotiation,
I have to come in person.
Hello.
This is He Qiaoyan,
CEO of the Heshi Group.
I'd like to invite you
to our company tomorrow.
You're the CEO?
I'm the chairman.
This kind of phone fraud,
I'll report one by one.
Hello?
Hung up.
Phone fraud?
It's impossible for me to be a private doctor.
I'm a full-time doctor.
Our hospital has regulations.
I've negotiated
with the Director.
Don't worry.
Besides, the money is just a deposit.
Dr. Qin
is an absolute beneficiary.
Your salary and bonus
will only double.
In your eyes,
everything can be done
with money?
It is true theoretically.
Because everything
has its equivalent value match.
Can children's psychological deficiency
be cured with money?
Not exactly.
But at least in material terms,
whatever he wants,
I can satisfy him.
Including you.
Sorry, Mr. He.
I feel offended
and don't want to see you again.
Please leave.
I'm so tough.
I regard money like dirt.
It's not in vain to read novels dominated by heroines.
About business negotiation,
Often I get used to
saying bluntly first.
Please leave now.
Excuse me.
Really left?
She pushed you out of the door?
She read the contract.
The deposit was also in front of her.
She still won't cooperate with me.
I haven't had such a tough project
in a long time.
I put out a lever,
but I couldn't find the fulcrum to pry her.
It's really not an ordinary woman.
I think,
You have to find a way
to make her really become your person,
thus,
she can be better used by you.
Know her, analyze her,
go into her heart.
In a word, having her in mind.
Dr. Qin
likes reading such novels.
These heroes,
ten poker faces,
nine psychoses.
Indeed,
It's like you.
No.
The heroes,
either lost their memory in a car accident
or were terminally ill.
or their parents died
and their brothers betrayed them.
Or, you were also standing in the middle of the road,
I'll crash into you like in the novel.
I made a general analysis.
These are all problems
that can be solved with money,
which is the same as business.
It's simple.
Don't think about it.
Trust me.
I will take full charge of the matter.
Chapter one
The president spends money on me.
However,
You must send money to her hospital,
let others envy her,
satisfy the vanity
of women.
But I want to remind you,
She's not a girl,
She is a weird aunt.
Is there something wrong with this person's brain?
He Qiaoyan is crazy.
He begins to retaliate against me because I'm not satisfied his request.
Secondly, date her in person.
Thoughts will throng her mind.
As soon as she goes out,
she will see you picking her up from work.
Right now,
You must plunder a burning house.
No,
You must strike while the iron is hot.
My god!
The swindler came after me.
She's gone.
Gone?
What are you doing?
Go after her!
Stop!
He's still following me.
I'll give you whatever you want.
As long as you want.
As long as I have.
You have to give me whatever I want.
As long as I want,
you have to give it to me.
he must be crazy.
No, no, not like this.
You're a macho boss,
not a robbery.
I'm not a robbery.
Robbery?
You screwed up.
I lost her.
Then keep on chasing.
Now I seriously doubt
the practicality and credibility
of your instructions.
Dealing with women...
Hello?
I have my own way.
How do you know my address?
I've read your resume.
Slow down, pretty.
Pretty.
Help!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Run and call the police!
Who are you?
So timid!
Do you have nothing to do?
Why don't you go to bed at night?
Come on!
Get away!
Thank you.
Why did you run just now?
It is the social responsibility of every citizen
to be brave for a just cause.
You're the opposite.
Turn around and run.
I have
my own principles.
Just like that,
before it's clear,
I'm not going to do anything rash.
Stop.
Follow me.
Have the police finished with this?
They're done.
Give me your hand.
It's a little painful. Take it easy.
Does it hurt?
Of course not.
Are you a man?
Okay.
It's done?
What about my wound infection?
Come to me if you are infected,
I have a magic hand,
can amputate for free.
Just now, at the end of the lane,
I saved you.
Based on the principle of equivalent exchange,
now, let's talk about
your way of return.
Are you kidding me?
I don't have any more. If you think this is not enough, don't take it.
Naive.
I declare,
from now on,
You're my man.
This is a token
of our agreement.
Here's one for you.
This is mine.
Let's make a pinky promise,
and it'll never change.
I'm not your man.
I'm your future boss.
The design is not aesthetic enough.
It needs to be separated from
the words "black" and "heavy".
Lack of adequate software and services,
and the user experience is poor,
and other issues.
Mr. He, what can I do for you?
Manager Xu,
I have a question for you.
Yes, please.
Recently,  in recruiting staff,
I encountered
a very difficult problem.
I offered the best conditions
within my ability,
but she was not interested.
You can try
to make the other person feel that
you not only recognize her ability,
but also are more willing to help her,
support her,
live and grow together.
It's the same as being in love.
Live and grow together?
Sure.
Go on.
Okay.
Look.
Because the public
has completely begun to
rely on smart phones,
and other smart devices
cannot be effectively applied,
it will only make people feel redundant.
There are difficulties in the definition of value.
Many products because...
Mr. He
Do you think our plan is not good?
Nothing.
Good.
Very good.
Young people's own needs,
and young people's awareness of
their own protection is gradually enhanced.
Value consumer groups
belong to the sensitive group.
As long as the product meets the actual demand,
and can also bring added value,
It will give users a stronger sense of experience
than cosmetics and clothing.
The first attempt of baking experiment.
Fault tolerance is
Zero.
Ready to start.
All right, it's done.
Mr. He,
It may take another 30 minutes
due  to traffic jam.
Is there another way?
The urban bus rapid transit
is the only one that won't get stuck.
Watch out, here is a kid.
I can't catch it.
It seems that Dr. Qin is not here.
And the last 30 seconds,
Let's see,
today,
who is the fish catcher?
Little friend,
You catch and uncle will help you pick them up,
ok?
If we win later,
just give me a candy.
Dear children,
Dear parents,
Next part is the shooting game.
It's your turn to
do your best for the children.
It's our turn.
I want the pink rabbit
in skirt.
OK, I'll shoot it for you right away.
It looks like Dr. Qin's eyesight is not good.
Some things don't have to be forced.
Wait and see!
The last chance.
Come on, Dr. Qin.
A girl and a boy,
are walking
and then hit the muzzle of the gun.
They hurt their faces.
There's a generation gap
between uncle and the children born after 2010.
That guy,
It doesn't seem to be
a cold, stereotyped nuisance.
It's so hot.
I cannot bear this.
Let me apply a mask and go to bed.
Wei, is there a power cut?
Help me to check it.
I forgot to pay the electricity bill.
So the day after tomorrow is Xiaobao's birthday.
Mr. Wen
Here you are.
This is the new test product
of R&D department
after debugging and modification.
And the outer packaging design
has also been modified.
True love guardian.
After it is bound with the app of the same name,
From a long distance.
it can master the physical condition
and geographical location of the other one.
And at the time of emergency,
it can send the emergency signal
to the other one.
It can make people feel
the protection of lovers all the time.
Mr. Wen,
His appearance
is really good.
He's getting better at dressing up.
Secretary Zhong here...
Don't think about our secretary.
Secretary Zhong,
Please pour me a cup of coffee.
I asked you to come to the meeting,
not for coffee
What is it?
Didn't you hear that?
This is our latest
and improved pair bracelet.
The one you're holding
is a pair with the one I'm holding.
Test it for me.
Are you declaring of love?
I didn't say I don't want it.
I heard about this product
can record
the heart of love.
Tonight,
Just a chance to use it.
To test this product,
We need
an adult with normal mind.
Obviously you are not.
You laughed at me again.
No kidding,
The day after tomorrow is the tenth.
Do you have any plan?
Our Xiaobao,
built a small house.
Xiaobao,
Do you have any
Birthday wish?
What's up?
Let Dr. Qin talk about it first.
Me, Dr. Qin,
I like birthday best,
but my birthday is in June,
either in time for the final exam
or the parents' meeting.
The worst is
it caught up with the math test in the college entrance examination.
So I can only envy
other people's children's parties.
I feel really sad, too.
Xiaobao,
Can you tell me
if you have received
any special birthday presents?
Do you want to draw it?
Let me envy.
Xiaobao,
What's up?
All right, Xiaobao,
Dad's here.
Don't be afraid.
Why is Xiaobao like this?
It's all my fault.
Five years ago, on Xiaobao's birthday,
we both
lost our closest family.
Over the years,
Because of traumatic stress disorder,
Xiaobao doesn't want to talk
and meet strangers any more.
I hope to make Xiaobao
have the happiness
of his age again.
In recent years,
I checked all the information,
and consulted a lot of doctors.
But the results are not satisfactory.
How about this?
We have a birthday party for Xiaobao.
Since birthday
is one of his stressors,
so this is
the first breakthrough
to rebuild his trust system.
But I'm not sure,
if Xiaobao would like to.
Trust me this time.
I have to go back to the hospital first.
Well,
When I'm off this weekend,
I'll prepare for Xiaobao's birthday
with you.
Bye.
Together?
It's a deal.
Xiaobao is so cute,
but at a young age,
he's suffering so much,
which make me feel pain.
I've never heard of Mr. He was married.
He's probably married in seclusion.
No wonder he's like this.
This is the plot
of most novels on the Internet.
For the death of his beloved,
the hero blames himself,
then he cut off all his passions and desires,
and went to the mountain to practice in seclusion.
For decades,
he has been practicing peerless martial arts.
Practice?
Are you reading martial arts novels?
Does it mean
He Qiaoyan
want to unify the whole country?
But I didn't expect that,
this poker face
also has an affectionate side.
I don't know if he is affectionate,
I just cherish Xiaobao.
He lost his mother when he was so young,
and he had such a father.
So?
You're going to help him and his son?
I just want to help Xiaobao.
And,
it's my job as a doctor.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Warm hearted Qin heroine.
Before cooperation,
I'm used to negotiating all the agreements.
Although helping Xiaobao to celebrate his birthday
is also treating him,
it will take up
your private time outside of work.
I will pay you
several times the price of your work as a reward.
In addition,
Before you formally accept
the invitation of the private doctor,
we will cooperate
in a short term.
It's the agreement.
Dr. Qin, please have a look.
Do you have a pen?
Dr. Qin, that's a pencil,
not suitable for signing a contract.
Pleasant cooperation.
Never Go Back.
Never.
What do you mean?
There is nothing
that a hot pot can't solve.
If there is,
add another cup of milk tea.
I'm hungry.
Please help yourself, Miss Qin.
Hot Pot.
Here we are.
What are you doing?
This is the second generation of health bracelet
launched by our company.
Give you.
You see that
I'm not moved by money,
so you try to
please me
with these small favors.
Here is the sample.
You are one of the experience users.
Sample?
This is a lover's bracelet.
Where is the one
that matches my bracelet?
There's a call button.
I want to make a call.
Well,
If you have anything cannot understand,
take the manual
and go home to study by yourself.
It's getting late.
It's time for you to go home.
Get out of the car.
Is it great to have a car with a loud sound?
I made an appointment with Dr. Qin today
for dinner tomorrow.
If some people don't want to go,
I'll call and cancel.
What's up?
Mr. Bao has changed his mind?
Are you all right?
Feel it.
You have a slight fever.
Did you take any medicine?
I can't take medicine.
If I take medicine,
I can't serve the patient today.
I'll have some warm water first.
The second generation of health bracelets
has only been pre purchased for a week.
Compared with the first generation,
the pre-sale volume has increased
by 27%.
So we decided to take the opportunity to launch
limited edition gold
and leather strap.
Uncomfortable.
Uncomfortable?
Is it because
the leather strap is not waterproof?
Or because of the metal strap,
which is not convenient
when people taking exercise?
It's comfortable when I wear it.
And the results of internal tests
is very satisfactory.
Well,
Let's take a five-minute break.
Dr. Qin, are you not feeling well?
You bribed Ruowei?
It's your bracelet data.
You have a slight fever now,
and sleep debt.
Aren't you a doctor?
Buddy, doctor is also human.
Doctors get sick, too, OK?
Remember to take the medicine.
Don't infect other patients.
Sis,
that...
That man,
He knows you have a cold.
So...
I'll get rid of it right away.
I'll eat.
Orange didn't do anything wrong.
Come on, have some too
Sis,
Are you really not going to get a cold medicine?
No.
I'm allergic to cold medicine.
It makes me drowsy.
But don't worry,
I took two tablets of vitamin C first.
It should be able to get through the current difficulties.
So tired.
Yiyue, I'm leaving.
I'm on a business trip at ten o'clock.
Can you handle it by yourself
You remember to take the medicine.
Call me if you need anything
Dear,
See you.
So tired
I feel sore all over.
I'd better take a bath.
Xiaobao, You wait for Dad in the car.
I'll go up and see Dr. Qin
Qin Yiyue
Why am I so sleepy.
I feel sore all over.
Not good
I think I have a fever.
I can't sleep in the bathtub
Password lock.
Validation failed.
Which one should it be?
The fingerprints
are concentrated in three places.
Six, seven, zero.
Validation failed.
Six, seven.
Incorrect.
Dr. Qin,
I like birthday best,
but my birthday is in June,
either in time for the final exam
or the parents' meeting.
The worst is
it caught up with the math test in the college entrance examination.
Qin Yiyue