♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
Episode 21
More than 100 patients have been arranged
in Qingshan Court recently.
By yesterday,
a dozen of them died
and few of them were cured.
Clinics nearby the capital city have reported
one after another that
smallpox is prevailing,
causing
innumerable deaths.
And
according to the report of Arm Moral Department,
Jun Jiuling has tested
on a few cattle
led to Qingshan Court lately.
Doctors of the Imperial Academy of Medicine didn't hear about such a test,
so they don't know whether it works.
It has been nearly half a month.
There're many discussions from the whole court.
They say Jun Jiuling
can be executed to death
for her failure in test
but the delay
causes the spread of smallpox,
which will endanger
the whole capital city.
We can't wait for a month.
Send a secret decree to Lu Yunqi that
I only give Jun Jiuling the last seven days.
If she can't find the way seven days later,
ask him to kill her.
Yes,
Your Majesty.
This is a secret letter I just received.
Miss Jun.
Guo'er.
Wait a moment.
Miss Jun,
you don't wear your veil,
so I can't approach you.
Can you approach me now?
Guo'er,
what's up?
Miss Jun,
my mom said you're the highly skilled doctor who protects us.
You protect my mom and me,
so surely I should protect you.
Why do you
come to me so late?
Where's your mom?
Miss Jun,
please cure
my mom quickly.
She has been crying lately.
She must suffer much pain.
I promise you
I'll let you and your mom
go home healthily,
OK?
Miss Jun.
My mom said it can secure people,
so I give it to you.
Test your new medicine on me.
I'm very brave.
Thank you, Guo'er.
Do you know?
You're the same age
as my brother.
Do you miss him?
Yes.
But
we can't go home
and get together with our families
until we eliminate smallpox.
So
you should
receive treatment actively.
Look,
there're fewer smallpox marks on your face.
You may go home soon.
Go back,
or your mom worries about you.
Miss Jun, I'm leaving.
Miss Jun.
The new prescription has worked.
Our severe patients here
have shown obvious signs of improvement.
Good.
But there're
more and more new patients
from various places.
I'll try smallpox viruses.
Miss Jun.
Miss Jun,
it's inadmissible.
You should take the general situation into account,
so you can't take the risk.
To cure patients, Shennong tried hundreds of herbs
and Hua Tuo tried Powder for Anesthesia.
And
it's my duty to eliminate smallpox.
We're short of doctors.
Let's
think out other ways.
No need.
I've decided it.
Miss Jun,
think it over.
Jun.
Your Lordship.
Then I'll leave.
Go on with your work.
What's the matter?
I believe
what you said today.
I haven't touched any patients,
so you can test smallpox viruses on me.
No way.
Why?
Stop joking.
I'm not sure I can make it.
If there is any error,
you'll die.
I see.
As I said,
if we're doomed to perdition,
I'll be in.
No way, anyhow.
Don't talk with me.
You have something important to do,
but I also want to do something for the people all over the country.
This isn't your…
Let me finish my words.
As the son of Lord Cheng,
I should set an example.
If the test on me turns effective,
people won't
fear it.
You save them,
and I appease them.
No.
Listen to me in this matter.
What…
Why are you here?
At His Majesty's order,
I come to watch here.
Well then, why
are you here?
Did His Majesty
ask you to eavesdrop
outside a girl's room
at night?
The same to you.
You're also running about
at night.
Your Excellency Lu,
unlike you,
I'm here to talk
about business with her openly.
Tell me
what your business is.
This is the person that you want.
The person I want?
You want
to test smallpox viruses on someone.
He can be tested.
Your Excellency, show mercy to me.
It seems
you're going to show your merit to His Majesty
at the cost of your subordinate's life.
I'm helping you.
Get out of here.
He committed a crime,
so he'll be put in prison sooner or later.
I just
advance his punishment time.
Your Excellency Lu,
what crime did he commit?
Dr. Jun,
Li Ze stole
all the items of the dead patients
you buried in the backyard
when he was on duty
and wanted to sell them down the hill.
Your Excellency Lu,
I did that
out of greediness.
Spare me.
Spare…
If
he sold those items with smallpox viruses
to the capital city,
the consequences would be too ghastly to contemplate.
Isn't it reasonable for me
to let you test on him?
Dr. Jun,
I was wrong.
Dr. Jun.
I was wrong, Dr. Jun.
I was wrong.
Your Excellency,
I don't force anyone to be tested.
I only test on those volunteers.
Please leave here.
Since so,
I don't need to put such a bum
in prison.
Go.
Spare me, Your Excellency.
Spare me.
Your Excellency, spare me.
Good at small tricks,
your subordinates
are really like you.
All of you should be killed.
He's more useful than you.
Why not
let Dr. Jun test on you?
Your Excellency Lu,
unlike you,
I don't have so many subordinates,
so I can only volunteer to be tested.
Your Lordship.
Your Excellency Lu,
do you
also want to be a volunteer?
Dr. Jun,
you only have the last seven days.
Time is urgent.
You have no choice.
Have you really decided it?
Come on.
Do you do this for me?
My father has devoted himself to the country all his life.
I've inherited
both his blood and virtues.
As his son,
I don't care about high position and great wealth
but the people
all over the country.
People within the capital city are free from the pain of smallpox,
but people outside the capital city
are in peril.
Without a preventive way,
how can I say I'll repay the country?
If you were me,
would you feel relieved?
Come on.
Zhu Zan,
once the smallpox viruses are blown into your body,
I can't control them.
How do
you feel?
I feel a bit thirsty.
Thirsty?
I'd like to eat this.
Orange?
I'll peel one for you.
Reach out your hand.
♫Outline in my dream♫
How are you feeling?
♫can be carved on your face♫
I'm fine.
Do you feel hot?
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
No.
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
Listen carefully.
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
Go to sleep
to build up your energy.
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
I'll stay here.
Tell me if you feel unwell.
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
Got it?
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
Would you like more?
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
Your Excellency Lu,
I come to reinforce your army by imperial decree.
Act in
two groups.
Your Excellency,
they said
they come to reinforce us.
We won't be spared, will we?
♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
Jiuling,
smallpox is terrible.
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
Luckily, you're a clever girl.
As usual,
you can
eliminate it
and bring those patients back to life.
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
Miss Jun,
you can get out of the jaws of danger every time.
I'm sure you'll eliminate smallpox this time.
-Go on sleeping. -Miss Jun.
How is he?
I just checked him.
His Lordship has still had a fever.
Luckily, we can see smallpox marks on his body.
Is it
good news?
It's good news
at present.
Miss Jun,
you're tired to take care of patients and His Lordship
these days.
Why not go and have a rest?
I stay here.
You haven't slept.
Go to sleep now.
I'll take care of him.
Miss Jun.
Dr. Jun.
There's a new patient.
What's wrong?
Her symptoms are out of my knowledge,
so I don't know what to do.
Let us go now.
Don't touch his scabs
when bringing his fever down.
Tell me if he has any problem.
OK, Miss Jun.
Let's go.
Dr. Jun, this way.
Here comes Dr. Jun. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Dr. Jun,
this new patient
who keeps foaming at the mouth
is different from other patients in symptom.
She suffers from cold diarrhea.
Don't prescribe periostracum cicada for her,
or her exterior deficiency will worse.
What can we prescribe then?
We should keep her condition steady first.
Use Radix Aucklandiae Powder.
Mill radix aucklandiae into powder, add a cup of water
and boil it to get four-fifths cup of decoction. Go now.
OK, I'll go.
First control her condition.
There have been no deaths recently.
Does it mean we've controlled the smallpox?
Don't let down guard.
Strengthen the monitoring for all patients.
Yes,
I'm Jun Jiuling.
Here is your prescription.
You
never dreamed about her, right?
Who are you actually?
Your Excellency,
it's the deadline tomorrow.
I've prepared
oil wood for ignition.
You can leave.
Yes.
Dr. Feng,
add some ginseng and angelica sinensis
to his Neituo Powder
so that more pus in his smallpox
will be discharged.
Thanks for your help today.
Miss Jun.
His Lordship's condition aggravates.
Go and have a check.
Please take care of here for me.
OK.
Zhu Zan.
What happened?
He was well.
But he has felt pain suddenly.
His smallpox viruses haven't been fully discharged.
What does it show?
They're still in his body.
Will His Lordship die?
It depends on him.
He has to fight alone.
Zhu Zan.
Your Lordship.
Miss Jun.
Miss Jun, what will you do?
Zhu Zan.
I'm beside you.
You promised me
you would save the people all over the country
after you overcame smallpox viruses.
You promised me
you would stay with me this time.
You can't go back
on your word promise.
Zhu Zan.
Jiuling.
I'm here.
Ling Jiu.
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
Ling Jiu, promise me
♫Let me weigh every word♫
to be safe.
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
You haven't finished
your Map of Capital City.
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
The bean curd cakes you introduced aren't tasty at all.
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
And I want to
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
eat in that rotisserie
we went to last time.
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
I'm waiting for you to take me there.
♫In long silence♫
I still have many places to go with you.
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
I have a lot of words to tell you.
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
I thought I feared nothing
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
after narrowly escaping death.
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
But I'm
very afraid now.
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
I'm afraid I'll never see you again.
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
Do you know?
As long as you can come to yourself,
I'll listen to you in everything.
Ling Jiu,
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
promise me
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
to come to yourself soon
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
and tough it out.
I still have lots of words to tell you.
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
Sorry
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
to keep you waiting for so long.
♫If memories can tell♫
I see everything you have done for me.
♫Every of its words will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
If you can come to yourself,
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
I will tell you everything,
okay?
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
In Zezhou,
you saved me
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
from a startled horse.
At Jinyun Restaurant,
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
you saved me
and helped me get rid of the assassin.
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
At the cliff side of Runan,
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫
you saved me.
When Yuan Bao was nearly spotting me,
you saved me again.
You saved me
when Lu Yunqi made trouble in my drugstore.
Zhu Zan,
you've saved me many times.
Let me save you this time.
Let me save you this time,
okay?
Ling…
Zhu…
Zhu Zan.
You finally came to yourself.
All your smallpox viruses are discharged.
When I was asleep,
you must have often pushed my clothes aside
to check my body.
You're doing this with ease.
Did you hear all that I said?
I don't know.
I had a nightmare,
in which I saw
Jiuling in the big fire.
She must
hurt a lot
at that moment.
Let me wet the towel for you.
Your Excellency Lu.
Chu Jiuling,
you're back.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Surely you know it.
Do you believe reincarnation?
No.
But I believe it.
You're Chu Jiuling.
I'm Jun Jiuling.
Chu Jiuling,
why don't you dare to admit your identity?
I don't know what you mean.
You've long known it.
You're still alive,
aren't you?
You ignore your duties.
Aren't you afraid His Majesty punishes you?
Is it important?
I just care about you.
It has nothing to do with me.
I'm not the one you're looking for.
I'm boiling medicinal materials.
Please don't bother me.
Did Zhu Zan name you Jiuling?
When he was in a coma,
did you admit it?
You ignore your duties
and even like to eavesdrop.
Yes,
I did
admit it.
Even if I'm not Chu Jiuling,
it's forgivable for me
to admit it as he risks his life
trying smallpox viruses for people.
You came here from afar
to open Jiuling Drugstore.
I threatened you to change the name by force many times,
but you refused.
The characters on your prescription
are the same as hers in style.
When I was in the Mansion of Prince Huai,
you seemed more worried
than Her Highness Princess of Jiuli.
Don't try to hide it.
I'm fed up with guess.
Your Excellency Lu,
all is your delusional speculation.
I'm not Chu Jiuling.
I don't need to explain
whatever I do to you.
You can cheat others,
but you can't cheat me.
How can you
let me go?
I won't let you go
this life.
I know you're obsessed with her,
but she's gone.
Anyhow,
she must dislike the way you treat me.
Your Excellency Lu,
be realistic.
Did you fall in love with someone?
Zhu Zan actually survived
from the smallpox viruses test.
Is it
good news?
I'm
slow-witted.
Your Majesty,
I follow
your idea
in this matter.
They eliminate smallpox
and save many people.
Surely it's good news.
Thank God.
Zhu Zan did a deed of great merit.
If I reward him generously,
what will Lord Cheng do?
According to His Lordship's character,
he'll refuse it
and say it's Zhu Zan's duty.
Though he is a military officer,
few people are as sensible as him
in the court.
Throughout the ages,
there have been few military officers
with excellent combat achievements
and widespread fame.
Clever as His Lordship is,
only you can see him through.
Your Majesty,
you're the most sensible person
in the world.
Such people
are the most terrible.
Dr. Jun.
Thank you.
Dr. Jun,
check the ratio of medicinal materials on this prescription.
Is it that prescription we discussed yesterday?
It's workable.
Dr. Jun,
check whether this prescription
lacks any medicinal materials.
Add two more qian of ginseng and angelica sinensis.
Go to handle it.
OK, next.
Take it.
Be careful not to burn yourself. Thanks.
Please line up one after another.
Why are you here?
Without a veil, you should go back now.
You…
I tried smallpox viruses.
Do you forget it?
Yes.
How do you feel?
I feel much better.
You haven't slept for several nights.
Thank you.
We're in public.
Don't do this.
I'm checking your smallpox.
Don't misunderstand.
You've recovered obviously.
It seems this prescription is effective.
So did we make it?
Not exactly.
I still need kid volunteers.
Will you also let kids try smallpox viruses?
Yes.
Please do me a favor later.
It's my pleasure.
His Lordship's smallpox
is less dangerous
and terrible.
Remember
to take bright
and big smallpox marks
as samples.
Bright smallpox marks.
I see.
Big smallpox marks.
Then
please take samples
from His Lordship.
OK.
Don't worry.
Come on.
Everyone,
please be gentle.
Don't be afraid.
-Don't worry. -It doesn't hurt at all.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Come on.
Jun.
Your Majesty.
His Lordship Zhu wants to present himself to you.
What?
Why is he here?
He may bring smallpox here.
Who asked him here?
It's bold for Lu Yunqi
to neglect his duties
and let him out without authorization.
Those guards outside
are also a bunch of bums.
I don't see him.
Let him go.
Your Majesty,
he said
what you worry about
won't happen.
He comes to discuss something important with you.
It's
about the criminal official Zhou Bentang.
Let him in.
Yes.
Those guards
are so thoughtless.
Your Lordship,
just say here.
Your Majesty,
I already overcame smallpox viruses,
so I won't be infected with
or spread smallpox.
Come in.
Yes.
Your Lordship, never mind.
The smallpox
is really terrible.
Did you survive
from smallpox viruses?
It's really good news.
Zhu Zan,
you've done a deed of great merit.
It's not
my merit,
but Dr. Jun's.
I'll
reward both of you.
Your Majesty,
I don't come to ask for reward.
I have something to bother you.
Please allow me
to take away Zhou Bentang's descendants.
Why?
Let them try smallpox viruses
in Qingshan Court.
The kids of the Zhou family…
They did commit
the capital crime of betraying our country.
If you take out
their descendants,
they have
the hope to survive.
Your Majesty, you're insightful.
I do so to find a way to eliminate smallpox
rather than out of selfish motives.
Didn't you survive from smallpox viruses?
Your Majesty,
yes, I did.
But it's a successful test on the adult.
There are physical differences between kids and adults,
so the dosage and treatment vary.
So,
we still need to make a test.
There're many condemned prisoners.
You may choose two.
Why do you
choose kids of the Zhou family?
Your Majesty,
Dr. Jun said
she needs
kid volunteers under 10 this time.
In the dead cell,
only Zhou Bentang's descendants
are qualified.
Your Lordship,
it's easy.
Buy two kids
on the border market.
Your Majesty,
it's unfeasible.
The kids on the border market
are healthy.
If we're censured by people
due to failure,
it'll affect Your Majesty's fame.
Descendants of the Zhou family are doomed to be executed to death.
It's more meaningful
to let them die
for the smallpox viruses test.
It's you who go to buy kids from the border market.
It won't affect His Majesty's fame.
Stop arguing.
It isn't a big deal.
I agree
to your request.
As long as you can eliminate smallpox,
more kids will be saved.
Go and lead them.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I'll
leave.
Miss Jun,
this is the prescription of restorative medicinal materials
I prepare as you ordered.
Come.
Look.
It's feasible.
Prepare more.
OK.
Go.
He who left Qingshan Court without authorization
has to be killed
for disobedience to the imperial decree.
Your Excellency Lu, what brings you here?
You know it.
I'm discussing
with them in the hall,
so I don't know.
OK.
Call Zhu Zan out.
I have something to ask him.
Since you want to see His Lordship,
go and find him.
Why do you come to ask me?
Won't you
call him out?
So did
we make it?
Not exactly.
I still need kid volunteers.
Will you also let kids try smallpox viruses?
Does
he go to find kid volunteers?
Since you all help Zhu Zan,
you'll be executed to death
due to disobedience to the imperial decree.
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫Every of its words will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫It's me♫
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
♫Any clues?♫
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫