♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
Episode 17
Jiuling Drugstore
Mansion of Prince Huai
Miss Jun.
This…
Your Excellency Lu, what do you want to do?
You know it.
I ask you again.
Rename it
or not.
Your Excellency Lu,
Jiuling Drugstore is the ancestral business of our Jun family.
Both of my grandpa and my father are dead,
and now only I'm alive in my family.
So I must
follow their wishes
to inherit the Jiuling Drugstore.
Please pardon me.
I can't do
as you require.
Your Excellency Lu,
Jiuling's families are all dead,
so she can only inherit her family business.
Please pardon her.
Jinxiu.
This matter
should be ended.
Smash the plaque
in front of Dr. Jun!
How dare you!
You're bold.
Jiuling.
Lu Yunqi,
you're arrogant.
How dare you bully a girl in the street?
Don't interfere in the matter
of the Arm Moral Department.
Now that you want to smash it,
I must stop you.
Only the stronger
can do what he wants to do.
Let's see
whether you can stop me.
-Miss Jun. -Your Ladyship.
Jiuling.
Are you mad?
You don't want to live?
I'll protect this plaque
at all costs.
You can't protect
something you like sometimes.
Zhu Zan.
Your Excellency Lu,
can I have a talk with you alone?
It's not necessary.
You can decide it
after a talk with me.
If you still
want to smash the plaque later…
Your Ladyship.
…I won't stop you.
Your Excellency Lu,
you have a bad omen.
You think
I'll believe
your nonsense?
She
had never appeared in your dream.
Who is she?
You know who I'm talking about.
She is your bad omen.
Really?
If so,
there's no need to treat me.
So good.
Much resentment
is not good, Your Excellency Lu.
Resentment?
You mean she resented me?
To be precise, she hated you…
-Listen up. -She hated you very much.
I don't know how you knew these
and made up this story,
but I don't believe
any word.
Don't draw a conclusion
before you take my medicine.
Please wait
to see
the prescription I make for you.
Your Excellency,
here is your prescription.
Jun Jiuling,
you are great.
I've remembered you.
Your Excellency, take care.
Thank you today.
Don't think too much.
I just dislike Lu Yunqi.
If someone else was bullied,
I would also help him.
I just
thanked you
for helping the weak.
What did you say to Lu Yunqi?
He looked very angry when he left.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
Even His Lordship couldn't drive him away at that time.
How did you frighten him away?
You can ask her,
but don't mention me.
I just told him that
he has a bad omen.
So I prescribed for him.
Then he left.
He would believe it?
He had to
believe it.
Sure enough,
our lady
is awesome.
What a flatterer!
I'm convinced.
Anyway,
no one dares to
bully the Jiuling Drugstore from today on.
I'm leaving.
Does it still hurt?
Much better.
Cousin,
Prince Huai fell sick
with a serious disease.
Some imperial doctors sold all their property
and exchanged the silver for notes
in Deshengchang of the capital city.
After secret investigation,
I found they exchanged notes early to facilitate the use
for fear that they'll be
punished and driven away
from the Imperial Academy of Medicine by His Majesty
due to Prince Huai's disease.
I remember
you once asked about Prince Huai,
so I took it seriously
and wrote to tell you.
Grandma doesn't know it yet.
Remember not to mention it to her.
Prince Huai's disease was not serious,
but as it relapsed again and again,
it became serious.
Jiuling,
it's easy to cure diseases
but hard to save lives.
Be careful.
These imperial doctors
are going to run away?
It seems that Jiurong's condition
is worse than I expect.
Today I deliberately showed my previous handwriting
to Lu Yunqi.
He'll try to test me again.
To get close to Jiurong,
I can only risk it.
Why is
her handwriting so similar
to that of Princess Jiuling?
She also renamed herself Jiuling.
What exactly does she want to do?
There's something wrong with the silver note?
It's true.
Of course it's true.
But the treatment expense
is 2,000 taels of silver.
No one may give you
so much money for no reason.
Why were you paid the extra 8,000 taels of silver?
The extra 8,000 taels of silver
is to rename the Jiuling Drugstore.
Are you worried about Prince Huai's disease?
These days
he is getting worse
and can't get out of bed.
Your Highness, please take it easy.
We'll find a solution.
So you believe
the soul reincarnation?
I don't know.
I didn't believe it before.
But now,
I'd love to believe it.
You want her to come back?
Yes.
I also want to believe it,
but
it's impossible.
Why?
The world is so big
that there are
various coincidences.
Others may have similar eyes,
or similar voice,
or
similar expression.
But they're
just similar
not the same.
It's late.
Go to bed early.
Even if I believe it,
I don't want her
to come back.
It takes a long time to arrive here
from Zezhou.
Zan,
you meet Miss Jun
so often.
Sanbing,
I also want to
meet a girl so often.
You?
Baotang will meet a girl like this later.
Zan,
well, I indeed want it,
but I can't
get what I want.
While someone
who doesn't want it
just gets it.
Sanbing?
So,
who is she?
Why didn't you tell me?
Shut up.
In my life,
I won't absolutely get myself into such a trouble.
Listen to me.
Women are always…
Very troublesome.
You know me very well.
It turns out that he hasn't been enlightened.
It's you who haven't been enlightened.
Baotang referred to you.
Me?
Zan,
you
like her.
Don't talk nonsense.
Otherwise,
I'll take you to see her.
Look. He wants to see her.
Baotang,
listen to me.
If you like a girl,
you can't let her go.
I see, Sanbing.
Why didn't you tell me
such a big deal until now?
Your Lordship,
you said you would concentrate on reading
and asked me not to disturb you.
And you didn't allow me
to inquire about Miss Jun
since last time.
They're different.
I just didn't want to badger
and inquire about her,
but this is different as she is in danger.
Commander Lu is a dangerous man.
How could you conceal me from it?
I see,
Your Lordship.
I was wrong.
I heard
it's because Miss Jun
didn't treat
Commander Lu's mistress.
And some said
both His Excellency Lu
and the son of Lord Cheng
like Miss Jun,
so…
Nonsense.
It's ridiculous.
Whenever you see a woman
arguing with a man,
you always think of this.
I didn't see it, either.
I heard from others.
The reason is very simple.
Due to the name of the Jiuling Drugstore.
Why did His Lordship Zhu do so?
I asked Miss Jun to enjoy the lanterns with me
on the night of the 15th day,
but she refused.
Probably,
due to His Excellency Lu.
He always do something
to annoy His Excellency Lu.
Your Lordship,
let's go to
see Miss Jun.
She doesn't need it,
and someone else will do it.
His Excellency Lu failed to achieve his goal this time.
Maybe he'll do it again.
Then,
will Miss Jun be in danger?
His Lordship Zhu
can't always protect her.
This matter
depends on the attitude of the Fang family.
If the Fang family would like to…
Jiuli.
Jiurong.
I'm here.
Sister.
Jiurong.
Your Highness.
It's time to take the medicine, Jiurong.
Come on, Jiurong.
Take the medicine.
Jiurong,
take the medicine.
Sister,
I feel bad.
I know.
Take the medicine.
Then you'll get better.
Come on.
Jiurong.
He could swallow yesterday,
but why can't he today?
Your Highness,
you can't go on feeding in this way.
How about using
a crane-mouth pot to feed His Highness?
Crane-mouth pot?
OK.
Jiurong.
Your Highness.
The imperial doctor said that
His Highness,
His Highness suffers from scrofula.
Scrofula?
Your Excellency,
Miss Jun came
and wanted to meet you.
How can you
recommend a female hand-bell doctor
to treat Prince Huai?
Are you mad?
Your Majesty, please calm down.
The reason why I recommend Dr. Jun is that
she is the daughter of Jun Yingwen,
a famous doctor in Runan,
and she has excellent medical skills.
Your Majesty,
I couldn't
cure the wife of Marquis of Dingyuan,
but she did it.
Your Majesty,
Command Lu asks for a meeting.
Let him in.
Yes.
Here are my respects,
Your Majesty.
You come at the right moment.
Just now
Imperial Doctor Jiang
recommended a female
hand-bell doctor
who is surnamed Jun
to treat Prince Huai.
You go to check
if she really has excellent medical skills.
Your Majesty,
that is
why I
came here.
Dr. Jun
volunteers to
treat Prince Huai.
Volunteer?
Yes.
Dr. Jun is
the granddaughter of the Fang family who runs Deshengchang.
The Fang family?
You get out first.
Yes.
The granddaughter of the Fang family
is Jun Zhenzhen who helped the Fang family to avoid misfortunes?
Yes, Your Majesty.
She is proficient in medicine?
Dr. Jun
has inherited her ancestral drugstore
and renamed
herself
Jun Jiuling.
Jun Jiuling?
Yes.
Jiuling.
Why did she rename herself Jiuling?
She also opened a clinic called Jiuling Drugstore
in the capital city.
The drugstore is called Jiuling Drugstore?
And she also renamed herself
Jiuling.
What is the Fang family doing now?
Your Majesty,
the Fangs
behave themselves recently,
and run Deshengchang as before.
Except for their identity of imperial merchant,
nothing else has changed.
What if I
ask Jun Jiuling,
the granddaughter
of the Fang family
to treat Prince Huai,
but she fails to
cure his disease?
Your Majesty,
there was
such a
precedent.
An imperial doctor misdiagnosed a concubine's disease,
which implicated his whole family.
As a result,
all his families were beheaded.
It's hard to cure scrofula.
If Jun Jiuling
fails to cure the disease of Prince Huai,
who is the son of the late emperor,
all the people
must burn with rage.
Then killing all her families
must be able to
please the people.
Then
let Jun Jiuling
have a try.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Ladyship,
don't you really need me to go with you?
No.
Scrofula is not
a common disease.
Are you sure of curing it?
I'll try.
But if you…
Enough.
Don't worry.
Wait for me to come back.
I'm leaving.
It's scrofula.
It's normal that it can't be cured.
It's just a bet.
If she wins, she'll be well-known and wealthy.
If she fails,
it'll be also normal.
If she wins, she'll be indeed well-known and wealthy,
but if she fails,
she will not only lose her face.
How about we spread a rumor?
What?
Let everyone know that
scrofula
is an incurable disease.
Zhu Zan,
why are you here?
Follow me.
What's the matter?
Let's do a deal.
If you cure Jiurong's disease,
I'll save your life.
If you fail,
I'll save the lives of the Fangs.
If you cure his disease,
you'll annoy His Majesty.
Then your life will be threatened.
If you fail,
the Fang family will be implicated.
Jun,
you have no choice.
It's inevitable.
Please do your best to save him.
Why do you do so?
He is Jiuling's brother
and also mine.
I'd like to do so.
I'm leaving.
Jun!
Indecent.
Scrofula.
The patient's sores will crack and suppurate at later stage.
It the sores can't be cured in time,
they would affect the liver and kidney.
Then the patient will be deficient in vital energy.
Prince Huai is young,
so it's hard for him
to resist scrofula.
Uncle.
Yunzhao,
why are you so interested
in Prince Huai's disease?
I just sympathize with Prince Huai
for his adverse fortune.
He is predestined to suffer.
You shouldn't sympathize with him.
Illness is just illness,
not adverse fortune.
There are countless orphans in this world,
and many patients who suffer from
incurable diseases are everywhere.
How could you
sign for
Prince Huai's disease?
You can benefit the country and people
in many ways.
Don't behave like a woman.
Yes.
Uncle,
I heard that His Majesty
has allowed Dr. Jun of the Jiuling Drugstore
to treat His Highness Prince Huai.
Don't worry.
Go back to the Imperial Academy for review.
Yes,
uncle.
Dr. Jun is a well-known great doctor.
Maybe she can cure
Prince Huai's disease.
But others all think that
scrofula is incurable.
Yunzhao,
you're sympathizing with Prince Huai
or worried about Dr. Jun?
Uncle,
I'm going back to the Imperial Academy.
OK.
If something happens in Prince Huai's mansion,
I'll tell you.
Thank you, uncle.
You really come.
I'm a doctor.
It's my duty.
Jiuli.
Jiurong.
I'm coming.
I'm back.
Your Highness,
Dr. Jun comes.
Here is my respect, Your Highness.
Get up please.
Sister.
Jiurong.
I feel bad.
♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
I'm here.
The doctor comes.
Let the doctor treat you later.
Sister.
I'm here.
Second sister.
Sister.
Come to see him.
Yes.
Jiurong's neck is clean and smooth
and has no lumps.
He doesn't suffer from scrofula.
It's lucky.
It seems that
scrofula is just
an excuse of the Imperial Academy of Medicine.
Second sister.
Your Highness.
You're here.
Dr. Jun,
what do you think about His Highness Prince Huai's disease?
It's indeed
hard to cure it.
Does he suffer from scrofula?
Yes.
Your Highness,
I have some experience in curing it,
so I can cure
His Highness' disease.
I heard that folk doctors have excellent prescriptions.
Now that you came confidently,
you must be able to cure it.
Tell me
whatever you need.
Yes.
Then I'm going to decoct the herbs.
Thank you, Dr. Jun.
Dr. Jun, this way, please.
Now
people say
how serious the scrofula is
and how hard it is to cure everywhere.
The Jiuling Drugstore
must be blamed for it.
Yeah.
They just want everyone to know
how serious the scrofula is
and then they can pass the buck
if the scrofula can't be cured.
Imperial Doctor Jiang,
what do you think about it?
Ignore it.
Suit themselves.
As long as His Majesty wants to blame her,
it doesn't matter
whether it's scrofula
and it can be cured or not.
Dr. Jun,
let me help you.
No need.
You go to guard at the door for me.
Yes.
Dr. Jun washed, cut
and decocted the herbs personally
and always kept an eye on the medicine.
She also didn't allow anyone to enter the eastern kitchen.
Your Highness,
the medicine is ready.
Go to fetch the crane-mouth pot.
He can't swallow now.
Wait a moment.
The use of crane-mouth pot
will make him feel bad.
Let me try.
OK.
Your Highness,
help him up for me.
OK.
Come on, Jiurong.
Jiurong,
take the medicine.
Come on.
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
make him breathe smoothly.
OK.
He should be able to swallow now.
Let's try again.
OK.
Jiurong,
listen to me.
Take the medicine,
OK?
Jiurong, be good.
He has swallowed it.
Whether His Highness
can get better
depends on whether his fever can be reduced tonight.
Can I
put him down?
Yes.
Keep him flat.
If you're tired,
you can go to bed,
and I'll look after His Highness Prince Huai here.
Jiurong.
Jiuling,
bless her cure Jiurong's disease
in the paradise.
Grandma, look.
Grandma,
do you like them?
Yes. Yes. Yes.
How did you buy
so many flowers and plants?
Beautiful.
Thank you.
I feel happy that you like them.
Today is neither a festival
nor birthday,
you
must buy so many flowers
for something.
Grandma,
please send the imperial decree
to the Jiuling Drugstore in the capital city.
Chengyu.
Chengyu, do you know
what you're saying?
Get up first.
Get up and talk.
Please promise me.
Don't kneel.
Get up.
Chengyu,
get up.
What happened to her
in the capital city?
You're so anxious
to ask me for the imperial decree here.
Command Lu
wanted to smash Jiuling's plaque.
Command Lu is narrow-minded,
so I think
we can only send the decree
to the Jiuling Drugstore
to stop him.
Why did she offend
the Arm Moral Department as a doctor?
Because of
the name.
Name?
The fever of His Highness Prince Huai has been reduced.
He is much better.
So he won't be dead, right?
Your Highness,
please look after His Highness first,
I'm going to decoct the herbs.
Where are you going?
I'm going to decoct herbs for His Highness Prince Huai.
Why don't you let someone else do this?
Isn't that faster?
I don't trust others.
Your Excellency knows
I came uninvited.
A lot of people are waiting to laugh at my failure.
If I lose,
it will be a shame for me.
By the way,
no one is allowed to touch
what I use to decoct the herbs.
Otherwise,
if His Highness Prince Huai can't be cured,
it won't be my responsibility.
Including Your Excellency.
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫Every of its words will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫It's me♫
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
♫Any clues?♫
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫