♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
Episode 28
Jiuling Drugstore
Danfengmen
Lord Cheng's wife Yu Lan
Your Excellency,
I've sent them
to Ghost Hand as you required.
How will we
explain it if His Majesty or the Imperial Academy of Medicine
asks about them?
A prisoner
suffered from a serious disease,
and Imperial Doctor Jiang
was always responsible,
so
he lived in the prison.
Do you know
what to say about the rest?
Imperial Doctor Jiang did his best to treat the prisoner
but suffered from an incurable disease in the prison
and then died.
You can go.
You shouldn't try to hurt my woman.
Your Excellency,
Miss Jun has left Zezhou
and headed north.
I don't think
she would bring too many men on the way.
I will take some people
to bring Miss Jun back for you.
But
you must do it
after she settles the problem.
Yes.
Let's go.
Your Majesty,
please let me
return to the North.
How dare you talk about the war!
OK,
let me show you something.
This one
accuses your father
of delay of military plan.
Read it.
This one
accuses your father
of cheating and disloyalty.
This one accuses you and your father
of occupying and spending the military expenditure in expanding your mansion.
You can read them.
How dare you mention the war?
Do you want to take this opportunity
to go on occupying the military expenditure?
Read them.
Read!
Read them carefully!
All are to impeach you and your father.
I trust you,
so I don't believe the contents in these memorials.
How could you repay me in this way?
No wonder people in the North say that
there is an emperor in the South,
while there is Lord Cheng in the North.
Your Zhu's army
is really awesome!
Your Majesty,
these rumors
are baseless.
You're the guardian god and the belief
of the North.
People always say,
without you,
my father won't be there
guarding the peace and prosperity of the North.
Your Majesty,
my father Zhu Shan is dedicated.
He'll risk his life for the court at any time.
He is loyal.
Your Majesty,
you're wise.
Don't hear and believe slanders.
That's what you say!
Tell me.
Don't you know
why I kept you in the capital city?
Do you know?
I'm trying to shut up those
who have impeached you.
I want to make them believe that
as you're under my control,
your father will be afraid.
I put on a show for them.
Your Majesty.
Fine.
Go to feed horses
in the Pasturage Department.
Your Majesty,
I want to redeem myself by good service.
I want to go out to battle with my father.
Miss Jun,
those of Arm Moral Department are following us.
They've done
nothing to us so far.
Just let them be.
What should we do?
Return to Zezhou?
Keep heading north.
We managed to come here.
I want to check if it's alright with the vaccine.
Lady Jinxiu,
Miss Jun sent a letter here.
Well,
let me have a look.
What,
what did she say?
Is it
about the vaccine?
Something went wrong with the vaccine,
but it has nothing
to do with ours.
It's false.
False?
What,
what's the matter?
Blinded by greed,
several doctors
who know how to vaccinate,
extracted vaccine from those
who got vaccinated.
However, they did it in a wrong way.
With strong toxicity,
the vaccine went wrong.
I see.
Luckily, it's solved.
Yes. Yes.
His Majesty doesn't let me go back,
but I must go back.
If you go out now,
more people will want to kill you.
Zan,
be careful.
By the way,
how about the vaccine in the southwestern Hebei?
Miss Jun has solved it,
but
she is missing.
I think she is
hiding from those of Lu Yunqi.
Your Lordship.
Someone is calling you.
I'll let you know
as soon as I get her news.
How troublesome she is!
Coming.
Your Excellency,
the princess is fine.
She just got a cold.
I'll take good care
of the princess.
Don't make any mistakes.
Don't worry.
I'll try my best.
I'll prescribe now.
Your Highness
needs to take good care of yourself,
even if
it's for His Highness Prince Huai.
He has lost Jiuling.
He can't afford to lose you.
I know.
Back then,
did Jiuling
ask you to take care of us?
No.
Then I have to be grateful to you.
Please have more rest.
Jiuling,
Princess Jiuli
thanked me for taking care of her and Jiurong.
She asked if you asked me to do that.
If you know that
I have done all this for you,
will you be moved?
Fine.
As I like you,
I'll try my best
to catch anyone
who is a bit like you.
I won't miss them.
Old Master,
His Excellency Yu is here.
Let him in.
Minister Huang,
thank you for your strategy.
It seems that
we'll get
the three counties in Zhending soon.
You got benefit
in this deal,
but
I got nothing.
Lord Cheng
wasn't killed by Beiqi.
He even defeated Beiqi
and recovered Hejian Prefecture.
Minister Huang,
we were sure that
we would get Hejian Prefecture.
However,
Lord Cheng
rushed to the rescue quickly.
Your handwriting
lives up to its reputation.
You can write beautiful regular scripts in Academy Style.
I admire you.
We still want to
make up with you,
so please
pass that on.
Zhu Zan
killed my son.
I'll make him and his father pay with their lives.
I wanted to kill Zhu Zan
through Lu Yunqi,
but it was in vain.
You want peace as you lost.
Who will
avenge my son?
His Excellency Junior Huang
was nice to me,
but
I can't go against the imperial order.
If you want to make peace at this time,
the credit will go to Lord Cheng.
In this case,
Lord Cheng will be known
not only in the North,
but also around the country.
What do you mean?
Whether you offer counties,
money or treasures,
they're external wealth.
You're
in good faith,
but that's far from enough.
Dare you
fight to death?
Express your sincerity
with lives
of Beiqi generals and soldiers.
It's such a big thing
that I can't decide.
Leave it to His Majesty.
A long delay may cause trouble.
Be quick.
Yes.
Minister Huang,
I'm
leaving.
I'll go north.
Your Ladyship,
are we going to travel again?
I wonder where we're going first.
Your Ladyship,
something happened.
Beiqi has waged
a war against our country.
Wage a war?
Beiqi has thrown down the gauntlet.
It has gathered its generals and soldiers
and attacked from east and west.
Lord Cheng has ordered
all prefectures to prepare for war.
The Yongxing Army and the Guangcheng Army
are currently being mobilized.
People's life
goes as usual.
They have reserved food
and reduced going out
as required,
but
the North
is not as peaceful as before.
We'd better not go north
for the time being.
Yes.
It'll be dangerous once the war is started.
Your Ladyship,
why don't we turn back?
Whether to Zezhou
or the capital city,
we'll follow you.
No.
In this case,
we must go to the North
and visit all prefectures.
Only when the vaccination is arranged
can Lord Cheng
fight again the enemies
without worrying the people.
But we...
-We… -Just do it.
Go pack things now.
We'll leave today.
Yes.
I didn't expect the war has become stalemated.
Get ready to move.
Gather those
of the Sky Pavilion in the southwestern Hebei.
We'll meet there.
How will you get out?
I have my ways.
Zan,
there is news of Miss Jun.
She went north from Qingyuan Prefecture.
Go find out about her first
and then meet us.
OK.
Minister Huang,
this is a jade seal that the emperor of Beiqi
asked skilled craftsmen to make.
You can use it after all is done.
Please have a look.
Do you like it?
It's too early
to talk about that.
The war situation
is unfavorable to Beiqi.
Lord Cheng is so brave.
We suffered heavy losses
in the battle in Xiongzhou.
I know
you can't handle him.
That's why we need your strategy.
Raid Kaide Prefecture.
It's
the sore spot of my country.
His Majesty will
recall Zhu Shan for help.
If he doesn't come back,
he acts against the order.
If he comes back...
Good idea.
Minister Huang, it's a good idea.
As soon as I go back,
I'll start a military action.
Be quick.
Don't worry.
It'll be foolproof.
As
the prime minister,
I feel sorry
for my country.
With civil and military skills,
you should be
the emperor of the country.
Governor,
remember.
I must get Zhu Shan and his son killed.
Don't expose your wound to water these days.
Be sure to wrap it up.
Your Ladyship,
here is Fuxi powder.
Right.
Give him Siwu powder
and decoct it with 1.5g of pseudo-ginseng
to take the decoction.
OK.
Fuxi powder.
Well.
Be careful.
-Let me support you. -Thanks, Dr. Jun.
Take this.
Your Ladyship,
those seriously injured have been arranged properly.
The vaccination has begun
over there.
OK. Thanks.
Liu'er,
conditions are tough here.
-Be careful. -You've worked hard.
I like
working with you.
Go.
Let's check over there.
Dr. Jun. Dr. Jun. Dr. Jun.
Dr. Jun is here.
It's my turn.
Dr. Jun.
Fellow citizens,
Lord Cheng asked me
to vaccinate you.
He knows clearly
your sufferings
and fear
in the intrusion,
so he specially
asked me to cure you here.
This is the blessing
of the people and the North.
Now
I've taught local doctors
how to vaccinate.
Please cooperate with them on the treatment.
Thanks, Dr. Jun.
His Highness Lord Cheng is so kind.
He is so kind.
Thanks, Dr. Jun.
Don't stand on ceremony.
Living in the North,
we're one big family.
Let's continue the vaccination.
Kids under 10 come first.
Well. Please.
Liu'er,
go help Mr. Lei.
OK.
Betel nut tastes bitter.
It's warm, astringent and non-toxic.
It promotes digestion and relieves diuresis.
It can eliminate phlegm, kill worms,
cure hidden diseases
and kill pinworm. It grows in the south coast.
What are you doing, Mr. Lei?
Miss Jun said,
after years of wars in the North,
food and drinking water here
have become so dirty.
In addition, there is miasma.
The people are certainly
breeding diseases and worms.
Betel nuts
can promote qi, kill worms,
eliminate accumulation and relieve diuresis.
It's a good medicine supplement.
Now that
Miss Jun has left the important task
of sorting medicinal materials to me,
I must not make mistakes.
I need to know the efficacy
of these herbs.
You're so attentive.
Your Majesty,
we can't let Kaide Prefecture fall.
Back then, Beiqi
attacked from there
and went all the way south
to surround the capital city.
Nobody could rescue.
The then emperor's father was captured.
At last,
he died in Beiqi.
Are they
going to
repeat it?
Your Majesty,
please order Lord Cheng
to protect Kaide Prefecture.
The same route.
The same strategy.
What a coincidence!
Your Majesty, please don't.
Lord Cheng is fighting
against Beiqi in the North.
If he is recalled at this point,
the North
will be trampled upon at will.
Minister Ning,
you mean we can ignore
the safety of the capital city?
I don't mean that.
Minister Huang, don't take this out of context.
I care about Your Majesty.
It's all for your safety.
Your Majesty, please recall
Lord Cheng to protect Kaide Prefecture.
Your Majesty,
even if you don't worry about your safety,
think about all the people in the city.
Your Majesty.
Please recall Lord Cheng to protect Kaide Prefecture.
Yaozi Pass.
Qingpa River.
Liangcheng City.
The capital of my country.
It's risky to raid
Kaide Prefecture alone.
It doesn't seem like
fighting to get into the interior.
What a coincidence!
All marching routes
are like those
in the third year of the Taiyan period.
They want to
disturb the morale of our army.
What's wrong with the horses?
The horses are running away.
They're running away.
Stop them.
Hurry up.
I can't.
Don't let them run away.
Someone.
Stop them.
Chase them.
Order
Lord Cheng
to dispatch troops immediately
to protect Kaide Prefecture.
Your Majesty,
I think
you can issue more edicts
to show your reliance on Lord Cheng
and to let him know that
it's serious,
so he'll return immediately.
Then issue another
two,
three...
No.
Issue ten edicts.
Your Majesty is wise.
Zhu,
Zhu Zan ran away.
Your Majesty,
How useless!
How can they let him run away?
What happened?
The horses were startled,
so he chased them.
However, as he whistled all the way,
the horses
followed him.
The horses
didn't fear swords and arrows.
Zhu Zan hid in them,
so no one could catch him.
Your Excellency,
it's my fault.
Though we were careful,
we didn't expect that
he ran away like this.
Pleas punish me.
Let it go
this time.
Do something for me.
Your Excellency,
what's your order?
Your Majesty has sent orders around the country.
Son of Lord Cheng fled to escape punishment.
Whoever sees him
can catch him.
Yes.
I'll notify men of all departments.
Your Ladyship.
OK.
Your Ladyship,
they've followed us all the way.
How persevering!
Let them go.
They've done nothing to us
all the way.
The North is uneasy now.
Take them as our body guards.
Go.
Protect madame.
There's a fight down there.
Your Ladyship,
shall we avoid it?
Help them.
Get on the horse.
Your Ladyship, be careful.
Your Excellency,
what should we do?
Laoba,
find a chance to escape,
or we'll be killed here.
Don't worry, madame.
I'll keep you safe.
Protect madame.
Laoba.
Madame Yu.
Leave.
Run.
I'm fine.
Be careful.
Madame.
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Are you alright?
What's wrong, madame?
Well, be careful.
Well.
Madame,
your feet may hurt a bit these days.
Hold on.
If it doesn't hurt,
it'll be troublesome.
Leave it to me.
Well.
Be careful.
Are you alright?
Yes.
What's your surname, young lady?
My surname is Jun.
Miss Jun.
Where are you going, madame?
Daming Prefecture.
He wasn't a robber.
He just killed and robbed us of nothing.
I think he was
from Beiqi.
Miss Jun.
Please wait, madame.
Mr. Lei,
what's going on there?
Your Ladyship,
they weren't robbers,
but Beiqi soldiers in disguise.
I see.
That makes sense.
Mr. Lei,
change our route to Daming Prefecture.
Daming Prefecture?
Yes.
Why?
I have no time to explain.
I'll tell you later.
Get ready and go.
OK.
Go
Everyone,
Clean up now
and get ready to go.
Madame,
I'll escort you to Daming Prefecture.
It seems that
you have no other choice now.
Your Excellency Jin,
thank you all the way.
What do you mean, Miss Jun?
I wonder when His Excellency Lu
will capture me to the capital city.
You misunderstand.
I don't mean to do that.
So you're escorting me.
In this case,
I have to trouble you in the following journey.
Coming.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Hurry up.
Is it ready?
A moment. A moment.
Well, here you are.
Pour.
Why are you crying?
Give me one.
Beauty,
let me have a look.
Let me have a look.
Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Pour. Pour. Pour.
Pour.
Fill it. Fill it.
Is it ready?
A moment. A moment.
Be patient.
I haven't eaten.
Someone is there.
Run.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Where is Baotang?
He gathered brothers in northwest
and went to Kaide Prefecture directly.
No news of Miss Jun.
Let's go
to Kaide Prefecture.
He has refused
ten of my edicts.
Damn Zhu Shan!
Your Majesty,
please punish
Zhu Shan, Lord Cheng,
for being treacherous.
Your Majesty,
please punish
Zhu Shan, Lord Cheng,
for being overbearing.
Your Majesty,
please punish
Zhu Shan
for being overbearing.
Your Majesty,
as Zhu Zan escaped,
Lord Cheng fears nothing.
How dare they
do that!
Your Majesty,
I've sent out wanted orders around the country.
We'll catch Zhu Zan
as soon as possible.
Your Majesty,
we just see that as his son
escaped,
Lord Cheng fears nothing.
But think about it.
As son of Lord Cheng escaped to the North,
the wanted orders will spread all over the country.
It's dangerous to him.
As a father,
the easiest choice for Lord Cheng
is to send troops back to defend.
Thus, your edicts will be obeyed
and his son will be saved.
It's the best way to achieve both.
But Lord Cheng
doesn't mind that his son
is in danger.
He just sees that
if he leads troops back to defend,
the North will be in chaos,
the people there will suffer
and the country will be destroyed.
Your Majesty,
Lord Cheng
seems to go against you,
but he is actually refusing to do
what a father should do.
He puts the North above everything,
Your Majesty.
It's alright now.
You mean
I'm inferior
to Lord Cheng.
Your Majesty,
I don't mean that.
It's my country.
Don't tell me
what to do.
Your Majesty,
please think carefully.
How arrogant you are!
I will suspend your position
and punish you
by pondering over your mistakes in solitude
for three months.
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫Every of its words will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫It's me♫
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
♫Any clues?♫
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫