♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
Episode 15
Opened by Fang Jinxiu
Ning Mansion
Mansion of Marquis of Dingyuan
Imperial Doctor of the Imperial Academy of Medicine Jiang Youshu
Mansion of Prince Huai
Lu Mansion
The Imperial Academy of Medicine
Jiuling Drugstore
I'll take this.
Which one?
This one.
-I want that one. -This one?
-Okay. -I want one too.
Okay.
It's freshly made and very sweet.
I'm sure you'll like it.
Here you are.
-Okay. -Let's go.
-Here is the money. -Okay.
Come on. This way.
Welcome next time.
Let's go.
Jinxiu.
Yuxiu.
Are you okay?
Long time no see.
I miss you so much.
I didn't expect the sugar figurines you made
are innovative.
However innovative they are,
they are just sugar figurines.
You've been selling sugar figurines here.
Will you feel wronged?
Not at all.
Didn't you just see
they sell good?
Don't worry.
How about
I introduce another business to you?
Then you can put the business knowledge
you learned into practice.
Really?
What business?
Here is a letter from Jiuling to you.
I know
you didn't get well along with each other.
But you know
her conduct and personality.
I think you can think about
the advice she gave you.
Okay.
I'll keep it.
Lantern.
Lanterns.
Then I'll go.
Go.
Sugar figurines.
Sweet sugar figurines.
Do you think it's really good
to ask her to go to the capital?
She has gone it through
and let go the past.
She has the ability to do bigger things,
instead of being trapped in Zezhou all her life.
Let me have a look.
Jinxiu,
with your intelligence,
selling sugar figurines is just a temporary strategy for you,
not a long-term business.
You have learned many skills in the Fang family
for more than ten years.
Don't waste them.
The capital has bigger
and more opportunities.
If you like,
come to the capital
to give full play to your ability.
What's up?
You look worried.
Sugar figurines are not selling well?
I don't want to sell sugar figurines anymore.
Then don't sell
them today.
Take a day off.
Do whatever you want.
Do whatever I want?
This is your style.
I want to go to the capital.
Is it true?
Yes, Young Master.
I don't know what's going on.
Only half a month later,
those who used to
avoid Miss Jun as much as possible
all came to visit her.
They asked,
"Miss Jun.
Look at me.
Do I have a bad omen?"
If Miss Jun said no,
they would be happy
and feel healthy.
Now those women
are proud of
having no bad omen
as Miss Jun said.
Young Master.
You're right.
Miss Jun
is really amazing.
All right.
I got it.
You can leave.
Imperial Doctor Jiang.
How is she?
Senior Madame.
She is the same.
Just continue
to take the medicine for observation.
But she has been taking this medicine for some time
and no improvement is seen.
Our Madame feels so painful
that she cries night after night.
How can she endure this?
People may get sick easily,
but won't recover that easily.
Madam's disease has last for a long time.
No hurry.
Thank you, Imperial Doctor Jiang.
Thank you so much.
I'm leaving.
I'll die first
before those drugs work.
Find some more famous doctors.
Who is more famous
than Imperial Doctor Jiang in this capital?
Senior Madame.
Speaking of this,
I want to
recommend a great doctor.
Mrs. Zhou,
who are you talking about?
The great doctor of Jiuling Drugstore,
Dr. Jun Jiuling.
Jiuling Drugstore
brings a patient back to life
and offers efficient  medicine.
Miss Jun.
What's up?
I finally found you.
What's wrong?
Someone from the mansion of Marquis of Dingyuan
is looking for you for a visit.
Mansion of Marquis of Dingyuan?
Yeah.
Their carriage
has been at the gate of our drugstore.
Go.
People on the street now
dare not to laugh at her.
What's more interesting is
if there's something wrong with anyone,
they would like to  go see her.
If Miss Jun
didn't say they had a bad omen
or ignore them,
they would think there was nothing wrong with them
and would go to other doctors for treatment.
Is it that she pretends to be mystery
or she just treats those she likes?
We'll learn it after a try.
Sir,
I don't understand the meaning of this sentence.
Your Highness.
It means…
Jiurong.
Your Highness Princess.
Your Excellency Lu.
Jiurong, you grow taller?
You'll be a man soon.
It's time for you
to learn martial arts.
Do you want to learn martial arts?
I can teach you.
You don't have to look at your sister.
If you want to learn,
just learn it.
If you don't want to,
just tell us frankly.
Your Highness,
stay and eat with him.
I have something else to do.
I have to go.
Now that you are here,
can I
rest for half a day
and continue reading in the afternoon?
Sorry for showing you this, Mr. Gu.
It doesn't matter.
His Highness has done well
in lessons recently.
I can give him a reward.
of half a day's rest.
Thank your teacher.
Thank you, sir.
Come here and let me have a good look.
During my absence,
did you eat well?
You still cough after a long time.
Didn't the imperial doctor come to see you?
Never mind, sister.
How can we ignore your illness?
Then later
I'll tell them to change another imperial doctor
to come and see you.
Sister, it's okay.
My status is embarrassing.
You don't have to call for imperial doctors.
Sister,
why are you crying?
It's the tears of happiness because I meet you.
This, this, this…
This.
Shopkeeper Liu?
Your Ladyship.
You're back finally.
I just left for a patient.
What made you so nervous?
Mansion of Marquis of Dingyuan!
That's a real royal family.
Can I not worry?
They all eat cereals
and all would be sick like ordinary people.
This…
Miss Jun.
It's fine to
say this in our store.
Don't say it out.
How's it going?
Doctors should keep the patient's condition confidential.
How can I tell you that?
Of course I'm not asking
about Mrs. Lin's illness.
I mean, how was your treatment?
Pretty good.
I gave Mrs. Lin a dose of medicine today.
She is getting much better.
I think,
she will be all right
in a couple of days.
So fast?
Before,
the mansion of Marquis of Dingyuan invited
Jiang Youshu from the Imperial Academy of Medicine.
Jiang Youshu
is the best doctor in the Imperial Academy of Medicine.
He had been treating Mrs. Lin for almost a month.
But her condition has not been improved a little.
If you cure her in three days…
You didn't tell the mansion of Marquis of Dingyuan this, did you?
Yes, I did.
This, this, this…
Shopkeeper Liu.
Take it easy.
I'll be careful.
All right.
Look at this.
Just follow this prescription
to prepare the medicine.
OK.
Imperial Doctor Zhou.
What's up?
What's wrong with him?
You really don't know it?
Because of the disease of that madam in the Mansion of Marquis of Dingyuan.
That Mrs. Lin
was born delicate and noble.
Imperial Jiang
spent more than a month
mildly adjusting
and slowly treating her.
But when she was about to recover,
a female hand-bell doctor
came out suddenly
and prescribed
a powerful dose of medicine.
Three days.
Only three days later,
Mrs. Lin got
much better.
It happened only a few days ago.
But this matter
has spread all over the capital.
Several ministers
had ordered the visiting of Imperial Doctor Jiang
have change
to call on that female doctor.
How can
he be all right now?
What's the name of that female doctor?
We can keep her name in mind
and find a chance
to teach her a lesson.
She may be called
Jun Jiuling.
On Qianmen Street,
she also runs a clinic
called Jiuling Drugstore.
Then we don't need to act.
Someone else would teach her a lesson.
Imperial Doctor Zhang,
what do you mean?
Someone doesn't
allow others
to call themselves Jiuling.
Lord Lu has been busy with official business recently
so he hasn't noticed it.
I think
we should remind him.
What do you think?
Good idea.
Your Excellency,
the granddaughter of the Fang family
Jun Zhenzhen
had come to the capital one month ago
and opened a clinic
called Jiuling Drugstore.
She also changed
her name into
Jun Jiuling.
Jun Jiuling?
It happened last month.
Why did delay in reporting it?
You are preparing for your wedding.
I didn't dare to use trouble you
with such a trifle.
In addition,
this news is deliberately sent by the Imperial Academy of Medicine.
The Imperial Academy of Medicine
wants to use me?
I know who's going to deal with her.
You don't have to send a message for others.
Your Excellency.
Although this matter
is really caused by the Imperial Academy of Medicine.
But she did
commit the name taboo of Princess Jiuling.
How about
we teach her a lesson?
No need.
Jiang Youshu is not a man who can swallow loss.
Since he's going to solve the problem for us,
we can just look on and do nothing.
Pass my orders.
When Dr. Jiang takes actions,
leave him alone.
Yes.
Jiuling Drugstore?
Jun Jiuling?
You look
well today.
If it weren't for Mrs. Zhou,
-I would be still lying. -Madame.
Miss Jun has arrived.
Here is my respect, madams.
Miss Jun.
Get up please.
Your medicine worked.
My daughter-in-law
is getting much better
and looks much better.
Madam looks
really much better today.
Miss Jun has excellent medical skills.
I've been ill for so many days.
These days,
I really don't feel any pain
and can sleep tight.
That's good.
I'll give you acupuncture today
to consolidate it.
Okay.
Thank you, Miss Jun.
It's my pleasure.
Senior Madame,
Commander Lu sends someone to invite Mrs. Fang.
Prince?
He lacks nothing.
Why did he invite a cook from his sister's house?
It should be for Princess Jiuli.
Princess Jiuli used to like the red bean cake
made by our Mrs. Fang.
Speaking of this,
she used to
invite Mrs. Fang into the palace
for making red bean cake.
However,
since the death of the late emperor,
she moved to Prince Huai's mansion
and hasn't sent anyone to invite Mrs. Fang again.
Let her go.
Just a cook.
Don't mind such taboos.
Yes.
Speaking of Prince Huai's mansion,
have you heard it?
Little prince
has been sick for days.
What can he do?
After his sister gets married,
none would care about
him sincerely.
He is just a kid.
Even slight negligence
would make him sick.
Yeah.
It's hard for such a kid.
Madame,
let's begin the acupuncture.
Okay.
Princess.
This is the new red bean cake made in the kitchen.
Please have a try.
This is made by Mrs. Fang of the Mansion of Marquis of Dingyuan.
His Excellency heard that you like this cake,
so he specially invited her to make some.
It tastes the same as before.
It hasn't changed at all.
If you like it,
I can let her come often.
Thank you.
Red bean cake is delicious.
Why not have some?
I don't like this.
You don't even like
such a delicious dessert?
I have something else to do.
I won't come back for dinner tonight.
Princess.
His Excellency,
His Excellency seems to
go over there again.
Princess,
you can't be always
so courtesy
to him.
In the mansion,
all the people
know that
on the wedding night,
His Excellency
didn't stay with you.
Princess…
Enough.
Are you OK?
Take your time. Thank you.
Candied Haws.
Your Ladyship, red bean cake.
Here.
Does it taste good?
Yes.
Red bean cake
is not delicious at all.
But my sister likes to eat it.
She has a strange taste.
You advised me to try it,
but I always refused.
Now when you're not with me,
I buy it myself.
It's not delicious either.
I just want to meet you.
Do you know Prince Huai?
Yeah.
I heard that
he is sick.
What sickness?
I don't know.
Looks like he has been ill for a long time.
It's not that easy
to learn things about the mansion of Prince Huai.
Where did you hear that?
I went to the Mansion of Marquis of Dingyuan today
to diagnose those madams.
They mentioned it.
It's said that
the Imperial Academy of Medicine speculates about the emperor's intention
and refuses to treat him well.
These bastards are at the helm.
I mean,
since you know Prince Huai
and I was one of princess' friends,
I should help them.
But if you want to go to treat him,
I advise you to give up.
Whether His Majesty or Lu Yunqi
won't allow you, a hand-bell doctor
to cure Prince Huai.
Then please
pay more attention to him.
Or,
is it feasible
to find
a doctor you know
to go to see him?
I will try my best.
But it will take some time.
After all, Prince Huai's mansion
is the watchful eye of Lu Yunqi.
You know my relationship
with him.
I will try.
Okay.
Here we are.
Jinxiu,
we have arrived in the capital.
Don't make a fool of yourself.
Looks like you haven't seen the world.
It looks close.
But I didn't expect to it takes so long.
It's killing me.
Who told you to follow me?
You can't ride a horse yet.
If I had ridden a horse by myself, I would have arrived long ago.
I heard that
selling sugar figurines
can make a lot of money in the capital.
Of course I would like
to make a fortune with you.
Who told you to follow me?
Don't worry.
Later, I, Chen Qi,
will never humiliate Fang Jinxiu.
You.
What are you shouting?
You have nothing
to do with me.
What a rare guest!
What does Your Lordship come to the Imperial Academy of Medicine for?
I just came back from the North.
I can't get used
to the diet
and have backache.
Thinking that
you are all busy
and I am idle,
I came for some treatment.
We are flattered.
If you send a message here,
we will go to see you
however busy we are.
No more polite words.
Where's Doctor Jiang?
I'm here for him.
What a coincidence.
He is not here.
How about I ask him
to go to your mansion when he comes back?
No need.
I'm free today.
I'll look around.
I can wait for him.
Fine.
Please help yourself.
I have to go.
Go, go ahead.
I wonder whether Miss Jun's clinic
has good business or not.
By rights,
it's not that easy to set a foothold
in such a big place as the capital
by relying on medical skills
in less than two months.
I don't think people
know Jiuling Drugstore.
Not necessarily.
You don't know her skills?
Just ask someone.
Hello, sir.
Sorry to bother you.
Do you know
the newly opened clinic called Jiuling Drugstore here?
Jiuling Drugstore?
Yes, I know.
Everyone in the capital
knows Doctor Jun.
See?
Follow this road
and go straight.
Around the corner,
it's Jiuling Drugstore.
OK.
Thank you.
Never mention it.
The situation in the capital is much more difficult than that in Runan.
I didn't expect that
Miss Jun really has this ability.
What did I say?
Go.
Here we are.
Let's get in.
How does she manage this shop?
The waiter is so lazy.
What business can there be?
Are you
Miss Fang and Childe Chen
from Zezhou?
How did you know?
Except you,
there are no more people coming to see a doctor.
Miss Jun has calculated the date and told us
you two would arrive in these two days.
She ordered us to receive you early in the morning.
But on her letter,
she didn't ask me to come here frankly.
She also predicted this?
Yeah.
Where is she?
Why is she here?
She left to be a hand-bell doctor.
She'll be back in a minute.
Please follow me.  -Hand-bell doctor?
The back wing rooms have been cleaned out.
Your Ladyship.
I am tired and hungry all the way.
I'd like to add a dish at noon.
-Is that okay? -Okay.
I want to eat that roast chicken.
Glad to meet you here.
Miss Jun.
You must have a tough journey to here.
No.
Let's chat inside.
Go.
Okay.
This is muscle strain.
It's not serious.
You'll get better after taking some medicines.
OK.
Dr. Feng,
come to treat him.
He is badly hurt,
but why are you so happy?
Miss Jun said that
it is
not serious.
So we
are happy.
Since that you had been to
the Jiuling Drugstore,
why do you come here now?
Dr. Feng,
you can't say so.
Miss Jun said that
it's not serious
and he'll
get better soon
after being boneset by you.
She said so?
She asked you
to come to my clinic?
Yes.
Dr. Feng,
Miss Jun also said that
you must
be able to cure him.
What are you talking about?
Dr. Feng has practiced medicine
for several decades
and is famous in the capital city.
How could she evaluate
Dr. Feng casually?
She is unqualified
to be compared with Dr. Feng.
Qi.
Now that you've gone
to the Jiuling Drugstore,
he should be treated there.
You'd better
go there.
Go.
Miss Jun of the Jiuling Drugstore is a doctor of saving lives.
My disease
is not worth Miss Jun's treatment.
Dr. Feng,
please treat me.
Treat him right now.
Yeah. What?
Save lives but not cure diseases?
It's ridiculous.
How could a doctor
behave like this?
Go.
Today,
let me accompany you to reason with her.
Go.
Go to have a look.
Come on.
Well,
there will be a great show in the Jiuling Drugstore today.
If I'm free,
I'll definitely go to have a look.
You'd better not go.
Only by avoiding it
can the Imperial Academy of Medicine
be not suspected.
Jun Zhenzhen
gets herself into trouble again.
I've long been expecting that
you could come here.
From now on,
the Jiuling Drugstore
is our house.
We just came once we made up our mind.
It's a long journey from Zezhou to the capital.
Lady Jinxiu
didn't expect this.
Sounds like you know me well.
I had enough time to know you well on the way.
You read the letter
from Miss Jun
again and again.
I just felt bored on the way,
so I read the letter.
Jinxiu,
you will
have a new life
after coming here.
I see.
I believe,
as long as you want,
wherever you are,
you can make it.
You believe me?
Of course.
Do, do you need me
to check the account books?
Do you have any business?
-Miss Jun! -Of…
Miss Jun!
Terrible!
There are many troublemakers outside.
Go to have a look.
You sit here.
I'll be back soon.
People often trouble the Jiuling Drugstore?
Occasionally.
Let's go together.
OK.
Let's go.
Come out! Come out!
Come out to see what you did!
Come out!
Come out! Come out!
Look at him.
Are you Dr. Jun?
Yes.
What do you come to
the Jiuling Drugstore for?
You're not a doctor at all.
Dr. Feng,
she is just a hand-bell doctor.
You're Dr. Feng, whose bonesetting ranks first in the capital city?
Just get to the point.
I just come to ask you a question.
As a doctor,
you should have medical ethics.
How could you choose patients at will
and ask the patients that you didn't want to treat
to make trouble
in other clinics?
Dr. Feng,
make trouble?
They told me that
you said
I can cure any disease.
There are various diseases in the world.
How can I cure them all?
What if I can't cure them?
Then I'll become a sinner!
I didn't say so.
Miss Jun,
you did say so.
Right?
Yeah.
She may forget it.
Sir,
did I see you before?
Miss Jun,
it's me.
You may forget me.
Yesterday my wife
asked you to treat me
in my house.
You said
my disease
is not worth your treatment at all.
Yeah.
Miss Jun,
you said Dr. Feng
can settle such a small problem.
How do you explain it?
Nonsense!
We didn't see you at all.
Did someone order you to do so?
What are you doing?
Since that you're exposed,
you start to slander us?
Yeah.
You don't have medical ethics at all.
You're unqualified for a doctor.
Dr. Feng.
Jun.
Your Lordship.
What are you doing here?
It seems that you can also cause a sensation
as a doctor.
We shouldn't be blamed for it.
Obviously, they come by order of someone.
They're making trouble deliberately here.
Make trouble?
I'm Zhu Zan, Lord Cheng's son.
Do you need me
to ask the guards of public security
to punish you?
It's a misunderstanding.
It's a misunderstanding. It's a misunderstanding.
Get away!
He runs
so fast.
Don't run.
Fake wound?
How could they do so?
Dr. Feng.
Dr. Feng,
you've seen the truth.
Sorry to startle you.
What a pedantic geezer.
He didn't admit his mistake at all.
Liu'er, don't say so.
Dr. Feng
is a doctor with medical ethics.
Thank you.
But if he's right,
you'll have to admit that you are wrong?
In this world,
nothing is absolutely right or wrong.
People in different positions
have different opinions.
In his position,
he is right .
Long time no see.
Why are you here?
I came to sell sugar figurines.
Now
the Jiuling Drugstore has a accountant
but lacks a shopkeeper.
Do you agree?
Yes,
I agree.
Look at your grin.
Lady Jinxiu,
wait for me!
Jun,
can I have a talk with you?
Lady Jinxiu, wait for me!
You said
it has something to do with the Imperial Academy of Medicine?
Perhaps you cured
the family of Marquis of Dingyuan
but offended Imperial Doctor Jiang.
Shopkeeper Liu reminded me.
But the doctors' duty
is to treat patients.
I…
You hang the plaque of "Jiuling Drugstore."
Don't you worry that you will offend your peers?
Let's not talk about this.
Did you find anything
in the archive?
It's a coincidence.
Jiang Youshu also went to Prince Huai's mansion,
and he recorded the symptoms as
"Qi deficiency and physical weakness."
He just prescribed
some common tonics.
How can he do this?
The condition will be delayed.
Medicines are always a little toxic.
The disease will become serious if the patient keeps taking medicines.
Yeah.
Jiang Youshu
is smart.
He had considered everything before doing it.
He doesn't hope for great accomplishment,
but hopes only to avoid mistakes.
And even
his mistakes
are merits
in the eyes of His Majesty.
The new emperor
is not broad-minded at all.
And
Jiurong is the son of the late emperor.
If Jiurong
had reached adulthood
and became the Crown Prince,
he wouldn't
have been the emperor.
So now the top priority
is to replace Jiang Youshu.
I also think so.
Dr. Sun is my dad's old friend.
I want to replace Jiang Youshu
with Dr. Sun.
Now we can only
believe Imperial Doctor Sun.
Please help me do this.
Jiuling's matter…
I meant Jiuling.
I would certainly pay attention to her matters.
You thanked me so solemnly,
as if
Jiurong is your brother.
Her brother
is also mine.
It's my duty.
Does she really
have such excellent medical skills?
Yes, Third Madame.
Others all think so.
Besides,
she also cured
the wife of Marquis of Dingyuan.
Can she
also cure me soon?
Well,
you've taken the medicines for some days,
but you still don't get better.
The doctor
asked you to go on taking the medicines,
but
His Excellency hasn't come here
for several days.
You can't go on waiting.
Go to call her for me now.
Go.
Right now.
Yes.
Chen Qi,
what are you doing?
Jinxiu,
have you checked the account books?
Yes.
How is it?
Did she make a fortune?
Nope.
First,
they don't have many patients.
Second,
she still need to pay the salaries,
buy daily consumables
and pay for the diet.
So she suffers a great loss.
It doesn't matter.
These,
and these
will earn a lot!
You know what?
This is not a common drugstore
but a shop
of rare treasures.
Don't talk nonsense.
How much can these herbs cost?
I've seen the purchasing cost.
They cost 1,000 tales of silver.
It's a big deal.
I hope this big deal
won't cause a big trouble.
Take it easy.
When we are alive,
we would always
be in trouble.
Troubles are inevitable
sometimes.
If we're powerful,
we won't be afraid of troubles.
Just take today as an example.
They came to make trouble
but didn't hurt Miss Jun at all.
Is Dr. Jun here?
Our madam asked Dr. Jun
for a home visit.
Your madam's illness is nothing serious.
This prescription is correct.
She is supposed to keep taking it for a few more days.
Dr. Jun,
you'd better go and have a look.
Why don't you understand?
According to
what our lady said,
your madam will be fine
if she takes the medicine on time.
Someone.
Invite Dr. Jun to our mansion.
What are you doing?
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫Every of its words will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫It's me♫
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
♫Any clues?♫
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫