♫Swords tell all the scars, and I sigh for fleeting life♫
♫Once we meet, how can I like to be apart?♫
♫Walking alone with cold in heart, I deep hide the past♫
♫I keep love and hatred deep in heart, naive no more♫
♫My memories roll when I see you again♫
♫I only dare to be gentle in my dream♫
♫This kiss is boiling with your complex♫
♫Intimacy has disturbed the stars♫
♫Take art of healing as a weapon to guard the homeland♫
♫I'm not swallowed by sorrow and hatred♫
♫I don't want to regret in troubled times Let me change sincerity for eternity♫
♫Let's embark this journey for a slim portion of prosperity♫
♫I'd like to rewrite life, but your looking back breaks my heart♫
♫With you for the rest of my life, I'll risk everything and wait for the morning♫
♫Early morning♫
Episode 26
Jiuling Drugstore
Fang Mansion
Tomb of Loving Father Jun Yingwen
By Daughter Jun Zhenzhen
Windmills.
Come to have a look.
Pendants and gadgets.
I think His Highness Prince Xian visited
Jiuling Drugstore with a hidden intention.
You just found it?
He came in person.
On one hand,
it shows that Jiuling has such excellent medical skills that
even relatives of His Majesty value.
On the other hand,
if she can make him happy,
perhaps
she can ask him to see His Lordship.
It's better than asking Lu Yunqi.
You can think of it.
I guess Miss Jun
already thought of it.
She is so lucky.
Whenever she meets difficulties,
she gets help from others.
She gets help from herself.
Go.
Let's work.
Come on.
Let me kiss.
Your Highness,
have a grape.
Yes.
Well. Come on.
Have another one.
Tasty.
For Twelfth Uncle,
it's the safest to pretend to be
arrogant and extravagant,
or he will be killed
by Chu Rang
like my father.
Don't do that.
Twelfth Uncle
was studious and ambitious,
but he must pretend to be a loser.
Will Jiurong be like that?
Dr. Jun,
have,
have you finished?
Yes.
Thanks to Your Highness,
Her Highness is healthy.
I brought some medicine for nourishing and conditioning.
I wrote down the usage.
You're so careful.
Thank you.
It's my duty.
Instead,
I should thank Your Highness.
Thank me?
Why?
You may go.
Go.
Your Highness.
Go. Go.
Just go.
Go ahead.
I guess
son of Lord Cheng asked
you to visit Jiuling Drugstore, right?
Nonsense.
Can anyone
order me?
I sent you over
for being aware of your reputation.
Moreover,
he is in the imperial prison.
He couldn't talk to me.
Whether he asked you or not,
your visit at this point
meets the will of the public,
but not His Majesty.
So I'm grateful to you
for your sincerity
and help.
Unexpectedly,
honest Zhu Zan
has clever friends.
You can see my intention at once.
OK.
But
I should
help you.
You cured Prince Huai.
It's a great credit.
I feel grateful to you.
Prince Huai has been weak since childhood.
Please
take good care
of him, Dr. Jun.
Besides Zhu Zan,
Twelfth Uncle cares about us.
Thank you for your trust.
But
I'm afraid that
I can't help you.
What do you mean?
I'm going to leave the capital city.
Leave?
You've been through so much before.
As the saying goes,
after extreme bad luck comes good luck.
Now you're
known to everyone.
Everything
will go well.
Don't fear.
Let alone others,
well,
my whole family
needs your care.
Whoever dares to bully you,
I won't let him go.
Thank you for your comfort.
However,
I don't fear.
I must go.
I wondered why
you gave me so much medicine.
I get it now.
You came to say goodbye.
Don't worry.
I'll come back.
But I have one more favor to ask.
Go ahead.
Your Highness,
please try to save His Lordship.
Well,
it's improper for me to get involved.
If Lu Yunqi helps...
Your visit to Jiuling Drugstore
is showy enough.
If I turn to Lu Yunqi in this case,
His Majesty will suspect us.
So don't come forward
unless you have to.
I know why
you came to me.
Baotang, Sanbing.
Miss Jun.
Where are you going?
We go to save Zan.
Arm Moral Department is torturing him.
What?
Flogging.
The bastards are torturing him with rod.
I'll kill them.
Can you enter like this?
We must enter there
even by force.
At the worst, fight it out with them.
Wait.
Arm Moral Department is heavily guarded.
You're fighting
a hopeless battle.
He is in the prison.
I must ensure your safety.
Then what should we do?
Zan is being tortured in the prison.
I'll turn to Lu Yunqi.
Are you sure?
Wait for my news.
Let's turn to those of the Sky Pavilion.
Here you are.
You know I'll come, right?
Now that you are here,
sit down and talk.
He is son of Lord Cheng.
You torture him without hearing.
I'm afraid you can't explain it.
Do you think I care?
I want to see him.
I'll treat him.
You care him so much that
I'll be angry.
But
it's great as you're here.
So regardless of my intention
and my feelings,
as long as I'm here
and under your control,
you are satisfied,
right?
Let me repeat it, Lu Yunqi.
I'm not Princess Jiuling.
You just want someone to replace her.
It has nothing to do with me.
You won't understand.
Do you think
His Majesty will kill His Lordship
due to the death of Huang Cheng's son?
If His Lordship dies,
what will
Lord Cheng do?
What will His Majesty think of you?
Have you thought about that?
So to save His Lordship
will meet the will of His Majesty,
but not His Excellency Huang's.
If you don't care these,
I'll leave the capital city.
It'll be easier for you to do anything to me.
You'll leave the capital city?
Yes.
That's what I want to talk to you about.
If you save His Lordship,
I'll leave the capital city.
Leave immediately.
Take her to the imperial prison.
Yes, Your Excellency.
It's time to replenish betel nuts again.
It can kill worms, eliminate accumulation, promote qi and relieve diuresis.
It's a kind of quality medicinal material.
Go.
What are you thinking?
I think
after the trouble caused by Lu Yunqi,
must we close the drugstore?
Let alone the whole country,
can he stop so many people
in the capital city
from visiting Jiuling Drugstore?
You're right.
Are you back so soon?
Where is Jiuling?
She went to Arm Moral Drugstore alone.
Did,
did His Highness Prince Xian have her sent there?
She went alone after leaving the Mansion of Prince Xian.
She went alone?
Didn't she mention to Highness Prince Xian that
she was going to see His Lordship?
I don't know.
She let me wait at the gate of the Mansion of Prince Xian.
She turns to Lu Yunqi in this case.
Is she out of her mind?
By the way,
Her Ladyship asked me to pack.
It seems that she will have a long journey.
Zhu Zan.
Can anyone enter
the imperial prison of Arm Moral Department?
Take her away.
I won't see her.
Lu Yunqi let me treat you.
Well.
Do you fear that we'll escape?
Go.
Why didn't you save Wan Qing?
She is still alive.
She has left the city safely.
Hold on.
Your Excellency,
I can't understand.
Do you really let her go?
Around the country
are men of Arm Moral Department.
As long as she is alive,
she is under my control.
If she leaves the capital city,
it'll be easier for you
to control her.
I know you did that for me.
You feared that I would be criticized
for saving Huang Ziqing.
But you shouldn't have done that.
You shouldn't have been so reckless.
You shouldn't have taken the risk.
Have you thought about
your father and the people in the North?
What if they're involved?
What if anything goes wrong?
I shouted at you,
because I don't want you to get involved.
Huang Cheng will certainly take revenge on those around me.
I saw Lu Yunqi.
I'll leave the capital city after treating you.
You made a deal with him?
I have nothing
to make a deal with him.
If you leave the capital city, he'll save me.
Hold on.
No.
He has complex connections.
No matter where you go,
you can't get rid of him.
And I'm in the prison.
If anything goes wrong with you,
I can't save you.
Don't trust him.
-No. -Stop.
Zhu Zan,
listen to me.
You must stay alive here.
You must be safe.
As long as you're alive here,
we'll find a way to help you out.
Whether it's for me
or your father...
Dr. Jun,
as you have finished treating,
please go.
Brother,
it's a nice day.
You really should have a walk in the imperial garden.
I'm not as free as you are.
You're wrong.
I know you're
occupied with state affairs every day.
But that's why
you should relax yourself
in your spare time.
You can read memorials better after that.
What brings you here?
You won't come to me without a reason.
You're running out
of money, right?
You know me.
I'm always
running out of money.
But
this time
I didn't come for money alone.
What's the matter?
You've asked for whatever
you want directly.
What makes you so hesitant?
Well,
I feel
awkward to mention it.
Go ahead.
No matter what it is,
I won't care.
Then I'll say it.
Please
spare Zhu Zan's life.
I didn't expect that
you're
the first one to intercede for him.
He beat you, right?
But you intercede for him.
Isn't that returning
animosity with kindness?
No discord, no concord.
Brother, you know what?
He is
good at recreation.
I really admire him.
Isn't it great
to me to play with
such a person
every day?
Brother,
let him
just suffer
in the prison.
Spare his life,
so he can play with me every day.
I promise,
he won't
disturb you
again,
OK?
Leave it alone.
You don't know
what's at stake.
Brother,
-I... -As to money,
I'll ask Yuan Bao to send you some.
OK.
I'm busy.
I'm leaving.
Are you trying to escape something?
Lady Jinxiu,
Miss Jun
isn't like that.
I'm sure
she goes back to Zezhou
to do things.
Moreover,
it has been a long time
since you left Zezhou.
It's time for you to go back.
Young Master and Senior Madame
will be happy.
Is Jiuling Drugstore still open?
It can't go on without you.
Anyway, we have no patients.
We're just selling medicine.
It can go on without her.
Yes.
Without me in Jiuling Drugstore,
you can still sell medicine.
But as you leave,
Lady Jinxiu has to work here alone.
I fear that she can't make it.
I can.
Let Chen Qi
return to Zezhou with you
to take care of you on the way.
Don't worry.
I'll go back with Her Ladyship.
Let me go with you.
It's not safe for you girls two
go alone.
When will you come back?
I won't come back
in a short period.
So you fear,
right?
No.
Well,
famous doctors are popular with the people,
but most of the famous doctors are killed by bigwigs.
Wen Zhi was killed by King Min of Qi.
Bian Que was framed and killed by the imperial doctor of Qin State.
Hua Tuo suffered a reckless disaster.
Now
Jiuling Drugstore is famous.
If I still stay here,
I fear Lu Yunqi won't let it go.
But fighting with a lunatic
will make me a lunatic sooner or later.
If I stay here,
he'll cause more troubles.
So we won't diagnose,
and sell medicine only.
Thus,
even if doctors from the capital city and others cities
come for medicine,
Lu Yunqi can't cause troubles
even if he wants to.
We retreat to advance.
In this case,
I'll go back
and prepare for the returning.
I'll help.
Thank you, Shopkeeper Liu.
Thanks.
I'll pack things.
OK.
You expected this situation,
right?
You asked us to work
as shopkeeper and accountant here.
Actually,
you want to leave Jiuling Drugstore
to us as you leave.
You always
think more than others.
Now you have time to consider
whether you should continue
to work as accountant of Jiuling Drugstore.
You've decided it.
Why should I bother?
Be careful
in the capital.
Jinxiu,
whatever happens to you in the future,
don't play tough.
When you meet troubles,
turn to Prince Xian.
You can trust him.
I asked Chengyu
to let Deshengchang
help when you need.
Keep it in mind.
Except humans,
we can abandon
everything.
I know.
I'm just an accountant.
I don't need to risk my life,
right?
By the way,
I really want to see
how furious
your future mother-in-law is
when she knows the engagement.
When will you leave?
We'll leave soon.
How about Zhu Zan?
He was seriously beaten,
but he won't die.
Lu Yunqi and Zhu Zan
have fought for times.
Lu Yunqi may seize the chance
to take private revenge.
Tell him not to
beat Zhu Zan to death.
Yes.
I wanted to see
who will plead for Zhu Zan
However...
So it's tricky
when it comes to Huang Cheng.
There are many discussions in the court,
but none dares to speak for him.
I'm afraid
they want to keep safe.
This is true for all ministers.
Should I be happy
or be worried?
What?
Do you think alike?
Your Majesty will judge.
I don't
dare to judge.
I saw Lu Yunqi.
I'll leave the capital city after treating you.
You made a deal with him.
I have nothing
to make a deal with him.
Zhu Zan,
listen to me.
You must stay alive here.
You must be safe.
As long as you're alive here,
we'll find a way to help you out.
How strange!
It has been a day.
Those of Arm Moral Department haven't appeared.
I think
someone stopped them for us.
Ordinary people
can't stop them.
Is it Prince Xian?
Will it be His Lordship?
If it is the case,
he told them
in advance to protect Her Ladyship.
He is
considerate
and kind to Her Ladyship.
I think after receiving my letter,
Lu Yunqi will keep his promise.
As I wrote in the letter,
he'll convince Huang Cheng
to spare Zhu Zan's life.
Let's finish eating
and keep going.
They are Zhu Zan's men again.
Yes.
Li Sanbing and Zhang Baotang
stopped us.
It must Zhu Zan who arranged it.
Your Excellency,
shall we send reinforcements?
Be patient.
Let her say goodbye.
They will
never meet again.
Yes.
You ask me to release Zhu Zan?
Your Majesty,
it's ascertained that
my son was killed
by the startled horse breaking into.
It
was an accident.
His Lordship
rushed there to stop
the startled horse.
No.
He must suffer more
in the imperial prison.
Your Majesty,
please don't do that.
The loss of my son
is a family matter,
but Lord Cheng guarding the border
is a state affair.
Do not affect him
with my family matter.
Now
it has been widely discussed
in the court and the commonalty.
We'd better
handle it properly.
Then
sorry to hurt you.
Thank you for your consideration.
State affairs are above everything.
Your Majesty,
please allow that.
Well,
Let him feed horses in Livestock Office
and ponder on his fault.
What do you think?
You are smart.
Grandma,
mother,
Chen Qi sent a man to report in advance
Jiuling will arrive at Zezhou
in a few days.
Good news.
Jiuling is coming back.
Let's discuss
how to arrange her.
Clean the yard
where she lived before.
How about letting her
live in a yard nearer to you?
We can see each other
in the Fang family at any time.
It's the same.
I wonder how long
she will stay here.
Does Jiuling know
what you think?
I'll make it clear to her.
Grandma,
mother,
please don't pay too much attention.
If she
doesn't have the same feeling,
she'll be awkward to live here.
Well,
I was about to report to grandma.
I've handled the account
of Deshengchang this month.
Tomorrow I will leave for the inn
outside the city to wait for her.
Is it too early?
Didn't you just say
she would arrive in a few days?
I guess
she'll arrive in a few days.
But things don't turn out as planned.
What if she travels faster
and arrives in advance?
Go.
Go get her back.
Yes, grandma.
Your Lordship,
admit your mistake.
This time
you did
go too far.
Eunuch Yuan,
I was wrong.
Whether I'll meet startled horse
or startled donkey,
I won't meddle in.
That's right.
Remember
to watch your mouth.
They didn't let me speak.
They just beat me.
Don't worry,
Eunuch Yuan.
I'll follow His Majesty's instructions.
Actually,
His Majesty showed his mercy
to let you ponder upon
your faults in Livestock Office.
Really?
Thank His Majesty for his grace.
So Eunuch Yuan,
can I go to the Livestock Office now?
Yes.
It really hurts,
Lord Lu.
Never mind.
I forgive you.
Many are the years to come.
He can walk.
Dr. Jun's medicine
really works.
Young Master,
are you tired?
How about resting for a while?
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
There is an inn ahead.
Let's rest in the inn.
Butler Gao,
I lied to grandma to let her
rest assured by saying that
I'll wait for Jiuling in an inn.
I'll
go all the way
to pick Jiuling up.
Go all the way?
Yes.
Butler Gao,
don't worry.
I've recovered.
I can ride horse
and shot arrows.
I can go all the way
to let her see that.
Fine.
Since you've decided,
we'll go all the way.
Go.
Master,
I came to see you.
I brought you
your favorite pastry.
This year,
a lot has happened to me.
I felt the warmth I have not felt in a long time
and encountered a lot of difficulties.
But
I won't be baffled.
Don't worry.
I'll certainly seek justice from Chu Rang.
The secret of Zezhou you told me
has something to do with the Fang family.
Now
I need to collect more evidence of Chu Rang's crime.
I hope you'll protect me.
Don't worry.
I'll come again
when I avenge.
Young Master.
Liu'er.
Where is Jiuling?
She went to worship Old Master alone.
I think
she will arrive at Zezhou soon.
That,
that's right.
Young Master,
why did you come all the way?
You may just way at the city gate.
I think
he wants to see Miss Jun earlier.
It has been
over a year since we last met.
What is this in your hand?
I picked the plums along the way.
It's a long journey.
I picked them to quench your thirst.
Then we'll enjoy it
without Her Ladyship.
Here you are.
Where will you
meet with Jiuling?
The post
10 miles outside the city.
We planned to wait her in a post,
but we changed our mind
and came all the way.
Yes.
I had planned to meet Jiuling earlier,
but I didn't expect that
it would delay me.
Never mind.
It isn't late.
If we go fast,
we may get there earlier than Her Ladyship.
Yes.
Let's go now.
OK.
Go.
Mother,
eat something.
You haven't eaten for days.
If I eat something,
the thought of their words
flattering that woman
will make me vomit.
Mother.
Yunyan.
Brother.
Brother,
mother is so angry at your marriage with Jun Zhenzhen
that she falls ill.
Mother.
I have questions.
No need.
I asked him outside.
The engagement is false.
His uncle also agreed to that.
It was the most appropriate to do so
in the critical situation.
Is it really false?
Yes.
In this case,
when will you announce it?
I need to discuss
about that
with Miss Jun.
You need to discuss with her?
To get rid of trouble,
she used the engagement
to get our family's protection.
You helped her,
but you need to
discuss with her.
Mother,
she is famous
and I'm No.1 Scholar.
Even if she hadn't met trouble,
the engagement
will be discussed.
Anyway, I'll get involved.
So
I took the initiative
to stop criticism
to get
a good reputation.
And
if someone utilizes the engagement
on purpose,
I'll be said
to be unfaithful.
It'll cause troubles
to my career.
You're right.
No.
Brother,
do you like Jun Zhenzhen?
you're clever
and resourceful,
you won't be afraid of others
making a fuss about your marriage.
Brother?
Say something,
brother.
Yes.
I like her.
Brother.
My precious son
who can bring honor to the family name
likes that bitch.
Mother,
you misunderstand her.
-In fact, she is... -Shut up.
Mother.
♫Outline in my dream♫
♫can be carved on your face♫
♫Time interlaces in the eye waves♫
♫For unspeakable cause and effect♫
♫Let me weigh every word♫
♫Life is full of twists and turns♫
♫So hard to be free and easy♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫It will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫Tomorrow always comes♫
♫I'd like to entrust myself to you♫
♫to enjoy stars and the land together♫
♫In long silence♫
♫We are far separated by a sea of faces♫
♫What else can I do except for a sigh?♫
♫The rest of my life is bumpy♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫I'm be eventually be passed by♫
♫The wind is in hot pursuit♫
♫to stay with nature♫
♫If memories can tell♫
♫Every of its words will make me shed tears♫
♫Rare to meet you again, tears well up in my eyes♫
♫You are like vast nature, while I'm a gust of wind♫
♫It's me♫
♫You shuttle through the bottom of my heart♫
♫Has nature ever asked for any clues about the wind?♫
♫Any clues?♫
♫If my longing for you can be written down♫
♫Every word would be as strong as pouring rain falling down♫
♫You take me as a stranger when we finally meet again♫
♫Tears well up in my eyes♫