♪In youth there is confusion♪
♪And collision♪
♪But so what♪
Free at kisskh.me
♪Invisible darkness♪
♪Gives me♪
♪More invisible power♪
♪The unyielding heart♪
♪Gives a signal♪
♪And has a pair of wings♪
♪Darkness won't be a problem♪
♪The day gets dark♪
♪So the light is on♪
♪Get ready to pull out♪
♪The gun is fired♪
♪Time goes by without stop♪
♪Days and nights♪
♪It keeps shining♪
♪Self-discipline is♪
♪The edge of the blade♪
♪Focus on enjoying♪
♪Every moment♪
♪Life will be worth♪
♪The power given by youth♪
♪Blood is burning♪
♪Scores determine the outcome♪
♪In the dark I am♪
♪The only light♪
♪Taking back hard work in old days♪
♪Applause replaces cold treatment♪
♪I'll always run to you♪
♪And be your eternal sun♪
♪The only light♪
=Hello, The Sharpshooter=
=Episode 38=
Look at this trending topic.
Xu Dian has left Zhengdao Media.
Really?
Let me have a look.
Speaking of which,
the photo looks quite real.
He kept such a low profile when he left.
He didn't even make an announcement.
He's the big-name anchor
who did the joint live broadcast of
Haiya's winter training with us before.
Where is he going afterwards?
Maybe
he's about to go solo.
My goodness.
A statement just released
by Zhengdao Media on its Weibo account.
Xu Dian, anchor of our company,
took advantage of his position
to sexually harass a female colleague.
The accusation
has been confirmed lately.
It is hereby announced that
Xu will be dismissed
and never be hired again.
This news indeed
comes as a bombshell.
In this case,
Tang Xin has also worked with him.
(Comment: It Takes Two to Tango)
These people
even said it takes two to tango.
What the hell?
This is too much.
Is it all set?
Yes, Mr. Zhou.
Tang Xin.
Come here.
Go.
Today I'd like to expose
a number of misconducts
Xu Dian has done to me.
Meanwhile, I'll clear up the previous
slanderous new coverage.
(Repost Weibo #Tang Xin METOO#)
(Keep it up!)
(Well-known Livestreamer Tang Xin
Publishes Video)
Come in.
Mr. Zhou.
We are No.1 of the trending topic.
Are you not happy?
Such a thing
cannot be measured
by the number of viewers.
This is really uncharacteristic of you.
You seem a bit different to me.
Do I?
Maybe.
I'm going back to work then.
Go.
In the end,
I'd like to clear up
some bad public opinion
(Non-bitter Lemon)
about me and shooter Shen Qingyuan
some time ago.
Those are…
(All Lies)
Indeed,
I am dating Shen Qingyuan.
Our story is a very complicated
and a very long one.
The two of us
are a pair of mutually supportive
PTSD patients.
Post-traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD)
is commonly seen in films and TV plays.
But on the internet,
it has become a meme
to make fun of others.
Today I hope
through my efforts
I can make people
have more empathy towards this term
and patients suffering its affliction.
Compared with me,
Shen Qingyuan is more special.
Athletes
grow up in environments
that are quite different from ours,
so they are prone to
have psychological problems.
Here
I'm also asking you
to pay continuous attention
to athletes' mental health problems.
Meanwhile,
I'll also work with
Dr. Ding Fang who has many years
of clinical experience
to find a treatment protocol together.
It's true
the more people paying attention,
the better.
(Head of TV Station Mr. Zhang)
Hello, Mr. Zhang.
Zhou,
how are you doing these days?
We haven't been in touch
for quite a while.
Ditto.
Yes.
We used to meet a lot.
Zhou,
I've thought about it.
Let's just drop the matter.
Come back to the station first.
What do you think?
Thank you for your favor.
Please give me more time
to think about it,
OK?
All right.
I'll wait to hear from you.
OK.
I'll get back to you ASAP.
(Divorce Agreement)
You'd better sign the agreement ASAP.
Are you ready?
Jiang Yitian,
this is the eleventh time.
Say it properly this time.
I'm sure I will.
Come on, come on.
Three, two, one. Go.
Has it begun?
Mr. Du,
please carry me under your wings later.
Can't you be serious?
This is a farewell video.
Serious…
Let's just record it together,
OK?
Come on. Give it to me, give it to me.
Come on, come on.
Let's do it together.
Wait a minute.
Intercut the scene here.
Ready.
Three, two, one. Go.
Come on.
Yang Zhou.
Hai.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Hai, Hai.
Let's record it together.
Come on. You first.
Mr. Du,
Free at kisskh.me
don't forget us in the coming days.
Yes, Mr. Du.
Make sure you don't forget us.
We're waiting for you
to give us a treat later.
Du Lingfeng, Du Lingfeng,
I did fortune-telling for you.
I'm sure
you'll be a billionaire in the future.
- Billionaire!
Why
did you steal a glance at me just now?
I didn't.
What are you talking about?
Just glance at me if you want.
Don't be shy.
Miss Tang,
we haven't finished recording yet.
Go ahead with the recording first.
Let's go on. Let's go on.
- Hurry up, hurry up.
- Come on, come on.
Hai, Hai.
Don't forget me if you get rich one day.
- Hai! Hai!
- Hai!
Come on. Let's do it together.
- Du Lingfeng, Mr. Du!
- Du Lingfeng!
- We love you!
It's my work time now.
I have patients coming to visit later.
Ding Fang,
I think I am a patient.
I have a strong feeling of inferiority.
My self-esteem gets in the way,
no...
My vanity gets in the way.
As you know,
I had a rough patch
at the TV station a few years back
and everything was going wrong.
At that time,
when I looked at myself every day,
I looked more and more
like an odious old man.
But you are always so glamorous
as if you haven't changed much
ever since I got to know you
from college till now.
You are only becoming more mature,
more intellectual
and more outstanding.
Is this really what you think?
Zhou Zuguang,
actually, there was also a time
when I worshipped you as a totem.
At that time,
in order to keep up with you,
I was pushing myself
to become mature day by day.
Later I did it.
But my totem
faded away.
I'm sorry I let you down.
Forget it.
It's all in the past.
Yes.
That makes two of us.
To be honest,
every time I faced
your well-reasoned analysis,
I was under a lot of pressure.
Seeing your career thriving
and you becoming a star psychologist
and a darling on social media,
I was jealous
and not willing to be outdone.
I did a lot of things
to try to keep up with you
or at least to keep abreast with you,
but it seemed the more I struggled,
the more things backfired.
All these things seemed to…
Seemed to be in vain.
I felt
I was no longer good enough for you.
It surprises me that
we both wanted to be closer
to each other.
But we ended up drifting apart.
Today
I get these things off my chest
and feel much more relieved.
For better or worse,
I think I have the duty
to tell you frankly
what I've been through mentally
during this period of time.
I…
I want to say
whether to patch up or get a divorce,
the choice is yours.
I'll think it over.
I'm going then.
Have you watched the video?
Yes.
What do you think of it?
I posted it too hastily.
I should have shown you
the script beforehand.
I posted it so abruptly.
I keep worrying
I said something inappropriate.
Don't think nonsense.
I think you've put it very well
in the video.
That's good then.
Do you know?
Sometimes it occurs to me
it is so hard
to be
a healthy adult.
Shen Qingyuan,
sometimes
I'm eager to help you cure your trauma,
but I don't know…
Shen Qingyuan,
will you go to see Dr. Ding with me?
Are you keen to have me on therapy?
But
I also want you
to follow your own wish.
OK.
I promise you.
For the gold medal.
And for you.
(Qianyang26)
Hello, Mr. Zhang.
I've thought it through.
I'm not going back to the station.
Rui Live is my brainchild.
It has just developed
and I can't bear to leave it.
I'm sorry.
OK.
Thank you for being so understanding.
Sure, sure.
Shen Qingyuan,
thank you for being willing to trust me.
(Doctor's Office)
Tang Xin,
Shen Qingyuan would like you
to be his safety island.
In trauma therapy, safety island
is usually
an imagined scenario
which helps a patient
to soothe and calm his mind
during the painful recovery process.
During the course of the therapy,
you may receive some stimulations
to your eyes.
But rest assured that
there will be no side effects.
It is the first time in my career
that I've seen a patient
decides to choose a specific person
as his safety island.
Dr. Ding,
Free at kisskh.me
thank you.
You are welcome.
Dr. Ding,
we are going for now.
♪Baby your smile♪
♪Lights up my world yeah♪
♪You make me realize♪
♪Company is
the longest confession of love♪
What are you reading?
♪Need no flowers or sweet talk♪
Look at him.
♪Holding you is like♪
Hey, look this way.
Look at me.
♪Your love is simple yet special♪
♪You made me realize♪
♪Something can be eternal♪
No.
I can't press this.
I'll use this instead.
♪My greatest luck♪
♪Is being able to be with you♪
♪Your love♪
♪Is simple yet special♪
♪Because of you♪
♪I've found my purpose in life♪
♪You make me realize♪
♪The simpler the love the better baby♪
Lingda Club
is open for business!
Great!
- Great!
- Thank you, guys.
Thanks.
Great!
Thank you. Thank you.
Please. Please.
Thank you, guys.
Today
good things come in pairs.
As you all know,
Xiaoci and Qingyuan
have entered the national team.
For Qingyuan
it was a bumpy road to get selected,
but Xiaoci
got selected with excellent performance.
Of course
this is no big deal.
After all, there will be
selections for the Olympics afterwards.
Next, I'm going to announce
the biggest event today.
Congrats on the opening of business.
Congrats, Du Lingfeng.
Shen Qingyuan!
You made a sneak attack behind my back.
Who can give me
a sophisticated weapon?
Du Lingfeng,
take this.
Well, this…
Theirs is a bit cute.
You know nothing.
Yours is for physical attack.
Mine is for chemical attack.
♪With the sound of prelude
for entry into the arena♪
♪All I know is to rush forward♪
♪Unfulfilled dreams♪
♪I can still laugh while trembling
when I'm tired out♪
♪Rain and sweat♪
♪Cannot extinguish my fanatical joy♪
♪The hand holding an umbrella for me
in the heavy rain♪
♪The idea of cheering myself up♪
♪Thank myself for having done my best♪
(Weibo: End of Shooting Career
Du Announces Founding of Shooting Club)
(Weibo: Shooting Video Reveals
Sides of Du Lingfeng You've Never Seen)
(Weibo: Du Lingfeng Plans to Participate
in Promotion of Shooting Sport)
(To Engage More People in Shooting)
(Mr. Du, I'm from Lemon TV…)
(Mr. Du, do you have time these days…)
(This is China Sports
Publications Corp…)
♪It's all worth it♪
Look at this one.
This is amazing.
♪It's all worth it♪
Miss Tang.
Can you also make a video like this
for me when I retire from shooting?
Don't think of retiring so soon.
Shooting is one of the sports
with the longest athletic lifespan.
Yes, yes, Captain.
At least
in my 20-year career,
I must try my best to get my first gold.
Good job, good job.
I almost fell asleep while watching.
Fell asleep? Let me have a look.
Look, your eyes are red.
Aren't you in tears?
- Mr. Du is moved.
- He's so moved.
All right, all right.
Stop laughing.
Next,
I have an announcement to make.
First,
I've talked to
Mr. Zhang,
and I'm just letting you know
that I
will continue the sponsorship for
Haiya Shooting Team in the coming days.
- Great!
Is this it?
I'm your sponsor anyway.
If you don't express your gratitude,
beware of my withdrawal of investment.
Didn't you agree to be our bro?
Why do you become a sponsor instead?
OK, OK.
The sponsorship is obligatory,
OK?
Next thing.
Upon my return to Lingda this time,
I'll be in charge of
marketing of a new product.
Whether I can thrive
in my position
is up to my performance this time.
Shen Qingyuan,
are you my bro or not?
What?
Just get straight to the point.
I want you to be the endorser.
Are you in or not?
It's a good thing, Captain.
It's a good thing.
Isn't it a good thing?
- Say yes. Say yes.
We are bros.
Let me tell you,
I've another piece of good news for you.
This time,
I contacted the Austria-based
Steyr company,
the one specialized in
manufacturing sports pistols.
It must be more familiar to you than me.
I'm going to
import a batch of pistols from them.
Their manager has been
following you with great interest.
This time they heard your pistol
had not been working very well,
so…
(Invitation)
Steyr World Gun Championship.
I know that competition.
It is a very mature
commercial event.
It's been held
a dozen times so far.
Many internationally renowned shooters
take part in it.
Du Lingfeng
is quite something.
He moved the home field to China.
But we usually
set our eyes on honor
and rarely join such commercial events.
Why do you want to join this time?
This competition
has good contestants.
Bachchan.
The one
who broke the Asian record last year?
He's one of
the outstanding
new-generation foreign players.
Lee Jae In of South Korea.
A gathering of master hands.
It seems we'll really have to
meet them in the upcoming competition.
So I think this competition
is a very good
practicing opportunity.
This is a very good opportunity
for exchange and learning
before the Olympic tryouts.
You can also take this opportunity
to find your top shape.
I'll talk to the coaches
of the national team.
Hope they'll approve your entry.
Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
But once you go,
you can't just take it as practice.
For this trial,
you must show your real skills
more than any big and small competitions
you've entered before,
as this competition
is closer to
a real international level.
Qingyuan,
your current performance
is slowly getting back on track,
but you are not yet in a stable form.
If you can really
surpass yourself this time,
I'm sure
you'll win the Olympic tryouts.
(World Gun Championship Invitation)
I see.
(WeChat Moment: The most romantic thing
I've fancied is we brush teeth together)
You are back.
Here.
I've washed both towels today.
Smell them. Are they fragrant?
Yes.
Free at kisskh.me
I think so too.
You…
What are you doing with your suitcase?
I'm going to Nanjiang.
Nanjiang?
Why are you going again?
For the World Gun Championship.
Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
I just thought
we also met again
in the city of Nanjiang.
You were in the middle of a competition,
and you said I'd distract you
and asked me to go.
I didn't expect now we…
The two of us
have a predestined bond with that city.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
I'm gonna stay for quite a few days.
Make sure you keep up the good work.
When you are away from home,
you must protect yourself out there.
Watch out for your safety.
Sleep and eat on time.
Remember to bring
the electric toothbrush I gave you.
Don't come into conflict with anybody.
All right.
I'll go with you.
(Qianyang26)
What are you doing here?
Which department?
Hello.
I'm from Rui Live.
Isn't this a weekend?
Your department.
OK. Go.
Mr. Zhou?
Tang Xin?
Mr. Zhou,
this is for you.
It's warm to drink with water.
Work is important,
but health is more important.
Thank you. It's very nice of you.
Mr. Zhou,
why are you still at the company?
I have to keep an eye on
the hotspot topics on weekends.
By the way,
the video you made for Du Lingfeng
is very good.
It's very well received online now.
Thank you, Mr. Zhou.
Mr. Zhou, it's like this.
Shen Qingyuan has received an invitation
to a big business competition.
It's scheduled for the next few days.
Do you think…?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
What a golden time it is!
Young people are on vacation
and lots of people
are watching livestreams, right?
How does this sound?
You are going this time.
On an official business trip.
Do a good job.
I see.
I'll go and prepare for it right away.
Dr. Ding,
Shen Qingyuan's condition
is getting more and more stable now.
Thank you for your help.
Thank you for
taking him back to Yongcheng last time.
That was
a very good exposure therapy
which makes the following therapy
so smooth.
Sometimes, I really envy you.
You are so rational
and well-organized in the work you do.
Without your help,
Shen Qingyuan and I
would probably still be
trudging through the mud now.
Since you've
both walked out of the shadow,
is it time for you guys
to tie the knot next?
Almost.
But there's also a promise
between us.
Sometimes
I really envy you young people
whose relationships
are simple and unencumbered,
unlike me.
Dr. Ding,
you are so enlightened that
you shouldn't be trapped
by relationships, aren't you?
Haven't you heard of the saying
"It's hard for doctors
to cure themselves"?
Even if I can see something through,
I still put it off again and again.
Somehow
I just can't make a decision
and speak my mind.
What's wrong?
Is anything the matter?
Mr. Zhou,
it took me and Shen Qingyuan
many years to meet
and well over half a year
to clear the air.
In retrospect,
I was just lacking
the courage
to face the reality honestly.
Sometimes without asking or talking,
we think by watching carefully
we'll be able to find the answer
without the knowledge of the other side.
But if
we end up with the wrong answer,
wouldn't it be
a prolonged drag
on each other?
Sorry, Mr. Zhou.
I even started talking about
my own understanding of relationship
in front of you.
It's OK.
You and Shen Qingyuan
got together
into a good union
under my watch.
You've eventually become a loving pair.
It's OK.
Well done.
Get on with your work.
Mr. Zhou, I'm going for now.
(Flight Information Beijing, China)
Thanks.
Shen Qingyuan.
(Haiya Linxi Airport Boarding Pass)
Shen Qingyuan,
you must thank
Du Lingfeng profusely this time.
To make this competition happen,
he did both sponsoring and legwork.
It was really hard work.
What's more,
he contacted all the contestants
one by one
to invite them to come.
He did it to help you get back in form
and get familiar with others.
Don't lose steam.
I know.
Besides, I reckon by now
Free at kisskh.me
he's already arrived at the venue
and is keeping an eye on
all the arrangements.
The last time he was so motivated
was when he was courting Xiaoci.
So
since he sincerely takes you as his bro,
make sure you don't belittle him.
Now
he's reported to be a responsible,
enthusiastic entrepreneur
and an angel investor for athletes.
Plus his previous
professional image
with the shooting team,
now everybody says he is
a promising, outstanding young gun.
All right, all right, all right.
I've kept them in mind.
Enthusiastic entrepreneur.
Angel investor.
I've kept them all in mind.
Don't bring him up to me.
Shen Qingyuan.
Have you kept them all in mind?
Let's go.
Hello, is there anything you need?
No thanks.
What's up?
I'm afraid you'll feel cold.
I don't feel cold.
I haven't finished
sorting through the files.
Loosen your grip.
I feel cold.
Hello.
What can I do for you?
Please get me a blanket. Thanks.
OK. Just a moment, please.
Here you are.
Thanks.
Done.
Do you feel warm now?
Are you unhappy?
Shen Qingyuan,
do you still remember that
on the flight back
from Nanjiang, you said
the air around me was too fragrant
and asked Jiang Yitian
to swap seats with me.
Do you remember?
Yes.
I remember
the first time I saw you,
I began to have
a miraculous feeling.
I didn't know until later
that it was because I had
gazed into your eyes
so many times before
that I had that miraculous urge
to want to get close.
No wonder you kept
talking about pheromone.
It was not pheromone.
It was love.
Tang Xin,
I had never forgotten you.
I just locked
that memory away.
♪I'm not used to being a yes-man♪
♪But unless I'm sure♪
♪Some things are better left unsaid♪
♪You watch how I fail again♪
♪Thoughts pour over me♪
♪I can't get away♪
♪When looking up I'm all wet♪
♪Memories flood back♪
♪I'm familiar with waiting♪
♪How can I avoid it♪
♪Why does it keep bothering me♪
♪It's simply a kind of self-defense♪
♪Cover my eyes♪
♪Hiding quietly in the corner
with lights off♪
♪Even steep roads will be much gentler♪
♪I've enjoyed the scenery♪
♪But I still don't want to leave♪
♪In front of you
I try to behave more naturally♪
♪But I'm still clumsy♪
♪I haven't said anything♪
♪In case I say too much or too little♪
♪Memories flood back♪
♪I miss you regularly♪
♪Finally I get free♪
♪Torture me as you wish♪
♪Love is just over♪
♪I pretend
I don't understand the failure♪
♪I still don't admit it♪
♪Memories flood back♪
♪Welcome and take care♪
♪When I leave♪
♪I nod whether I smile or feel sad♪
♪I've bidden farewell
to everything about you♪
♪From this day on♪
♪I'll get ready and leave♪
♪My future can be bright♪