♪Confessing to the moon
in the rustling wind back then♪
♪Like a boat being swallowed up
among the cities♪
♪Watching the flowers fall in unease,
worries and troubles fill my mind♪
♪Am I going to where I want♪
♪To stay or to leave, you decide♪
♪Nations are different♪
♪One without desire
is one that is not alive♪
♪Looking at the sky side by side♪
♪We've gotten closer with time♪
♪One glance,
the city of Chang'an is bare♪
♪Among the ridiculous people
and things is me♪
=Dream of Chang'An=
=Episode 4=
(Now,)
(I'm sure that Cheng Ruoyu)
(is disappointed in me too.)
(Royal Repository)
You are here, Little Fish.
How is it?
Did you find anything?
(Liu Juan)
We are too late.
What do you mean?
It means that
someone has cleaned up this place.
(Royal Repository)
Every book that is related
has been tampered with.
And he left no trace.
(Guan Wu)
(Ren Cuilan)
Did you notice anything?
The ink inside
Zheng Wu's book
is different from others.
Resumes are often written in ink
from She Prefecture.
But it was sealed off by snow
on the 9th year of Tai'an.
We didn't get any ink
from them for two years.
So, the secretaries
had to use ink from Heng'an.
These two inks
are almost identical
in colours and shine.
The only difference is the smell.
This Resume of Zheng Wu
is written in the ink
from She Prefecture?
On the 10th year of Tai'an,
when you entered the palace,
this ink shouldn't have existed.
Is this the only one
with different ink?
Yours too.
Mine?
(Cheng Ruoyu)
(Guan Wu)
You found this?
Not me.
It's Qiu Yanzhi.
When I went to the Royal Repository
to investigate,
she was there too.
Why are you smiling?
Did you already know that
our Resumes
have been tampered with?
They are not tampered with.
These two books
are written afterwards.
Every six months,
Resumes will be put under the sun
to get rid of bookworms
and they'll be restored.
One time,
yours and Zheng Wu's book
were on top of each other.
And they were soaked in tea.
So, the secretaries
made another copy of them.
There's a record of this incident.
Didn't you see it?
No.
So, it means that
there's nothing wrong with my Resume.
Of course.
Not only yours,
but there's also nothing wrong
with Guan Wu's Resume too.
The problem started
before she entered the palace.
Not after.
Okay then.
Yu'er.
Don't get too close to Qiu Yanzhi.
Don't worry.
I have my boundaries.
Looks like they've found out about it.
Luckily,
we have a fail-safe.
In order not to make it obvious that
Yu'er's Resume is different,
we soaked the one below hers too.
And that happened to be Guan Wu's Resumes.
This is really fate.
As long as they don't investigate Yu'er,
everything will be fine.
I'm not worried about Yu'er.
I'm worried about Qiu Yanzhi.
A girl brought up by a cunning person
is indeed hard to deal with.
(On the first day of lunar January,
10th year of Tai'an...)
On the first day of lunar January
in the 10th year of Tai'an,
Emperor Wen rebuilt the Violet Bureau.
He chose 1000 people
and gave them 1000 bolts of silk
and 1000 koku of corns.
There were 1000 people?
But the Violet Bureau now
has only 36 maids.
Even if we include
the musicians and performers,
it'll just add up to 100.
Where are the rest?
They said that others were
asked to leave
after failing certain tests.
But according to the spies
I sent out to investigate,
a lot of them didn't go home.
They went missing?
This is the record of
His Majesty's hunting expenses
in recent years.
What do you see?
I'm having a headache
just by looking at it.
Just tell me the conclusion.
It's getting more and more costly.
Last year,
His Majesty spent as much as
the Chess of Generals Camp.
It means that
His Majesty's hunting expenses
for a year
can afford another
Chess of Generals Camp.
Cheng Xi used to serve the late emperor.
And the late emperor and His Majesty
are enemies.
His Majesty shouldn't have
spared Cheng Xi.
But not only he did that,
he trusted the Cheng siblings
with the Violet Bureau.
Why?
He wants to use the Violet Bureau
against the Chess of Generals Camp.
How can he do that?
With
those 36 maids?
So,
you suspect that
the girls who were sent away
are actually
being brought up by Qi Yan?
And the money comes from
his hunting trips?
I can't think of
another possibility except this.
I think
it's time for you to go back
and play chess with Sir.
I'm planning to do that.
(Duke Chu's Residence)
You want to...
When I travelled with Qi Yan,
we ran into two assassination attempts.
And they were more like a provocation.
If we add your birthday banquet,
it'll be the third time.
What do you suspect?
The Violet Bureau
has been building forces in secret.
Someone found out about it
and wanted to use this chance
to make us fight.
So,
they sent a maid from Violet Bureau
to assassinate you
and frame it on Qi Yan.
Who is it?
I don't know that yet.
But since they purposely exposed
the secrets of Violet Bureau to us,
I'm sure they've planned out something.
I want to use Guan Wu's case
as a bait to uncover
this person's identity.
Your Majesty.
I have the answer.
Yu'er.
Get back.
Where's Yanzhi?
What answer do you have?
Yanzhi said that
when Zheng Wu and I entered the palace,
the ink in our Resumes
is different from others.
She suspects that
they have been tampered.
I've checked this
with Aunt.
They were damaged due to an accident.
Not forged.
What else?
Nothing else.
Let me ask you.
Why are you here?
Are you going to continue
investigating this together
with Qiu Yanzhi?
I want to continue
with this investigation.
But I don't plan to
join hands with Qiu Yanzhi.
I already said,
this case is closed.
It's not.
(Royal Repository)
What did you say?
I said,
this case is not closed.
Your Majesty,
Zheng Wu's revenge
is just the start.
During the Morning Dew Rebellion,
almost 1000 officials had been killed.
We had countless casualties.
Why won't you let me investigate?
What are you afraid of?
If I can't even find out
the identity of our enemies
and their purpose,
how can I protect you
with my sword?
For your safety
and to prevent the next assassination,
this is my duty
as the Sword Bearer.
I have to do this.
Yu'er!
Okay.
I'll tell you this then.
You are no longer the Sword Bearer.
Wait.
Cheng Huaizhi.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Pass down my decree.
Cheng Ruoyu will be removed from
her position as the Sword Bearer
and she's now just a commoner.
She'll leave the palace
and never come back.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Leave now.
Do you think I want this?
Yu'er.
Wait.
The matron is still trying to help you.
This is not final.
Madam Li.
I've made up my mind.
No need to persuade me.
But where can you go
if you leave?
What about us?
Can you really abandon us?
I'm sorry that
I didn't live up to your expectation.
Before you became the Sword Bearer,
I was worried about you.
After you became the Sword Bearer,
I was even more anxious.
Now that you are not a Sword Bearer,
I'm still worried about you.
Aunt.
I'm sorry.
I've never wanted to
become a Sword Bearer.
I just want to be by your side.
Actually, this is not bad.
I've been kicked out from the palace.
But,
with my capabilities,
I can come back anytime.
So,
nothing will change.
Everything will be the same.
You.
Forget it.
This is...
I didn't give you this because
I didn't want you to get into trouble.
But if I don't give it to you now,
how can you protect yourself
outside of the palace?
You are the best.
After you leave the palace,
stay in Cai's Wine Store for the moment.
The owner is Li Rong's sister-in-law.
She'll take good care of you.
Then, I can eat biángbiáng noodles
every day.
Aunt.
I have another request.
I want to
continue investigating Wu's case.
We are like sisters.
Her death is too unnatural.
I feel bad about it.
Aunt.
Let me investigate.
Or else, I can't sleep.
I always dream about her
crying to me.
Okay.
Is that a yes?
How can I reject you
when you said that?
Go.
Thank you.
Before this, you said that
this case has to be investigated from
the outside of the palace.
It's good that I'm fired.
It's easier for me
to investigate from
the outside of the palace.
Aunt.
Now,
I'm no longer the Sword Barrier.
Please return this
Qingguang Sword
to His Majesty.
Since His Majesty
didn't take back this sword,
I'm sure he has his reasons.
Keep it for now.
Okay.
(When a man is meant for greatness,)
(his mind will be tested,)
(his body will be put to labour,)
(he will face hunger,)
(he'll be emptied out)
(and he has to face
countless obstacles.)
(So, this challenge)
(will be beneficial for me.)
I don't need any help.
I don't need anyone to be understanding.
And I trust no one.
So,
leave.
(West Fair)
(Cai's Wine Store)
Mrs. Cai.
I'm here.
Yu'er.
Come.
Be careful.
Are you surprised?
Are you shocked?
I miss you so much.
Come, Aunt.
- Let's go.
- Let's talk inside.
Sir.
(Chess of Generals Camp)
Cheng Ruoyu has been kicked out
from the palace.
(Chess of Generals Camp)
Looks like his pawn
is no longer under your control.
Yes.
Based on my deduction,
Qi Yan is the one who ordered
the Violet Bureau
to keep his power in secret.
If that's the case,
he shouldn't have kicked out
Cheng Ruoyu.
Based on your deduction,
why did Qi Yan
end Zheng Wu's case in a rush?
To prevent us
from gathering more clues
through Zheng Wu's admission
to the palace
and find out the magnitude
of the Violet Bureau.
Am I wrong?
No matter it's true or not,
we need the evidence.
When you are playing chess,
you'll change
and your opponent will change.
What do you mean?
You think that
you are baiting him.
But he wants to
use you as his pawn too.
(Chess of Generals Camp)
(Zheng Residence)
This is Zheng Wu's previous home.
I'll start from here.
(Memorial tablet of Zhengs)
Who are you?
How do you recognise Qingguang Sword?
Qingguang Sword is just
a useless piece of metal in your hands.
Where is she?
We saw her coming in just now.
Let's go.
Don't move.
There's really no one here.
- Let's go.
Your swordsmanship is not that good.
But your reaction time is not bad.
If you are on the battlefield,
your inexperience
will kill you.
What did you say?
My swordsmanship is bad?
Since young,
nobody dared to say that to me.
Don't act tough.
You should win me first.
Are you saying that
we'll meet again?
No.
Someone like you
will die soon.
You don't know that.
Do you want to make a bet?
Let's bet
if I can stay alive to meet you again.
And the next time we meet,
I'll defeat you.
Your Majesty.
Time to wake up.
You are so clumsy.
Get up.
I can't believe you.
Come, Your Majesty.
Okay.
Huaizhi.
What is your niece doing?
She went to Cai's Wine Store
to sell wine.
Is she really selling wine?
Why do you ask?
The sash of Violet Bureau.
Cheng Ruoyu's sash.
How can you tell?
Cheng Ruoyu wields the Qingguang Sword.
Her sash has silver threads in it.
Why will her sash
appear
on His Majesty's boot?
Looks like
the person she saw
in Zheng Residence last night
is His Majesty.
(Cai's Wine Store)
Mrs. Cai.
You are going out?
Yu'er.
I'm going out for grocery shopping.
Take care of the shop for me.
Don't worry.
Be careful.
Okay.
(The whole Zheng family
was punished to death.)
(How did Zheng Wu escape?)
(Who gave her a false identity)
(and sent her into the palace?)
(She has been lying low for so many years.)
(Why did she suddenly
try to assassinate)
(His Majesty?)
(With her martial art skills,)
(she knew that she wouldn't succeed.)
(Why did she choose
to sacrifice herself?)
Yes.
Why did she do that?
Another thing.
Who is
the man in black?
Could he be the person
who saved Wu
back then?
I'm having a headache again.
You followed me home?
Stop right there!
Your Majesty.
Why are you running?
I...
What are you doing?
Let go of me.
Why are you here at west fair again?
I know.
You are an emperor
who doesn't need to
attend the imperial court meeting.
I'm here to eat biángbiáng noodles.
Where is Mrs. Cai?
What a pity.
She went out for grocery shopping.
Goodbye.
Bring me some wine.
Why are you so shocked?
This is a wine store.
Don't tell me that there's no wine.
The palace has all kinds of great wine.
Why are you drinking here
instead of your palace?
Are you deaf?
What's so hard about
getting me some wine?
Go now.
He came here alone to drink
without his guards.
Here you go.
Thank you.
But I don't drink.
I'm not asking you to drink.
I'm asking you to try.
I'm no longer
your Sword Bearer.
Why do I have to test the wine for you?
Since you are my customer
and I'm the seller,
I'll do that for you then.
This has been watered down.
No.
I'll inform the authorities
to close down this shop.
Your Majesty.
Those two jars of wine
are just some mistakes.
Rainwater must have gotten in
when it rained
a few days ago.
Actually, it's not true.
I was just being naughty
by adding water into the wine.
Those are for me.
Cheng Ruoyu.
Are you sure you want to commit treason?
Your Majesty.
Just tell me what you want.
No need to beat around the bush.
You've kicked me out from the palace.
Are you going to
kick me out from Heng'an City too?
Yes.
Why?
You know why.
You go against my decree.
By kicking you out
instead of killing you,
it's already
the biggest mercy from me.
Should I thank you for your mercy then?
But,
I think you better kill me.
Or else,
I'll continue to investigate
Wu's case.
Cheng Ruoyu.
Do you really think that
I won't kill you?
Unfortunately, I'm not afraid of death.
I couldn't save my friend
when she was suffering.
I couldn't uphold justice for my friend
when she was wrongly accused.
I couldn't stop you
when I knew that you were being cruel.
These
are scarier than death.
Good.
Very well.
With you being so weak,
I'm going to
teach you a lesson today.
We received an urgent report.
His Majesty
went to Cai's Wine Store in the east
to visit Cheng Ruoyu.
And he's attacked by assassins again.
We'll know soon whether or not
Qi Yan has changed.
(Cai's Wine Store)
I'm no longer the Sword Bearer.
I don't have to protect him, right?
An evil emperor like his
should just die.
He even wanted to cripple me just now.
But,
what if he gets hurt?
Forget it.
Tell me.
Who are you?
Why did you try to assassinate
His Majesty?
You can kill me.
Shut up!
You can still talk.
Don't worry.
I won't kill you.
I'll give you some wine.
Tell me!
Cheng Ruoyu.
You know me?
Sir.
All six assassins
are killed by hidden weapons.
No one is alive.
What about those who fired
the hidden weapons?
We couldn't see.
And we can't find them.
What?
It's the same as the assassination
in the wine store last time.
They leave no trace.
We can't track them at all.
How is that possible?
You couldn't see who fired
the hidden weapons?
When you play chess,
unexpected moves are the worst.
Those moves are unexpected
because of your own uselessness.
Checkmate.
Your Majesty.
Chase after them.
Why did you stop?
Cheng Ruoyu.
You are skillful, right?
I lost them.
Come down.
No.
You better come down.
Just now, you said that
you are going to cripple me.
I won't go down.
Stop investigating, okay?
No.
Let's talk properly.
Don't fight.
Since you protected me,
I'll forgive you.
Really?
Your Majesty, where are you going?
What should I do with these bodies?
Report them.
Yes, Your Majesty.
All six bodies are inside.
You are a noble woman.
How about
I ask the coroner
to give you a report?
Silver needle used in acupuncture.
Based on my observation,
it's the same hidden weapon
used by Zheng Wu.
But,
this needle is coated in poison.
It's good that it's coated in poison.
There aren't many poisons that kill
on contact.
We'll be able to identify it.
Find out about it.
It's you,
right?
I'm no longer
your Sword Bearer.
Why do I have to test the wine for you?
Since you are my customer
and I'm the seller,
I'll do that for you then.
If I can't even find out
the identity of our enemies
and their purpose,
how can I protect you
with my sword?
For your safety
and to prevent the next assassination,
this is my duty as the Sword Bearer.
I have to do this.
Looks like
she really knows nothing about
the Violet Bureau.
If I let her stay in the capital,
she'll ruin the plan.
I have to think of a way
to chase her out.
(Prefecture Court)
Officer.
Don't close the door.
How did the investigation go?
You said that
you'd give me an answer soon.
It has been three days.
Have you found the assassins?
Even if we have,
we'll report it to the court.
It's none of your business.
Leave.
You are wasting my time.
(Prefecture Court)
This homicide case happened in my shop.
Why can't I ask about it?
They are useless.
They are as crooked as their superior,
that useless emperor...
This is not right.
Why did His Majesty...
What are you doing?
Visit the wine store?
- This is Prefecture Court.
- Could it be that
he really went there
to eat biángbiáng noodles?
Stop this!
Don't make a scene
in front of the court.
Stand back!
Leave.
Your Majesty.
He's here.
Prince An
has been taken away by Duke Chu.
(Library of Historical Records)
I'm sorry.
Too many people have died in front of me
in the past two days.
So,
you better
save yourself.
Your Majesty.
Qiu Ziliang has detained Prince An.
He wants to...
He's giving me a warning.
If I don't do as he says,
he'll dethrone me.
What should we do then?
What should we do?
How about you ask your sister?
Madam Cheng.
Ask her to come out with a solution.
You still refuse to say anything?
Is it not working because
they have been watered down?
Continue to drink.
Let me ask you.
How many fingers am I holding up?
One.
This one?
What about this one?
One.
Okay.
You are almost there.
You can leave now.
♪Life is a dream,
how long do happy times last♪
♪In the windy rain,
where will my heart settle?♪
♪The sword can't break this karma♪
♪Look how blurry
and lonely the world is♪
♪Fate can't do anything
about the bleak bonds of this world♪
♪Still can't let go of this life
as time goes by♪
♪Even the iron and golden dagger-axe
cannot extinguish the fire in my heart♪
♪Remembering the past
and letting time while away♪
♪The past is in front of you♪
♪Forgetting while piecing it together♪
♪Like when I sincerely
put my hands together♪
♪I only wish that you can be saved♪
♪The past is in front of you♪
♪Forgetting while piecing it together♪
♪Like when I sincerely
put my hands together♪
♪I only wish that you can be saved♪