( walkers snarling )
( snarling )
Do not fire
that weapon.
( chuckles )
Shit.
Look at what we got here.
Oh, honey, look at you.
You're a damn mess.
Damn it.
Shit.
Can I borrow
that a sec?
Thanks.
Oh, I'm not leaving
you out.
There's some rags
in the back.
What?
- What?
- Never seen that before.
I've seen you
do the same thing.
You smiled.
You were smiling.
Well, I'm the...
luckiest guy in the world.
How about you help me
with one of these cars?
We got some miles to go.
( theme music playing )
( laughs )
Do you have something to say
about my extremely comfortable
and attractive shirt?
No, no, no.
It looks great.
Oh, you missed a...
I wish we had
some soy milk.
Seriously?
Yes, seriously.
Have you ever tried it?
My best friend
in third grade,
- he was allergic to dairy.
- Uh-huh.
And every day he would bring
this soy stuff to lunch.
- I tried it.
- And?
- I threw up.
- Oh, yeah, right.
All right, all right.
I almost threw up.
But I was like, ugh.
- ( laughs )
- It was so gross.
I mean, literally,
I would rather have powdered milk
than to have to drink
that stuff again.
I would rather have
Judith's formula--
I'm gonna go
finish my book.
I have a couple
chapters left.
Thank you.
I heard him
laughing in there.
Almost forgot
what that sounded like.
I can't be his father
and his best friend.
He needs you.
I know that's a lot
to throw at you.
So if you're ever feeling
like you need a break...
I'm done taking breaks.
So what's the plan?
This place,
is it home
or just a stop
along the way?
Well, let's--
let's just stay here
while we figure it out.
Well, we'll need
more supplies.
I'll go with Carl
and get some.
I'll come, too.
You were unconscious
yesterday.
- I'm awake today.
- We need you strong.
Just rest.
Just one more day.
How long you think
you'll be?
Fill a couple bags,
shouldn't be too long.
It's 8:15 now.
We'll be back
by noon.
All right,
you follow her lead.
You understand?
Hey.
Everything okay?
Yeah, I'm just...
hungry.
All right.
I'll see you
in a couple hours.
( grunts )
( ticking )
Find anything good?
Candy bars?
Comic books?
Crazy Cheese?
Huh?
Bam, Crazy Cheese.
Found it still sealed
and everything.
Now I'll be nice
and let you have the first pull.
No, thanks.
Are you sure?
I'm fine.
You don't seem fine.
I'm just tired.
Okay?
( squirting )
( hisses )
I'm sorry.
I'm not very good
at making boys your age laugh.
- ( knocks )
- I was laughing.
Inside.
( knocks )
Toddlers
find me funny.
Two, three-year-olds.
( knocking )
What do you mean
toddlers?
I had
a three-year-old son
and he happened to find me
extremely funny.
( door opens )
We need food, batteries, water,
in that order.
Why didn't you ever
tell me you had a kid?
What was his name?
Did you have
any others?
Were you married?
Okay.
I'll answer
one question at a time,
one room at a time,
and only after
we've cleared it.
- ( man grunts )
- Man #2: You're a coward.
- Man: No, I'm sorry.
- Man #2: You're a lying coward.
- That's all you'll ever be.
- Man: No, please, I'm sorry.
- Don't do this, please.
- Man #2: What the hell'd you say to me?
- Man: I said don't do this.
- Man #2: This ain't your business.
- Man: I'm sorry, man.
- Man #2: Aw, shut up.
- Man: I'm so sorry. No, don't.
- Man #2: It's gonna happen.
Man: We can work this out.
Please, don't do this.
Man #2: It's gonna happen.
Man: No, no, no, please.
Please don't. Please!
- ( blow lands )
- ( man screams )
( men laughing )
( man screaming )
Oh, God!
Man #3: You plan on
finishing the job?
- Man #2: Yeah.
- Man #4: I'm getting an earache
and I know he's just gonna
let his ass squeal.
Man #2: After what he did,
the man deserves to bleed.
( footsteps approaching )
Man #4: Y'all stay down
there if you want.
( footsteps approaching )
( indistinct chatter )
( door opens )
- ( footsteps approach )
- ( chattering continues )
( watch ticking )
( ticking stops )
( floorboards creak )
( banging )
- ( bed squeaks )
- ( man sighs )
Man: This will be our
abode for the evening.
Clean up your mess,
Harley.
What was your son's name?
I said after.
Well, these are actually
two separate rooms
and we already cleared
that one, so...
Andre.
His name was
Andre Anthony.
Make sure there isn't
box of cookies hiding in there.
Did you have
any other kids?
Rules of the game,
my friend.
So?
Did you?
( scoffs )
You know, you could be a spy.
Or a cop.
( sighs )
No.
One was enough for me.
And Andre was a handful,
like you.
Does this hallway
count as a room?
If you can find
something we can use.
This is the only thing
I could find.
Does it count?
Technically, yes.
So?
How long has it been?
It happened after--
you know, after
everything happened.
Does my dad know?
Never told him.
Never told anyone
till just now.
Your secret
is safe with me.
It's not really a secret.
It's still safe with me.
( sighs )
( breathing heavily )
Michonne?
Everything okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
There's a baby in there.
It's a dog.
My dad let me name her.
Maybe--
maybe her and Andre
are together somewhere.
Come on.
It's almost noon.
Your dad will wonder
where we are if we're late.
( man snoring )
- ( indistinct chatter )
- ( footsteps approaching )
- ( snoring continues )
- Yo.
( knocking )
Comfy?
You waking me up
to see if I'm comfortable?
I want to lie down.
Two other bedrooms
up here to choose.
Them's kids' beds.
I want this one.
- It's claimed.
- I didn't hear it.
You gonna have to lay
claim somewhere else.
( both grunting )
( punches landing )
( groans )
( groans, coughs )
Len!
Len, stop!
Stop, Len!
- Stop!
- Hell, no.
Stop!
( Len panting )
My bed now, jackoff.
( bed creaks )
( groans )
( sighs )
Hey, don't move.
Here's some water.
Where are we?
I don't know.
We were fighting biters
and you passed out
right after we left the prison.
I didn't know what to do.
The back of the truck seemed safer
than the side of the road.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
Did we pass a bus?
On the road,
did we pass a bus?
Yeah.
What did you see?
They were all dead.
How long since
we passed it?
Three hours.
- Hey.
- ( tapping )
Hey, stop the truck.
Hey, numbnuts,
stop the truck.
Stop the truck!
Where the hell
are you going?
is he going?
I don't know what your
lady friend's told you
about the special nature
of the mission we're on,
but this shit
is time-sensitive
and we're already
way behind schedule.
So I need you to turn your ass around
and get back in the truck.
- I gotta go.
- It seems like neither one of you's
been paying
close enough attention
to the hell on
earth we've been living in.
So let me tell you how
to best avoid
winding up just another
dead-alive prick.
You find some strong,
like-minded comrades
and you stay stuck together
like wet on water.
We need people.
The more the better.
We need each other, partner.
Even with all that gear on your
shoulder, you won't last a night.
Not by yourself.
I'll take my chances.
I'm gonna have to insist
that you hold the hell up.
All right,
believe it or not,
the fate of the entire
damn human race
might depend on it.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Who is this guy?
I'm Sergeant Abraham Ford.
And these are my companions
Rosita Espinosa
and Dr. Eugene Porter.
We're on a mission to get
Eugene to Washington, DC.
Eugene's a scientist
and he knows exactly
what caused this mess.
All right.
So what happened?
It's classified.
He'd been talking
to the muckety-mucks in Washington
on his satellite phone.
The past couple weeks,
nobody's been picking up
on the other end.
We saw how you handled
those corpses back there.
We could use your help.
Sorry.
I had to get us
off that road.
You were passed out,
we were out of bullets.
I know how to get
back to that bus.
I wrote down
every turn.
I will get you back
if I can, okay?
That's where
she'd go to find me.
- That's where I'm gonna go.
- It's a waste of time.
Tara told us
what went down.
There is zero chance
you will ever find your wife again.
Alive or dead.
Mainly because,
sorry to tell you,
she's gone.
No need for you
to die, too.
Now, come on.
Get back in the truck.
Do something with your life.
( pack drops )
When the people
we love kick...
well, they disappear.
Doesn't mean you've got
to go out that way, too.
( grunts )
She's alive
and I'm gonna find her.
You son of a bitch!
- ( shouts )
- ( grunts )
- Tara: Hey, hey, hey!
- Rosita: Abraham!
Hey, get off him.
Come on.
You don't want this,
Abraham.
Glenn:
Let me go!
- Rosita: Abraham!
- Tara: Stop!
( snarling )
Hey. Hey!
- Hey!
- Rosita: Abraham!
- Hey, get--
- ( Glenn shouts )
- ( snarling )
- ( fighting continues )
Hey, hey, hey!
Come here!
( growling )
Tara: Stop!
( gunfire )
Eugene!
Stop firing, damn it!
Stop firing!
We need to get our weapons.
( gunfire continues )
Rosita:
Leave 'em!
Glenn:
Hey, give me a gun.
Give me a gun.
( gas spilling )
Son of a dick.
- ( ball bouncing )
- ( man snoring )
( men chatting )
( gasps )
Man: Tony, Len, get your
asses down here.
( ball bouncing )
Yo, you hear me?
( clattering )
Man:
Claim, claim, claim!
Len: Shut the hell up.
I'm trying to sleep.
Man #2: There's a woman
shacking up in here.
- Len: Say what?
- Man #3: Come on down.
Len: She hot?
Man #4: Don't grab
your pecker just yet.
She ain't here.
Len: What the hell
you hollering about?
Man #2:
Found her shirt.
Must have washed it
this morning.
- Man #3: Smells good.
- Oh, you found a shirt?
She could be miles
away by now.
Man #2: Why'd she go
to all the trouble of washing a shirt
if she's just
gonna ditch it?
- She'll be back.
- Len: I call first when she gets here.
Man #5: Who knows who else
she got with her.
We need to be ready
for anything.
- Len, take the side room.
- Hold on, let me get a gun.
I'll watch the front den,
you've got the other side room.
- I thought Tony got that.
- Where the hell is Tony?
Tony!
Get him the hell up.
( grunts )
( choking )
( panting )
( men chatting )
( door opens )
( ball bouncing )
Abraham: We were running
a convoy in one of these.
Coming up a dune,
there's this camel,
looks like
it's about to puke.
Probably because
shitbird's packed
about four pounds
of C-4 up its ass.
We were within 20 feet
of that blast
that sent that animal's hump
half a klick into the desert.
And we drove home.
So you tell me
how in the holy hell
did you possibly
kill this truck?
A fully amped-up state
and an ignorance
of rapid-firing weapons.
Is this yours?
Sorry about your ride.
Hope you guys
make it to Washington.
Wait for me.
( sighs )
What the hell else
are we gonna do?
Go to Washington.
Fix the whole
damn world!
That way's clear.
Who knows what's north.
We'll find another vehicle.
We'll go with them until we do.
Trust me.
I'm smarter than you.
( ball bouncing )
( spits )
( whistles )
Come on.
- ( walker snarls )
- ( man screaming )
- Man #2: Stop her!
- Son of bitch.
- Man #3: Kill her! Kill her!
- ( gunshots )
( men shouting )
Go! Go!
( shouting and gunfire
continue )
Abraham:
Got to hand it to him.
He's a persistent
son of a bitch.
I get why you're
following him.
You're loyal.
You're a good person.
I like it.
But what we're doing--
I don't know
how else to say it--
saving the world
is just--
( chuckles )
is just more important.
I mean, even if he does
find his wife,
so what?
How long do you think
they'll live happily ever after
if we don't get Eugene
up to Washington?
You think because
I'm following Glenn,
that makes me a good person?
I'm not.
( laughs )
You're good.
You don't know
anything about me.
Just like I don't know anything
about why you're going to Washington.
I get why
Eugene's going.
He's the only one that
knows how to end this.
And Rosita, she loves you.
She'd follow you anywhere.
But why the hell you agreed to drive him
halfway across the country...
It's that hard to believe,
I want to save the world?
Because you're
a good person?
You don't have
to tell me why.
Just don't lie to me.
Crazy Cheese?
What do you think?
Let's go.
( theme music playing )