( walkers snarling )
( snarling )
( theme music playing )
Carl, slow down.
Carl, stop!
We need to stay
together.
We got to find a place
with food, supplies.
Hey.
We're gonna be...
( crows cawing )
Wait outside, okay?
- Keep watch.
- You keep watch.
You can barely stand.
I'm not gonna let you
go in there alone.
- Excuse me?
- We've done this before.
I'm gonna help
you clear it.
You should just
let me do it myself.
Let's go.
Kitchen's clear.
( snarling )
That might be
all that's left.
- I can get it from here.
- No.
No, it's weak.
I'll draw it out.
Stay back.
Damn it.
- Don't.
- ( gunshot )
I said not to.
You couldn't do it
with the ax.
I had it.
Every bullet counts.
We'd have needed
that one later.
See what you can find.
Then let's move on.
Kitchen wasn't empty
after all.
My haul.
You?
I win.
Hey.
That one's as good as any.
Quick and quiet.
We need to clear it
before sundown.
Carl.
- Carl.
- I got it.
All the doors
down here are open.
Just stop!
- ( pounds wall )
- Hey, asshole!
Hey, shitface!
- Hey--
- Watch your mouth!
Are you kidding me?
If there's one of them
down there,
they would have come out.
( coughs )
( chuckles )
Rick:
Find anything?
Check the back door?
( grunts )
I tied the door shut.
We don't need to take
any chances.
You don't think
it'll hold?
- Carl.
- It's a strong knot.
Clove hitch.
Shane taught me.
Remember him?
Yeah, I remember him.
I remember him
every day.
There something else
you want to say to me?
( wheezing )
This'll have to do
for the night.
You gonna have some?
You should eat.
We should save it.
Hey.
I don't want any.
Eat it.
Now.
( wheezing )
( wheezing continues )
Listen, I'm just
being honest.
I thought it was a bit...
pedestrian.
- ( laughs ) Pedestrian?
- As in lame.
- And played.
- Played?
Where have you seen
anything like it before? Tell me that.
I've never seen a gorilla
drive a car before,
but if you put it in a museum,
I'm not gonna call it art.
( jazz music playing )
Mike, would you please
talk some sense into your lover?
Oh, my God.
You did not just call me that.
- Mm-hmm.
- I agree with my lover.
- I mean, the whole thing was--
- Very lame.
- And very played.
- Oh, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, don't do that.
Don't do that.
Don't start finishing
each other's sentences, man.
It's just gross.
I was going to say that the whole thing
was like a monument
to someone trying too damned
hard to be different.
Hallelujah.
Listen,
I'm glad I saw it
even though
I did not love it.
- ( giggling )
- Hope we're not boring you, peanut.
Come here.
I don't think that we
should stay at the camp.
No. I'm not taking
my son out there.
I don't know if this place
will work out,
but I know it won't
if we go out there.
Does it even
matter anymore?
Are we just
kidding ourselves?
Okay.
All right, I see
what this is.
Really?
What is this, Michonne?
I mean, you've gotten
good with a sword.
You know how valuable
that is now?
- You know what that makes you?
- For what?
What are we going for?
Where's the happy ending here?
This isn't life.
This isn't anything
close, okay?
Not for me,
not for us.
And for our son.
What's the answer here?
Well, what is
the damn question, Mike?
Why?
Okay.
That's good.
Now I have a question.
Who's gonna open
the wine?
No. No.
No, no, no, no.
No. No!
No! No! No! No!
No!
( gasps, panting )
( walkers snarling )
( groans )
Dad?
Dad, wake up.
Wake up.
Come on.
Mom used to do this
to me when I was sick.
( labored breathing )
No.
You have to wake up
right now.
Wake up!
Wake up! Wake up!
- ( thudding at door )
- ( snarling )
- ( thudding )
Hey, you!
Fresh meat right here.
Come and get it.
Let's take a walk.
Keep up.
That's it.
Keep coming.
Very good.
Come on, keep coming.
Come on.
Right here,
look at me.
- ( snarling )
- There you go.
Come on.
That's it.
Just a little farther.
That's right.
Keep coming.
Just a little farther.
Come on.
- ( snarling )
- Oh, shit.
( grunts )
( gunshot )
( grunting )
( gunshots )
( exhales )
( panting )
( groaning )
( coughing )
I win.
Cool.
( sniffles )
I killed three walkers.
They were at the door.
They were gonna get in,
but I lured them away.
I killed them.
I saved you.
I didn't forget while
you had us playing farmer.
I still know
how to survive.
Lucky for us.
I don't need you anymore.
I don't need you
to protect me anymore.
I can take care
of myself.
You probably can't even
protect me anyways.
You couldn't protect Judith.
You couldn't protect...
( sighs )
Hershel or Glenn
or Maggie.
Michonne, Daryl,
or Mom.
You just wanted
to plant vegetables.
to hide.
He knew where we were
and you didn't care!
You just hid
behind those fences
and waited for...
( sighs )
They're all gone now.
Because of you!
They counted on you!
You were their leader!
( sniffles )
But now...
you're nothing.
( sniffles )
( sighs )
I'd be fine
if you died.
( grunts )
Damn it.
( door creaks )
( snarling )
( gunshots )
( gunshot )
( clicking )
Oh, shit.
Come on.
( grunts )
( whimpering )
- ( pounding )
- ( panting )
( walker snarling )
No!
No. No.
No! No! No! No!
( panting )
( sobbing )
( raspy breathing )
( gasps )
( breathing heavily )
( hammer clicks )
( raspy breathing )
( bowl clatters )
( crying )
( crying continues )
I can't.
I was wrong.
Just do it.
Carl.
( wheezing )
Don't go outside.
Stay safe.
I'm scared.
( crying )
Mike.
I miss you.
I missed you even
when I was with you.
Back at the camp.
It wasn't you
who did it.
( sighs )
You were wrong.
Because I'm still here.
And you could be, too.
And he could be.
( sighs )
I know the answer.
I know why.
( sighs )
( snarling )
Rick:
You shouldn't have risked it,
going out there like that.
It's dangerous.
I was careful.
It's good that
you found more food.
I found even more.
But I ate it.
What was it?
112 ounces of pudding.
( chuckles )
I know...
we'll never get things back
to the way they used to be.
What?
I only clung
to that for you.
For Judith.
Now she's gone.
And you...
you're a man, Carl.
You're a man.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to be.
( sobs )
( knocking )
( cocks gun )
( chuckles )
What?
It's for you.
( theme music playing )