♪Waking up in a nightmare♪
♪Facing this cruel world♪
♪Whose heart is flipped♪
♪Missed farewell to lover♪
♪If the ending is tragic♪
♪Fearlessness is born in adversity♪
♪Even if the wings are torn♪
♪And fall back to the abyss♪
♪Hold your hands and move forward♪
♪Never stopping day or night♪
♪Transcending time and distance♪
♪I may be hurt and heartbroken♪
♪Yet be brave to fight on♪
♪As a hero♪
♪Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops♪
♪Turning behind, you are always there♪
♪Lash out the curse in life♪
♪Let the story be eternal♪
♪Martial Soul surges aggressively♪
♪To embrace your lone wolf braveness♪
♪Even if the future is harsh♪
♪I will never give up♪
♪When there is no way out in reality♪
♪Hope is vexed by desolation♪
♪Yet smiling freely♪
♪Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant♪
♪The power of twin souls illuminates♪
♪Surviving in every plight♪
♪I will never give up♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
The squeezing on my body
is extremely painful.
The last six steps are as scary as hell.
There are ten steps left.
Fourth Soul Skill, Invincible Golden Shield.
Explosive Eight Flinging into Nothingness!
Tang San has passed the test.
I made it after all.
[Episode 177]
Fatty.
Xiang! I'll be back soon!
Get off me.
Get off me!
It's pretty cute.
Ao broke through the God-given Soul Ring!
Ao!
Rong Rong, I did it!
I finally have a martial soul form too!
Rong Rong, thank you for being with me
these past few days.
You gave it your all
so that you can protect me in the future.
I...
Back then, Brother Dai gave all his effort
to absorb the God-given Soul Ring for Zhu Qing.
I was very touched.
He told me before
that he was willing
to lay down his life for Zhu Qing.
Even if I can't pass
the clan test later on,
I will rescue her
even if I die.
That's right.
Since I was little,
there's only been one person in my heart.
But compared to Ao,
I'm still not as good.
Are they flattering each other?
They're really shameless.
You...You've really told Ao that?
The longer we are together,
the more I'm in love with you.
My heart become more selfish,
and I want to spend every day
together with you.
That's why
I started training as much as I could.
He did so much for his loved one,
and you called him shameless?
Xiang, for you,
I can give up everything too.
Xiang!
Your Holiness.
For the Seven Clans Re-selection Contest,
ten clans have been selected already,
including the Elephant Armored Tribe,
Sacred Dragon Tribe, Black Tiger Tribe,
Wind Sword Tribe, Panther Tribe,
Steenbok Tribe, and Hornet Tribe.
They have all arrived in Martial Soul City,
and are awaiting your orders.
Very good.
Send my order.
Three days from now,
the Seven Clans Re-selection Contest
officially begins.
[Soul Land]
We've taken enough of a break.
It's time to begin the second test.
We first need to figure out what
ocean soul beasts exist in the Round Ocean.
You guys stay on the shore,
I'll go down and take a look.
San.
(Something's wrong. My support is weakened.)
(Something's wrong. There is a special
power stopping me in the water,)
(and increasing my soul power usage.)
(Arrow Fish Ocean Beast.)
This is so unfair.
Brother San doesn't have
an attack advantage in the water,
and we can't kill any ocean soul beasts
in this test.
What will Brother San do?
(I've only gone 20 meters into the Round Ocean.)
(These Arrow Fish are definitely
not the only challenge.)
(I need to finish them quickly.)
(These Arrow Fish are not scary.)
(The Round Ocean is what's
exhausting my soul power.)
(It's time to stop playing.)
(Hao Tian Nine Extremes.)
[Shock]
(Shock Form!)
(They are too scared to attack again.)
(What's going on?
There's a weird surge happening.)
(Why did I teleport such little distance?)
San!
Brother San!
San! Are you alright?
I'm fine.
But the ocean is too restricting.
I can usually teleport 100 meters,
yet then I could only teleport 5 meters.
Also, the ocean soul beast
at the end was shockingly fast.
I didn't even see it clearly.
We managed to see it. It was a white shark.
It appeared and disappeared
in the blink of an eye.
You were thrown out after.
A white shark?
Its large volume didn't affect
its agility at all.
It looked a lot like the Devil White Shark
Purple Pearl and Ji Xiang mentioned before.
Rong Rong gave her full support just now,
but you were still thrown out by it
with one wave.
It can't just be
a normal Devil White Shark.
Could it be
a Protection Beast,
the Devil White Shark King?
But it guards the outer border
of Haishen Island.
How did it get into the Round Ocean?
Since there are multiple inner oceans
on the island,
there must be tunnels
connecting the outer ocean underneath.
But it didn't seem to intend to hurt us,
it's only stopping us from crossing the ocean.
If it launches lethal attacks,
we won't be able to get out unharmed.
With the Devil White Shark King
guarding the Round Ocean,
the second test is very difficult.
But we just need to break out
of the barrier, not overpower it.
Maybe this is a good chance
to increase our battle experience.
Brother San, do you actually want us to fight that?
Is there any better training
than fighting a century
millennium soul beast
that won't hurt us
in highly restrictive waters?
Right! It's like the first test.
This is a fantastic cultivation opportunity.
We'll get to learn how to swim.
A fire phoenix becomes
a drenched chicken in the water!
Careful!
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 177 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1620 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2675]
[Total scene: 64293]
[Total CGI: 29050]
[Total plan of action scene: 12792]
[Total scene model: nearly 582]
[Total character model: nearly 1057]
[Total props model: 13434]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪We still have to part from each other♪
♪I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving♪
♪Amidst the grieving woods♪
♪Who is crying out there♪
♪I still relentlessly hold on♪
♪I refuse to accept this destiny♪
♪Desperately searching♪
♪Any signs of you♪
♪The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight♪
♪In your eyes, the world never changes♪
♪Yearning grows and interweaves with the past♪
♪Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you♪
♪You are the memory I refuse to let go♪
♪And the craziness of my desperation♪
♪Can you hear♪
♪My calls♪
♪Breaking through extreme dolours♪
♪Rushing towards your embrace♪
♪You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair♪
♪And the wish I made upon a star♪
♪One day♪
♪You will turn up gorgeously♪
♪And hold my hands♪
♪To envisage our future♪
[Next episode]
It turned into a human!
Appearance transformation.
Evil humans.
I'm going to kill you!
Careful!
What happened? Didn't you say
it wouldn't hurt us?
Her Holiness has arrived.
I declare
that the Seven Clans Re-selection Contest
officially starts now!