father emperor
go out
father
free at kisskh.me
go out
father
why are you laughing
Grandpa, you don't have to waste time
You asked Mr. Xia to accompany me to visit the countryside
Understand the suffering of the people
Master Xia always makes me eat glutinous rice
I have hated it for a long time
So I sent people to investigate secretly
looking for evidence of his crime
But the man I sent came back and told me
Lord Xia only has cloth and pottery in his house
nothing else
In fact, it's just a trivial matter whether Xia Yuanji kills or not.
That
what's the big deal
grandfather
You've been sick twice
grandson wish you long live
Let your grandson go on your behalf for the Northern Expedition this time.
OK
One hundred years of life
The world has many
all gone
unknown
Yan Hui thirty
Famous for generations to come
I want to create eternal merits
Why should one hundred years of life
But you can't go
grandfather
I don't worry about Beizheng
because you stayed in Beijing
I can't take risks with Daming's future
Arutai
every year
The people are suffering
I always think about it
biting
They scold me for being so overjoyed
by him
scolding me
also by him
I
Even if the infamy left behind
Never allow an inch of Daming's land to be trampled on
Not to allow the people of Ming Dynasty to be displaced
child
Your father has read a lot of sage books.
Being fooled by a bunch of bookworms
since you think
That old thing from the Ministry is still useful
I'll leave it to you
grandfather
You have been on the throne for more than 20 years
All over the morning
Ask the dynasties
With the respect of the Son of Heaven
Conquer the desert
how many people
your heart and vision
How can it be known by the swallows under the gallery
There are few eagles in this world
How many short-sighted chaffinches
wear thousands of times
It's just flattery
What other good words
you
free at kisskh.me
Have you finished what I asked you to do?
don't do it yet
go
Junji
Waiting for the grandfather to win
Let's go hunting
Yes
grandson retire
Yongle twenty-two years in April
Zhu Di led an army of hundreds of thousands
The fifth expedition to Mobei
Order the crown prince to supervise the country
June
Daming army arrives at Dalanamur River
Arutai fled after hearing the wind
The Ming army searched the valley for 300 miles and found nothing
Insufficient food and grass in the army
Zhu Di ordered the class teacher
July
Holy car arrives at Yumuchuan
Zhu Zhanji was ordered to return to Beijing to raise grain
soon
A piece of news that can shake the world
follow
姚 palm set
don't you have anything to say to me?
The slaves are frightened
There's no fear in your face
I will go back to Beijing in March
Met with the grandfather and left in a hurry
May 归 kyo stop three days
I deliberately didn't call you
I just wanted to see if you would take the initiative to find me
long time no see
nothing to say
Your Highness
This Braised Rabbit Meat
It was specially prepared by the Shang Food Bureau for His Royal Highness.
Handmade by Hu Shangshi
you put me
The rabbit brought back to you from thousands of miles
cooked
Your Highness this
i write to you
you answer me a month late
Let someone bring you a gift
How dare you make braised
With such a dedicated female officer as you
really impressive
What laughing
Your Highness
This is another
The one your Highness gave me has already run away
How can you stay until now?
I haven't been back to Beijing for so long
you don't miss me
Your Highness
I
Say
Your Highness
stay in the food court
don't go anywhere
Your Highness, Father
you left too suddenly
My heart hurts
Your Highness, don't do this
It hurts so much
take care of your body
Your Highness
father emperor
What about the grandson?
back to the princess
Lord Yang Rong and Hai Shou go to Beijing for a secret report
As soon as the emperor got the news
Reported to His Royal Highness
Immediately leave Beijing for the funeral
Once the court hears
Everyone will be afraid
pass my life
Block messages
When the emperor's grandson Fengzi Palace returns to Beijing
mourning again
Yes
emperor
Yongle twenty-two years in August
The Crown Prince sent his grandson Yingzi Palace to Kaiping
mourning in the military
be careful
come down first
hurry up
free at kisskh.me
grandfather
Clearly said good expedition return
You and my grandson and grandson will go hunting in Nanhaizi
Now the old bow is still there
But where did your old man go?
You have made a promise in your life
never renege on others
But why only this time
you lied to me
why
His Majesty's Register
His Majesty
what
Emperor Taizu passed away
Forty concubines in the harem
burial
According to the ancestral system set by the Taizu
The concubines who have nothing in the harem
to be buried underground
how many people
sixteen
all from the funeral
His Majesty
wait
please ask the queen
Families of concubines and concubines
Give preferential treatment as usual
Father and brother hereditary Jinyiwei Qianhu
Concubine Zhuang has served the late emperor for a long time
Better to send her on the road
go
Yes
you can't go in
Queen is alive
Be extra kind to Concubine Zhuang
Moreover
Concubines and concubines have to eat before they go on the road
Why are you two making it difficult for Concubine Zhuang?
Concubine Zhuang
This is the walnut cheese you mentioned many times before
you try
Does it taste the same as before?
Different
Walnut cheese made with my mother
Help
I beg you again to help me
Concubine Zhuang
you get up
You took care of us many times in the past
But we are just the little maids of Shangshi Bureau
Burial is ancestral
how can we help
Deadline for Burial
after sunset today
you help me out of the palace
help me out
Concubine Zhuang
you
The queen refuses to see us
I can't beg her
I'm not I'm not running away
I just want to see my mother
she has no son
no one to rely on
i don't ask for anything else
I just need to see her once
even if
Say your last goodbye
I just say goodbye and come back
I beg you to help me
please
I just say a word and I'll be back
I
I just want to see my mother one last time
even such a request
Can't satisfy me
you want to leave the palace
Concubine Zhuang
There are only three now
If you don't come back before sunset
The three of us will lose our lives
You have a way to get me out of the palace
Great
I swear
I will definitely be back
I swear I'll be back
before sunset
Yao Zijin
know i'm dying
Take this kind of thing to perfunctory me
roll
all roll
get out
roll
empress
go out
What are you doing, madam
Niang Niang calm down
Slave, this is redone and sent
Today is every Thursday
Outside Xuanwu Gate was supposed to open an inner city
You can go out with a badge
But the market went on strike during the funeral
In and out
Most of them are people who go to various supervisors and bureaus to do errands.
Go all the way across the long street
Encounter with patrol guards
Show them the badge
just say
The number of grains and sauces sent by the wine and vinegar noodle bureau is wrong
Hu Shangshi sent you to ask
Next
waist card
what are you doing
queuing
Obviously I came first
what's wrong with me standing in front
Are you unreasonable?
do you know where this is
wanton noise
hurry up
take away
let's go
go
not her first
out of Xuanwumen
The really sad one is at Bei'anmen
You are so kind girl
a dying man
Really redo it and send it
the dying man
Why bother with her
I am full
You'll be on your way soon.
go in
why
Yes
I used to help her and it was profitable
But now she's about to die
is a useless person
Why are you
To take such a big risk to help her
what are you looking at me
am i wrong?
Obviously follow the steps that Concubine Zhuang said
to make walnut cheese
why the taste is different
people are dying
What's the difference?
Okay
even if you say
She got out of Xuanwumen successfully
But how did she get out of Bei'anmen?
I heard that there are eighteen red shops there
Hundreds of guards
There is no escape from the wings
Zijin
Let's go get the man back now
also atonement
How
free at kisskh.me
Zijin
Is it the problem with these walnuts?
Yao Zijin
Only you will believe her
If it were me
a chance to escape
I'm not going away right now
The lady will be back
She never broke her promise
in the face of death threats
Anyone can become selfish and cowardly
no exception
Obviously you don't have to come in to deliver the meal
Then why come?
not afraid of death
You will be afraid by yourself
Ziping
will be back
I knew it
Who will take the initiative to come back to die?
fraud
Yao Zijin
you fool
go
hurry up hurry up
hurry up
And Concubine Zhuang, the head of Yongning Palace
go fast
Yao girl
palm lamp
they'll be there soon
quick
just ahead
Don't waste time
Yes
you go
you go now
Ziping
You don't have to worry about implicated others in Yongning Palace
I stayed
why do you say that
I should have been dead
I'll give you my life this time
You and I will never owe each other
what does this mean
The night our family died
I'm the only one who escaped
Do you think
The person who opened the cricket jar
Is it really my brother?
Now know that you send kindhearted people
What kind of monster is it?
you go away
I do not go
you go
Ziping
open the door
Yes
Why are you still plugged in?
knock
Yes
open the door
bumped away
Yes
I will go to serve your majesty
Dress up by yourself
who allowed you to be so presumptuous
no rules
Concubine Zhuang
Please
I thought Concubine Zhuang would never return.
but
How did she get out of Bei'anmen?
Zijin
What's up
Aren't you your favorite to eat scallops?
So delicious pancakes
usually eat
I can't help but swallow my tongue.
do not know why
It's not tasty at all now
This is when I made walnut cheese for Concubine Zhuang
leftover food
What's up
where are these from
Liao County cotton walnuts and Lingbao red dates
All are great tributes
here
This is the ingredient that the pharmacist sent to the medicinal meal
Although the nuts are large
But far from soft and crispy walnuts
Still a bit bitter
what is this
Is there any time to make walnut cheese now?
It's for Concubine Zhuang
The number of ingredients delivered recently has become more perfunctory
Basmati Rice Dried Fruit Antlers
There is a problem with the number of seafood in the East China Sea
Wang Sishan is determined not to accept
If it wasn't for the perfunctory servants
I am afraid that I have already gone to ask Guanglu Temple.
I know
I am afraid that Wang Sishan will be stubborn
In case she finds out
I'll take care of it
Yes
Where did Zijin go today?
you go check it out
I go by myself
empress
Zijin
not rude
Concubine Zhuang
The slaves made walnut cheese for you
you try
Ojizen
I just want to give my last thought
Zijin
Ziping
quick
right
When I was a child in Jiangnan
The walnut cheese my mother made for me tastes like this
empress
free at kisskh.me
No matter how great the food
The most beautiful taste in the world
It's the memory of my hometown
I am sorry
i deceived you
I walked out of the Forbidden City
I don't want to come back
But the bearer was scared away
I can only carry my mother
knocking on the door one by one
may cling to our kin
No one dares to resist the containment
But my feet
not far
Even if I give birth to wings
There's no way to fly out of here
Lady, it's time to go
my last moment in this world
is warm
empress
the emperor arrives
Your Majesty is down
Has Your Majesty come here specially to see you off?
Today I am willing to die
I beg your majesty to remember your promise
Take good care of my mother for me
don't let her be displaced
no branch
His Majesty
Ancestral system cannot be violated
Zijin
Daughter
i went
empress
Madam, are you alright?
go down
Now
do you understand
presumptuous
Concubines and concubines can only be buried without children
After the honorable minister, he was exempted from death according to the law
not to mention
Your Majesty is in good health
I just
I can't bear it
He died for Emperor Taizu
There are also many concubines who have given birth to children
why not think
Who will decide your fate in the end?
you
empress
your hands are shaking
The slaves will take you back to the palace
Ziping
Yin Ziping
Zijin
Hurry up
you come back
what are you doing
Don't you know how to get out of Bei'anmen?
Now the whole country holds mourning and crying festivals
we still have a chance
go fast
come here
You tell me
why are you leaving
burial
Only the concubines were buried
We are the maids of Shangshi Bureau
then you promise me
Don't care about the grandson again
Let's not be concubines
Just be a good woman
OK
Ziping
Prosperity, richness and fresh clothes
everything that is precious
insignificant in the face of life
look at today's situation
I'm afraid you will follow in the footsteps of Concubine Zhuang
rest assured
I will not
became a concubine
if childless
possible burial
became a female officer
go wrong
worry about life
Go out of the palace today
no way
martial law throughout the city
How to get out of Beijing
lonely woman
how to make a living
Even if you start a business
How to hold
Zijin
what can we do
Is there a king's land under the whole world?
Does Concubine Zhuang not want to escape?
she thinks
But where did you escape to?
Even if you really escape
That is also the nine tribes
escape
can never escape
Since there is no escape
then stay
Ziping
It's a wrong burial
The world is wrong
If it's wrong, correct it
But that's ancestry
Even today's prince can't openly
I'm not afraid
Ziping
don't be afraid
Whenever you remember four words
man-made
Think about it
Whether it's a female officer
still be a concubine
even the most common people
Who has no trouble
There will always be a way out
wherever you go
how far
as long as someone is with you
not alone
have this belief
can support me for a long time
the end
Maybe the way out
Hu Sishan
This is my recipe for medicinal food
take the time to help me see
She gave Concubine Zhuang a jade pendant
Just walked out of Bei'anmen safely
what kind of jade