[English subtitles are available.]
[Luoyang]
[Episode 28]
Since when do we
take orders from you?
Hold on!
Do as he says!
What genius plan do you have?
I am all ears.
I don't think
you can figure out where Baili Hongyi is kept
just by watching over here.
We need to find a way
to let Hongyi know
we are here.
Well, what way?
Zhang, make something nice!
No problem.
I'm off!
[Hanjia Granary, Luoyang]
His Highness and I are here to check inventory
of the Granary by order of Her Majesty.
Sir Wu, thank you
for escorting us here.
Madam Yang, it's my pleasure.
It is the interior guards' job
to protect you and His Highness.
Besides,
you're here by order of Her Majesty.
So, we shall be extra diligent.
Youjue, is this the first time
for you to visit Hanjia Granary?
I passed it by when traveling
between Luoyang and Chang'an.
This is the first time I've ever set my foot in here.
I've long heard that
Hanjia Granary is the livelihood of Luoyang.
Now that I've seen it,
I am more convinced that it's true.
Indeed.
The crops enough for 200,000 households
and millions of people
are all stored in the Granary.
No wonder Her Majesty
thinks of it as crucial.
Her Majesty cares about
the wellbeing of the people.
We all feel utterly grateful
to be able to serve her.
Indeed.
Your Highness, Her Majesty let you
take charge of inventory.
It shows her high expectations for you.
Hongyi,
ever since we got married,
I've done nothing to help you.
All I did was to get you in trouble.
We are here because of me...
Liu Ran,
we are married.
We are supposed to
be each other's rock.
Ever since we got married,
you've always been understanding.
Our life has been in harmony.
I feel quite nice about it.
I knew it!
Hongyi, you went to
18 cosmetic stores in Luoyang to find me
and you drew a portrait for me.
You must care about me.
I'm glad you like it.
Thank you, Hongyi.
Anyway, I'll never leave your side
for the rest of my life.
Zhang!
Coming!
What's for dinner?
I made hoto noodle soup.
Come on, open it.
Have a look!
Is this even human food?
Well, they can have it.
I won't eat any.
Open the door.
See you!
Hongyi,
did they send you food?
You should eat first, Liu Ran.
I am not hungry.
Hongyi, have some food, please.
Or I'll keep worrying about you.
Okay.
Let's eat together.
Weren't you worried that
I didn't get your hint?
Sir!
Where were you
sending the food?
I was
delivering food for the Taoist priests
in the house ahead.
Do you do it every day?
Not really.
That house was empty,
but not long ago, some Taoists came.
I happen to live downhill,
so it's quite convenient for me
to deliver meals for them.
When you were there today,
did you see
a young couple?
No.
Sir,
I want to make a deal with you.
What deal?
Do you know how to make hoto noodle soup?
Of course.
Liu Ran.
I am here.
I've got a plan.
Wait for me here.
Hongyi, where are you going?
Hongyi, be careful!
Hello?
I want to see Taoist Tiantong!
Do you think you're a distinguished guest?
How can you see Master Tiantong as you wish?
There is a special ingredient missing
in his formula.
He'll never figure it out.
Take me to him
and I will tell him.
Hongyi is out.
What is he doing?
He's trying to tell us
where Liu Ran is.
Move! Why are you standing there?
I've been inside for a whole day.
I was just stretching.
Now that we've known where they are kept,
let's save them right now!
It's not time yet.
Tell me, then.
When shall we take action?
Wait.
Add more wood.
Fan the flames.
Yes.
Add ice after the fire gets bigger
to balance the temperature in the furnace.
Control the heat.
Master.
Who told you to bring him here?
Well, it's good that you came.
I've figured out the secret.
The key is the heat.
Now that you're here,
you can witness my success.
The key to making elixirs is not the ingredients,
but the heat.
If others hear you say it,
you'll become a laughingstock.
Adding ice will only
make the fire intensified.
You need to add some apatite of cooling nature
to balance the heat.
Apatite?
If I do that,
the furnace will explode for sure.
I've been practicing alchemy for ages.
Do you think I'll believe
a rookie like you?
Although you've been doing it for ages,
it was me that told you
to keep the fire from getting too big.
It's commonsense that
apatite can fan the flames,
which may cause the furnace to explode.
However, few people know that,
as recorded by Ge Hong in The Baopuzi,
apatite has a cooling nature.
With the right proportion,
it can cool down the furnace
and keep the heat balanced.
Nonsense!
I've tried it myself.
You can simply try it
and see if I am lying.
However, if you succeed,
you must release Liu Ran and me.
Master,
he's acting so mysteriously.
Do not believe him!
He and his wife
are in our hands.
I don't think he dares to play any tricks.
Lady of Autumn has set a tight deadline.
Let's try it.
However,
since you claimed
that the key is apatite,
will you do me a favor
and add it yourself?
If you lied to me,
you'd be the first to die.
Please.
Let's go!
Get him! Now!
I'll go save Liu Ran.
Careful!
Siyue!
Liu Ran!
Were you hurt?
I am alright. Go save Hongyi!
He's in danger!
Don't worry!
Gao Bingzhu went to save him.
Let's go.
Baili Hongyi!
Hurry!
He's here!
Go get him!
Hurry!
You bastard! How dare you lie to me?
Kill him!
Where is Liu Ran?
Siyue went to save her.
I'll go after Tiantong.
Gao Bingzhu!
The noodle soup was too salty.
-Hongyi!
-Liu Ran!
Hongyi, are you alright?
Yes, I am.
It's over. Let's go home.
Where is Gao Bingzhu?
He went after Tiantong.
Beiqi!
Escort them back.
Yes.
Hongyi, are you alright?
Gao Bingzhu!
Where did he go?
He just went into the cave.
I think it's copper from Mount Lian.
Could this black powder
be...
It's called the Thunder.
Although these are all defective products
that are flawed,
you can still
witness how well they'll work
in a minute.
Leave!
[Lord of Spring, Four Season Clan]
Brother,
I've been taking care of
all the matters in the Clan
so that you can have time
to solve the bigger issue.
The Heavenly Temple
is due for completion soon.
Once it's completed,
the evil Empress will hold
the Celebration of Light.
We are left with little time.
Sister, why are you standing there?
Have a seat.
This is, after all,
the most powerful object of all time.
If we could make it in a day or two
from scratch,
we'd be omnipotent
and conquer the world.
Sister, please be patient.
Tiantong is doing his best.
I can be patient,
but if the greater good
was put off...
Brother,
neither you nor I can
afford to take the blame.
Sister,
I've been told that
you've been referring yourself
as the leader
of the Clan.
Sister, have you forgotten that
our teacher is still alive?
Brother, what do you mean?
I didn't mean anything.
I just want to share
my joy with you.
Once the greater good is achieved,
we will be able to bring him back.
My lord, my lady,
Tiantong sent a message.
Good news!
[Baili Mansion]
My lady!
My lord, are you alright?
Yes.
Liu Ran is injured.
Go get a doctor.
On it.
Yunzhi,
take her to have a rest.
Prepare some medicine with a calming effect.
Hongyi, what about you?
Go back and have a rest.
I need to do something.
Shen Fei,
come with me.
My lord,
what are you doing here in Master Baili's room?
After my brother died,
all his written texts
were hidden by my father.
Do you know where they are?
Lord Kuanren?
Let me think.
Uncle Baili said that
they were hidden
in one of the cabinets.
Cabinets?
Cabinets...
My lord!
Here it is.
Careful!
My lord,
why do you need Lord Kuanren's stuff?
[A well-educated gentleman]
[Xuanwu's Pearl]
[Baili Kuanren]
[The Xuanwu's Pearl from the Ke Tribe is the best]
[The best]
I think I saw my brother's handwriting
back at Tiantong's house.
That's impossible!
He died ten years ago!
[Characters finished with upstrokes
written by Baili Kuanren]
I am sure.
My brother was born with an extra finger.
[Characters finished with upstrokes
written by Baili Kuanren]
So, he'd finish
every character
with an upstroke
to keep his little finger from ink.
[Dragons and snakes slither around,
looms are hidden outside the capital.]
Looms are hidden outside the capital.
Dragons and snakes slither around.
[Baili Kuanren]
Mountains overlook the crowd.
Siyue!
Siyue, where are you?
I am here.
Gao Bingzhu, where are you?
Where are you?
Gao Bingzhu!
I am over here.
Siyue,
are you over here?
Gao Bingzhu!
Siyue!
Are you here?
Gao Bingzhu!
Siyue!
Hang in there.
Gao Bingzhu, I am here.
Gao Bingzhu, where are you?
Are you alright?
Yes.
I am coming.
Gao Bingzhu!
How are you?
My leg got jammed.
I'll move the rock
so you can get it out.
Come on!
Lift your leg a bit.
Hang in there.
Alright.
This will stop the bleeding for now.
What was inside the box?
How come it's so powerful?
Now is not the time to discuss this.
I'll go and find an exit.
Gao Bingzhu!
Gao Bingzhu, careful!
Anyone there?
Help!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
May Your Majesty be blessed with longevity
and infinite glory.
Youjue, you're here.
You're in poor health.
There's no need for formalities.
Do you know why I asked to see you?
The case of the informers is not closed yet.
I didn't do my job well.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
You've been working hard for me.
Why would I punish you?
Sir Wu of the Interior Guard Services,
please take the order.
I am all years, Your Majesty.
Sir Wu is an outstanding member of the Wu family
and a reliable talent of the country.
Although he is in poor health,
he still fulfills his duty to protect the country.
Therefore, he shall be granted
the title of Duke of Ying.
He'll be rewarded a fief of 300 households,
effective immediately.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
It must hurt badly, right?
All the interior guards knew
that I went to look for you.
I believe that they'll come and find us
since we have
gone missing for so long.
Yes.
You're right.
They will come and find us for sure.
Siyue,
our top priority right now
is to save energy
and wait for them,
okay?
Don't worry!
Recently,
I've been busy working on the case.
I couldn't remember the last time
I've sat quietly like this.
I feel relieved, actually.
You handled the Crown Prince situation well.
The Interior Guard Services has been thriving
under your leadership.
I've been saving the title of Duke of Ying for you
for a long time.
I am deeply grateful
for your grace, Your Majesty.
I only wish for Your Majesty to live long
and forever!
Forever?
Outsiders can say this
all they want.
We're family.
What's the point of fooling ourselves?
I am old.
Who knows how long I'll live?
The Heaven Project
is my only wish that hasn't been realized.
It's been 20 years.
Finally,
it's due for completion.
I want to paint the statue of Buddha gold
in the Heavenly Temple
and light a candle myself.
On the day of the Ceremony of Light,
I want you
to be in charge of security.
I will do my best.
I won't let you down, Your Majesty.
My lord.
[Dragons and snakes slither around,
looms are hidden outside the capital by Baili Kuanren]
looms are hidden outside the capital.]
[Stars are buried underground,
mountains overlook the crowd by Baili Kuanren]
Brother,
The Nine-Linked Rings puzzle
is too difficult to solve.
I've tried everything,
but they're still separate rings.
I can't make a loop out of them.
Do you think
my brother is still alive?
My lord!
[The Interior Guard Services]
I was trying to
secure the position of Minister of War for you.
However, Her Majesty never said yes.
To be honest,
to be Duke of Ying
is an honor, indeed,
but it's nothing more than a title.
The Minister of War, on the contrary,
holds real powers.
In fact, I am happy enough to be able to
shoulder burdens
for Her Majesty and you, Your Highness.
We're cousins. No need for these nice words.
Don't get upset yet!
Her Majesty
asked you to take charge of the Ceremony of Light.
If you do a great job,
Her Majesty will most likely reward you.
Thank you, Your Highness.
It's a pity that
Her Majesty might let go of the Dai Zhou case.
She only grounded the Crown Prince
for self-reflection.
What a pity!
Your Highness,
we are at Her Majesty's service.
All we need to do
is to share Her Majesty's burdens.
You need to be discreet
on certain matters.
Sir Wu!
How dare you!
Please forgive him, Your Highness.
What?
My lord!
Uncle!
The interior guards are here.
Baili Hongyi!
Siyue has gone missing.
I don't even know if she's alive.
I was told that
when she went missing,
a loud noise came from the North Mountain.
It was deafening!
It must have something to do with her missing.
What do you know?
Tell me!
Come on! Tell me!
Was the North Mountain House
destroyed by interior guards?
It was my fault.
I was being
negligent.
Someone!
Cut off his hand.
Yes.
Please don't!
I...
I've figured out
-the secret of the Thunder!
-Wait.
Brother,
who knows if he has
really made it?
Maybe, he's just trying
to make up some excuses.
I say, we just cut off his hand.
We can try it and see if he's telling the truth.
If he's lying,
we can still cut off his hand later.
If he's telling the truth,
are we going to make the Thunder
by ourselves if his hand is cut off?
I still haven't figured out
what exactly the Thunder does.
I only know it's extremely powerful.
It can even blow Tiantong's furnace into pieces.
How dare Tiantong
use that against Siyue?
If I guessed right,
that thing is extremely explosive.
It needs to be kept away from light.
It's likely that Tiantong hid it
in some shady area in the North Mountain.
Everyone! Go to the North Mountain with me!
I'll come with you.
No need.
Siyue got herself in danger because of you.
If she's safe, I'll spare you.
If she's not,
I'll kill you.