[English subtitles are available]
[Plot Love]
[Episode 20]
You can't wait, huh?
Can't wait
to look for the next man.
Don't you think it's too early?
Chris, let's go.
I can't believe you're trying
to cheat on me.
Aren't you afraid I'll use it
as evidence of affair against you?
I've asked my lawyer
to handle the divorce.
I don't want to see you again
until it's settled.
Bei Bei,
please don't abandon Nan Nan.
It'll break my heart.
Good boy, I love you.
If it wasn't for the kid,
I wouldn't want to see you either.
Chris, come here.
Daddy loves you.
I forgot to tell you.
Chris will live with me from now on.
Lu Nan, what do you mean?
What do I mean?
My legal team will tell you.
Do you still mean what you said this afternoon?
Of course.
Alright.
I agree.
Then see me in the office tomorrow.
Alright.
What did you agree to?
Let's go.
You're playing with fire.
You'll put yourself in danger!
I don't think so.
I'm happy with it all.
[Gu's Group]
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Good proposal.
I'll work on it then.
Welcome, sister-in-law.
We'll be working together
for a long time in the future.
Aren't you tired of faking?
As Gu's design director,
I'd like to welcome you to the team.
You're working independently from brother now.
I really admire
your competence at work.
I like your action
more than your words.
Don't worry, sister-in-law.
You'll see me working a lot from now on.
Have you had breakfast?
I've got coffee and breakfast for you.
Thank you, Mr. Gu. I appreciate it.
I've already had breakfast.
Alright.
Way to go!
Ms. Lu,
please vacate your office
and give it to Ms. Su.
Actually, that was what I thought too.
My office is bigger
and easier to communicate
for work.
I hope you'll like it.
It's very nice of you.
Thanks.
Mr. Gu, I'll pack my things now.
Go ahead.
Let's have dinner tonight.
If I'm free,
I'll tell you in advance.
What do you mean?
Why did you
outsource part of the environmental project
to Su Bei?
Don't you even knock before you come in?
Which role are you in now
when you're asking?
Wang Ying,
do I need to remind you
of our relationship?
Please call me Lu Fei'er.
Do you think you can turn from a crow into a phoenix
just because you've changed your name?
And let me remind you that
we're business partners.
We're also employer and employee.
I don't have to report to you
what I want or plan to do, do I?
What do you think other staff members
will think of me
as the new design director?
Is your pride,
or our goal more important?
Eminence is about to be listed
and there's nothing we can do about it.
But as long as we can pitch Lu Nan
against Su Bei,
we still have a chance to bring him down.
You're too clever to be wise.
Thanks.
Just do your job.
If you can't,
you'll be fired.
[Project Planning Expert Q&A]
Alright.
That's it
for our company's
environmental friendly philosophy.
Turn on the light.
The above
is the survey that we have done
on the environmental organizations
in the community,
and the environmental protection concept
promoted by designing this outfit.
If you have any questions,
please feel free to ask me.
The materials are very well prepared
and will be of great help to us.
Well done!
If we need anything else,
we'll let you know.
By the way,
here are some ideas
from our design team
for evening gowns and daily wear.
You can take a look first.
Mr. Gu.
- Hello, Mr. Gu.
- Mr. Gu.
Thank you all. Sit down.
The meeting isn't over yet.
It's time for lunch.
You have to eat on time to be healthy.
I bought you your favourite cake.
I remember it's this brand.
It's this brand, isn't it?
What are you waiting for?
Eat it and then work.
Health comes first,
you know?
It's the first time for us to eat
in the middle of a meeting.
Mr. Gu,
I've never seen you so nice to someone before.
That's right.
- Thanks, Ms. Su.
- This is for you.
I'll take one.
Get one for me.
Here.
Do you like it?
Thanks.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's probably a bit too cold and
irritating my stomach.
I'm having a stomachache.
Then
forget about the meeting.
I'll take you to the hospital for a check-up.
No thanks.
I'll just rest for a while.
Are you sure?
Come on,
have some hot water.
I'm sorry to
give you something so cold.
Sorry.
I've delayed your work.
Your health is the most important thing.
I'll be able to continue the meeting
after a break.
Look at you.
I told you that your health is the most important thing, all right?
That meeting can be cancelled.
You should take a good rest
and resume work tomorrow.
No, I can't.
We're too slow
in progress.
Everyone's waiting for the project
of the environmental conference.
I have to work hard.
If I can't make it,
I'll let you down.
Are you undervaluing
our friendship?
We're both businessman.
Profit is our priority.
It has nothing to do with our friendship.
We're friends
and colleagues.
We're very close. Don't worry.
Come in.
Sis,
I bought you the medicine for stomachache.
You'll feel better with this.
Thanks.
This is Yu Jia,
the best tailor in our company.
No,
the best tailor in China.
We're not related,
but we're like sisters.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Gu.
Sis.
I'll take my leave.
Take your medicine and rest for a while.
I'll go now.
I've taken my medicine
and I'm ready to get back to work.
Take care of yourself then.
[How take care of someone with a stomach flu?]
What's wrong?
You look so serious.
Damn it.
Look at how thoughtful
and passionate Mr. Gu is
in expressing his love.
It's just stomach flu
and he wants to show his concern to the whole world.
Unlike some guy,
who's as insensitive as a stone
and gives the cold shoulder to his loved ones.
Do you think I'm not passionate enough?
You said it yourself.
Alright.
I'll show you how passionate I am.
What's wrong with you?
You've gotten into acting now, haven't you?
No.
Then why do I get the feeling that
you're going to leave me
for that Gu Yan?
Am I passionate enough for you?
Mr. Jealousy is getting jealous again.
Then Mrs. Jealousy,
would you like to take a bite?
[Gu Yan]
Hello?
Are you asleep?
Not yet.
Do you still have a stomachache?
I'm getting much better.
Get some rest early.
Alright.
Then tomorrow...
I'm going to get mad.
Su Bei,
there will be serious consequences.
Really?
Stop!
Are you really in love with her?
Don't think too much.
I know you're faking.
But every time I see you being nice to her,
I'm worried that
you'll fall for her.
Just do your job.
I'm putting up an act now.
When we're done,
I'll give you what you deserve.
Are they really
getting a divorce?
They've been arguing a lot.
It doesn't look like pretending.
Besides,
Su Bei has met with her lawyer several times
for discussions.
So it's all worth it.
Thanks.
When they get divorced
and you get
what you want,
we'll be able to
make our relationship public, right?
I'm looking forward to that day.
But you'll have to speed up.
And
don't come to see me lately
so we won't get caught.
Delivery!
Don't go.
Stay in bed.
I'll take a look.
Who is it?
It's me, Gu Yan.
Hide somewhere! Gu Yan is here.
We're married.
It's not an affair.
What's the panic about?
Stop it!
If he finds out, we'll be in big trouble!
Go go go!
Here.
Come on!
Su Bei,
anything wrong?
Sorry,
I just went to the bathroom.
What are you doing here?
I bought you breakfast.
Porridge.
It helps warm your stomach.
Thanks.
You don't have to...
Any time!
I'll buy you breakfast
every day
to take care of your stomach.
Thanks.
You don't have to do this.
I'd love to.
Here.
Try it.
I waited in line
for over an hour this morning
to buy it for you.
The porridge is really good.
Thank you.
Next time, don't bother.
It's my pleasure.
You...
What's wrong with you?
Are you feeling sick?
Nothing.
It's just the weather is dry.
I'll have some water and it'll be fine.
You don't have a fever.
Here.
Thanks.
Thanks for your concern.
Of course I'm concerned about you.
Because I'm very serious about you.
What's that noise?
Well...I...
I don't really like the egg.
It's okay.
I bought you another one.
Why is there still a sound?
Look, the flowers I bought
two days ago are nice, aren't they?
Yes.
Should we have breakfast first?
It'll get cold.
OK.
What are you doing?
I've had enough of you!
You're staying out all night.
You're a bad dad.
I'm going to find Bei Bei.
Go ahead. Go!
Did you find another woman to be your wife?
The short-form videos were right.
If there's a stepmother, there's a stepfather.
No wonder you're kicking me out.
I'm going to tell Bei Bei about it.
You...
You're doing bad things behind her back.
Hurry up.
You'll lose your mother
if you keep wasting time here.
Hurry!
Go!
Who said she didn't want to eat
and had to head for work?
I wasn't hungry then,
but now I have the appetite.
I'm ready. Let's go.
That's it?
Have more of this!
I'm telling you.
You have stomachache
because you're eating too fast.
Not really. It's because I eat too much.
Bei Bei.
What's wrong, Chris?
Who made you upset?
Nan Nan is cheating on you,
and Bei Bei is cheating on him.
Come here.
Chris, let Uncle Gu hug you.
Chris, what's wrong?
Don't cry. Don't cry.
Don't cry. Don't cry, all right?
All right.
I'm telling you.
If you keep crying,
you won't look handsome, okay?
Don't cry.
Uncle Gu, be a good person
and don't break up my family.
I just found my father.
Chris, say sorry to Uncle Gu.
That's very rude.
It's okay. It's okay.
Don't cry.
Don't cry. Don't cry.
Sorry,
I'll help him wash his face.
- I'll dry-clean this for you.
- No worries.
It's fine.
Go.
You go wash your face first. I'll wait for you.
Don't cry.
[Gu's Group]
- Hello, Ms. Su.
You don't have to do that.
We're all family.
I don't care about
formality.
I only value results.
Ms. Su,
what can I do for you
today?
Do your job first.
I'll ask you if I need anything.
OK.
I've got some good news for you.
In order to welcome Ms. Su to our team,
- Mr. Gu.
we'll go to Yonghong tonight for a party!
Great!
Get back to work.
Sis,
I'll go back to work.
Su Su,
what's going on?
In order to welcome us,
Gu Yan is inviting everybody
to Yonghong for a party tonight.
Bro,
any good news?
You're all glowing.
Are you...
Should I call Ye Ting
and tell her you miss her?
It's all your fault!
If it weren't for you,
she wouldn't have hated me so much.
Don't bother to call.
Why don't you just
send me
to work with Su Bei?
You wish!
We must be patient
and go through this together.
Well.
I've made a dinner reservation with Mr. Qian
tonight at Yonghong.
It's a waste of time.
I'm not going.
Then,
I'll tell Mr. Qian to go to another place.
[Gu Yan is having a dinner party at Yonghong tonight at 7pm to welcome Su Su]
If you keep important information to yourself again,
I'll donate all your bonuses
for the next three years.
Don't, bro!
You can't do this to me.
You'll lose me if you do that.
[Yonghong Grand Spa Thermal Resort]
Why isn't he here?
- Mr. Lu, please come in.
- Mr. Lu is here.
Leave the door open. Get some air in.
Mr. Lu, you're here.
Welcome!
Mr. Lu, the seat of honor is there.
Please.
Mr. Lu,
it's not appropriate for you to sit here.
Mr. Yun.
Mr. Yun, Mr. Lu is...
Mr. Lu likes to sit there.
Let's take our seats too.
All right.
Make yourself at home, Mr. Lu.
Be my guest.
Go away.
Ting Ting, serve Mr. Lu some wine.
Mr. Lu, is red wine okay?
I need to go to the toilet.
Yun Fan, you talk to Mr. Qian.
Mr. Lu,
I don't think it's a good idea.
I think it is.
Shall I ask Ye Ting to talk to him?
Mr. Yun,
did I not serve him well?
Is he upset?
No.
Come on. Let's eat.
Come on.
Alright.
OK.
Here.
- Try this.
- Good.
This is their signature dish.
It's very good. Give it a try.
Thanks.
Oh my god.
It's too sweet, Mr. Gu.
Spare a thought for the single ones!
I've always thought that Mr. Gu and Ms. Su
This is delicious too. Try it.
are a perfect couple.
They are a perfect match.
Full of love.
I'm so jealous.
That's right!
Yes.
PDA.
So sweet.
Right.
They're drunk.
Don't take it personally.
No worries.
They're so good together.
A perfect couple.
I agree.
Right?
Yeah!
I'm envious!
Right.
Brother!
What are you doing here?
So sweet.
Who's the perfect couple?
Mr. Gu.
What's wrong?
We're friends.
Do you mind if I take a seat here?
Of course I do.
And if I remember correctly,
isn't this supposed to be our Gu's party?
Your employees aren't allowed to bring family to the party?
That's too bad!
Very good.
I think it's better to work for Eminence.
Our employees can bring their family
to parties
and events.
By the way,
if you want a new job,
tell me.
I'll give you a position in Eminence with good pay.
Mr. Lu, you gotta be kidding.
You're trying to poach my staff in front of me.
And as far as I know,
isn't Su Bei going to be single again soon?
It's not appropriate for Mr. Lu
to still act like her family member,
is it?
Su Bei.
Isn't this your favorite rib?
Give it a try.
It's very good.
Thanks.
Rib is no good.
Here.
Come on.
Have...
some vegetables.
They‘re full of vitamins.
I'll take care of my own wife.
Just mind your own business.
[Yonghong Grand Spa Thermal Resort]
- Mr. Gu, we're leaving.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
Su Bei, I'll drive you home.
She's going with me.
Thank you, Mr. Gu.
Pleasure. Just call me Gu Yan.
Be careful.
[Yonghong Grand Spa Thermal Resort]
Brother!
Director Lu, you must be mistaken.
Brother.
Brother, I know you don't want to see me.
I know you don't want to talk to me.
But I miss grandma.
I really want to go home and see her.
Don't call her grandma anymore.
You have nothing to do with the Lu family.
Brother!
I thought you were taking me home.
Why are we here?
[Meeting you, meeting love]
Isn't it beautiful?
I prepared all of this.
Do you like it?
It's beautiful.
Mr. Gu, you're brilliant.
People say that fireworks are beautiful but short.
In fact, there's no need to be pity.
Because everything that's beautiful
can be replicated.
You may think
something is unique,
but it's only because
you haven't met a better one yet.
Look ahead,
and there's always a surprise.
[Meeting you, meeting love]
I fall in love with a woman.
I like her a lot.
You do?
She must be really good
and really adorable.
I think
she's unique.
I want to be close to her,
but
I'm afraid she'll hate me.
I want her to know how I feel,
but I'm afraid she'll be scared.
I'm nervous
because I don't know
if she likes me back.
It's getting late.
I should go home.
I need to work tomorrow.
Why don't you turn on the light?
Where did you go with Gu Yan?
Do you know how long I've been waiting?
My neck hurts so much right now.
Mr. Lu, can you give me a massage?
Be gentle.
Gu Yan
took me to the place where you
confessed your feelings to me last time.
Why did he take you there?
He...
confessed his love to me.
What are you doing?
Confess his love?
How dare he!
We're not divorced yet.
He thinks I don't exist?
If you go now,
we'll lose everything.
Who was the one
who swore to me
that he could do it right?
Now you're breaking your promise!
I'm not good at faking.
I don't give a damn about
putting up an act anyway.
Yes, yes, yes.
Mr. Lu is right.
But now Gu Yan has fallen for the trap.
If we stop now,
all our efforts will be in vain.
Mr. Lu, will you please calm down?
You know I care about you.
You really don't want to talk to me anymore?
The show can't go on
without me.
Of course, you're the leading actor.
I can cooperate,
but you have to promise me a few things.
Go ahead.
First,
only sleep with Chris once a week
so he can learn to be independent.
Second,
you should be considerate about me.
As soon as I'm feeling down,
you should make me feel better.
And, of course, I'll do the same for you.
Third,
you can't go out with other men during the night
unless I'm there.
Fourth,
for our healthy relationship,
we will kiss goodnight every day.
Fifth,
grandma wants Su Ziyi to change his family name to Lu.
Su Bei, I know it's been difficult
for you over the past few years.
I'll try to make it up to you,
but grandma...
You don't have to say that.
Chris is your child.
He will always be.
Let's find a time to register.
I want to make sure our family
will stay together forever.
Is Mr. Lu happy with practising the fourth condition?
No.
Goodnight kisses are for bedtime.
So this one doesn't count.
Isn't it time for you to go home?
This is my home.
Come on. Don't let him find out the truth.
If you hadn't turned off the lights,
Gu Yan would have found out
when he drove me home.
One more thing.
Don't mention other men
in front of me anymore.
You've been so thin from staying abroad.
I worry about you.
I'll cook for you
so you can look healthier.
Thank you, grandma.
This is Chris.
You probably don't know.
Chris is your brother's son.
Really?
No wonder I like him the moment I see him.
He's your brother's son.
After all this time,
I finally became an aunt.
Chris.
Come here.
Say hello to your aunt.
Come on.
Come!
Here!
I...
I've got homework to do.
He's shy.
It'll be better if you spend more time with him.
Where's my sister-in-law?
She's not home today?
It's your brother's fault.
They already have a kid.
But they're getting a divorce!
Divorce?
The kid is small.
I don't think she has the heart to divorce.
Brother, you're back.
She only left for a short period of time.
Why do you look like strangers to each other?
That's not nice.
Come on, have a seat.
This is your brother's house.
Make yourself at home.
Come on.
Why are you back?
I missed grandma.
I found a job in China.
No matter how it is in other countries,
there's no place like home.
You don't want me to come back, brother?
No way!
He just doesn't mince his words.
Fei'er is such a sweet girl.
Of course your brother wants you back.
Why did you have to look for a job?
Eminence is so big.
If you want a job,
ask your brother to arrange it for you.
I'm still learning. I'm afraid
I'll be a nuisance to brother if I don't do well.
We're family.
Don't say that.
You can count on him.
Grandma is the best!
My sweet girl.
My lovely girl.
I warned you to stay away from grandma.
Ever since I was a child,
you won't let others into your study room,
just like your heart.
I thought
you were like that to everyone.
Until you met Su Bei,
I realized that
not everyone was the same.
What are you trying to say?
I just want to say that
you got me wrong, brother.
I came back
because I missed you and grandma.
Grandma missed me too.
It's only right for me
to come back to visit her.
How do you get
the fragrance brocade?
You mean
the book with a beautiful cover?
Is it something important?
I happened to see
your text message from Yu Qinglan.
I thought since you were so busy,
I'd go get it for you.
Then
it suddenly occurred to me that
Yu Qinglan
was a very important person to Su Bei.
I didn't want to upset you,
so I stopped it for you.
I don't care what you're up to.
But you must stop.
If you hurt my family again,
then
it'll be more than just sending you abroad.
Family?
I'm not your family?
Lu Nan,
you've never thought of me
as part of this family, right?
Am I
an outsider to you?
Get out!
Su Bei is with Gu Yan now.
You think she cares about
how long you've been waiting for her?
Seven years ago,
she left you behind without a second thought.
Seven years later,
she is still the same one.
She doesn't deserve your care and love.
Brother,
I'm the one who loves you the most.
Even if I divorce Su Bei
and even if she didn't exist in the first place,
it's impossible
between me and you.
Besides,
Su Bei is still your sister-in-law.
Be respectful
when you refer to her.
If you speak ill of her again,
I won't let you off the hook.
Why can't I do the same
as Su Bei does?
Because you can never be compared to her.
And stay away from grandma.
I didn't tell her about what you did
because I didn't want to break her heart.
I can accept that you don't love me,
but I can't accept that you love someone else.