little women dare
please forgive me
plead guilty now
may reduce the sentence
The girl has a mole on the palm of her left hand
I remember really right here
don't pull
I will do it myself
see
sorry girl
Free at kisskh.me
a little woman abrupt
It's good to know the truth
Lord Liao Gongzheng said
There is no place in the world that Jinyiwei can't go to
There is no one who Jinyiwei can't arrest
but this does not mean
They can arrest innocents at will
this time
If I endure it any longer
What's the face of Shang Food Bureau
It's all a misunderstanding
If someone impersonates the palace, what if they plan to do something wrong?
Involving royal safety
easily neglected
Liao Gongzheng has now revealed the truth
If you are still unrepentant
search here
Can our errands be done?
There are no idlers in the food bureau
what to see
go back to do their own errands
Mr. You since the imperial concubine Zhaoxian left
Most of the palace affairs are managed by the Crown Princess
This Meng Shang food has always been favored by the princess
I was going to check it out and report back to you
But now it seems
Meng Shang food
can you promise me
There are really no impostors in the Shang Food Bureau.
Naturally no
Okay
Since there is a guarantee of Meng Shangshi
Of course I have to believe
But in the future
If anyone finds out about the food bureau
There are really fake palace maids
Meng Shangshi should be punished together
checked all
Talking is useless
You adult
please
When Lady Xiao was in charge
Strictly enforce the law
No successor now
It's getting worse
As early as the Hongwu period
The matter of cooking and drinking
food bureau
It follows the old example of the Taizu period.
Now it's being called a power grab
The food bureau is still like this
Not to mention the other sisters
Today's six innings and one division
The prestige of the past is gone
If only Empress Renxiao was still alive
All right
you come with me
follow me
Come with me
Come in
give me hand
Even the moles are ruined
your heart is so cruel
let go
you let me go
you
I'm worried that Jinyiwei finds out that you have entered the palace as a fake
So now I'm dead
suicide
can stop you
All this controversy and doubt
is not it
But you didn't think
Witnesses come so quickly
go
Free at kisskh.me
you follow me
I tell you
Now my troubles are over
here comes your trouble
you go with me to Meng Shang Shi's
make things clear
go
what to do
I won't confront you
I'd rather die than leave the palace
I definitely don't
OK
A man who is not afraid of death
then you tell me
Is there anything scarier than death?
you will never understand
Thousands of households in Daming
Since ancient times
are all good
But there are countless pariahs in the area of ​​Zhezhi
Just because their ancestors were traitors
always discriminated against
Become a pariah from generation to generation
Not allowed to take the imperial examination
lifelong career
pretty woman
Once grown
to sell the pillow
Pay heavy taxes to the government
My parents lost their money
looking for crickets
just to escape
But it ended up being empty
do you know
My whole family is dead
only me
i don't want to hurt you
But how many people will be involved in the event of an incident?
so
you are for revenge
just entered the palace
revenge
I'm struggling to live
what am i revenge
who do i take revenge on
I don't want to laugh at the door like my mother
I don't want to bow down like my dad
I don't want to be like my brother
Killed by a cricket
I want to be an upright person
So I've been pretending to be stupid
I finally got my chance
escaped successfully
I've been to many restaurants
Be a handyman cook
they don't want girls
I don't want wages
i eat leftovers
no matter how they bully me
I also endure
Only in this way
I can stealthily learn the cooking skills of a cook
why are you looking at me like that
right
I'm from a scumbag
Almost made a skinny horse
I also steal other people's cooking skills
i'm a thief
The family of the prosperous landlord did not want to let their daughter enter the palace
Bought the eunuch
So I entered the palace
This is my only chance
only
Born in a cheap family, went to nowhere
How is it similar to her?
All right
I tell you
Hanging and killing traces
are different
Don't be stupid again
Just do as I say
Meng Shang food
I have something to report
I quit first
what happened
do not worry
I won't repeat
just one thing matters
must let you know
meal
What's up
Free at kisskh.me
Isn't the eldest sister the most disciplined?
Why are you trespassing without reporting it?
You go down first
what are you doing
you understand
Concubine's forgiveness
Your Highness the past six months
The concubine Taisun sent people to the pharmacy department several times
Receive medicinal materials on the grounds of illness
Medicines are self-prescribed
After seeing the medicine, there is no major problem
let go
you are a brilliant doctor
Naturally knows how to collect herbs slowly
but i don't understand
Taisun Concubine is the supreme glory
Why do you want to die again and again
right
Of course it's good to be a concubine
high bed soft pillow brocade clothing and jade food
But Mrs.
If it's all based on human life
how do you want me to be happy
human life
what life
elder sister forgot
I didn't want to be my father's puppet
leave him at his mercy
He secretly went to his grandfather's house
Sometimes he's not in the pharmacy
I also took a prescription for him.
once
I prescribed medicine for a woman
within three days
It's one corpse and two lives
you quack
kill my wife
i want your life
stand up
what are you doing
smash me
Stop
Medical lazy
What kind of hospital do you run?
kill for life
stop
I can only blame you for not being good at medicine
disobey the father
Unauthorized medical rescue
The patient is pregnant
But you missed the medicine for promoting blood circulation and promoting menstruation
can it be okay?
The patient has three daughters
Poor family can't afford
I listened to her pleading
I can't bear it
want to help her
Just because of your assertiveness
made a big mistake
If it weren't for my father's painstaking efforts to save
Can you still be safe here?
help me
I thought it was because I was not good at academics
kill people
implicated grandfather
I want my father to cover up
So I'll just listen to you
Entering the palace as a concubine
But I didn't know until my grandfather got news.
for you to force me back
increased the dose
Kill the patient alive
elder sister
what does your heart do
For glory and wealth
so vicious
Grand Concubine
still sour
Your Highness
I am the auspiciousness you carefully built
It is your tool to seek power and wealth
Respectfully on weekdays
treat me like a gentleman
Now it's revealed
Finally no need to hide
every time you
Add a small amount of poison to the food
just waiting for the day
able to go unnoticed
Weakness and death
But I was stopped
But you still haven't given up
That day also accidentally implicated the emperor's grandson
right
you should be lucky
Grandson, he is fine
little madman
no matter how crazy you are
how painful
you have to remember
Thankfully it didn't spread
Otherwise not only will you die
Even the whole family will be buried with you
you don't care about the elder sister and father
But you always have to care about your mother
with innocent siblings
Be your great grandson
If the imperial grandson hates you
You are not even auspicious
Zijin, let me help you
Yin Ziping, come here
Hidden set
What is your order?
from today
You can't go into the big kitchen anymore
why
What happened
What did Yin Ziping do wrong?
Yeah, what did Yin Ziping do wrong?
Hidden set
Okay don't ask
get busy
I told Meng Shangshi
About Yin Ziping's real origin
you overheard our conversation
I don't understand why you
To give such people another chance
but I
would never work with such a person
But
Meng Shangshi is already in full view
Guarantee that no one is impersonating the food bureau.
so she is lucky
Even if the entire Shang Food Bureau
Everyone knows her secret
Nor will it be openly dismantled
After the storm
Find a way out
go away
Is what Fang Dianshan said true?
such a filthy man
do not know
let's go before we get tired
come in
Slower
ok ok ok
Just leave it here
come over here
this
Free at kisskh.me
Yuehua
The wound is alright
thank you
why are you still ignoring me
it's too cold outside
They asked me to send the bed out
Remember to take the medicine for a while
I'm in
you are lying
They all think I'm filthy and disgusting
how could you care about me
i have a teacher
Smart and beautiful
calligraphy and painting
she's a joy
same as beggar
are all scumbags
according to law
Happy households can't eat beautifully
Can not intermarry with good nationality
Can't even walk in the middle of the avenue
So she suffered cold eyes all her life
wandering everywhere
But she doesn't agree
Fighting all my life
the more humble
The more you can't lose your ambition
even if i want to change
There's no chance
My teacher
she loves to drink
drunk
she kept saying
I don't agree
I'm not convinced
that's what she is
So no matter if the world hates you, hates you and scolds you
One day you will prove to the world
You can be a decent person
I don't agree
I'm not convinced
I'm not convinced I'm not convinced
okay
Drink the medicine in a while
go to the kitchen and sleep
it's warm there
I'm in
you
I am sorry
I know it's wrong
elder sister
Don't you want to go to Siwansi?
we'll send it
thank you
Thanks for your hard work
Sister Yao treats people kindly
take care of us all
How good would it be if she served as a pawn?
let's go
Meng Shang food
I beg you
I beg you to promise me
Meng Shangshi, I beg you
I beg you
get up
Meng Shang food
you allowed me to cook
Do you have no self-respect?
really want to participate in the test
nature
I'm not like you
Not even a shadow
see you
what
you chased
just to look at him
nothing more
One is a high-ranking royal aristocrat
One is a little palace maid with her head down to wash the dishes
distance between you
It's farther than the Tianhe
Maybe it's not fate
That's not necessarily
Can't tell, we're doomed
My mother was ill
I went north to live in my ancestral home
I think it's too restrictive
just run away
Play with the girls of the tenant's house
His Majesty brought the imperial grandson to familiarize himself with farming
I had a chance to meet him
do not move
you see
get up
come for a drink
go fast
What are you saying it's not destiny?
Fool
You are grateful for the small favors of others
do you know him
In case you want to understand
you don't like it
Free at kisskh.me
So you have to get to know the man
know what kind of person he is
Is it worth your love
You are young and know a lot
From time immemorial
Naturally beautiful and talented
I can listen to more drama
forever old
forever and ever
May all lovers in the world be married
Zijin
what do you say
I said the world is only willing to sing the West Wing
But I forgot the legend of Yingying
Mr. Shang Shi is busy with official business.
really make me wait
prince
The palace gate is locked
How dare you enter the palace privately
adults misunderstood
Today I play chess with my father
I'm going to accompany him tomorrow
So I only have to stay in the palace tonight.
then you shouldn't be here
Please
Facing the savior
You are as cold as ice
Your biological daughter reunites after a long absence
also indifferent
On ingratitude and ruthlessness
you think second
No one dares to be the first
it's you
it's me
I sent someone to send the news to Su Yuehua
To reunite you mother and daughter
I'm still really struggling
why are you looking at me like that
Don't be too impressed
you want to threaten me
Have you really forgotten my life-saving grace?
let me go
go away
help
stop me
go away
wronged
adult
presumptuous
go away
my lord, I am a wronged lord
I'm the wronged adult to let go
let go
adult
wronged
let go
then
I just killed one
drunken sinner
You killed your husband's brother
But you know
I kill my relatives because I refuse to rape
I am innocent
Lun Jigang is always better than right and wrong
according to law is a death penalty
But you shouldn't die
Encounter with the world of amnesty
Just absolved you of the death penalty
Later you were abandoned from the clan
I'm extra kind again
Let you enter the palace as a maid
You can be a decent chef today
Shouldn't I be the first to thank you?
When entering the palace
I'm just a humble maid
It's all up to me to be where I am today
Besides, I also helped you
Even if there is a great kindness
There's always a day left
Believe it or not
I helped you
never thought of getting anything in return
When I saw you for the first time
so I
what to laugh at
prince
why don't i tell you
From the day I killed Su Feng
The former Meng Ziyun is already dead
me now
is a fatherless
No husband and no daughter
more ungrateful woman
I can help you one last time
Say it
do something for me
get out
His Royal Highness
Father
I just saw that you were in a hurry
Are your legs uncomfortable again?
I'll give you a click
Come
Daughter
Your Highness
You know that your father loves the king of Han
More than a day or two
Why do you have to suffer so much
During the second brother's stay in Beijing
The chariot and horse equipment used by the royal family for many times
and never returned to the fief
Ministers call for impeachment
The father heard the report
humiliating me for being obese
no relatives
I haven't seen the ministers for many days
Let alone instructing them to impeach Gao Xu
I know my father loves my second brother
But I am also his relative
close relative
Is it because
fat and thin
Your father's heart is so narrow
Your Highness
Your Highness is cautious
The grandfather of the emperor is too old
Everything must be according to his will
Can't contradict anywhere
The second uncle acts arbitrarily on the surface
But he fought with his grandfather for many years
Outstanding military exploits
It is necessary to prevent him from being pretentious and deliberately tempting
The father's difficulties, the son understands
But he was angry with his second uncle
It's better to go to the emperor's grandfather's side and offer the soup and medicine in person
To show the sincerity of a filial son
unspeakable resentment
Abandoned dry city
Okay
good son
I go out to catch my breath
Your Majesty let you think behind closed doors
where are you going
If the emperor put me in prison
you are the jailer
If you keep it, you will keep me for twenty-seven years
what's the matter
I now
Don't you even have the freedom to go out and take a breath?
jailer
Mother
leave first
go
Did you check it out?
Today, the King of Han did not enter the palace to defend himself
But after lunch, His Majesty suddenly became furious
Urgently ordered the prince to meet
lunch
These are all returned by the Qianqing Palace.
Yes
Your Majesty has not touched the lunch delivered today.
all back
this is
This is a dessert made by Meng Shangshi himself
In those days, Song Taizu attacked the Southern Tang Dynasty for a long time.
Anxiety, worry, not eating
fell ill in the barracks
Lucky to have a chef
Locally grown orange cake
Dessert made from walnuts
Only then did Song Taizu turn the corner
Since then, this dessert has made great achievements
called the Great Rescue
The slaves heard that when the war was going on
whenever the emperor is in danger
Han Wang disregarded his own safety
Rush into thousands of troops with fine horses to save them
Turned the tide of the battle many times
Therefore
Free at kisskh.me
Whenever the emperor sees this dessert
will recall the filial piety and merits of the Han king
back off
Yes
It seems that your food bureau is not very peaceful.
Thank you princess for your forgiveness
The slaves promised to help the King of Han
It is also expedient
I just wanted to find out what his plans were in Beijing.
Will it be detrimental to His Royal Highness