[English subtitles are available]
[ACE TROOPS]
[Episode 28]
Good one.
I've never seen that before.
We always think we're on top of the world
even if we've never seen the world.
As Deputy Commander Xiao said,
war is those who know how to fight fighting those who don't.
I don't believe that
the melee skill
of the foreign army
is higher than that of the forest battle.
We lost because
we've never seen it.
I agree.
We should really expand our horizons.
The military district has made it in time composing a special force.
Find sniper.
Finger bend,
like you're holding a cylindrical object in front of your eyes,
like in tough sight in the mirror.
Army Commander,
the foreign army instructor we invited,
is he good among
the special forces around the world?
He's a guest we invited.
I don't want to judge.
It's rude if I tell the truth,
and it makes me feel bad if I lie.
I understand.
What will a better one be like?
Special Operations is highly dependent
on learning from experiences.
The last thing you should do is
blind repetition at a low level.
Country M is not going to share their experience.
We'll have to explore it ourselves.
We start as elementary students
and elevate one step at a time.
This is the team job.
Your partner always checks in
the angle first.
If it's safe,
then the second partner goes in to check another angle.
Only when it's ready,
then you're following.
We always move in slow and quiet.
Safety's first.
Remember that.
You should always protect your partner.
Once he's dead,
everyone is dead.
If you couldn't find a way to go out,
you're not anywhere near windows or gates,
it's not a problem for the Special force.
Just make sure you're always…
find the hole!
Three,
two,
one.
Go! Go! Go! Go!
So, we're just getting on the field
for the special operation.
China is a big country,
so you should do better.
This is why we need
more excellent Chinese soldiers
just like you
to learn more and train more.
Yes.
It's originated from some
privileged British military officers
during the Second World War,
but what it needs more is
to have those who're not that talented
but push themselves onto their limits over and over,
and get over it,
turning the impossible into possible.
According to future operational needs,
the Special Operation Battalion of the military district is expanding.
Our third Reconnaissance Company
was transferred as a whole
to the newly-found Hong Kong Garrison.
They will station in Hong Kong in 1997.
We need to select an outstanding Company
to incorporate into the Special Operation Battalion.
Comrades,
we are here for the farewell ceremony
of our foreign army instructors.
Through this training,
you've for the first time opened your eyes
to see the world outside.
Special Operation
is a brand-new subject
to our military.
It's the extension of the most ancient
two elements in the spirit of soldiers:
valor and wisdom.
I believe that
you can complete such subject.
Let's express our gratitude
to our foreign friends!
[The Company of Live and Die Together]
[Zhangmu Station]
Alright, there's still time before the train arrives.
Don't just stand there like a tree.
Sit down for a while.
Picked them yourself?
Xiu likes them.
Some wild flowers aren't sincere enough.
So the wedding is gonna be held
in the hotel of your Regiment?
What, do you have some advice for me?
What advice?
It's your wedding, not mine.
We're just going to make some jokes
and give you a hard time.
The bad guy like you
must have a really hard time
to satisfy us.
Seriously,
don't make it too much,
Xiu may not be able to take it
if you go too far.
When I was a Sergeant,
I told Jiang Weixing
to give the Platoon Leader a hard time.
I regreted that so much
after what happened.
That's because I wasn't there.
If I were there, you wouldn't have had the chance.
I could have raised his roof off.
How's Xiaofei doing?
Kids
really grow fast.
Last year, I went home to visit my family,
he was like
this tall.
But he's so naughty.
He isn't like the Platoon Leader at all.
He's that tall.
Maybe some years later
when he's older,
we'll find a chance
to have a good talk with him.
Tell him
all about his father.
The train has arrived at Zhangmu Station.
-Xiu. -Please be careful of getting off the train.
Xiu. Here, give me that.
Hi, Gao.
Here, here.
Thank you.
Xiu.
You won't leave this time, right?
Where's Xiaofei?
Can…Can I drive for a while?
Look, Xiaofei.
The wheels are feet of the train.
Can you see me, big train?
Zhang Fei!
Ms. Xiu!
Can you hear me?
Xiu! Xiu!
Are you okay, Mom?
Why are you crying?
Ms. Xiu! Ms. Xiu!
Salute!
Hi, big train!
Look at me, big train!
[Love]
Look, Mom!
The bed is huge!
Get off it, Xiaofei.
Why are you on the bed with your shoes on?
Get off.
Come and get me.
You brat.
Get off.
No.
Xiu, it's OK. Just let him play.
The house is assigned to us specifically by regiment leaders.
It's not big. Please try to understand.
I think it's nice.
Li Shaobing really did a nice job.
Stop jumping.
Let me go!
I'll give you some privacy.
-Help me, Mom! -I'm taking him outside.
Let's go!
Let me go!
I'll go get you some fruit.
Come and get me!
[Love]
You can't get me!
Let me do it.
Xiaofei is naughty.
Comrade Gao must be tired.
He won't.
Gao is never tired.
Here, Xiu.
Take a seat.
Let me do it.
I got it.
Xiu,
my dad said that
he's not coming
to our wedding.
Is Uncle Gu
mad at me?
No way.
My dad likes you very much.
And he's happy to see
us getting married.
But this time…
Comrade Gu,
you don't have to comfort me.
It's my fault.
I know well
about my situation.
I just feel sorry
to make Uncle Gu unhappy.
Xiu,
the relationship between me and my dad
is unlike other father-son relationships.
Ours
is special.
Let me tell you a story.
My mom died when I was little,
and my dad tried to make me independent
since I was young.
I grew up in a boarding school,
so, the bond between my father and I
is different from that of others.
It's tacit,
but is never spoken.
It's like the dummy game.
Whoever talks first
loses the game.
And later,
we got used to such a way of communication.
It's quite enjoyable.
So this time,
he just wants me
to take care of this thing myself,
and then take you home.
Will you and Xiaofei
become such father and son?
To be honest,
I really don't know.
The road I'm going to take is in the army.
When I was a child,
I determined to become a soldier
and forever.
And I want to see
how far I can go as well.
I don't have the experience of being a dad at all.
I still need to learn.
You're good.
If Xiaofei can
be like you in the future,
I'll be satisfied.
And that's also what I'm worrying about.
People like me
are going to suffer a lot.
I don't want this to affect the kid.
Xiaofei and I,
are we holding you back?
Don't think that way.
Look,
Comrade Gu,
I know you're
good to me,
and I also understand that
I don't deserve you.
If it weren't for Fei boy,
we wouldn't have met.
We belong to two different worlds.
I didn't dare to expect
you to like me,
I only want to
repay your kindness.
I'll be nice to you,
and I want to do this as well.
I'll treat you well more than you think,
a lot more.
Don't worry.
If you get tired one day,
Xiaofei and I will leave immediately
and won't be a burden for you.
Are you done?
I can see why you feel anxious,
but I think you don't understand
why I want to be with you.
You said that I was comforting you,
but have you thought that
you're the one who's comforting me?
How's that possible?
I'll tell you one thing,
but you have to promise
you won't get mad.
You might have heard of it
that I was in a relationship with Nanzheng
when I first came to the army.
You two are such a good match.
I felt the same
at first.
But after a few years,
I started to think that I was wrong.
I was asked to be
a tough person when I was a kid.
I was fascinated by
the distant world that
could not be seen or touched.
I don't care about
the people around me.
I don't know how to take care of others.
And I thought Nanzheng was just like me
who only wants to go forward.
So we broke up.
But then I also wanted to change myself.
I want to be a person
who isn't just tough
and only thinks about
the distant world.
Then,
I met
you and Xiaofei.
Xiu,
I'm telling you the truth.
And I really think that
it's me that doesn't deserve you.
Don't talk about yourself like that.
You are a really good person.
Let me ask you a question.
Why do people get married?
They want to spend time with someone,
forever.
It requires strong determination,
deep affection,
and big courage
to do it.
Xiu,
thank you and Xiaofei
for giving me a home.
Are you saying
we give you a home,
and you are going to hand you over to us?
A real home.
Besides Xiaofei,
I am the most important person to you.
Yiye,
I am afraid that I'm too clumsy
to give you a good life.
But I'll try my best.
I will try to
make our life better.
A real man
is fully capable of building his own family
and taking good care of it with his heart.
[Love]
How was that?
Great!
Go,
ask your dad to bring me some water.
Hope they're done talking now.
He is not my dad.
What are you talking about?
He didn't give you life, but he get to raise you.
If you want to be my nominal father,
I can think about it.
Thanks, but no.
I'd rather have my own son.
I'm telling you,
from now on,
you should love your dad
as much as you love your mom, got it?
If you are naughty,
I'll beat you.
Got it?
Do you want to learn that move?
Yes.
Come here, try it.
One, two, go.
[Learn from Comrade Lei Feng. Mao Zedong]
[Love]
Everyone, please be quiet,
now we have our groom here
to give a speech.
Applause!
Great!
Come on.
Thank you all for coming.
I'm going to say something today.
I'm not
a good speaker.
I want to
say something to Xiu.
Xiu,
honestly, I feel quite ashamed.
It's a little bit late
for you to wear this bridal gown.
You had been waiting for
this day for five years.
Two years waiting for me
to finish my study,
and three years for
mourning
Mrs. Zhang.
You've been always
living for others.
But since today,
you are my wife.
It's my responsibility
and an honor for me
to make you
live a happy life.
I'll definitely do my best
to take care of you
and Xiaofei.
[Love]
I want to experience everything
holding your hands in mine.
Maybe it's going to be hard,
but I'll treasure it.
Bravo!
Nice!
Well,
where's Gao? I haven't seen him today.
He's on his way.
I'm late.
It's okay.
You're in time.
The school is strict.
It is hard to ask for a leave.
[Zhangmu station]
I was planning to give Xiu
a good dress up
and make her the most beautiful bride in the world.
What?
What about you?
Me?
When are you going to be my bride?
Stop kidding, we're running late.
Xiaofei,
you're eight today.
You can do arm wrestle with me now.
From today,
I'll take good care of you as my son,
and take the responsibility
a father should take.
I am not your son!
You are not my dad!
Xiaofei,
what are you talking about?
The Village Clerk told me that
my father was a combat hero.
He is the pride of the village.
My father is Zhang Fei.
Yes,
Xiaofei,
your father Zhang Fei
is our hero.
You should know it.
Where is he?
He sacrificed.
Gao.
He's old enough to know the truth.
Xiaofei,
you are a big boy,
right?
I'm not.
I slept with my mom last night.
Xiaofei,
we all
miss your father.
He is a hero.
He sacrificed himself
saving his mate,
and for people's peaceful life.
He is this country's hero,
and everyone's hero.
He's just gone
to another place.
Xiaofei,
this is your dad's military medal.
I'll find another time
and tell you all about
your dad Zhang Fei's heroic stories.
I believe,
at this moment,
Zhang Fei
is watching over us silently
from another world.
He will be happy
to see your mom
holding hands with Dad Gu.
Because
your mom
has found the new happiness.
Dad Gu
loves your mom very much, too.
[Bride]
For you and your mom,
he's reborn,
and made a lot of people reborn, too.
Xiaofei,
after you got your new dad,
your dad Zhang Fei
would also be very happy.
All your aunts and uncles here
are very happy, too.
Because we love you,
and we love your dad and mom very much.
We are telling your dad Zhang Fei
in this way
that we live and die together,
and we are never apart.
[Love]
Come,
tell us,
what's your name?
But,
I don't want to be Gu Xiaofei.
I want to be Zhang Xiaofei.
Then, Zhang Xiaofei it is.
It's a good name.
I'm Zhang Xiaofei.
“Zhang” is easier to write.
“Gu” has more strokes.
I don't want to be Gu Xiaofei.
Son,
you'll know how to write it soon.
Zhang Xiaofei,
maybe we can
talk about it later.
♫ When you leave ♫
♫ The sunlight is gone ♫
♫ The mountain breeze blows away ♫
♫ The enthusiasm in my mind ♫
♫ When you fall ♫
♫ The world is gone ♫
♫ My persistence is scattered ♫
[Love]
♫ On the ground ♫
♫ I miss the vows and legends ♫
♫ That you left quietly ♫
♫ And the immortal red flame in your eyes ♫
♫ Do you remember ♫
♫ The timidity falling like a meteor ♫
♫ The trembling that is as lonely as a wave ♫
♫ I still remember ♫
♫ The rivers that we crossed together ♫
♫ I still remember♫
♫ The songs we sang in tears ♫
♫ Do you remember ♫
Dad?
♫ The timidity falling like a meteor ♫
Xiaofei,
Xiu.
♫ Do you remember ♫
♫ The trembling that is as lonely as a wave ♫
Dad.
♫ I still remember ♫
Xiaofei, call him grandpa.
♫ The rivers that we crossed together ♫
Grandpa.
♫ I still remember♫
♫ The songs we sang in tears ♫
Good boy.
♫ Do you remember ♫
♫ The timidity falling like a meteor ♫
♫ The trembling that is as lonely as a wave ♫
♫ I still remember ♫
Gu Yiye really did it.
♫ The rivers that we crossed together ♫
He shines so bright as the people I love.
♫ I still remember ♫
♫ The songs we sang in tears ♫
He is extraordinary
but is not arrogant anymore.
He takes responsibility
and devotes himself sincerely.
♫ We are always together ♫
He is hard to himself
but is kind to others.
He is another kind of hero.
♫ We are never apart ♫
Having a comrade-in-arms like him
is the luck of my life.
I give them my blessings.
[A year later, 1995.]
[Certificate]
[Special Operation Battalion 2's Yearly Working Goal]
You are improving so fast.
I have to hurry up,
or I won't possibly catch up with you.
[Unachieved]
Nanzheng,
I've been transferred to the Special Operation Battalion of the military district
for three months.
I learned
what the real savageness is,
and what real desperation is in this team.
We are aiming at
the cruelest devil
in this world.
Those who dance with the devil
can't be angels.
Almost every day, I wake up
grateful
for being alive.
I'm grateful that my arms and legs
are still complete.
I'm grateful that I didn't give up.
Then,
I think of you.
It warms my heart all the time.
No matter how hard or cold it is,
I can always pull through.
Sometimes,
I think,
the reason for that
is because I have you in my life.
Lower your head.
Dear Gao Liang,
your team is the blade of the troop.
It is the true man among the men.
Also,
I concern this kind of you deeply.
I can't imagine
what savageness and desperation you said about are,
but I know that
they must be impasses one after another.
I love you growing in impasses,
because that kind of growth
is the charm that solely belongs to men
and solely belongs to soldiers.
I like this hormonal feeling.
I think this kind of love
is the only one in this world.
This feeling
hurts
but also brings happiness.
It makes me feel that
even though we are apart,
our hearts
still beat together.
Chief.
The meal is ready.
Here.
Take a seat.
Alright.
Here.
I'll make a toast to you.
Chief,
you are making me scared.
I've been with you for all these years,
and you didn't toast to me
when I got awarded in the war.
What's happening today?
You've been in the Special Operation Battalion for a year and a half, right?
Yes.
Counting this all-round-champion
in today's district's contest,
how many gold medals have you won?
12.
That's why I'm toasting to you.
Here.
Thank you, Chief.
Fill in.
Your cooking is great.
It's been 10 years,
and your cooking hasn't gone rusty at all.
It hasn't changed, right?
I can't forget the skills of cooking for you.
Let me have a taste.
This Meng big nose,
where does he surpass me?
He's not as good as me for training soldiers.
He's not as good as me for fighting in wars.
But that guy has one thing better than me.
His three sons are all married.
And me?
Why is this?
Chief,
when Zheng graduates,
we'll get married.
Stop bluffing.
Chief,
do you think
I can only
get gold medals on the training field?
Today,
I'm officially reporting to you.
Zheng and I,
our relationship,
has a rapid development
and deep growing.
Two letters a week.
She's thinking about me every day.
Did I agree to give my daughter to you?
Chief,
you encouraged me to do it before.
Why are you changing your mind
when I'm about to make it?
But,
why doesn't she tell me herself?
I have no information at all.
Does she still know I'm her dad?
Chief, you are not making any sense on this.
Zheng definitely didn't tell you
because she hasn't thought it through,
and she's not ready yet.
Zheng's your daughter,
don't you know her well?
Wait till she's ready.
When everything's all set,
she'll definitely tell you first.
That's more like it.
I'll tell you something.
The Artillery rapid reaction system experiment
of our district
had the first success.
Next, we need a breakthrough
on improving soldiers' and canons' coordination level.
To be frank,
that means when soldiers need
artillery support,
it can be ready whenever it is called.
About this,
Gu Yiye should be an expert.
He is called that
Armor Madman.
Let me finish.
The key here is the communication problem.
The headquarters prepared a plan,
trying to organize
a unified experiment contingent
to fully examine this system's
technology
and tactic performance.
They are planning on transferring a contingent
that has top training records from the Special Operation Battalion to corporate.
I think this mission
should be assigned to you.
Then how many days
will it take?
Days?
You won't be off the mission for less than 3 months.
That won't work.
Three months,
how will we catch up
what we miss on the training field?
Chief,
now every Special Operation Battalion in the army
is fixing their eyes on us like we are the target.
I'm telling you
Meng big nose's Army B
is working on this thing, too.
When the equipment is nearly set,
and the Army B gets a head start
in front of us Army A,
that's a big problem.
This is a great thing,
understand?
Chief,
I'm just
a small
cadre at battalion and company level.
I could barely manage the things in our squadron.
The things in the army
still need you to worry about.
Cut it out.
If you won't go, I'll dismiss you.
I really can't go.
The training comes first.
Are you nuts?
I forgot to tell you,
the deputy leader of the research group for that system
is Zheng.
Chief,
you
always told me
the collective interests are above
the individual interests.
I think this mission
has to be accomplished by me.
Report.
Come in.
Section Chief Zhao, come.
Sit.
Please.
Who's Shanwang One
examine group's leader?
The Deputy Section Chief Yang Ping from the Communication Section.
Communication Section is mainly responsible
for the developing and debugging the equipment,
and this mission
is focused mainly on
testing if the equipment is of use,
and of how much use
in the process of battle and training,
so, the keywords
are battle and training.
We should let
the training unit take charge.
Deputy Chief He,
what do you have in mind?
Let Xia Lin take charge.
He's from Regiment 720,
and is more familiar
with the situation there.
I don't think that's appropriate.
You still don't really
trust him?
Yes.
Since this mission is of great importance,
there's something
I have to make clear now.
I'm just talking about the business here.
Comrade Xia Lin,
his working style
is not really dependable to me.
When he was leading the grassroots troop,
he was always looking up to the leaders.
He cares too much about the benefits,
and he likes playing tricks.
That's why in the Red Arrow Exercise
he fell so hard.
I don't think it's a great idea
to hand him this important mission.
Chief Zhao,
you shouldn't use
the old vision to examine the problem.
As the old saying goes, a fall into the pit, a gain in your wit.
Don't you believe he can change?
He's the one.
That's settled.
Help.
Yes, sir.
Hurry up, hurry!
Welcome all the leaders to the Special Operation Battalion
to guide our work!
Welcome!
What kind of leaders are we?
The leader is beside me.
Leader, come on.
Welcome, welcome, welcome!
Welcome!
You must be exhausted.
Thank you so much.
Why is he here?
Be careful.
Captain Xia is really something.
I'm Captain Xia of the United Team.
Welcome, Captain Xia.
We sincerely welcome
the visiting of the United Team.
They are all experts and scholars.
Their visits are reasonable.
But Captain Xia, which unit are you in?
Who sent you here?
The army sent him here.
He's here on behalf of Army Headquarter.
Shut your mouth.
I said nothing wrong.
I was telling the truth.
Dear leaders, welcome to guide our work!
Welcome!
Hello, Captain Xia. I'm Commissar Jiang Weixing.
Hurry up, unpack your stuff.
Honestly,
that guy
is indeed
arrogant.
He's on behalf of the Army Headquarter.
Our attitude to him
implies our attitude toward the higher-ups.
The Validation Team is in charge of technical problems.
Which unit is Xia Lin in?
He's coming with them.
How can he be helping?
Gao,
you're wrong.
It's empiricism.
Empiricism
is one of the great inventions of mankind.
It improves the efficiency
of interpersonal interactions greatly.
No matter what he did in the past,
he's the Captain now.
We need to respect that.
This is basic awareness.
Niu's right.
From now on,
in the name of
Party Branch Secretary of the Squadron,
I remind you
to stop being judgmental.
Do well and cooperate with them.
By the way, your girlfriend
is in our team.
Watch it and control
your own emotions.
Understand?
Are you being bossy to me?
What? You don't like it?
Why don't I give you a lesson on political theories?
I'll teach you a lesson.
I'll teach you a lesson on how to fight the war of annihilation,
and how to hit on
the Head Nurse Tong Bing in the General Hospital.
Get out!
Don't rub it in.
Wait.
Just tell me how to fight
the war of annihilation.
Chunyu.
Hi there.
Let's have a meeting
an hour later
to reschedule
the plan.