Previously
on "The Good Doctor"...
Ethan: How hard can it be
to just act like
a normal human being?!
[ Grunts ]
No!
Stop petting
that stupid rabbit!
[ Thud ]
We're never
going home again.
We have each other,
and that's all we need.
Shaun: My brother went to heaven
in front of my eyes.
Steve: Never forget,
you're the smart one.
And I'm proud of you,
Shaun.
[ Television playing ]
[ Knocking on door ]
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Knocking continues ]
Kevin: Dad?
Hey!
Hey! [ Laughs ]
I missed you, too!
Oh, Penny, come.
Stay.
Hey, Dad.
Sorry it's so early.
I just landed.
Actually,
you're a bit late.
Five weeks.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I-I-It's a long story, okay?
But h-how was it?
It was
your mother's funeral.
Dad, I'm --
[ Exhales sharply ]
Okay.
Well, um,
you have my cell number.
It only works
if you answer it.
[ Sighs ]
[ Thumping, glass shattering ]
Dad?
Dad?!
[ Wheezing ]
Dad!
Hey, hey!
Hey -- you okay?
You okay?
You can't breathe?!
No? Okay.
Hold on, I'm gonna call
for help, okay?
911? My dad collapsed!
He can't -- he can't breathe,
please hurry!
Just hold on, Dad!
[ Indistinct P.A. announcement ]
Good morning, everyone!
Right on time.
What, did you sleep here
or use
a teleportation device?
I used
a teleportation device.
[ Laughs ]
Nonsensical questions
usually imply sarcasm,
which I've found people
often answer sarcastically.
Good one.
Trauma wants a consult
on a 66-year-old male
who collapsed
from severe anaphylaxis,
complicated
by respiratory arrest.
His son just got back
from Thailand.
Almost immediately, the father
had his allergic reaction.
Merrill: [ Groaning ]
Patient has
a few allergies --
pollen, mold, shellfish --
but no corresponding allergens
were in evidence.
Why are we doing a
surgical consult on an allergy?
Well, we're not.
We're doing a consult
on the excruciating
abdominal pain he now has.
[ Groaning loudly ]
As you may have heard.
Mr. Wilks, hi,
I'm Dr. Neil Melendez.
Heard you had
some abdominal pain.
**
-- Captions by VITAC --
The guy
was in some serious pain --
10 milligrams
of morphine worth.
Test results show
elevated lipase,
amylase,
pancreatic enzymes.
Pancreas is enlarged.
Could be pancreatitis,
maybe alcohol-induced.
The son said he smelled alcohol
on his father
at 6:00 in the morning.
And anaphylaxis has been known
to precipitate
attacks of pancreatitis.
Guess that's it, then.
Meaning
you totally disagree.
Not everyone who starts
their day off with a Mimosa
fries their pancreas.
Your eyesight must a
hell of a lot better than mine.
Because I can't see
the entire pancreas
due to the overlying
bowel gas.
We'll order an abdominal CT
and take a better look.
There you go.
Where the hell is Murphy?
It's a severe fracture,
but I don't think
you'll need pins.
Young bones tend to heal
very well.
Young Bones? Isn't that
a "Star Trek: Origins"
graphic novel?
I'm not sure.
No, that was a joke.
Where are your parents?
They're coming.
They both work in the city,
so it's a long drive
for them.
I was on
a school field trip,
and I tripped
over my own feet.
Of course, it was
right in front of Shelby Lomar.
At least
it was pretty gross,
so I got some sympathy points
for that.
I would expect this
to have been caused
by a more serious
accident.
Nope, just a trip.
I do that a lot.
What can I say?
I'm clumsy.
Yes. Now follow my finger.
**
You have
some nystagmus --
an involuntary eye movement.
So what's that mean?
When you fell,
did you hit your head?
No.
What, you think I have
brain damage?
Nystagmus can be a sign
of a neurological issue.
Oh.
Well, that would explain
the "C" I got
in social studies.
That was another joke,
wasn't it?
Mm.
I'm going to order
a head CT for you.
Go for it.
Shaun,
are you getting any sleep?
Yes.
Really?
I mean,
really getting sleep?
I got here on time.
Well, that's good.
I used
a teleportation device.
**
Radiology form, please.
Shaun, that boy,
he looks like --
Steve.
He does.
Is he related?
His name is Evan Gallico,
so I don't think so.
Wow. That is uncanny.
Just coincidental.
He looks
exactly like your brother.
No, he doesn't.
His hair is shorter.
It freaks me out.
It doesn't freak you out?
No.
It's okay if it does --
No, he's not Steve.
Steve's dead.
"I used a teleportation device"
was a joke.
Yeah,
that's...that's good.
[ Indistinct P.A. announcement ]
Kevin: So, I couldn't come
to Mom's funeral
because I fell in love.
She was another teacher
at the school.
A Thai woman.
And she was kind
and --
and beautiful
and loving...
and very, very sick.
She had
a congenital heart defect.
Look, if you don't want
to tell me where you've been
for the last six months,
then don't.
It's your business.
But don't insult
my intelligence.
Well, I couldn't
just leave her.
You couldn't leave her
for five minutes
to make a phone call?
[ Knocking on door ]
This a bad time?
No, come in.
According to the CT,
you have a lesion
on your pancreas.
Well, what do you think
this lesion could be?
Not sure.
That's why we need
to biopsy it.
It could
just be a benign cyst.
Or...?
Or...
it could be cancer,
right?
We'll know soon enough.
**
This won't take long.
Evan: I know.
I've had two of these.
One more
and I get my Scout badge.
[ Chuckles ]
That was funny.
Tough to tell
without looking at you,
but I'm guessing
that was sarcasm.
No. I have autism,
which makes it hard
for me to read social cues.
Jokes are difficult.
I used to know a kid
with autism. Peter.
He was kind of weird
but super nice.
Used to know?
You don't know him
anymore?
He died.
Hit by a car.
You know anyone
who died?
My brother.
That sucks.
Why did you have
the other CT scans?
My parents have...
uh, what's the word
for fear of getting sick?
Hypochondriasis?
Mm, no, worse than that.
They have...nosophobia.
I love that word.
What do you think
of Miss Gannett?
She's nice.
I think
she's callipygian.
She's what?
Callipygian?
It means "having
shapely buttocks," Shaun.
Duh.
You read the dictionary.
What it lacks in plot,
it makes up for in vocab.
So, you married?
Girlfriend?
Boyfriend?
Tropical fish?
I like Lea.
Ooh. And who's Lea?
Lea is a friend.
A friend you date?
A friend with benefits?
I lend her batteries
sometimes.
I like
where this is going...
[ Machine beeps ]
So, you know,
keep going.
'Cause if you don't,
I will.
It's kind of my thing,
you know?
Just constant talking --
annoys everyone.
Murphy.
Well,
I guess not everyone.
Hey.
My family's pretty
used to me now. I mean...
Hey.
[ Button clicks, beeps ]
...my friends are
very talkative as well, so...
You're giving
the fractured arm a head CT?
Yes.
Get back
to the pancreas.
He's not clumsy.
He has a brain tumor
behind the inner ear.
Forget the pancreas.
Mr. and Mrs. Gallico?
Hi.
I'm Dr. Shaun Murphy.
I'm treating your son.
Well, how is he?
We were told
it was a bad break,
but it should heal
no problem.
I know why Evan tripped.
He had a tumor
in the temporal bone
behind his left ear,
which is affecting
his balance.
I've arranged for a consult
with Dr. Najid in oncology
and she's going --
No, that won't be necessary.
We --
We already have
an oncologist.
[ Sighs ]
Evan's been diagnosed
with stage four osteosarcoma.
He was complaining
of a sore shin.
The last thing that we expected
was bone cancer.
The doctors at SFM,
they gave him
a year to live.
That was seven months ago.
Osteosarcoma explains
the severity of his fracture --
he will need pins in his arm
after all.
Uh, can we see him?
Yes. He's in room 414.
Uh, Dr. Murphy?
He doesn't know
about his diagnosis.
We would really like
to keep it that way.
**
He's the patient.
Doesn't he have the right
to know the truth?
Well, no.
He's also a minor,
so, no, he doesn't.
Evan's
very intelligent --
he'd be able
to handle it.
Well, Shaun,
maybe it's not just about Evan.
Maybe it's about his parents,
as well.
Maybe it's just too difficult
for them to tell Evan right now.
I don't know.
Then they're the ones
who shouldn't be told.
Well, let me ask you this,
Shaun --
what's so wrong
about Evan being allowed
to enjoy as much of his life
as possible?
Evan wants to know
the truth.
How do you know that?
If this were Steve,
if this were your brother,
would he want to know
the truth?
Is that what this is?
Dad's such a tool.
I found
my birthday present --
in their closet,
right where they always hide it.
I was just about
to open it
when Dad caught me snooping
and freaked out.
I hate
all that phony surprise stuff.
It's an
AquaBlast Water Cannon.
I was with Mom
when she bought it.
Thank you, Shaun.
Your honesty's refreshing!
Yes, he would want to know
the truth.
Well, there's nothing
we can do about it.
It's not your decision --
it's theirs.
He's their son.
**
[ Door beeps ]
[ Sighs ]
**
Claire, I need you.
Sure, what's up?
I need someone
to lie for me.
Okay...
I'm flattered?
Hey, doc?
There's something
I need to tell my dad.
We haven't moved him.
He's still in room, uh, 326.
Do you have
a medical question for me?
Is he dying?
We don't know yet.
The biopsy
will tell us more.
Okay.
My dad is a good guy.
We've just never been
on the same page, you know?
My mother was the one
that I could talk to --
same for him.
So, without her,
we're both pretty useless.
Room 326.
Right.
**
Dr. Murphy called me in
for a second opinion.
Um, you need some pins
in your arm.
Why?
What's changed?
Well, after studying
the radiology report,
given how bad
the break is,
we just think it would be
a prudent step
to ensure an efficient and
thorough mending to the break.
Will I be able
to play baseball again?
Well, I don't see why not,
once it's completely healed,
after some physiotherapy.
How long
before I can pitch?
It's hard to say.
[ Monitor beeping ]
He wanted someone to lie
for him.
[ Scoffs ]
And he picked you.
Merrill's son asked
for personal advice.
And he picked you.
I know, right?
[ Scoffs ]
He's lying to his dad
about something.
Yeah? What?
I don't know.
You didn't ask?
It didn't seem relevant,
medically.
You know it's not that difficult
to be a human being.
Just tell him
to "come clean,"
"honesty
is the best policy,"
"a lie is a stone
in your heart."
Who said the last one?
Me.
I made it up.
Hmm.
[ Chuckles ]
And...I got it.
[ Beeping quickens ]
He's anaphylactic.
Would you get me an epi?
I'm coming out.
The throat's constricting.
Pull the tube.
[ Gasping ]
[ Saw whirring ]
[ Whirring stops ]
So, what's up
with "Dr. Browne"?
She's Lea, isn't she?
Claire is my colleague.
Oh, come on, I saw the way
you were looking at her.
How?
I don't think
I look like that.
Okay, so then why'd you
call her in for a "consult"?
Mm...
Okay.
Yes, she's better at talking
to people than I am.
Wow. I counted
like 50 tells there.
You really suck
at lying.
I know.
Too bad.
It's an important social skill.
So how do you know
when to lie?
When people
need to know things,
they need to know.
If they don't,
lie through your teeth
and feel good about it.
What if they need
to know the truth,
but it'll hurt them?
Some can handle it,
some can't.
So how do you know
who can and who can't?
You tell the truth.
If they like you after,
then you'll know.
If they don't?
Then it doesn't really matter
anyway.
You have cancer.
[ Sighs ]
Yeah, I know.
My parents took me in
for a sore leg.
After a whole bunch
of tests,
they talked
to the doctor,
then came out
and told me I was fine.
That's it.
Just "fine."
The next day,
they bought me a PS4.
So I Googled my symptoms,
and I narrowed it down
to osteosarcoma
or growing pains.
Kids don't get gaming systems
for growing pains.
Hey, it's okay.
I'm not afraid to die.
You're not?
Well, I mean,
the dying part will suck
if it hurts, but...
I'm not afraid
about the actual death part.
Because you believe
you're going to Heaven?
Because I don't.
If I believe in Heaven,
then I got to believe
in God,
God made me sick.
How messed up is that?
It's just easier to think
that it's all random
and when it's over,
it's just...
over.
So what about Lea?
Where'd you guys meet?
In the hallway.
That's a beautiful story.
Yes.
She's my neighbor.
Convenient.
He had
another allergic reaction.
The pancreas?
Merrill Wilks, yeah.
And the second attack
was even more severe
than the first.
It coincided with biopsying
the pancreatic lesion,
which now appears
was a cyst.
Well, now we know
he's allergic
to whatever's
in that cyst.
We also that
the next cyst that pops
will probably kill him.
Well, if there is a next.
Let's run a couple tests,
see if there's any evidence
of parasites.
And MRI his entire body --
if we're lucky,
he only had the two cysts
and he can go home.
Are you looking
for loopholes?
Hoping to save Evan?
Everyone makes mistakes.
Which means you should
double-check
every file
in the hospital.
The oncologist flagged
his neutrophil count of 634
as low.
That is low.
Low normal.
I can still hear
the word "low" in there.
Mm.
He's just a kid.
I know how hard it is
to think of him dying.
He's okay with that.
I find that
hard to believe.
We all die --
if we accepted that,
we'd be happier.
Maybe. But we're not good
with contentment.
Fighting death
is what keeps us alive.
[ Computer beeps ]
**
Okay.
We got a hit --
Echinococcus.
Jared: Echinococcus?
The cysts are filled
with tapeworms?
Cysts?
There are more?
Three more?
Four more.
You missed the one
in his brain.
**
[ Knocking on door ]
Jared: Dr. Glassman?
Yeah?
You used to be a neurosurgeon,
right?
So they say.
Take this, will you?
I need one.
Who would you recommend?
What you got?
Wow, that's cool.
How the hell did I get tapeworms
in my head?
No idea, but you do.
You can pick up the eggs
from coyotes or wolves.
You been hanging around
coyotes or wolves?
I live
in the suburbs --
we don't even have
a petting zoo.
You might've had these cysts
for quite some time.
When one of them burst,
that's what caused
the first allergic reaction.
Well, why did it burst?
Why did it burst?
Any sudden movements, twists,
turns, squeeze.
A hug?
Could be.
But you weren't there
for the second one.
I punctured the cyst
on your pancreas
during the biopsy.
As you've seen,
allergic reactions get worse
each time they happen.
So a third one,
that would be bad.
That would be...
[ Chuckles ]
That would be very bad.
So we're gonna have
to surgically remove
all the cysts intact.
Dr. Glassman's
one of the most highly acclaimed
neurosurgeons
in the state.
You are very lucky
to have him.
And Dr. Kalu is fast becoming
a very accomplished flatterer.
The cranial cyst,
that is a big deal.
We're gonna have to take off
the top of your skull.
You'd be digging in
to my brain?
Well, yeah, pretty much.
With saline.
We use it to gently displace
the cyst,
and then, poof,
it magically pops out.
Kind of like
delivering a baby.
You know,
if childbirth were painless.
And then we move on
to the other cysts.
Hey, we're gonna take
good care of you.
**
Evan doesn't have cancer.
* Cowards cowering in concrete
showers in Rikers Island *
* Victims, we the wolves
that's wilding *
* We often smilin'
at sights of violence *
* Acting brave and courageous
* Ain't advantageous
for health and safety *
* So when we say
"run the jewels" *
It might not be cancer!
* And that goes
for a guy or lady *
It might not be cancer!
[ Music stops ]
Look at you on time --
two for two.
It might not be cancer.
Fractured arm?
Yes.
You said he'd been diagnosed
with stage four osteosarcoma.
Evan was diagnosed with the flu
eight months ago,
but his symptoms were actually
a better fit
with Epstein-Barr virus,
which is linked to
Langerhans cell histiocytosis,
which causes
osteolytic lesions
in the long bones
of the upper limbs.
And those lesions
could be misdiagnosed
as signs
of osteosarcoma.
Yes.
What about
his brain tumor?
Langerhans can also manifest
in the skull.
Instead of
a death sentence,
he could have something
that could easily
be treated
with prednisone?
Next, we need to do
a bone-marrow aspiration
to confirm.
I assume
you've looked at his file.
For a very long time.
Well, there must've been
a biopsy.
What did
the pathology report say?
Yes.
There were two biopsies.
Both were positive
for osteosarcoma.
Murphy...
They could be
false positives.
Do you have any idea
how unlikely it is
to have
two false positives?
0.3%.
Which we can comfortably
round off to "not likely."
It is possible --
Yes, but it means telling
the parents of a dying child
that there's hope,
when really there isn't.
Grab a shower
and get ready for rounds.
Glassman:
Wow. [ Chuckles ]
Imaginative and creative.
Yes.
What are the chances
you're right?
0.3%.
330 to 1.
333 to 1.
You really think
that it's worth
putting Evan's parents
through all this?
Of course.
If we did this
333 times,
we'd be giving false hope
to 332 people
for approximately
four hours,
and we'd save one life.
Isn't that worth it?
[ Exhales sharply ]
Anyway, Dr. Melendez
won't let me
ask for consent to test.
What if I don't tell them
what I'm doing?
A blatant ethics violation --
that's your solution?
Yes.
How do I do that?
[ Scoffs ]
Well, uh, [chuckles],
you do it
and then don't tell anyone.
No one.
If anyone asks...
your attending noticed
a low RBC count
and needed to find
the cause --
that's it --
no biggie.
Hmm.
**
[ Coughs ]
You know Wilks' Grocery
on Santa Clara 17th?
It's been an institution
for nearly 60 years.
My grandparents
started it in 1958,
and my wife and I took it over
in '82.
But when my wife got sick
and I started talking to Kevin
about taking it over,
he just...took off.
To him,
it was just a place
to sell lettuce
and toilet paper.
My father chairs a real-estate
development company in the U.K.
Thought I'd be
the perfect person
to set up
the U.S. office.
You wanted to be in
the "helping profession," hmm?
I wanted to be
in my profession.
It's not about how small
or how big the venture is,
it's about doing something
that's yours.
I guess.
When he was little,
we were inseparable.
[ Chuckles ]
Ah, he used to love
to come to the store to "work."
[ Laughs ]
I even had a little apron
made for him --
had his name on it, too.
Still, you know,
kids...
grow up.
I'm just grateful that he stayed
close to his mother.
He could talk to her,
tell her anything.
[ Voice breaking ]
So could I.
And when she went...
[ Sobs ]
...I lost them both.
Looks like he's back now.
All I know is he ditched me
when I needed him.
Well, you know,
as a wise person once said,
"holding a grudge is a stone
in your heart."
[ Sighs deeply ]
What's that for?
Local anaesthetic
for a bone-marrow aspiration.
Why do I need
a bone-marrow aspiration?
My attending saw
a low RBC count
and wants
to find the cause --
no biggie.
"No biggie"?
You're lying.
What's going on?
You already told me
I have terminal cancer,
what's worse than that?
You might not.
It might not be
osteosarcoma --
might be
Langerhans cell histiocytosis,
which is treatable.
Treatable?
As in,
I might not die?
That's why
I need to aspirate --
to find out for sure.
Do my parents know?
Mm...I was told not
to get their hopes up.
Then let's do it
before they get back.
Roll onto your side.
**
Is there a Scout badge
for aspirations?
[ Chuckles ]
I think someone
just made a joke.
Hello.
What are you doing?
Painkiller.
My arm hurts.
That wouldn't explain
why I'd be injecting
your lumbar region.
Okay. Yes, hello.
I think Evan may have been
misdiagnosed with cancer.
I think he has something
that creates bone lesions
that look like
osteosarcoma.
It's a small chance, 0.3%,
but I --
You -- You told Evan
that he has cancer?
And now
you are telling him -- and us --
that he doesn't?
I'm telling you
he might not.
That's why I need
to perform this aspiration.
He says whatever I have
might be treatable.
Are you insane?
No. I am not insane.
I thought you'd be happy.
There is a significant link
between
Langerhans cell histiocytosis
and --
Go! Get out!
[ Coughing ]
Let me get you some water.
[ Coughing continues ]
[ Breathing sharply ]
-Oh, my God!
-Hands right here --
-[ Coughing ]
-Right here!
Respiratory, stat!
**
He has a massive embolus,
probably thrown
from his fracture.
It's located
at the bifurcation
of the pulmonary arteries.
He's close
to hemodynamic collapse.
Yeah, no kidding.
I'd like to assist.
Not a chance.
Okay.
I'd like to assist.
You're obviously
too close to the case.
I think I'm just
the right amount of close.
Murphy,
you lied to the parents
just so you could try
to prove your ridiculous theory.
You're too damn close.
Saddle embolism,
scrub in.
**
Melendez: We have to get rid of
the embolus before he arrests.
His heart
is barely pumping blood.
I can feel
the pulmonary artery...
I just need to find
the obstruction...there!
I got it.
Knife.
EKG is showing
right heart strain.
He can't take this
much longer.
I know, but if I move
any quicker,
I could nick
the left main artery
and kill the boy.
**
The phrase "no biggie"
gave me away.
You really got to learn
how to lie, Shaun.
Am I in trouble?
Yes.
Unless you're right.
If I'm wrong,
they shouldn't be upset.
They know
it's highly unlikely.
False hope, Shaun...
it's just plain cruel.
**
Hey.
He talk to you?
Did you talk to him?
I don't know
what to tell him.
You love your father,
don't you?
Yeah, of course.
Right. Well, he's about to go
in for brain surgery.
There's huge risks involved.
Whatever this lie is,
can you live
the rest of your life
knowing you kept it
from him?
My -- My girlfriend
wasn't sick.
Okay? She dumped me.
She's married
with two kids --
had no intention
of leaving them.
I-I was an idiot.
You got your heart broken,
that's the problem here?
No -- no, Dad.
The problem is...
[ Sighs ]
I didn't run away
to Thailand
because I thought
Wilks' Grocery was beneath me.
I was afraid
that I would never be able
to fill your shoes...
And then
I proved myself right.
**
Left pulmonary artery's
open.
Ring Forceps.
**
Come on.
Got it.
[ Exhales softly ]
EKG is normalizing.
He's okay.
Nice job.
All right,
flush the left pulmonary artery
and close him up.
Okay.
**
Um...Dr. Melendez...
Take a look at this.
**
Recycling --
Shaun, very responsible.
It's a book.
I appreciate that.
[ Chuckles ]
Thanks, Shaun.
[ Door opens ]
Melendez:
We got the embolism.
He's in recovery
and he's doing fine.
But while we were
in there,
we did find
something else.
Lesions on his ribs.
Irrefutable proof
of osteosarcoma.
It's metastasized
to his chest cavity.
I'm sorry.
[ Sighs ]
[ Sniffles ]
[ Sobbing ]
I'm very sorry.
**
Glassman: Give that
a nice, warm saline bath.
Forceps and Taylor scissors,
please.
Thank you.
**
Look at that.
That's what built
the pyramids,
painted the Mona Lisa,
invented the Internet.
[ Exhales sharply ]
There is our interloper.
Squeezeball please,
Deidre.
Squeezeball?
His name for it,
not ours.
The saline gently displaces
the cyst
and coaxes it out
of its little hiding place --
Hopefully in one piece
so we don't have to call 911.
Come on, now...
Tray, please.
There we go...
A little bit more...
And there we go.
Got it.
[ Exhales ]
He has his father's eyes.
That was incredible.
One down,
three to go...
**
Hey.
There he is.
Hi, Sweetie.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
We're just happy
you did so great.
You had
what's called an embolism.
It clogged an artery
in your lungs.
But the good news
is they got it.
And you're gonna be
just fine.
Still...
too bad
about the cancer, huh?
No, no, no, no.
The doctor did not know
what he was talking about --
Dad, I know all about it.
I have for a long time.
[ Inhales deeply ]
I --
I am so sorry.
It's okay.
[ Sniffling ]
**
Because I'm not
gonna be alone.
Grandma's gonna be there,
too.
Auntie Arlene.
Uncle Jim, if he figured out
how to stop swearing.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Clears throat ]
I'll get you some water,
buddy.
**
So, I took Penny
for a walk --
just around the block.
And I picked her up
some of those rawhide treats,
you know...
the ones that Mom
used to like to give to her.
[ Voice breaking ]
I miss her, Dad.
**
Evan: Coast is clear?
Yes.
Thank you.
Mm, I was wrong.
You tried.
I was wrong.
Your parents hate me.
I know.
I gave you false hope.
Yeah.
But for a minute there,
it was pretty awesome.
I'm going to ask you
for a favor.
Well, I'm not giving away
my Make-A-Wish.
Mm, would you mind
if I read you something?
It's not long.
That I can do.
"Atticus was right.
One time he said
you never really know a man
until you stand in his shoes
and walk around in them.
Just standing
on the Radley porch was enough.
The streetlights were fuzzy
from the fine rain
that was falling"...
**
* I can't protect you
from the course of life *
* But you know me
and you know I was born to try *
* It's just the symptom
of a middle-aged attack *
..."'Atticus,
he was real nice.'
His hands
were under my chin,
pulling up the cover,
tucking it around me.
'Most people are, Scout,
when you finally see them.'
He turned out the light
and went into Jem's room.
He would be there
all night,
and he would be there when Jem
waked up in the morning."
**
Sounds like a good book.
Could've used a spoiler alert,
though.
**
Thank you.
* Confusing you,
from what you need *
* Every hand that you hold
* It comes back
That's all.
* Every word, every ride
* It comes back every time
**
* Every time