♪I want to get closer♪
♪I walk lightly♪
♪Yet accidentally♪
♪Walk into your trap of love♪
♪Oh no, no, no♪
♪You cannot simply confess
your love when you are drunk♪
=Campus Ace=
=Episode 17=
(Meet by chance)
You're up.
What is this?
"This is my Crabapple Award.
Don't touch it."
This is your beloved Crabapple Award.
Momo.
Come on.
Trophy.
-I have...
-Let's go back to our dorm.
I have a speech for the award.
Momo.
Listen to me.
Thank you for presenting Crabapple Award
to me.
It's been my goal all along.
I want to thank my father.
I want to thank my mother.
-I want to thank my hometown fellows
-Come down.
for educating me.
Come down.
Thank you.
Also,
I want to thank my best friend.
Han Xiao'ai.
Let's go.
-No. No.
-Let's go.
One more thing.
The last one.
On this day of national celebration,
I want to present a song.
"Tonight Is Unforgettable".
Let's go. Okay?
Let me sing.
♪Tonight♪
You sing.
♪Is unforgettable♪
♪Tonight is Unforgettable♪
-Don't snatch it.
-Come on. Let's go.
This is my trophy.
My trophy.
See you.
This is embarrassing.
Xiao'ai.
Momo.
Is this necessary?
Don't call my name.
I suppose I won't
be recognised like this.
I'm troubled
by the exam.
Tang Momo!
I'm coming.
Are you kidding me?
What happened?
Why has she become
like this after one night?
Yao.
Did you do something to her?
Why did she turn around
as soon as she saw you?
Is it because of you?
Did you upset her?
Have you gotten an idea
for starting a business?
We're gossiping.
Don't get serious.
You want to gossip, right?
I heard that
a few days ago,
you went to be the model once again
for Han Xiao'ai's drawing class.
You and Han Xiao'ai...
Get serious.
What matters the most
for starting a business?
People,
money
and creativity.
But we have neither money nor people.
Not even creativity.
How to get started?
I can
get the money.
As the president
of the computer club in school,
I have some fans.
Therefore,
I can
find people.
What about creativity?
Creativity.
It matters the most
for starting a business.
Quality of creativity
determines the success
of entrepreneurship.
Creativity and entrepreneurship
are closely connected and inseparable.
Let's go.
Then we should...
I haven't finished talking.
Why are you leaving?
What are you drawing?
You smile cheerfully.
Han Xiao'ai.
Could you be drawing
pubescent comic again?
Let me see.
Give it to me.
No.
So Hua is...
It's just a casual drawing.
Tang Momo.
Let's go.
They are here.
Xiao'ai.
In regard to application creativity,
I've done market research.
I suggest
a mobile application on fashion.
Fashion blogger?
You may take it like that.
But we'll do
an application that can smartly
provide dressing solutions to users.
Users may upload pictures
of their own clothes
and make their personal wardrobe.
Provide different
dressing suggestions to users
based on different
occasions and ambience.
To make profits,
we may collaborate with some
fashion brands.
You may go through it.
We can't stay in the school anymore.
We meet too often.
It's said
that if we meet by chance
thrice a day,
that's our fateful encounter.
Don't believe in superstition.
Why don't we
go and buy some materials?
All of the sudden?
We can't fall in love.
We should build our career.
Let's go.
What's the matter?
Ling Yao?
Thrice.
Further back.
More.
Okay.
There.
How do you get a permit
to take photos in this coffee shop?
Qian Duoduo of the class next door
is working here as a part-timer.
I asked for her help.
It's enough with these photos.
No.
Change another pose.
Smile.
How should I pose it?
I don't know.
Cut the nonsense.
We have no money to hire a model.
This is our only way.
Smile.
Put your hand down.
You should bend instead.
To the left.
This side?
Yes.
More.
More?
Wait.
You...
Why are you here?
We meet by chance.
Do me a favour.
Come with me.
So this is a fateful encounter.
Mr. Tan.
Just like what I've said earlier,
our application
doesn't only invite fashion brands
but also
professional image stylist.
She can mix and match different styles
based on different requests of users.
The same clothes
probably produce only a certain style
on the official website.
However,
our stylist
can mix and match countless
possibilities for users.
Furthermore,
our application
can also let customers
try mixing and matching freely.
♪I always picture it in my mind♪
It sounds good.
Launch it as soon as possible.
Come to my company
on next Monday.
We'll talk about the details.
-It's nice working with you.
-Me too.
♪Shall I continue to pursue
this dazzling dream?♪
♪I always♪
Why?
Are you still avoiding me?
Me?
No.
♪The colour of this world♪
Really?
♪You love bumping into her♪
♪On every sunny day♪
♪Approach gently♪
♪My letter of love confession♪
♪I chat shyly with her♪
♪While avoiding her gaze♪
♪I predict our destiny♪
♪We are not lovers yet♪