[English subtitles are available]
[Love Unexpected]
[Episode 16]
[Hai Bo Bookstore]
[The new issue of the comic is out.]
[When can you bring it to me?]
[Sister Lu hasn't come yet today.]
[However,]
[she found out
that I was messaging you yesterday]
[and threatened to confiscate my phone.]
[Brother,]
[do you want to buy me
a mobile phone first as backup?]
[I don't think it's safe to
use my old phone anymore.]
[If my phone…]
You're sending messages
to Liu Ruo Chen again?
I just want you to be Brother Ruo Chen.
You're still young,
but you already know how to ship couples.
What if you have grown up?
What does shipping couples mean?
Let me delete Liu Ruo Chen's phone number
so that you can't send
messages to him anymore.
[Delete contact? Liu Ruo Chen]
[One contact has been deleted]
Deleted.
The latest comic book,
here.
Hurry up and finish your homework.
[Brother Ruo Chen]
Luckily, I have jotted it down.
Feel free to delete it.
Who is here so early?
Liu Ruo Chen?
Good morning.
Why are you here?
I'm here to send you flowers.
Where are the flowers?
What are you planting?
You will know after it blooms.
But I already have
enough flowers in my yard.
But this is different.
This is the flower that
symbolises our friendship.
So, it's different.
You really don't have to do this.
As long as the matter of
Gao Ru Wen is not resolved,
I can't feel at ease.
I understand.
But it doesn't stop us
from being friends, right?
[We don't even know
where Gao Ru Wen is now.]
[After the matter of Yu Li Qing,]
[it's impossible for us
to make friends with him.]
[But I can't let him
do anything to hurt people.]
[What should I do?]
[She's missing someone again.]
[Let me call Brother Ruo Chen.]
Hello.
Hello, Brother Ruo Chen.
Sister Lu is in a bad state today.
I think
she still has you in mind.
[You should take the initiative
to care about her.]
I will only displease her if I
take the initiative to find her now.
In fact, I do not know what I do poorly.
She said the better I treat her,
the more burdened she is.
This is so strange.
It is true that girls are
difficult to understand.
You're a girl too.
I still young,
it's different.
Then, what should you do?
I don't know too.
Just give her some time.
[You can't give her a chance.]
We need to use some tactics
while she still likes you.
You said she likes me?
Why are you so surprised?
You should have confidence in yourself.
[How about this?]
[I will arrange an offline event for you.]
[You two can meet again.]
[Maybe she will be soft-hearted,]
[or make her feel a sense of crisis.]
It sounds like it makes sense.
Then,
what exactly is the offline event?
I'll keep it a secret for now.
Anyway, call all your friends to join us.
The more people we have, the merrier.
Alright.
[She still has to work tomorrow.]
[What should I do?]
Hello, Qin Yang.
[Hello, Ruo Chen. What's the matter?]
What are your plans for tomorrow?
I will have to carry out
the Hall effect experiment tomorrow.
[Don't stay at home everyday.]
[Hang out with me.]
Wait a moment.
Take
Yi…
Take Yi Xiao with you.
Why should I take her with me?
[A sense of crisis.]
[I can create it if there is none.]
Can somebody tell me
what is love all about?
Don't touch me.
Do you have to be like this?
I just asked you to
clean up the kitchen today.
You've been depressed all day.
What are you not satisfied with?
Say it.
Are you going to say it?
If you don't want to say it,
I will leave then.
Faded.
Your love for me
has faded.
I worked so hard to clean up
the kitchen today.
But…
But I'm not even rewarded.
Isn't that what you're supposed to do?
And you're asking for a reward?
Why?
Do I no longer deserve to be rewarded?
Madam Li Ya Xi,
I'm not even worthy of
encouragement in your mind now?
Gosh.
Mr. Lu Fen Jin,
what do you want as a reward?
At least it must be that kind of
suffocating
embrace.
Otherwise, I will surely
have insomnia tonight.
Okay.
Let me give you a hug.
Can you two stop
being flirty in front of me?
I'm still a kid.
Why are you here?
Have you finished your homework?
I have.
If you have finished it,
why don't you do some reading?
I want to discuss something with you.
What is it?
Say it.
Can you give me a break for tomorrow?
A break?
Why should I give you a break for a day?
Because I have a
very important thing to do.
Lu Fan Fan,
what could be more important
than your studies now?
It's about Sister Lu.
Sister,
If you're in a bad mood,
you don't have to sweep the floor anymore.
Let me help you.
You're almost done sweeping anyway.
I'm not in a bad mood.
Lu,
haven't you and Liu reconciled yet?
Do you feel better when you keep yourself
so busy every day?
That's true.
I'm not in a bad mood.
I can take care of my own business.
You
don't have to worry about me.
Silly girl.
We can tell by your looks.
You've been
forcing a smile these days.
There's a good saying.
When there's someone for you to rely on,
you're still a kid
no matter how old you are.
When there's no one for you to rely on,
you're an adult
no matter how young you are.
Here
is your home.
You are always a kid in this home.
At first,
I was
really not
feeling sad.
But now you say so,
I feel that
I am still quite aggrieved.
Silly girl.
Cry out if you want to.
Can somebody tell me
what is love all about?
What time is it now?
You're still expressing
your feelings here?
I just lamented a little.
Right,
the weather
is very good these days.
I'll let you off tomorrow.
You can hang out
with Fan Fan.
Yeah.
You will still get paid.
This is such a great offer.
Say yes now.
Thank you, aunt.
A real Counter-Strike game?
This is what you said about
taking me for a break?
Yes.
What is more relieving
than beating people
when you fall out of love?
It makes sense.
Besides,
I heard that this
Counter-Strike store is different.
If you win,
you can get a
mysterious number of the city.
Just call this number
and you'll get
all the answers you want.
I heard that Uncle Xiang
got the mysterious number of the city
after winning the game
and later won the lottery.
It's already 2012.
you still believe in this?
Just have a try.
Don't you have any questions
you want to ask?
[If I really had a question to ask,]
[it would be about
my future with Liu Ruo Chen.]
Hi.
We want to register.
Two people?
It's enough to have both of us.
We can shoot all the enemies.
If you have only two people,
the number of participants is not enough.
How about this?
Or
I'll see if there are other participants
and help you team up later.
Alright.
Thank you.
Okay.
[They are coming.]
It's Brother Ruo Chen!
Lu!
What happened?
I sprained my ankle.
Here.
Sit down.
You are here to play
the real Counter-Strike game,
how can you wear high heels?
Look.
Luckily, I brought flat shoes.
[How could Liu Ruo Chen]
[get together with Yi Xiao so quickly?]
[Bad guy.]
Fan Fan,
you're here too?
Do you want to be on our team?
Sure.
It's fine.
Thank you.
What was she
gesturing there?
She asked us
to follow her.
She will help us.
Did you tip them off?
It's not me.
Let's go team up.
Let's go.
[Lucky box]
Dear participants,
since there are only five of you now,
so
I'm joining you
for a three-to-three battle.
I don't want to play.
Since you're already here,
let's play one round.
Just one round.
So, have you decided?
Yes,
we will join.
How about you?
Little girl,
you draw first.
[This girl]
[is so beautiful.]
I'm in the blue team.
You are in the red team.
[Red team]
Brother Ruo Chen is in the red team too.
I'm in the red team too.
Ruo Chen,
have you forgotten
that my ankle still hurts?
You have to protect me later.
Protect Fan Fan too
because we are girls.
Don't count me in.
I'm not that weak.
I will protect you two.
I'm leaving first.
Walk behind me.
My shooting skills are good.
I can play as a forward.
Why do I have to walk behind you?
Yes.
Fan Fan's shooting skills are so good.
Let her go to the front
and we can walk behind her slowly.
Strategically,
those with poor shooting skills
should be in front.
You cover me
and I will shoot.
Just now, you said you would protect me.
Now, you want me to be shot.
Forget it.
My ankle is still in pain.
I won't be your burden.
I'm going to watch at the side.
Yi Xiao.
Now, it's just the two of us.
How are we going to fight
Trust me.
Even if it's just the two of us,
we can still win.
Let's go.
This is so tiring.
I even have to play
Counter-Strike game with them.
Fan Fan.
Two o'clock.
Cover me.
Ruo Chen,
you sneaked up on me!
Brother Ruo Chen,
you shot me!
That's my instinctive response.
Fan Fan!
Ruo Chen.
Shoot!
Liu Ruo Chen,
what are you doing?
That's my instinctive response.
That was a very precise shot.
It was just okay.
I'll help you up first
You…
Didn't you say
you wanted to keep a distance from me?
Can you let me go?
We won!
Won already?
This Counter-Strike game
is not as difficult as
I thought it would be.
I think
this gift is the
shared reward of our team.
The three of us should share it together.
I play the game just to relax.
Don't count me in.
I'll
settle the score with you later.
I'm leaving.
Sister!
Take this.
I don't want.
Thank you.
I'll go clean up first.
-Bye.
Do you guys think
she noticed something?
I think
we overacted a little bit.
What?
You asked me to be affectionate with you
to see if Fan Fan will be jealous?
No, I can't.
Please help me.
Consider it a favour for your friend.
Fan Fan is my friend too.
I don't want to care about you.
I really can't think of any other way.
Please be kind.
This can be considered a white lie, right?
You'd better not do it, Ruo Chen.
I am also afraid that
Fan Fan will get angry.
Alright.
You guys just watch me grow old alone.
Okay.
I will help you.
I will help you just once.
Just once.
Could she have made up her mind
to leave me?
Don't worry.
I'm here.
You?
You're going to pretend that you like me
to make Fan Fan jealous?
I don't want to, even if you do.
I mean,
we are here.
We are on your side.
Cheer up.
Liu Ruo Chen and others
have gotten the number
at the Counter-Strike store.
But they gave it to others.
Got it.
Just say what's on your mind.
I would like to know
the function of that number.
Why do they all wish to get that number?
It's not everyone is willing
to achieve something through hard work.
I am only
taking advantage of their weaknesses.
Starting from today,
keep an eye on their movements,
especially Lu Fan Fan.
You have to report to me
every move she makes.
Why her?
[Stay tuned for the post-credits scene!]
Our coffee is here.
♫ Gently put a star in your hand ♫
♫ Carefully measure our distance ♫
♫ If you use an expression
that I can never forget in my life ♫
Don't think too much.
I just want you to be happy.
♫ And walk into that downpour
in the centre of the world ♫
♫ I will wait behind you with
an umbrella for the rain to stop ♫
♫ When the sky clears, I'll give you ♫
♫ This box of secrets ♫