♪Following the way she walked through♪
♪He searches for every piece
of memory that he had with her♪
♪An unexpected encounter in the crowds♪
♪Was the start of their destined journey♪
♪No one can tell the end of the story♪
♪Since every heart is overloaded♪
♪The dream about blooming
flowers is illusionary♪
♪Painful yet addictive♪
♪Love is too wild to be reined♪
♪Too deep to be forgot♪
♪The pain will forever
stay with the scar on the chest♪
♪He wants to linger in his dream♪
=Tears In Heaven=
=Episode 10=
Miss Du is my schoolmate in college.
We haven't had much contact
since graduation.
I didn't expect that
we can meet in this place.
Miss Du is working in Boyuan.
Xinsheng is now cooperating with Yutian.
Small world.
Isn't it?
So, Mr. Lin and Miss Du were schoolmates.
This is called a meeting of old friends.
Mr. Lei, let's go back.
Don't keep the guests waiting.
Yuzheng,
what brought you here?
To meet someone for dinner
with Mr. Lin.
Boyuan is having a dinner party today?
Nope.
I'm dealing with some customers.
So I called Xiaosu over here
to come and help me.
Yuzheng,
I'm doing this for the sake of
the Group's performance.
That's why I'm working so hard.
Shouldn't you think about
how to reward me?
If you want to increase your salary,
that's easy.
But I'm afraid you despise that money.
That's not what I meant.
I mean...
Xiaosu, why are you still here?
Mr. Wei and others are
waiting for your toast.
Yuzheng, you don't even know
how cunning they are.
They seem to be very prudent,
and not willing to sign the contract.
You are not tolerant to alcohol,
so don't drink too much.
If you drink too much,
no one can carry you back.
I knew you would care for me.
Don't worry, Yuzheng.
It's our responsibility to be here.
Right, Xiaosu?
I'll go in first then.
Mr. Lei, let's go back.
Thank you very much for
the hospitality, Miss Jiang!
Thank you for coming here, Mr. Wei.
Miss Du is a good drinker.
Thank you, Mr. Wei.
Nice to work with you.
See you.
Miss Jiang, see you.
Xiaosu, how will you go back home?
Do you need a ride?
No, thanks, Miss Jiang.
I'll just take a taxi myself.
OK, I'll let you be.
Miss, shall I call you a cab?
No, I want to walk by myself.
OK.
♪The pain brings out
the weakness inside♪
♪Sometimes it's better
not to nail the white lie♪
♪Love and pain keep
wandering between us♪
♪Can't find a way out♪
♪I want to turn back the time♪
♪Would it change anything then?♪
What on this street
is so attracting to you to wander alone?
Mr. Lei!
Are you sleepwalking?
You are so funny.
I just want to
walk down the street by myself.
Aren't you afraid of
encountering some bad guy
at this dark night?
Me?
It's hard to say.
Maybe you'll run into a greedy one.
In the dark night like this,
anyone is OK.
And then,
he will put you into a woven bag
and drown you in the Huangpu River.
It's scary to even think about it.
Get in the car. I will give you a ride.
Didn't you hear me?
You are not afraid of being
put into a woven bag
and drowned in the Huangpu river?
And then,
you will disappear forever.
Here's the only chance.
Fasten your seatbelt.
It seems that Miss Du
drank a lot today.
Not too much, just a little.
A little.
Enjoy all the pleasure in your life.
And never leave your
wine cup empty under the moonlight.
It seems
you are upset.
Why are you laughing?
You know what?
You are really annoying.
Really?
I'm not surprised.
Don't you want to know why?
Tell me about it.
Are you feeling particularly
good about yourself?
It makes sense.
Look at you.
Growing up in a wealthy family.
Highly educated and handsome.
It is natural to feel superior.
But,
don't you think this self-righteousness
and your proudness
are really annoying?
It feels like
you are going to tell
the truth after drinking.
That's the beauty of alcohol.
You always wrap yourself in a shell.
It looks good on the surface.
But inside,
you are an extremely insecure person.
Miss Du,
I advise you not to speculate
on other people's minds.
What makes you think that
you know me so well?
How could I?
By my intuition.
Do you know what it's like to
be stuck in a swamp?
Struggling only makes you fall
deeper and deeper.
Pray for someone to come to rescue you.
Bullshit!
No one can save you.
There is never anyone in this world
that cares about other people's
sorrow and pity.
Looks like my previous judgement
on you was right.
You are a heartless person.
You cannot feel any pain.
Your heart
is like a cold stone.
Fine.
I'll take that sarcasm from you
as a compliment.
But I'm not like you,
drowning in your own misery every day.
Maybe.
Xiaosu!
Not again!
(He Qunfei)
He Qunfei,
what's wrong with your boss?
Since Xiaosu entered your company,
she has never been home
during normal time.
Devil indeed.
Is that excessive for her?
She did that for work.
The competition in Boyuan is so fierce.
All she can do is to keep going.
You know all the reasoning!
How come I didn't see you
being more active?
Why don't you make some extra money?
How come you didn't do the hard
work and hustle of others?
Damn it!
Awake?
Why didn't you wake me up?
Thank you for the ride.
I drank a little too much today.
I talked too much.
Just take it as a joke
and forget it.
It seems that you come back
from the alcohol.
Sometimes it's good
to listen to your true thoughts.
It is hard to hear someone
speak out the truth.
It's great.
Goodbye, Mr. Lei.
Miss Du,
actually, I've always had a question.
What exactly made you
break up with Zhenrong so suddenly?
It's because you fall in love
with someone else
or is it that you have secret troubles?
It's all about destiny.
You must have heard of it, right?
For us,
the only way to be free
is to let it go.
But who can really let it go?
Yuzheng.
Hello, Mr. Lei.
Fanlv.
Miss Du.
The elevator is here.
Mr. Lei, your special
elevator is over there.
Can't I get on this elevator?
Fanlv,
didn't you just get off that elevator?
Where are you going?
I left my car key in the office.
I'll go and take it.
Aren't you coming in?
I'm that scary?
When I come, you can't even
get on the elevator.
Yuzheng, look at this.
As soon as dinner was over yesterday,
Mr. Wei asked his secretary to
send me the contract.
How is that?
I put all the efforts into your matters.
Good job, Fanlv.
We all know that Mr. Wei
is a tough nut to crack.
You just started the company's business.
Very good. Keep going.
With your words, it's worth the efforts.
Oh,
why did you leave without me yesterday?
You didn't say anything to me,
so I was worried.
I dropped someone off last night.
I was home too late,
so I didn't contact you.
Who was so honored
to have that opportunity?
Du Xiaosu, were you OK last night?
Me?
I am fine.
No way.
The one you sent yesterday was Xiaosu?
I saw Du Xiaosu walking along the street
last night.
Just gave her a ride.
I see.
Du Xiaosu,
you dawdled there yesterday
for a long time.
You were waiting for his ride.
No, it's not like that.
Just a coincidence.
Coincidence?
Shanghai is so big, and there
are thousands of streets.
How did you get so lucky
and come across with Yuzheng?
Sorry, Mr. Lei.
Fanlv,
the elevator was angry after your talk.
Du Xiaosu,
you were
planning something on Yuzheng,
weren't you?
No wonder.
Yuzheng always takes care of you.
How could I ignore
there is such an outstanding girl
right by me?
Enough, Fanlv.
I got a few calls last night.
All from
the owners of some investment companies.
The situation is better than I thought.
They are all interested in the
Entertainment Center project.
All want to participate.
You think this is good?
Is it not?
Yutian has difficulties in cash flow.
The project always fails to start.
We're all looking forward to A round
financing.
It's OK now.
Our trouble
will be fixed easily.
I don't think so.
Things that don't seem risky
are inherently the biggest risk.
Mr. Lei,
caution is good.
But I have to remind you
water from afar cannot
put out a fire nearby.
With my knowledge of Yutian's
financial situation,
I know it's not good.
If strategic investors are on board,
we will reduce the debt ratio of Yutian,
and get the Entertainment Center
project to start.
Isn't it beneficial for both sides?
Here.
Give me two days.
I'll think carefully about
what Mr. Lin said.
Mr. Lei, caution is necessary.
But there are some things that
need to be decided as soon as possible
to avoid some extra accidents.
Hi, Mr. Lin.
Enjoying some fresh air,
in the back garden.
Ting,
you've just got better
and now you start to walk around.
What's going on?
You don't want to admit you are not
a young boy?
Come.
Have a seat.
Ting,
health matters.
We can't compete with the young.
Well,
how is it going with the
Entertainment Center project?
Everything is fine.
Under Yuzheng's overall control,
it will be OK.
It's just...
Just?
Recently,
my assistant Lin
complained something to me.
The cooperation plan he prepared
was not approved by Yuzheng.
I wonder what he is hesitating about.
Yutian and Xinsheng
have entered an agreement
in cooperation.
Keep moving
is the right thing to do.
What do you think?
There's no need to worry about.
I'll handle it.
Thank you.
-Look forward to working with you!
-Nice to work with you!
Fighting!
I am leaving.
Bye.
Yuzheng,
come and have tea with me.
Dad, you forgot what doctor said.
You cannot drink tea.
You dare to teach your old man?
Take a seat.
I have something to say to you.
How are you and Fanlv recently?
Dad!
You know that
I treat her like my little sister.
Why do you and Uncle Jiang
have to do this to me?
You are making me embarrassed.
Fanlv matches you perfectly.
Isn't she beautiful or clever?
I think
she's the perfect woman for
your marriage.
I'll decide it now.
Dad!
You don't have to talk tough with me.
I'm not afraid of harsh words.
You...
Best friends,
business partners,
growing together since young,
these are not reasons.
Besides,
I just took over the company.
The Entertainment Center project
is complicated.
It makes me feel headache.
What do you mean by that?
Uncle Jiang
told me yesterday
that everything is fine.
How come it becomes
complicated in your words?
Dad, I'm telling the truth.
I've been checking the company's
financial reports for a while.
The revenue seems to be
growing gradually.
But the corporate
debt is not optimistic.
There is also redundancy issue.
That's a warning sign.
Carry these two bombs
to start a huge project like this.
What do you think
is the chance of winning?
I see what you mean.
Next you will say...
Dad, you're old and confused.
Dad, business is business.
With an attitude like this,
we can't talk any more.
I think you are being emotional.
I know you well.
You talked about so many things,
just to make me get
married as soon as possible.
Ancient people said
no matter how much food you own,
you only need a small part for a meal.
No matter how large is your house,
you only need one bed for a rest.
That's it.
Dad had a favorable life.
It is worth it.
If anything happens to me,
I'm not regretful.
You have been independent
since you were a child.
And even a little withdrawn.
The reason why you don't want
to get married
must be about me and your mother.
What do you mention her for?
I already forgot her.
Yuzheng,
actually,
your mom...
You can't blame her for all the things.
It was my fault too.
Or even worse.
Dad!
Do you have anything else to talk about?
Yuzheng.
Enough. I don't have mom.
It's only you, Dad.
For me,
she's dead already.
Miss Du,
I've credited your card
with this paycheck.
Please have a check.
Transaction completed.
Please remove the card.
Yuzheng,
the reason why you don't want
to get married
must be about me and your mother.
I already forgot her.
Actually,
your mom...
You can't blame her for all the things.
It was my fault too.
Or even worse.
I can't live like this anymore.
I want a divorce.
Get out!
Mom, mom!
Mom, don't leave.
I beg you to stay.
Mom!
Uncle Duan!
Mom, don't leave me.
Yuzheng!
I beg you to stay.
Mom, don't leave me.
Xiaosu, whose cake is this?
Whose birthday is it?
Zhenrong's birthday is tomorrow.
I'm going to see him.
This is the first birthday you
celebrate for him, right?
He used to celebrate my birthday.
Love between you two
in the present society
is really a fairy tale love story.
Siqi,
if I were you,
I will cherish He Qunfei.
You don't know how much I envy you.
How could it be?
The hard life I had with him.
I don't know if I can take it myself.
I actually want to have a relaxed life
without any stress.
Oh,
how's the money thing going?
Plus the money from last time,
in total,
it's less than one fifth.
Am I right?
That is
a mission impossible.
Lei Yuzheng is torturing you with it.
You're the only one who believes in it.
Fine. No one is blaming you.
The most important thing is
that we are happy.
Listening.
Mr. Lei, all your schedules today
are cancelled as planned.
But the other side just informed me
their CEO temporarily changed his plan.
The flight has arrived Shanghai.
Do you think...
Send them my apologies.
Tell them I'm not available today.
I will talk to their CEO
privately later.
That's it.
(Beloved son Shao Zhenrong
By Shao Kaixuan 1989-2016)
Zhenrong,
today is your birthday.
I came to see you.
Do you still remember this pudding?
It was my birthday.
I forgot it myself.
How are you doing over there?
I remember
the day you left me
was a rainy night.
I never expected
that was the last time
we both saw each other in our lives.
I didn't even have the time
to say goodbye to you.
And you left me forever.
If time could be turned backwards,
or if the gods
would give me another chance,
I would have never
agreed to Aunt Shao's request.
That's the grudge between them.
It should not be repaid by us.
I feel regretful.
I regret deeply.
Why didn't I insist?
Why gave up on you so easily?
But don't worry.
I'm having a good time.
Just a little busy.
Once I stop,
I will be thinking about you
all the time.
It seems that you never left me.
You just went to a place
that I cannot see, waiting for me.
Zhenrong, I'm too tired.
I don't think I can hold out any more.
Do you remember our apartment?
You said you wanted to design it well.
Put up white curtains.
Grow lots of flowers on the balcony.
We would get a puppy.
But now,
I may actually have to give up.
Will you forgive me?
Take care of yourself.
Me too.
Live well.
If you miss me,
meet me in my dream.
Goodbye.
Zhenrong.
Letting go is a very difficult decision.
During this time,
for the purpose of this engagement,
I give it all I've got,
but still in vain.
I love Zhenrong, and I can live
without the apartment,
because Zhenrong
never left me alone.
Come in.
Mr. Lei.
Have a seat.
Mr. Lei,
about the thirty-day bet,
I admit defeat.
Why?
I admit it.
This is my resignation letter.
Miss Du, you are a woman of your word,
very cool.
It's not due yet.
I remember you said
you will never give up.
I overestimated myself.
So, you mean
you give up the apartment?
Yes.
Miss Du, you can think like that,
you must have cleared your mind.
I'm going to leave here,
to start over.
I'm not surprised at
your decision,
because that is your style.
Since you have made up your mind,
I wish you good luck in the future.
By the way,
where are you going?
I used to love this city very much.
Because in this city,
I have my beloved one.
But now for me,
every place is the same.
Mr. Lei.
Farewell!
Miss Du,
hold on a second.
As usual，
your resignation should
go to Director Ning,
not me.
But it's OK.
I'll take a look at it for him first.
Siqi and Qunfei,
I have presented my resignation today.
Du Xiaosu, what's wrong with you?
What happened?
Today,
I admitted defeat.
What do you mean?
The bet she made with your boss,
saying that the apartment will be
paid off within thirty days.
Or she will leave.
Forget it. I am really tired.
No matter how hard I tried,
I could not make it.
Xiaosu, I think
we need to think more about this.
I know about Mr. Lei.
He's not a bad person.
Maybe he just wants
to make you feel frustrated.
You can apologize to him.
And that's it.
Look,
you can stay quiet.
Tomorrow, let me probe for you.
Who is it?
Hello, your delivery.
OK. Please sign here.
Thank you.
What is it?
Du Xiaosu, your package.
Wait.
Is this the apartment of Yiping?
So, it was sent by Lei Yuzheng?
He returned it to you.
No way.
(Resignation)
How could it not be?
See? Is this your resignation letter?
It seems that Lei Yuzheng
not only returns the apartment to you,
but also wants you to go back to Boyuan.
Told you! Mr. Lei is a kind-hearted man.
He won't care too much about
a little guy like you.
Now that we got the key,
let's check out the apartment.
Slow down!
Slow down.
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in
pain and delight♪
♪Will that day of that year♪
♪start over again?♪
♪Who else will stay awake like you do?♪
♪Between us♪
♪is the time of unknown length♪
♪As well as the tangle in
pain and delight♪
♪Your love weeps for a withered soul♪
♪That teardrop of sadness
brings extreme beauty♪
♪Indulged in the black
whirlpool of your eyes♪
♪Dreams have never been this quiet♪