Why is it so late
Meng Shang Shi
Recipe canon meal
Make an inventory
Meng Shang Shi
You this
How can you be confused
Why is it still called Lord Shang Shi
Let me count it with you
Vegetables delivered today
It doesn't seem very fresh
The food delivered is not fresh
How did Aunt Meng forget
You used to say it yourself
Fresh vegetables
It takes less than an hour from picking to cooking
Sometimes it comes in a hurry
The dew hasn't dried yet
But you see
Sorry
Excuse me, you are affected
Go back and change to another car and come back
Wen Dian Shan this
Don't cut it
Walk, walk
Wen Dianshan bullied Aunt Meng again
Don't go
I'll take this
Meng Shang eats such a woman with such a mind
Why do others need sympathy and pity
Let's work hard
Let me do it
White has a pair of eyes
So regardless of honor or inferiority
Let's go
Moon flower
Next time I meet Meng Shangshi
Don't be so rude
Hu Sishan is now in charge of Shangshi Bureau
It's only a matter of time before you get promoted to still eat
Why care about unrelated people
Miss Yao, you're here
Please wait a moment
Yes
I'll wait
Lord Yang
Your Highness is still deliberating
Is there any way for the household department
I don't know
Where did your highness get the news
Royal Guards reported it
Royal Guards Vocational College Guard
Local disasters don't seem to be their concern
Listen to everything
If they hadn't interviewed the people's feelings,
The household department doesn't know when to hide it
Or Hejian Prefecture deliberately concealed it
This
If you don't wake up,
I kissed
Your Highness
Handmaiden Lost Manners
Your Highness, please forgive me
There are so many places where you lose your sight
First, I fell asleep halfway through the meal delivery
Second, it is too overstepping
I'm so tired that I hug you myself
Anyway, I don't forgive
Bearer
Pull out the staff and blame twenty
Your Highness
Be afraid
See clearly
This is the way the master treats the handmaiden
Raise one's head
Handmaiden dare not
Put your head up
I order you to look up immediately
Like
Why did you fall asleep just now
Handmaiden
Tell the truth
In order to prepare for the New Year's Eve banquet,
The handmaiden didn't sleep a wink for four days
This is true of the whole food bureau
So hard
Let's transfer you to the study
No
Handmaiden daring
Your Highness, please allow the handmaiden
Stay in Shangshi Bureau
Good
Unless you promise me one thing
From now on
Don't talk about your handmaiden and handmaiden
And you told me
Why do you like cooking so much
Your Highness
My mother had high expectations of me when I was young
Always ask the master to teach strictly
Can't remember the piano score
That's going to be beaten
At that time
The kitchen is the only one for me
Where you can avoid rattan
Because the place is small
Duoduo porcelain
It is inconvenient to swing the rattan
During this time in Shangshi Bureau,
Is the easiest thing in my life
The happiest time
Over there
Get the recognition of others for the first time
I also found the meaning of my own existence
Your Highness
Let this time last a little longer
I thought
Your happiest time is in the study
It seems that I think too much
Your Highness
That's totally different
Your Highness, when dealing with government affairs,
When leading the troops to fight,
Is it another kind of satisfaction
And carefree
Good
Give me a caress
Yes
You guys wait here
Your Highness clearly refused to allow musicians to enter the study
Who is playing the piano here
This is the piano score written by His Highness himself
Originally only half
The other half
Your Highness said that without the state of mind at that time,
I didn't expect it to be renewed today
Screen drawing
Go and find out who is in the study
I want to see her
Right
Know who is so bold
You can't be lenient
Hu Shang Shi
Zi Jin
Have you finished sorting out the list of medicinal diets in the past dynasties
Yes
It can be finished tomorrow
What is this doing
On that day, Tai Sun Fei happened to be at the banquet
I tasted the meal made by Zihao
Tell her to make snacks and send them over
To make such delicious food
She must be a woman with a bright mind
Can you play chess
Yao palm meal
I invite you here today
Actually it is
Tai Sun Fei
Please
I'm losing again
Come and play chess with me when you are free in the future
Xie Tai Sun Fei
Handmaiden leaves first
Screen drawing
You said this Yao girl
What kind of person is it
This handmaiden can't tell
So kind and kind
I'm not a man
It will also give birth to closeness
What's more, the emperor and grandson
Tai Sun Fei
Do you really want her to serve your highness
Now someone can make your highness happy
Is to atone for my sins
Read me that poem again
Big Brother
Not that you used to say
You don't have to weigh your words in reading
As long as you understand the great sense of justice
I don't have to take a fame test
The desert is lonely and smoky
Long river falling yen
Three-year-olds can recite it
Look at you
A few words are wrong
It's solitary smoke, not smoke from kitchen chimneys
It's sunset, not steamed bun
Big Brother
I draw the sunset
You see
There is still glow here
Zhu Zhanyan
You're going to piss me off
Hurry up, hurry up
Come on, come on, keep up
Emperor
His Royal Highness Emperor Taisun
Grandpa Emperor
Today is the Shangyuan Festival
Ministers are waiting for you to visit Long Live Mountain
Why did you come here alone
The emperor is not in Ganqing Palace
Everyone is looking around the Forbidden City
Why only you know where I am
This war horse followed Grandpa Huang for more than ten years
I heard that he is ill today
Presumably, Grandpa Huang will come to visit in person
It's not sick
Is old
Grandpa Emperor
Remember the Dragon Boat Festival banquet that year
You hit the ball and shoot willow
Force the pack
Ministers, foreign emissaries were amazed
I also made a pair
Wanfang Yubo Fengyunhui
Grandchildren still remember that the lower couplet is
Unify the mountains and rivers, the sun and the moon
What a unified mountain and river, the sun and the moon are bright
There is such heroic spirit at the age of fourteen
Brush next
Zhan Ji
After the festival
Get out of the palace and do me a job
Everybody be careful
Quickly
Zi Jin
Nine-story archway lights were erected in Ganqing Palace
It's tall and beautiful
Let's go see it
Go quickly
I'm not going
You don't like it
Qiongyuan also has acrobatics and illusion performances
There is also a bow of Qiyun Society
It's lively
The Crown Princess finally gave everyone a day off
Don't you stay here
Ziping, I really won't go
Go, go, go
It's lively
Let's go. Let's go
Let's join in the fun, too
Don't do it yet
Let's do it tomorrow
Don't worry about this first
Let's go let's go
Let's go let's go let's go
There will be more people later
Hurry up, hurry up
Hurry up and join us
Moon flower
Princess Han died unfortunately
Stop blaming yourself
Master
I didn't kill anyone
I didn't
Master knows
None of this is your fault
I really didn't kill anyone
I didn't kill anyone
Master knows
Master knows that
Give it to me give it to me
This way
Into
Good
Come again and again
Go on, go on, go on
Attachment prevention point
Over there over there
To
Come and give it to me
One past this way
Good
Attachment prevention point
Come again
Come and follow
How awesome
To continue
None of them are useful
You play with me
Pass it over, pass it over
Purple Azolla
The Crown Princess had a word first
Regardless of identity on the court
Just on winning or losing
Wu Cairen, she has a charming temper
You go on stage and let her
Remember
I'm calling you. Come here quickly
Go
Go ahead
Give it to me
Watch out for her
Miss Yao
Have you seen Empress Zhuang Fei
Empress Zhuang Fei
To
She
I looked everywhere
There is no figure
Could you help me find it
Don't say anything
Yes
Then
This way this way this way
Stop her
Come on
Catch
Continue
Come here
Quick, quick, quick
Guard against her
Come again and again
Empress Zhuang Fei
Today's Shangyuan Festival
I
Empress
Kim is looking for you everywhere
Thank you very much
I'm here
Empress Zhuang Fei
Empress
Madam
This way, please
Then let's go and have a look
Watch your step
What did you do wrong
The one just now
It's Mrs. Peng Chengbo, the mother of the Crown Princess
Being the most strict
If she bumps into her
You sneaked out to join in the fun
You must be severely punished
Lord You
Today, the female official has a day off
Permission to come out to see the celebration
But why is Lord You here
As a royal eagle dog,
What's the errand
It's more important than staying by the emperor's sickbed
Everyone in the palace
Crying Zhuang Fei
And you
A female official covered in secrets
Every word and deed is recorded in the book
So
Don't make mistakes
Your Excellency
Can you and I know each other before
Of course not
What are you doing standing there
Don't go yet
Attachment prevention point
Guard against her
Prevent
Come again and again
Come
Quickly
Here, here, here
Pass it over
Here here
Here
Stop her
You sit
Then
Come again and again
This way this way
There are illusion performers in the square over there
Why don't Taisunfei accompany me to have a look
Go ahead
Pay attention to defense
Then I'll have a look, too
Less company
Give it to me
Come here
She is a gentle and kind child
Mother, why do you have to
In the world
Who would be better than the girl I picked myself
You've all met her
Even the emperor himself promised the marriage
Everybody knows
She is the real great grandson
Who knows your majesty listens to the alchemist
Go back on one's word
I changed this woman
Married for so long
Have never given birth to children
Return good fortune
She is an unlucky woman at all
Far less than
Mother
Go
Come and give it to me in the back
Come again and again
Go
Your Highness
The holy man invites you to watch the lights on the tower
You disappeared in a blink of an eye
Let the Holy One know that it is time to punish you again
Your Highness
Today is the Lantern Festival
The ladies-in-waiting all went to see the lights
Miss Yao must not have come
You see
What did I say
Didn't come
Your Highness
Don't follow
Good good
You see
How awesome
Good
One more
Your Highness
I think it seems to like you very much
I've brought so many pets
Only treat it closest
Comb and feed it yourself
But it treats me most MoMo
And every day, MoMo
Your Highness loves many pets
Presumably, it is not rare for a raccoon slave to be close
You're not an inkstone
How do you know
In my opinion
It just has no conscience
I just know
How do you know
Does Your Highness know
The inkstone is a raccoon slave
My name is Ali, too
I heard that folk children grow up safely
Will have a cheap name
That's an interesting name
Your Highness
I'll go back first
I'm leaving Beijing
Since Daming moved its capital to Beijing
South-to-North Grain Transfer
Reopening Huitong River
Earth dam that can be built
Be destroyed by water every year
Annual repair is overburdened
This time, Grandpa Huang ordered me to inspect the river workers
Supervise and repair river course
I don't know when I can return to Beijing
Go with me
Your Highness
I'm here
Waiting for you to return
Yao Ziliao
How many secrets are you hiding in your heart
Go play
Go ahead
I went to play, Your Highness
Who is it
Purple Azolla
What's the matter
Why are you here
Purple Azolla
I let her go everywhere
But she is adamant
See I won in the end
Tell someone to stop me in private
Thirty slaps
Anything you say
Don't make trouble
Don't fight back
But these noble people on high
We are not treated as human beings at all
I'm not reconciled
I'm so unwilling
Take it
Smash it
What a pity
Your Highness
You draw so well here
Why did you tear it up
Not like
How can I
Your Highness
That hand of yours
Miaoshou Danqing
Then what kind of flowers, birds, fish and insects, famous mountains and rivers
What about all the paintings
How could it not be
Business matters
Stay in the Forbidden City if you are in love with your children
Right
Your Highness, the horses and chariots are ready
Your Highness
This is the ninth year of Yongle
The new dam built by Song Li when he was ordered to harness the river
This is the position
Since then
Boats come and go on the Jeju River
An endless stream
Here is the part that was washed away by the flood
It uses the old transportation road dug in Yuan Dynasty
You see
Your Highness uses tea
Just in time
You can have extra meals tonight
Stay in the Forbidden City if you are in love with your children
Miss Yao
Thank you very much
Here
Father
Xia Yuanji is right
Compared with the old teacher, there is no work
Army and Horse Savings Ten Lost Eight Nine
He tried to block your northward expedition
It is out of patriotism and sympathy for the people
It's offensive to speak in a hurry
I also hope that my father will see that he has been an official for 20 years
The point of loving the people with one heart and one mind
Give him a break
He is dedicated to caring for the people
Then I am
A belligerent bad king
Father
My son has no such intention
This man must be killed
Your Highness
Arutai committed a crime against me in Datong Kaiping
The holy man insisted on the northern expedition
Xia Daren, the minister of the household department, resisted
Speaking of going out for years,
Insufficient food and pay for troops and horses
The holy man flew into a rage
Adult Xia and Cheng Zou Shiyan of Dali Temple
They are all in prison
Fang Bin, the minister of the Ministry of War, also committed suicide in fear
Your Highness
The wrath of the holy dragon
You dissuade me
Be careful
Grandpa Emperor
The grandson is back
Why did you bring him back again
Tell you
Xia Yuanji must die
I want to kill him
It's no use persuading anyone
And copy his whole family
I'd like to see it
Keep saying clean and patriotic
Household ministers who love the people like children
What is the incorruptible law
Father
Out