Don't clip it
How is it
Hanwang always liked meat
It was my negligence
Your Excellency
We have just received orders, too
Lord Wang
Tonight, even the military forces of the five cities are dispatched
Who the hell are you going to take
Counter-insurgency
Come with me
Don't always look at me
It's hard to eat a piece of meat
What's the fun of being a man
Father, don't forget your business
Carassius auratus is thick in winter
Taste delicious
This painting was created by Mr. Yun Lin, a painter of the former dynasty
Crucian Carp Belly Soup
Take only two pieces of meat from the belly of the fish
Prepared with Zanthoxylum bungeanum
Extremely fresh and tender
Unique flavor
Fresh and tender lubrication
Melt at the entrance
When I was in my boudoir,
Mother often cooks crucian carp soup with her own hands
What's the matter
Recipe canon meal
Let Purple Azinge Replace Jade
No
Can't
If we lose to the supervisor tonight,
Everyone will be punished
Row
The next dish is Dinghu Shangsu
I know
Needle tip to wheat awn
Bird's Nest to Snow Ear
Just fit
You should accompany her to dress up quickly
Good
Go
Let's go
Let's go. Come on
Hurry up
Your Majesty
This dish is made of snow ears, yellow ears and stone ears
Made of fungus, elm ear, sweet-scented osmanthus ear and six ears
Combined with Nostoc flagelliforme and
Precious ingredients such as fresh lotus seeds are boiled together
It is rare to make it smooth and delicious
So again
Fresh and elegant
Take away
Don't withdraw yet
Yes
Don't make a mountain out of a molehill
It was just an oversight
Sovereign
I can't wait
When can I see him
You have to wait until after the family dinner
Emperor
Ten thousand handprint dishes are coming
It seems to have a refreshing bouquet
Blow on one's face
Your Majesty
This dish uses abalone, shark fin and ginseng
Twenty-eight kinds of ingredients such as Yaozhu deer tendon
It is simmered in an aged flower carved wine jar
The vegetables are slightly fragrant with wine
Oily but not greasy
Three things about the name of the dish, Fu Shou Quan
Meat fragrance around the tongue
The soup is rich
Endless aftertaste
I have never tasted such delicious food before
Good
Good luck, good luck and longevity
Grandpa Emperor
This is a good sign
Emperor Pu Cha
It's very delicious
Is
Grandpa Huang rarely has a big appetite
Looks like it's the crab soup
Crab sauce
Yeah
Crab meat is a very fresh thing in the world
Only the big armour
You can compete with Fu Shouquan in three things
But now is not the best season to eat crabs
Can't bring the delicious soup into full play
I'll use crab cream to mix tofu soup
Put the lightest and most delicious in the world
Combination of two ingredients
Neutralize the freshness of crab flavor with the clarity of tofu
To be just right
Crab sauce still has such an effect
That's no ordinary crab sauce
The fattest hairy crab in the middle and late September
Abandon crab meat
Take only crab cream and crab roe
Elaborate bald butter
Crisp, beautiful and fragrant
The best taste in the world
Which can be compared with ordinary crab sauce
And
That cup of tea
No wonder
Remove fishy smell and greasiness with ordinary tea
You can taste it with your tongue
The fragrance of tofu and the delicacy of crab sauce
Zi Jin
You are really good.
So how many wins and losses do we have now
What was our first game
They won the first game
They won
What about the second game
What happened in the second game
I don't know either
Why did you return it intact
Princess Han has asthma
Don't eat chicken all the year round
To avoid offending the princess
So I told someone to withdraw
What are you talking about
You say it again
What's the matter
Princess Han
Xiuzhen
Princess
Princess Xiuzhen
What's going on
Moon flower
What's the matter
You can't eat chicken clear
But my walnut fried kidney flower
Every waist flower
They are all soaked in chicken
Not good
The princess has a recurrence of a chronic disease
Xuan Tai Yi
Quick Xuan Tai Yi
Yes
Slow down
Sovereign please stay
Mother
The princess has a recurrence of a chronic disease
No delay
It is necessary to hurry to make a diagnosis and treatment by Xuan Tai Yi
Mother
You take people to your palace first
Please send the medicine manager, too
Handmaiden is going to invite him
Go
Sovereign
Stand down
Father
What does this mean
Bring it up
Go
Quickly
Kneel down
Your Majesty
Meng Xian, commander of Changshan Guard
Yulin avant-garde Peng Xu
Qin Tian Jian Guan Wang Shecheng
And the attendant Qing Yang and his son
All the rebels have been won
What crime have you committed
Grandpa Emperor
Wang Shecheng, the official of Qin Tianjian, conspired with Meng Xian
Said he had a different view of the sky recently
There will be a king in the world
And conspired to offer poisoned wine at the banquet
Waiting for an opportunity to poison your majesty
Soldiers rob the arsenal and Fu Bao of Neifu
Then win the six ministers of the five governments of Gonghou Bo
A fake imperial edict has been found
Fu Bao to be stamped
You can abolish the crown prince
Embrace the King of Zhao
Sure enough, he is my good son
I'm just occasionally infected with minor diseases
Can't look at the direction
Why do you remember
What about this dragon chair and his eldest brother's head
Third brother
The third child
Wake up
Third brother
The third child
Do you really collude with others to poison your father
Conspiracy to usurp the throne
I drink too much
Big Brother
What are you talking about
Say what
What's wrong with this
Why do you want to say this to your heart
My loyalty and filial piety to my father
That's where heaven and earth can show the sun and the moon can learn
How can I collude with people
What about plotting evil
Who said that
Is that you
Who instructed you to frame the king
Shut up
Down
Yes
I said third
Chang Shanwei is your guard
Who can afford to transfer but you
Everyone was taken down and refused to recognize it
No
Father
I was greedy just now
I fell asleep
I don't know what happened
But someone must have planted it
I want to trap my son in injustice, my father
Let him drink it
Emperor
Go
His Royal Highness the King of Zhao
Since I know nothing,
Why don't you dare to drink
Father
There are neither elite soldiers nor strong generals in my son's hand
The army is more selfless and close friends
My son is really alone
Stay in Beijing for several years
That's also half a step, I dare not step on the wrong line
That's a partisan in the army
Supported by military commanders
And who is it
The third child hurt me again
My son is wronged
In the early years of war,
My son has a life-long friendship with many military commanders
But they were all fought in hard battles
Since my son went to the fief,
There will be no contact with these military commanders
What's more, I don't know where to talk about the so-called support
To say that it is supported by courtiers
Who can compare with Big Brother in the world
Those sour civil servants in this court
That's not a prince's benevolence
Father and Father
My son wronged his father
All right, don't even say it
Father
This glass of wine today
My son is willing to drink
But before you drink it
My son must swear to heaven
I have no intention of committing insurrection
What happened today must be someone trying to frame up
Someone must be going after the yellowbird
Father
If you must use this glass of wine today
Words from proving innocence
My son is willing to do it
Father
Make one's father impossible
The third brother has always been humble and wise
Never disobey
This time it must be wronged and wronged
If this is a glass of poison wine
My son is willing to replace him with his own body
I'll do it
Big Brother
Third brother
That's enough
Everyone wants to drink poisoned wine to prove innocence
Don't I dare to be alone
And I'm innocent
Come and give it to me
Give it to me
That's enough
Grandpa Emperor
My grandson hasn't finished his words yet
Meng Xian Peng Xu
It's just a mere commander
How many soldiers can you have in your hand
To hijack the heavily guarded vault
It's simply nonsense
Two uncles are extremely clever
How could you do such a foolish thing
Grandchildren have already found out
It's just that those ignorant officials conspired
It has nothing to do with two uncles
Zhanji
You said so
Third uncle is timid
You scared my uncle to death
Two uncles
You guys reacted too quickly
Before I finish speaking
Even if they are not behind the scenes,
It is also arrogant and indulgent on weekdays
Make a group of ministers greedy
Seek power and usurp the throne
Your Majesty, calm down
Imperial edict
Wang Shecheng is attractive by astronomical phenomena
Zhu
Other people involved, etc.
Xia Zhen Fu Si Prison Yan Shen
Handmaiden's decree
You two
Zhao Wang introspects behind closed doors
Yes
And you
Go back to your fief tomorrow
Thank your father
Han Wang to
Sister-in-law
Mother
Princess Han suffers from chronic diseases
Why don't you take care of the sick first
Stay in the fief and rest well
The dishes cooked by eight famous chefs in Shangshanjian
How did you know beforehand
And the walnut kidney flower
And who reminded you
Specially cooked with chicken clear
Chicken clear
Princess Han has always had old diseases
Take water wave eggs in the morning to recuperate your body
Fried kidney flower with walnut kernel in the food list
Cook with chicken clear as usual
It's him
Mother
You believe me
I really didn't do anything
I have never met Princess Han
I didn't know she had asthma
Mother
You believe me
Naturally, you don't want to murder Princess Han
You're just trying to set me up
What are you talking about
You clearly know that Princess Han relapsed and died of his old illness
I'm still the palm print of the Food Bureau
Can't escape dereliction of duty
This is not a deliberate framing. What is it
Dereliction of duty
So you're so angry
It's not because Princess Han is dead
I'm afraid of losing your position as a food eater
What you just said about him
Who on earth is it
Tell me
Say
Who the hell is ordering you
No one told me to
I did it myself
I did it all
You are the handprint of Shang Food Bureau
People were killed on New Year's Eve
Naturally, you can't get away with it
I'm deliberate
Just want to see
The way you end up with nothing
Look at you, a woman who abandoned her husband and daughter
What will happen in the end
I did everything
I did it all
You're satisfied
You are so disappointing to me
Meng Shang Shi
Crown Princess summoned
Don't be polite
Grandpa Emperor
Rebellious minister's palace
It's a child's play to find out the rebellion edict
The third child
Be meticulous at ordinary times
How can you get the wind out in advance
One net into a capture
A Washington
If so
A treasure that arouses people's greed
The thief keeps on going
On the contrary
A ruined temple outside the city
Except for cobwebs
Have nothing
Even
Rats don't want to patronize either
Imperial dragon chair power
How tempting
Your two uncles
While I am old and sick,
Collusion with internal officials
Interworking messages
I don't care, they think
I am deaf and blind
Who told you to scare them
Grandpa Emperor
It is clear that you are scaring them
Bold
Grandchildren never wronged one person
I have fought more in my life
Decisive war
It is also strictly guarded against parents and children
The world often scolds me for being cruel and violent
What do you think
Say
When grandchildren are young
Grandpa Huang once said
What is a leader
At first, when people hunted,
Elect the bravest man in the crowd
As a leader
And this man
Is the man who takes the most lives from the beast
Take up arms and organize an army
Protect tribes and food
This is the leader
The tribe is still like this
What's more, a country
Ordinary people want to be good people
Doing good deeds and accumulating virtues is
But for emperors,
Adhere to the road of benevolence and righteousness blindly
Will only become a mediocre emperor
What do you think is a good emperor
For the people
For the country
Benevolence and righteousness can be abandoned
To give up one's own flesh and blood
Even if you are reviled by thousands of people, you have to endure it
Adhere to the right path of the country
Defend one's territory and people
This is the emperor
You always care about your family
Leave room for them
Is that glass of wine poisonous
Even if it is highly toxic,
It only poisons the heart of rebellion
Poison can't defeat the real dragon emperor
Come
Walk with Grandpa
Crown Princess
What happened at the New Year's Eve banquet
It's all the handmaiden's fault
Handmaiden is willing to be punished
Don't defend yourself
Handmaiden is a humble person
Rely on the protection of the Crown Princess
To have a place to stand today
It should have been a grass-bearing ring to repay your kindness
I made a mistake at the New Year's Eve banquet
Let the villain take the opportunity to make trouble
This is the end of the matter
What face is there to defend before you
Meng Shang Shi
Who do you mean by the villain
People who are familiar with propriety and righteousness in the world
It should be understood that monarch, minister and father and son
The principle of being superior and inferior from top to bottom
I won't make a humble offense and respect the following offenses
Slaves are lax in royal affairs
Blindly tolerant and patient
Let the villain push his luck and wait for an opportunity to make trouble
One over here
Meng Shang Shi
Hu Si Shan
Handmaiden serves the Lord wholeheartedly
Forget the hidden dangers close at hand
The food list has not been checked again
Give the villain a chance to form a trap
It was the handmaiden's mistake
This is over two
It's just that handmaiden is deeply gracious
Have to dare to speak out
A man who can betray Shangguan so easily
How can you be trusted
How can you stay around
Imperial Doctor has treated Princess Han
Said she was suffering from chronic diseases
This time, despite dissuasion, I came to Beijing for a long distance
So that the old disease recurs
There is no way to return to heaven
There is nothing wrong with the food list prepared by Guanglu Temple
There is no big mistake for the Food Bureau to make meals according to the order
Besides, Your Majesty appreciates the crab soup very much
The right to make meals still belongs to the Food Bureau
If the food bureau has nothing to do with the death of the princess,
And why
Someone tipped off
You sent a private message to Hanwang
You can plead guilty
This is a false accusation
Hu Si Shan
How dare you say anything in front of your master without evidence
Handmaiden visits Crown Princess
That day in Ganqing Palace
Witnessed Lord Yuan being expelled from the hall
Meng Shangshi once talked about your majesty taking elixir
Dragon's body is unsafe
It is also asserted that there will be changes in the palace
Handmaiden thought afterwards
Fear in one's heart
Don't dare not report it
Meng Shang Shi
If it weren't for the news of having an affair with Hanwang
How can you know that there will be changes in the palace
Pay attention to everything
You can see the micro-knowledge
Crown Princess
Zu Xun has long said clearly
Female officials of empresses and concubines in every palace
Do not interfere in all affairs outside the palace gate
Meng Shang's private glimpse of the Lord is a great sin
Not to mention repeatedly passing messages with the captaincy
Besides, she used to repay the grace of Han Wang
Contrary to your will
Meng Shang Shi
Anyone who writes a post privately has an affair with the outside world
Writers are cut when they receive them
You are still eating in the palace
Knowing to commit a crime
What sin should I commit
If you want to add a crime, you can't say anything
Crown Princess
You are wise and wise
I actually believe this provocative statement
Doubt my loyalty
Over the years
You serve Your Majesty
Preside over the Shang Food Bureau
It's also a dedicated effort
Crown Princess
But you peep at the Lord and talk about palace changes
Words and deeds do exceed the rules
Sin is unforgivable
According to palace rules
Take away the job of still eating
Go to Gongzhengsi to get the crime by yourself
Take care of yourself in the future
The handmaiden said goodbye
Wanwang Crown Princess Treasures
Congratulations
Meng Shang Shi
Now it's no longer a food
How will I address you in the future
I'm curious
I trust you so much and reuse you
Why did you take refuge in her
Enter the palace from a young age
We are best friends
Later, he entered the Shang Food Bureau
Because you are overbearing and suspicious
Anyone who doesn't agree with you
Try to suppress expulsion
In order to blind your eyes, we
I've been pretending to be at odds
Ten years
You've been pretending in front of me for ten years
It's great
A Wai
Don't be soft-hearted
I know
In addition to acting overbearing, she
Be fair and just
But as long as there is her in one day,
I will never get out of the head
In the past ten years,
She has always been absolute monarch
We are obviously the best friends
But always pretend to be discord
Don't you have a hard time
In the future
I don't need it anymore
Wake up, wake up, wake up
Everyone is safe and sound
Safe, safe, safe
Great, great
It's good to be okay
That's great
It's all right at last
It's okay it's okay
I was scared to death just now
What's going on
Do you still have to be held accountable
Come on, come on
Come and come
I wish adults good health
Everything means everything
Wish you good luck
Everything goes smoothly
Hurry up, hurry up
Come
Thank you
Thank you, thank you, thank you
Be careful of burning
Come
So delicious
Come and come
Get me some vinegar
Zi Jin
The new year is safe and smooth
May you be as lucky as you desire
Reward you
Thank you, Your Highness
All the blessings of the Forbidden City
It's all in this bowl of flat food
I'll eat first
Your Highness has something on his mind
Some things
I have a plan in mind
Be comfortable
But there are some things
I haven't tried it either
I don't know what to do with it
Your Highness
There is no blessing at all
It's empty
But I followed your highness
Is my greatest blessing
It's you
Why did you set me up
We have no grievances and no enmity
How could you
It's a fair deal
You did something for me
And I also got the meal list of the supervisor for you
Do you know that
I became a murderer because of you
It's all your fault
Don't come over
Go away
Who hurt you
What's the matter? This is
You mean to be unhappy, don't you
Just like your mother who killed people
My mother didn't kill anyone
Daughter of a criminal woman
How dare you talk back
You see I won't hit you
You come here
See if I don't hit you
My mother didn't kill anyone
Telling you to talk back didn't kill anyone
I told you to talk back
You fought back
You're right
I'm not unaware
But pretend not to know
I just want to know
If I stand in danger,
Will anyone notice
I always follow the rules. If I do something wrong,
Is there anyone willing to understand
Even one person is fine
It's just that I didn't think of it
This error
At the cost of human life
It's my choice
Have nothing to do with others
Off you go
You can hate me as much as you like
Only in the future
Don't put others
As your hope to live
How did you get out
Walk in
What are you doing
Yuehua hasn't come back yet
You care about her
It's freezing. Get in there
You know everything
Except for you
Who has the courage to openly attack the princess
It's too presumptuous
I told you
Never let go of the initiator
She regrets this matter to this day
I came to see you this time
You bastard
It seems that you won't go back with me either
Accompanying a gentleman is like accompanying a tiger
But today our emperor
The most annoying thing is to be smart
You take care of yourself
After I left Beijing,
You don't have to deliver a message
Just take care of yourself
My father's teachings have been remembered by my son
There are also official duties
One step ahead