Unforgettable Love
EP05
Tonight,
I'll sleep on the couch.
You two will sleep in my bedroom.
Let's break up the meeting.
Wait.
Dear, don't break up the meeting.
I just saw
a storage room over there.
You clean it up.
I'll just live there with your dad.
Lao Qin,
Let's
stay more days
with our daughter.
No problem.
I
Stop. It's settled.
Yes.
You.
Stop talking about it.
You help clean up the room, right?
Yeah.
Oh, my god!
I'll clean up the room.
Go ahead.
Arrhythmia.
Shortness of breath.
Hello, brother.
A man
sent a woman home.
What does that mean?
Love couples.
According to the information I have,
Dr. Qin is single.
And
there has never been anything
about this man before.
Then you need to
cheer up.
I tell you that
this person
is likely to be
a roadblock
in your cooperation.
The name of this kind of people
is called rivals in love.
Hello, sir.
Do you have an appointment?
It's you, Mr. He.
Do you come here today
especially to see Yiyue's cat?
Yiyue.
When does my fiancée
have a cat?
Well, I'll bring it out
for you to see.
Mr. He, sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm coming.
Touch it.
Mr. He, you're here, too.
I am just passing by.
Hi.
Did you sleep well?
Did it sleep well?
It rested well
after my check yesterday.
It's fine now.
Do you have a cold?
You should get some rest.
Brother,
in order to welcome you,
I'll treat you to a slap-up meal in the evening.
I know that
there is the No.1 popular hot pot restaurant near here.
OK.
Are you with us?
-Well.  -He won't go.
How can Mr. He get into
such a dirty and noisy
public hot pot restaurant?
Mr. He, right?
It is Yiyue who understands me better.
Hot pot
is both high in calories and fat.
It is full of grease
and food that
have not been professionally handled.
In addition,
meat, the raw and the cold are in the same pot.
I, He Qiaoyan,
have never eaten this type of diet.
You see.
I just said he never eats this type of food.
Let's go and put the cat back.
Hi.
Navigate to
the No.1 popular hot pot restaurant.
This one is delicious.
Then take more.
I'm surprised you remember what I love to eat.
Of course.
Hello, sir.
Are you alone?
Yes, only me.
Would you like to order a medium pot?
Yes.
Would you like to order a double combo?
Waiter, a rubber band, please.
No need.
I have one.
Thank you.
There is also a free birthday celebration.
If necessary...
Anything is ok.
Please hurry up.
Roll up your sleeves.
I forgot. Thank you for reminding me.
I saw that
the online articles that insult you
seem to have disappeared.
What's going on?
He Qiaoyan made it.
It seems that
he is not as unkind
as you described.
I admit
he really
isn't that annoying either.
After we learned that your birthday is today,
we have customized
a free birthday celebration especially for you.
I wish you
happy birthday,
everything going well,
good health,
getting rich soon,
and getting thinner.
Is there anything else you need?
No, thanks.
This is not a birthday celebration at all.
This is embarrassing situation.
It's really embarrassing.
Distinguished guests.
Today is our third anniversary.
There are activities in our restaurant.
Music will be played soon.
After the music stops,
if a customer
can embrace a person of the opposite sex
as quickly as possible,
she/he can enjoy a 50% discount.
If they can kiss,
it's free for them.
Kiss?
Great.
It's another show of love.
Don't look. Let's eat.
First level risk warning.
The precursor of the crash.
Take a selfie.
This scene
is really beautiful.
Let's
give you applause.
Brave and handsome men.
Table Six and Table Fifteen
will be treated free of charge.
Why are you here?
I came to see if this restaurant
could be acquired.
So do you want to
sit down and eat some?
Great.
Eat more.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I'm tired.
Do you want to get married by capture?
You must be a shortage of people.
Get these people
out of here.
I'm very upset.
They are here,
so no beautiful girls will come over.
Do you think
my charm has gone down?
I'm not interested in you.
But I love you.
Don't always
push people around you away.
No wonder Lin Wei went abroad.
Why do you mention her?
Don't you want to know
why she left?
She must had some reason.
I don't care.
That's right.
There are so many people who like you.
It doesn't matter if one person doesn't like you, does it?
Then you should try your best to
get married
to Dr. Qin soon.
I see
the man named He
coming with his child.
I'm going to a meeting.
You play with the Rubik's Cube here
by yourself for a while.
All right.
Here you are.
Wait for me here.
Hello.
You're
so cute.
What's your name?
I can't talk.
What a pity.
Why can't such a lovely child
talk?
Is that your father just now?
Where is your mother?
This is your...
Is this your mother?
Uncle Qin, Aunt Qin.
Please eat pomegranate.
You're welcome.
Finally you are back.
Mom, dad, have you eaten yet?
If you haven't eat...
Finally you are back.
They just kept asking me
about the He Qiaoyan.
Don't betray me.
I didn't say anything.
I really can't stand it.
I'll leave first.
Uncle Qin, Aunt Qin.
I'm going for a run.
Please take your time.
Okay.
I put my handbag down first.
Don't do anything else.
Come here.
Why are you
so serious?
Make me very nervous.
We've been to see
He Qiaoyan.
What?
Take it easy.
We just looked at him,
and did not do anything else.
Do you still want to cheat us?
His son has said
that you are his mother.
If you want to fall in love, we will not interfere.
We have no objection to your marriage.
But he has a child.
Do you know
the pressure and responsibility behind this?
And
do you know about his past,
his family
and his real situation?
According to you,
He Qiaoyan looks like a liar.
Your mom is right.
Tomorrow,
We'll meet him.
Let's see what kind of person he really is.
We'll ask him what he's going to do with you.
You have to make it clear to us.
Right.
You get him to come
and give us
a clear picture of what's going on.
I have nothing to do with He Qiaoyan.
Believe it or not, it's up to you.
What's up?
How can I have a sudden heart ache?
Are you OK?
You made you mom so angry
that she had a heart attack.
This is my daughter.
You've grown up,
so you've started hiding everything from me
She doesn't tell me about her relationships.
She doesn't tell me about her breakup.
Now she even doesn't
tell me about her marriage.
She makes me so sad.
I'd rather die.
All right, mom.
Stop pretending.
I didn't pretend.
I'm so sad now.
I feel like I'm going to die.
Oh no.
I can't enjoy being a grandma.
Stop saying that.
Let's die together.
I'll see you in heaven.
Are you OK?
So sad.
Take it easy.
It's over.
Ruowei broke her foot.
I'll take a look.
Pomegranates and grapes are especially delicious.
Have some more.
I must
figure it out.
Come on.
My God.
Thank you for saving me.
He just tried to come to your home.
I managed to find a reason
to stop him.
Good job.
Never let him
run into my parents.
Now I'll
leave you two to talk.
Goodbye, Mr. He.
Don't you invite me in?
Oh no.
Help me shade from the sun.
It's too sunny.
Can't you see the light?
You'll get a tan.
Qin Yiyue.
Are you afraid of something?
I'm not afraid.
Mr. He.
What can I do for you?
You're right.
What did I say?
You said we don't know each other very well.
You are right.
So I decide
to give you some time
to get you know me better.
That's all?
OK, I see.
Mr. He, please leave.
How long do you need?
In your past
twenty-nine years,
there must have been filled with stories
and bits of knowledge.
It's comparable to
a wonderful epic game.
To get through this game,
I need two years.
Two weeks at most.
Two weeks
is not enough for me to get through a mini-game.
I have all my information
organized for you
according to the timeline.
Remember to look carefully.
If there's anything unclear
or missed,
Let me know.
I will answer you truthfully.
OK, Mr. He.
I will definitely
learn from your glorious past.
Goodbye, Mr. He.
Does she hide
another man in the house?
It's over.
Do you tell him about your parents?
Of course not.
I think
you should just let your parents
meet He Qiaoyan.
Don't make your parents
really angry.
Absolutely not.
And from my experience,
He Qiaoyan
is definitely a trouble maker.
I want to get as far away from him as possible.
What else can you do?
Are you really not afraid
that they will go to He Qiaoyan on their own?
Or
He Qiaoyan once again rushes into our house.
Yes, I do.
So I have to
get them both back tomorrow
anyway.
I think this time
they are determined to meet him
before they leave.
Stop playing with your phone.
Let's sleep.
When does Mommy move in?
Xiaobao.
Our plans
may have to be postponed by two weeks.
When Dr. Qin comes,
remember to take this pillow away.
She's not Dr. Qin, she's Mommy.
OK, I see.
Turn off your cell phone and sleep.
Give it to me.
Just lie down.
Mommy, I miss you.
Are you sending a message to He Qiaoyan?
Why do you stop?
Ok, I send
it right now.
My parents said
they want to meet you.
My God, I have a stomachache.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Lao Qin,
Let's take a look at her phone.
You shouldn't do that.
Why not?
One,two,three.
The fish has taken the bait.
Get ready.
Dr. Qin.
Hello, Mr. He.
I'm Qin Yiyue's mother,
Luo Mingmei.
Hello, Aunt Luo.
He replied.
If you have time,
can you meet with us?
Of course.
I will visit you personally
right away.
He said he would visit in person.
You want me to pretend to be He Qiaoyan
to talk with your mother?
Yes.
You should promise to meet my mom.
And you should say you are young.
You should visit them in person to their home.
In that case,
you would be reasonable
to send them back.
You're right.
You are so smart.
Mom.
What are you talking about with He Qiaoyan?
I say I am your mother.
I want to see him.
He Qiaoyan
is pretty straightforward.
He agreed.
He also said that he would visit in person to our home.
You rush to buy tickets for us.
There is a train at two o'clock.
We should be able to catch that train.
Come on.
Mom, stay a few more days.
No.
Stay a few more days.
Mom.
My mother is leaving soon.
I'm so sad.
Great job.
I'll treat you to dinner as a reward.
Lao Qin.
Hello.
After I drop off my stuff,
I'm going to get my hair styled.
My hair is so ugly.
OK.
I will also buy a dress.
The red dress you chose last time
is quite nice.
Then I'll buy that one.
Great.
The danger is over.
Just now my phone suddenly broke down.
I just got my phone fixed.
What do you mean
by "Great job"?
I haven't sent a message to your mother yet.
It's over.
Is this
to go for wool and come home shorn?
It's over.
Dr. Qin.
Thank you for being willing to
let me come to your hometown.
Does this mean
that you are trying to accept me?
No.
This matter
can not be said clearly in one or two sentences.
Anyway.
This is a mistake.
A big mistake.
You go back first.
I will explain to you later, OK?
Go.
Lao Qin, I'm going to buy a dress.
You hurry to buy some fruits.
You buy some good ones.
Don't worry. I buy imported ones.
Yueyue?
Mom.
Visiting the parents
is a crucial step
in determining your marriage relationship.
Let the father-in-law and mother-in-law satisfied.
You will win.
Mom, dad.
I'm Yiyue's fiance,
He Qiaoyan.
What are you talking about?
Xiaohe, hello.
I am Yueyue's father, Qin Qiuyang.
Just call me Uncle Qin.
It's a little early
to call mom and dad.
All right, dad.
It's pretty good.
You
should show
that you are rich.
And you are able to
give her daughter a good life.
So many gifts.
Are you paying tribute to the emperor?
No one will slap (over) the smiler.
And no one will blame politeness.
There is
another crucial step
that can achieve two things at one stroke.
Don't say anything else.
Just boast them about being so young.
You look so young.
Is it?
I have learned that
although you are fifty years old this year,
it looks like
you are only forty-nine years old.
I said I'd better go for a facial first,
but you wouldn't let me go.
I don't know what do you like.
So I buy
a lot of kinds of things.
Please sit first.
Yes.
No need.
You have sent gifts.
You also visit.
Well, then, we'll go.
Why do you go?
You just sit there.
No interruptions.
Come in and sit down.
Lao Qin, come here.
Sit down.
Why are you sitting here?
You sit over there.
Xiaohe.
I always hear Yueyue talk about you.
She said you are exceptionally good.
Very reliable.
When did I say that?
Our daughter
is indeed
the apple of our eye.
For marriage,
how do you think?
Please wait a moment.
For the project of marriage,
I set up
a special project team.
I made a most detailed
and complete plan.
The engagement,
wedding preparations
and post-wedding matters
are all listed in detail.
Please review.
If there is anything
unclear,
please tell me at any time.
Mom, do you see that?
I told you that
our marriage is fake.
We're just for our benefit.
Just a fake marriage.
Mom.
He's reliable.
Although he looks silly,
I didn't expect
him to be a practical entrepreneur.
It seems that he is also serious about marriage.
Sure enough,
men are the most attractive
when they are serious.
I can forgive
whatever he just said about me.
Xiaohe.
Do you
have a son?
What about his mother?
Dad, it's a private matter.
We have to
figure this thing out.
Xiaohe.
In fact, we are very open-minded.
We will never
be prejudiced
against this marriage
just because you have a child.
You can relax.
We are just worried
that Yueyue will be wrongly treated in the future.
Xiaobao's mother passed away.
I have raised him by myself.
Mom, dad.
You've asked what you want to know,
so we'll leave.
So let me ask you last question
have you completely
let go of the mother of your child now?
Mom.
My information based on timeline is ready for you.
Remember to look carefully.
If there's anything unclear,
or missed,
let me know.
I will answer you truthfully.
Xiaobao's mother
is the closest family member
to me.
A virtuous elder sister-in-law is comparable to a mother.
It turns out that Xiaobao
is your brother's child.
I thought
Xiaobao is your child.
Except for those close to me,
no one knows
who Xiaobao's biological father and mother are.
I don't want any people to know.
It's not easy for you.
You are so young,
and responsible.
But your brother and sister-in-law
must be
very grateful to you.
Xiaohe.
I am especially good at taking care of children.
Moreover,
We've seen that kid.
He's a sensible and smart boy.
If you're busy,
you can leave him to us.
Don't make yourself so hard.
Have you met Xiaobao?
Yueyue.
You sent me a picture,
it's like I've seen him.
You must be hungry.
I will cook for you.
Please have some fruit first.
Do something.
It'll be ready in a minute.
Come on.
This is "Braised Steak Fillet",
one of my culinary specialit.
Try it.
And try this.
Thank you.
Eat more vegetables.
Mom.
Let's get another pair of serving chopsticks.
It doesn't matter.
I haven't had dinner
with family members like this
for a long time.
Great.
Let's have a drink.
You can't drink.
I should take care of
your "Three highs".
I'm happy today.
Xiaohe.
You must drink with me.
You can
only drink a little.
All right, that's enough.
You see, more and more.
All right.
You have to take care of me.
You have to take care of me for the rest of your life.
In your dreams.
Who cares about your life?
Come on.
Cheers!
Drink slowly.
Well.
You drink it all.
If you can't drink,
don't drink.
You are so sincere.
Take some food.
Come on.
The fish is still stewing in the pot.
I forgot.
One more please.
Come and eat.
Well.
Here comes
the fish.
Here comes the fish.
You don't serve it, it's too hot.
Move it.
Slow down.
Are you hurt?
You should use a towel.
This is
cold, you will be better
if you hold it.
Well.
Don't use this.
There's toothpaste in the bathroom.
Apply some toothpaste,
it will be better.
You should use it.
Should be soy sauce.
Not soy sauce.
Toothpaste.
Soy sauce.
I'll go and
apply some toothpaste first.
Go ahead.
It's amazing so many stuff
in such a small space.
But
why does
it feel so warm?
Have some more.
Uncle Qin, let's have another drink.
Okay.
Come on.
Stop drinking
and have some soup.
Just a little.
Come on.
Drink it slowly.
Well.
You should drink it slowly.
You made it spilled.
You see what you did.
I'm sorry
for the interruption today.
It's getting late.
I just asked the driver
to go back to take care of Xiaobao.
I wonder if it is convenient for you
to let me stay here
tonight?
What?
Yes.
You can share a room with me.
You don't say anymore.
Xiaohe.
We only have the couch
for you to sleep on.
I'll clean up first.
Don't bother, Aunt.
If so,
I can share a room
with Yiyue.
Do you have facial cleanser?
I forgot to bring it.
This guy comes prepared.
Actually, I'm used to sleeping alone.
Because your mom
cooks really good,
I want to have another breakfast tomorrow.
He smells like a bar.
All right.
You sleep on the sofa.
I sleep on the sofa?
Why?
I haven't slept on the sofa.
Then I'll sleep on the sofa.
You sleep on the bed.
Talk to me for a while.
You may not know
I envy you so much.
You have the home.
You have family.
Your towels hang together.
Your toothbrushes are put together.
You eat together
and sleep together.
But I have nothing.